<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Snowbreak: Containment Zone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668080/Snowbreak_Containment_Zone/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Snowbreak: Containment Zone is a 3D sci-fi RPG-shooter powered by the Unreal Engine 4 that offers a next-gen, cross-platform gaming experience, sharing your progress across all of your devices. <br/><br/>The Descent of the Titans turned a once-vibrant city into the devastated wasteland of Containment Zone Aleph. As the Adjutant of Heimdall Force, bravely undertake missions alongside Manifestations with the powers of gods and unique personalities, seeking to bring this bitter winter to an end...<br/><br/>[Enjoy Hybrid Combat]<br/>Snowbreak's weaponry injects realism into a sci-fi setting, with designs closely simulating future firearms technology. This combines with the otherworldly, RPG-like skill mechanic to create a refreshing combat experience.<br/><br/>[Take on Titans]<br/>The Descent of the Titans completely changed the world, and the battlefield. Feel the thrill of battling giants in this dystopian future!<br/><br/>[Befriend Operatives]<br/>Spend time with your Heimdall Force companions in the Base system. Decorate, chat, and give gifts to grow closer!<br/><br/>[Play Co-Op in Gigalink] <br/>Tired of exploring alone? Join up with friends and fight enemies together!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milo and the Christmas Gift</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2716140/Milo_and_the_Christmas_Gift/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							After his adventure in Milo and the Magpies, Milo is looking forward to spending a cosy Christmas at home. But a Christmas gift is about to upset his holiday celebrations, especially when said gift disappears after a little misunderstanding! Can you help Milo bring home the lost Gift and save Christmas for Marleen… and himself?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_playing_1.gif?t=1703496663"> <br/><br/>Milo and the Christmas Gift is a free-to-play short and atmospheric point-and-click adventure game created by artist Johan Scherft. The game is a spin-off story following the events in Milo and the Magpies. The game has 5 chapters and a gameplay time of around 30 minutes!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/>■ Relaxing yet stimulating game-play<br/>Join Milo in his home and revisit some of the neighbouring gardens, but this time in a wintery Christmas wonderland! Interact with the festive environment and solve small point-and-click / hidden-object puzzles.<br/><br/>■ Captivating artistic atmosphere<br/>Each hand-painted, interior and snowy garden Milo has to search through has its unique personality, reflecting that of Milo’s owners and next-door neighbours respectively.<br/><br/>■ Atmospheric soundtrack<br/>Each chapter has its own festive theme song composed by Victor Butzelaar.<br/><br/>■ Average playtime: 15-30 minutes<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_snow_1.gif?t=1703496663"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few Nights More: Genesis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713070/Few_Nights_More_Genesis/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Please note: This is a free prologue and it includes act 1, and only 1 playable character and blood school is playable, The maximum heritage gained is limited to 50, and the maximum difficulty can be set to 2. As well only one castle will be available. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Blood3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Conquer castles and claim your birthright!</strong><br/> <br/>The fight to reclaim your place in this world begins. Rebuild lost ruins, make them stronger and defend them against your enemies. After you regain your strength, move on to conquer more territories and eventually claim your birthright.<br/><br/>Few Nights More offers the unique fusing of castle management and turn based rogue-like combat. Fight against humanity, the undisputed masters of this world in your absence. Choose between eight different Vampire Lords, each with their own ambition and history. Find your trinkets, skills and perks along your way. Design your very own castle by placing the right rooms, adding decors that directly contribute to your army and your Vampire Lord. Conquer more castles so your influence and power grow, until you claim your birthright.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Ferocity3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Core Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Design your castle by adding new Rooms, Traps and Minions. Stack up on some buffs with shiny decors to get ready for the invasion screen to defend it to the end of every night!<br/> <br/></li><li> Choose among 7 different Vampire Lords with unique History, Gameplay and Abilities.<br/> <br/></li><li> Master 1 out of 3 Disciplines each time you play, each with 60 unique skills.<br/> <br/></li><li> Acquire new random skills, perks and trinkets to survive the nights.<br/> <br/></li><li> Excel in either being a Prestigious Vampire, a Seductive one, or master a Terrifying presence against your enemies.<br/><br/></li><li> Test the builds you made against a variety of Hunters, Veterans and Unique Bosses in an action packed turn based combat system.<br/> <br/></li><li> Endure three acts across 12 difficulty levels, striving to survive and progress. Accumulate Heritage Points to enhance your lord's starting stats, skills, and unlock new castles and talents unique to each lord.<br/><br/></li><li> Engage in the boundless challenge of Infinity Mode, where you can continuously test your limits without relying on a castle. Each night, you will be presented with three options to advance, growing stronger as you push yourself to see how far you can go.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703259090"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703259090"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703259090"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703259090"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703259090"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703259090"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1702674942"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1702562956"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1702562956"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1703493452"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1703493452"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1703186631"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1703318086"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1703318086"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1702747783"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobalt Core</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2179850/Cobalt_Core/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_1.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>Cobalt Core is a sci-fi roguelike deckbuilder with a unique single-axis combat system that will throw you for a loop. Many loops! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_2.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>Give orders to your crew by playing cards: Will you <strong>raise shields</strong> to protect your ship, <strong>dodge</strong> incoming missiles and cannon fire to avoid damage outright, or <strong>strike</strong> preemptively to disable your enemy’s weapons? Outmaneuver your foes to stay just ahead of impending calamity, and reach the Cobalt Core!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/characters.png?t=1703278835"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fresh new spin on tactics –</strong>  dodge attacks and target weak points in this unique single-axis take on tactics combat. Outwit the enemy in a high stakes game of cat and mouse!<br/></li><li><strong>Customize your deck –</strong> hundreds of cards and split upgrade paths means no two runs will be the same. Find that perfect combo that brings your deck from powerful to overpowered.<br/></li><li><strong>Get to know your crew –</strong> each character comes with a completely unique playstyle and their own personal story. Bring 3 along, mix and match their decks, and see how these little goobers get along with each other.<br/></li><li><strong>Tons of replayability –</strong>  hundreds of different character+ship combinations before you even hit “start run”. Crank up the difficulty and really test your skills!<br/></li><li><strong>Get in the groove –</strong> featuring 90+ minutes of catchy and electrifying original music by <i>Minecraft</i> composer Aaron Cherof!<br/></li><li><strong>Forward momentum –</strong> untangle a narrative and unlock more playstyles as you go. Is there any escape from this time loop?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/grandma_cookies.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>By the makers of <i>Sunshine Heavy Industries</i>, recipient of IGF's <strong>Honorable Mention for Excellence in Design 2022</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658820/Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							10 possible fruits and one goal, reach the Watermelon.<br/>Your job is to combine matching fruits to evolve them to the next one and eventually reach the coveted Watermelon.<br/>To help you, you have 3 different abilities at your disposal. But watch out, using these will cost you some of your points. Be smart about when you use them to get the highest score!<h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLAYER</h2>Measure your fruit skills against another player.<h2 class="bb_tag">GET THE WATERMELON</h2>How many Watermelons can you combine before your basket overflows?<h2 class="bb_tag">USE YOUR ABILITIES</h2>Power, level up and destroy — These abilities will help you reach the Watermelon, using any of those will also allow you to angle your aim.<h2 class="bb_tag">GOLDEN FRUIT</h2>If luck is on your side, you might even see the mysterious Golden Fruit. Find it and witness its effect firsthand.<h2 class="bb_tag">STATISTICS</h2>Track your progress with in-depth statistics. Visit the menu to see the number of fruits you've combined, your ability usage, and much more.<h2 class="bb_tag"></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.codecks.io%2Fwatermelon-game" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/extras/Roadmap_Banner.png?t=1702238677"/></a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EA SPORTS™ WRC</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1849250/EA_SPORTS_WRC/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1849250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build the car of your dreams in our biggest rally game ever, EA SPORTS™ WRC, the all-new official videogame of the FIA World Rally Championship, the first developed by the award-winning team behind the DiRT Rally series.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1849250/extras/WCR_GameFeatures_PostLaunch.jpg?t=1702998175"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For The King II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1676840/For_The_King_II/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/header_alt_assets_7.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_AboutThisGame_Steam_StoreBanner_2_EN.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Once beloved by her people, Queen Rosomon has turned against her subjects, casting them into servitude in the darkness of Fahrul’s mines whilst building alliances with sinister and malevolent forces.<br/><br/>Gather your party in four player co-op or adventure alone through Fahrul as you risk everything to fight the tyrannical queen and bring an end to her oppressive reign.<br/><br/>From the creators of For The King, the much-loved RPG that blends roguelite and tabletop gameplay comes a new chapter in Fahrul’s history, designed on an updated engine bringing innovation and gameplay refinement for returning heroes and new adventurers alike.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading01_Inspired_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>For The King II is easy for anyone to pick up and play, but takes skill, patience, and strategic excellence to master whilst remaining infinitely replayable with a procedurally generated map that ensures no two playthroughs will ever be the same. Unique yet familiar dice roll inspired movement, encounter and combat mechanics add even more spontaneity and variety as your fortunes rise and fall on the roll of the dice.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF01_InspiredByTabletop.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading02_Digestible2_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>For The King II provides a complete campaign with over 30 hours of gameplay, split into 5 separate adventures, each narratively linked. The journey is long and the path is treacherous but fear not, if your party fails you will start stronger and wiser on your next playthrough with better starting items to draft into your loadout.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF02_RogueliteCampaign.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading03_Muster_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Create your party from 12 unique character classes, each with their own unique perks, strengths and playstyles. From the heavy-handed hitter of The Blacksmith, to the wily potion-wielding Alchemist, you choose which characters will take on the fearsome Queensguard and the combat strategies that will ensure success. Introduce new characters to your party with mercenaries and companions that enable you to pluck wild beasts from the forest floor and recruit ruthless mercenaries from local taverns (for a price of course) to bolster your ranks in times of trouble.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF03_MusterYouMight_.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading04_Party_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Traverse Fahrul solo or with up-to three friends in four-player co-op. As a solo player you can control all characters in your party, giving you complete ownership of the campaign map and combat strategy whilst in four-player co-op you must coordinate and negotiate with your party members. Play online multiplayer with your friends controlling your own character(s) or play offline co-op on the same PC. Offline co-op supports multiple controllers; each controller will have input control on everyone’s turn.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF04_PartyofFour.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading05_Evolved_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Inspired by turn-based classics, For The King II adds strategic depth to much-loved combat mechanics with the new Battle Grid, where movement and position provide you and your enemies with strategic buffs and penalties. Defend the back row by equipping a mighty Tower Shield, push enemies into lethal pools of burning fire, or entangle melee troops with dark magic cast with weapons looted from vanquished foes. The choice is yours!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF05_EvolveTurnBased.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading06_Explore_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Fahrul is both beautiful and deadly in equal measure. On your journey you will encounter a wealth of diverse biome environments brought to life in a breathtaking art style. From lush forests, toxic swamps and lava-filled wastelands to pirate (no scratch that!) Merling-infested tropical seas, For The King II transports you deep into the wonders of Fahrul, leading you further than ever before into this stunningly-imagined land of adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF06_ExploreFantastical.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Ffortheking" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTK_Discord_Banner_EN.gif?t=1703284946"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoboCop: Rogue City</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1681430/RoboCop_Rogue_City/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FGzNdTVQAs6" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/ROBOCOP_ROGUE_CITY_BANNER_DISCORD_615x195px_EN.jpg?t=1701074570"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif01_EN.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif02_EN.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Description_Banner01_EN.png?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif03_EN.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Description_Banner02_EN.png?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif04_EN_V1.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Description_Banner03_EN.png?t=1701074570"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underground Waifus TCG</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2602510/Underground_Waifus_TCG/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Underground Waifus: Dive into the Future of TCG multiplayer with PVP Battles. Play for free this CCG and battler card game and compete, achieve quests and earn free rewards!<br/><br/>The universe of Underground Waifus takes place in the future, corrupted by the scarcity of materials, money: stardust, and the desire for power. An eternal war between different races and more than 9 factions. The gameplay merges several themes: cyberpunk and manga, anime waifus cards based in a post-apocalyptic future.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602510/extras/gifTitle.gif?t=1703760151"><br/>Underground Waifus is more than just a TCG, CCG, or JJC. It's the dawn of a new era of TCG  gaming. If you are tired of traditional Card PVP games, enjoy battling in a vast Battle Arena CCG with players worldwide.<br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602510/extras/gifPacks.gif?t=1703760151"><br/>One of the main sources of innovation is that it proposes a circular economy model that combines F2P (Free to Play) in that TCG (Trading Card Game), we’re shifting gears to warp speed!<br/><br/>Can you create a top deck building strategy? There are several combat modes in this card F2P collecting action game:<br/><br/>PVE CCG training available in the F2P mobile and PC version. <br/><br/>PVP Battler Card version with a game pass, winning player gets all. <br/><br/>PVP Player Battle Card Battler version of winning ELO will determine who is the winner of each SEASON.<br/><br/>That JJC trading card game is focused on a competitive side, with an easy PVP (player vs player) battles game with no barriers to entry and hybrid F2P for all players!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602510/extras/gifCards.gif?t=1703760151"><br/>FEATURES of an awesome CCG game based on a TCG game:<br/><br/>TCG and CCG Fusion: Enjoy the flavor of the card battles both Trading Card Games and Collectible Card Games with an awesome deck builder.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602510/extras/gifCombat1.gif?t=1703760151"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602510/extras/gifKill.gif?t=1703760151"><br/>Deck building Dynamics: Conquer all factions, strategy and deck builder here is that fun but with cards!<br/><br/>Join us in crafting a tale of strategy, card battles, trading and prosperity in the ever expanding cosmos of Underground Waifus TCG (Trading Card Game).<br/><br/>2023 and 2024 Underground Waifus TCG it is a trademark or registered Jurval Corp (Warlands Corp and Nexxyo company)						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel Heldritch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2726310/Hotel_Heldritch/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							“Hotel Heldritch” is a first-person horror adventure that transports you to an old abandoned hotel, steeped in dark mysteries and deadly dangers. Your goal is to survive and escape the hotel within an hour and a half gameplay limit, cracking codes, collecting keys, and evading monstrous creatures that roam the dark corridors.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost Princess: Darkness</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2701610/Lost_Princess_Darkness/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Story:</h2><br/>Play this third part of Lost Princess  FPS walking simulation where mission is to collect hidden items to get achievements and try to find Princess in darkland. . Player start his journey at darkforest and mission is to collect different items which gives achievements and when player finds Princess journey is finished. So explorer big open dark world and try find all items<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2>- lot of collectable items which gives steam achievements<br/>- Big and dark world where mission to find princess						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect LegendofAutumn</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2371720/Connect_LegendofAutumn/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2371720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Taking place in the autumn forest,<br>
A heartwarming story!<br>
In the world of maple,<br>
A match unfolds!<br>
For those who like autumn and board games for solo play.<br>
I'd love to!<br>
<br/>
―Synopsis―<br/>
When autumn came to a certain forest...<br/>
Using two types of maple leaves,<br/>
There was a game called maple placement.<br/>
Vosenski, a participant,<br/>
to participate in it,<br/>
I came to the forest.<br/>
So, he had<br/>
Meeting unique friends<br/>
He was waiting.<br/>
<br/>
system<br/>
A board game that requires strategic thinking!<br/>
player and opponent<br/>
Place the pieces on the board alternately.<br/>
Sandwich the opponent's piece with your piece<br/>
Erase your opponent's pieces! !<br/>
(of course,<br/>
Conversely, if your piece is caught between your opponent's pieces, your piece will be erased. )<br/>
The game is over when a certain number of your pieces disappear...<br/>
Clear the stage by erasing a certain number of your opponent's pieces! !<br/>
(The fixed number of your opponent's pieces varies depending on the stage.)<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Anyway, let's enjoy autumn! !						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fritz 19 SE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707140/Fritz_19_SE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Attacker, coward, swindler or endgame wizard: I'll show you how to win against anyone! After my World Championship victories in 2022 and 2023, I am the reigning Chess Software World Champion and am now looking forward to showing you how to become even stronger against your opponent With my innovative training method, I simulate typical player personalities you know from tournaments and online chess: brash attackers, cautious cowards, passive players. But how do you win against them? Fritz will show you how! And for beautiful attacks, combinations or sacrifices, there are the new ChessBase cards as a reward for you. Practical training that's also a lot of fun. Or let's train openings: you can try out a new repertoire ideas directly in a match against me. And how about the new calculation training for a quick Elo boost? As Fritz19 I can make you play better again.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707140/extras/Fritz19_2e.jpg?t=1703750480"><br/>Fritz 18 marked the beginning of a new era, and Fritz 19 drives this development onward: a game against Fritz should be more than just a game - it should be an experience. In a time when online chess dominates, a chess program has to offer something special to be a real alternative to human opponents.<h2 class="bb_tag">In Fritz 19 it works like this</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>There are six different characters that mimic typical club players: Allrounder, Aggressive, Positional, Swindler, Fearful, Endgame Expert.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fritz plays human moves that fit these types, but builds-in tactical mistakes so that you can win with a sacricial attack, for example. The sharper the position, the more likely the program will misstep.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>There is a wide range of tips and support that you can use to the full, or ignore, depending on your mood. With all the tips, you will practically always win against the “strong club player” level. If you ignore them completely, it becomes challenging for a player like me (ELO 2000).</li></ul> <ul class="bb_ul"><li>At any time during the game, you can switch to “assisted calculation” mode. Where is no clock, so you can train your calculation without stress in positions you have played yourself. This has an enormous training benefit.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">The opponent zoo</h2>The character Allrounder is probably the strongest opponent for every level of play. It is a development of “Easy Game” from Fritz 18. Everyone knows the Aggressive Player from their club. They regularly play on the attack, with a sharp opening repertoire. They are the ideal opponent for defence training with Black. The Swindler takes aggressiveness to the extreme, and o!en overplays the position. Material and solid position are of no interest, the main thing is to go for the king. Against this swindling fox, one usually has a material advantage, but suddenly it becomes highly dangerous. The wise owl symbolises the Positional Player. It loves a good pawn structure, a secure king of its own and coordinated piece-play. The distorted echo of this, is the fearful mouse. It appreciates crowded, safe positions and is afraid of complications. That is why it often plays weaker. The Endgame Fan, on the other hand, plays specifically for exchange. Simplification is paramount, the opening is o!en unambitious. When it comes to the endgame, on the other hand, things get really tough. An effective training opponent for this phase of the game!<h2 class="bb_tag">New opening training</h2>We all manage our opening repertoire in variation trees, stored in databases. If you want to play against it, it gets technical: opening books have to be converted. On today’s powerful computers, this has become obsolete. In Fritz 19, you play directly against databases, your own repertoire, or an opening article from the ChessBase Magazine!<br/><br/>If the White player, the Black player, the tournament title, or the source begins with “White” or “Black”, then all the moves in this game belong to this colour. Fritz will then only play these moves. A repertoire is always rather narrow from the point of view of one’s own colour and broad for the opponent’s moves. Try it out: Your Najdorf repertoire with Black against the “aggressive” player! Tip for ChessBase users: Save a generated opening survey from ChessBase and play against it immediately<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707140/extras/Fritz19_3e.jpg?t=1703750480"><h2 class="bb_tag">What else is available</h2>The new engine in Fritz 19 is the Computer Chess World Champion for 2023. The Calculation Training has been extended, especially in the important preliminary query of candidate moves. The Buddy Engine and the annotated engine analysis from ChessBase 17 have found their way into Fritz. The notation (and the whole program interface) has been enormously enhanced in places. Tactical Analysis, the important full commentary of your games, has been improved and much more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707140/extras/Fritz19_4e.jpg?t=1703750480"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arsenal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2697380/Arsenal/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Overview</h2>Kill enemies to absorb their energy, and use that energy to craft yourself a new gun when ammo gets low. The more energy used when you craft the more points you gain.<br/><br/>If your ammo gets too low you start using your health as ammo so be careful.<br/><br/><strong>✩Rifle</strong> — basic auto fire<br/><br/><strong>✩G. Launcher</strong> — shoots out bombs<br/><br/><strong>✩Charge gun</strong> — hold down and let go to shoot out a more powerful projectile<br/><br/><strong>✩Flamethrower</strong> — burns enemies<br/><br/><strong>✩Shot gun</strong> — shoots out multiple projectiles<h2 class="bb_tag">Controls</h2><strong>✩WASD Keys</strong> — move <br/><br/><strong>✩Space</strong> — collect new gun<br/><br/><strong>✩Left Click</strong> — to shoot						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Prophecy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2736140/Black_Prophecy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Among all game types, audio games are also a category that can bring joy to players, as players can enjoy the joy brought by music.<br>
 In the game, players can follow the rhythm of music by tapping falling notes, or by sliding and tapping continuous melody notes to obtain a pleasant gaming experience. During the game, not only is there an auditory enjoyment brought by music, but also the thrill brought by "playing" music.<br>
 Players can tap the falling notes along the track with their fingers according to the rhythm of the music, combining various operations such as "point", "press", and "slide" to bring a refreshing gaming experience. While listening to the music, they can also feel the infinite charm of rhythmic swaying. <br>
After each game, you will receive a score. Let's give it a try.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet Rock Duty</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2698910/Pet_Rock_Duty/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">FIND THE WAY OUT</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698910/extras/keygif.gif?t=1703743740"><br/><strong>In order to escape the pocket dimension school building you've found yourself trapped in, you must scour its confines for any items and info you can use to get the exit open before the school days end.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">KEEP HIM FED</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698910/extras/bobbygif.gif?t=1703743740"><br/><strong>Make sure you have your wits about you however, as your classroom pet Bobby the Pet Spider Flesh Rock has an insatiable appetite and must have his needs tended to throughout the school day. </strong><h2 class="bb_tag">STAY HIDDEN</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698910/extras/monitorgif.gif?t=1703743740"><br/><strong>There are also many members of the school staff who seem to be intent on keeping you from leaving.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Will you be able to best the schools various creatures, uncover the items needed to escape, and live to hear the school bell ring? I suppose only time will tell...</strong><br/><br/><strong>The gameplay of Pet Rock Duty includes:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Slow and strategic gameplay that rewards planning ahead </li><li>Multiple difficulties each with their own ending </li><li>Ambient music tracks that grow with your progression </li><li>Unlockable bonus content </li><li>Bonus challenges </li><li>Funny rocks </li><li>Other stuff probably</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Da Vinci Cryptex 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2729220/The_Da_Vinci_Cryptex_3/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729220/extras/h1.png?t=1703742562"><br/>The genial Italian inventor is back with new logical puzzles!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729220/extras/img1.png?t=1703742562"><br/><br/>Unlock the Cryptex by solving the riddles drawn in a book, it seems easy, but you need to use all your brain skills to escape!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729220/extras/h2.png?t=1703742562"><br/><strong>The Da Vinci Cryptex 3</strong> is a brainteasing game with 50 unique handdrawn puzzles. The more you crack them, the harder they become<br/><br/><strong>Warning</strong>: This game may be addictive!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729220/extras/h3.png?t=1703742562"><br/>- 50 new unique enigmas that will put your brain to work<br/>- Hints available (click the bulb button to get a hint)<br/>- A new room you're trapped in<br/>- Captivating background music<br/><br/>If you're a fan of puzzles, word games, brain thinking, mind games, IQ logic riddles, and enigmas, <strong>The Da Vinci Cryptex</strong> is the game for you, have fun in your spare time!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729220/extras/xslogo.png?t=1703742562"><br/><strong>XSGames</strong> is a solo indie game developer from Italy.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2472180/Gash/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2472180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2472180/extras/StorepageBanner_3.png?t=1703733126"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2472180/extras/Gash_Gameplay_GIF2.gif?t=1703733126"><br/>Gash is a hack-and-slash roguelike game. You play as a ronin seeking the strongest swordsman in the Sengoku era of Japan. You start weak; over time, you will become more robust to challenge the strongest swordsman. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2472180/extras/StorepageBanner.png?t=1703733126"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2472180/extras/Gash_ExtraGameplay_GIF_01.gif?t=1703733126"><br/>Gash has up to 5 possible maps where players can explore and endure. Each map has its unique enemies and challenges the players must face!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2472180/extras/StorepageBanner_2.png?t=1703733126"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2472180/extras/Gash_Gameplay_GIF3.gif?t=1703733126"><br/>There are 5 known legendary warriors in the world of Gash, each unique, creating a legendary battle between you and the enemy. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2472180/extras/StorepageBanner_4.png?t=1703733126"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2472180/extras/Gash_Gameplay_GIF4.gif?t=1703733126"><br/>Every enemy, boss, and map has their loot pool of trophies for you to collect. Depending on its type, each trophy will grant you strength and blessings to make you stronger. Strong enough to eventually take down the strongest swordsman.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S.E.C.U.</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2095120/SECU/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2095120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Features :<br/>• Rougelite Mode (ACT 1-3)<br/>• Arenas Mode (3 Maps)<br/>• 28 Weapons<br/>• 10 Melee Weapons<br/>• Firing Range<br/>• Tutorial<br/><strong><i><h2 class="bb_tag">DESCEND TO THE DEMON INFESTED AREAS AND CONQUER THEM</h2></i></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2095120/extras/ScreenShot00208_-_Copy.png?t=1703723826"><br/><br/><strong><i><h2 class="bb_tag">SLAY DEMONS WITH AN ARSENAL OF FIREARMS AND MELEE WEAPONS</h2></i></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2095120/extras/ScreenShot00210_-_Copy.png?t=1703723826"><br/><br/><strong><i><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME STRONGER WITH PERSISTENT UPGRADES</h2></i></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2095120/extras/Invocations.png?t=1703723826"><br/><br/><strong><i><h2 class="bb_tag">DIE, RISE, REPEAT</h2></i></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2095120/extras/ScreenShot00206_-_Copy.png?t=1703723826"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heading Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2717390/Heading_Home/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the captivating world of "<strong><i>Heading Home</i></strong>", an enchanting <u>open-world 3D platformer</u> that follows the endearing journey of Glyph, a lovable little orange robot that goes on an heartfelt adventure around the world seeking a place to call <strong><i>home</i></strong>.<br/><br/>As players guide Glyph through this vibrant and colorful world, they'll encounter a plethora of challenges and opportunities. The narrative revolves around Glyph's emotional journey, initially driven by the desire to find a place that promises security and joy. However, the journey unfolds to reveal a deeper truth: Glyph's true destination isn't a physical place but resides in the person of Widgette.<br/><br/>A core aspect of gameplay involves collecting Widgette's favorite ice cream—mint chocolate. These delicious treats serve as more than mere collectibles;<i> they symbolize Glyph's unwavering affection for Widgette</i>. Each ice cream collected becomes a cherished memory, encapsulating Glyph's adventures. This delightful mechanic not only adds a sweet layer to the gameplay but also serves as a symbolic connection between Glyph and Widgette.<br/><br/>As Glyph continues his adventure, encountering various challenges and making new friends along the way, the players become an integral part of his emotional journey. The game ingeniously weaves together gameplay and storytelling, ensuring that every jump, every collected ice cream, is not just a progression in the game but a step closer to the heartwarming reunion of Glyph and Widgette.<br/><br/>In the end, "<strong><i>Heading Home</i></strong>", isn't just a game about a cute robot seeking safety and happiness. It's a testament to the enduring power of love, the lengths one is willing to traverse for it, and the heartfelt moments that define a truly remarkable adventure. It's an interactive symphony of colors, emotions, and platforming challenges, inviting the player to experience the joy of reuniting with the one you cherish most.<br/><br/><i>Sometimes, home is not a place. It's a person.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Eternal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2703910/Life_Eternal/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							                                       <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703910/extras/Story.png?t=1703719264"><br/><br/>A necromancer awakens in a dilapidated tower he once knew as a pristine stronghold for his lord and sorcerer that he was apprenticed under. Somehow, the necromancer slept through it all in a sleep so sound, not even his lord's death woke him up. But that's all right; his lord had foreseen this coming and made sure the necromancer had the knowledge and training so he could raise his dead lord all on his own. <br/><br/>                                                                <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703910/extras/Necromancer.png?t=1703719264"><br/><br/>Now, it is up to you to help the necromancer collect the spell and tools necessary to bring his lord back to life so that he may take revenge on those who sought him harm. Although, perhaps, his lord's death could signify another kind of rebirth.<br/><br/>Life Eternal is a story-driven adventure game with a focus on exploration and no battles, from the developer behind the cult classic Star Stealing Prince. Uncover the secrets left behind by your lord's death and piece together the necromancer's own fragmented memories to find your answers.<br/><br/>There are two endings facilitated by a choice at the end.<br/><br/>                                       <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703910/extras/Controls.png?t=1703719264"><br/><br/>KEYBOARD<br/>Arrow Keys - Movement (hold SHIFT to dash!)<br/>Z - Confirm &amp; Interact with objects<br/>X - Cancel &amp; Open your main menu<br/>S - Displays guide arrows<br/>Q &amp; W - Scroll Up and Scroll Down in menus<br/><br/>XBOX CONTROLLER<br/>D-Pad - Movement (hold X to dash!)<br/>A - Confirm &amp; Interact with objects<br/>B - Cancel<br/>Y - Open your main menu<br/>LB &amp; RB - Scroll Up and Scroll Down in menus<br/><br/>MOUSE<br/>Left-Click - Confirm, Move to clicked area &amp; interact with objects<br/>Right-Click - Cancel &amp; Open your main menu<br/>Scroll Wheel - Scroll Up and Down in menus						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Monk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2726680/Pixel_Monk/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Pray for the World. Feed the Ducks.</strong><br/><br/>You play as an Orthodox Christian monastic who has gone to their favorite lakeside to pray and feed the ducks. With prayer rope in hand and pocket full of peas (bread is bad for their digestion), humbly quiet your heart while caring for the least of God's creatures.<br/><br/>Pixel Monk is a casual game about acquiring a peaceful spirit: an experience players can enjoy through interactive background elements and ambient sounds. The game features two leisurely actions: Pray, and Feed the Ducks, both of which interact with the environment in different ways. Players can also mix a variety of calming sounds, toggle daytime and weather, and cycle through inspirational quotes from the Bible and Orthodox Saints.<br/><br/>In Pixel Monk you can choose between:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Male or Female Monastic (with option for Angelic Schema robe)<br/></li><li> 10 Classical Piano songs<br/></li><li> 5 Mixable Ambient Sounds: Ducks, Wind, Rain, Frogs, Crickets<br/></li><li> 4 Orthodox Christian Icons: Christ, Theotokos, Venerable Monk, Holy Virgin<br/></li><li> 50+ quotes from Holy Scripture and Orthodox Saints<br/></li><li> Launch the game during Orthodox feast days (Old or New Calendar) to find special Icons and background items.</li></ul><br/>Pixel Monk is ultimately an experience, aimed at inspiring that same experience in the real world. In the hustle and bustle of life we may not always get to retreat to our favorite place to find peace, but we hope that Pixel Monk can bring players a small part of that peace until then.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Henry's Escape: Prison</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693900/Henrys_Escape_Prison/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The inaugural season of "Henry's Escape: Prison" comprises a meticulously crafted series of five episodes, each intricately interwoven to create a cohesive narrative. Ensuring a continuous and engaging experience for players.<br/><br/>Season One offers an immersive gameplay experience lasting approximately 2.5 - 3.5 hours, featuring a collection of challenging puzzles and mysterious conundrums that players must adeptly navigate. This game has been meticulously designed with a keen focus on replicating the intricacies of real-life escape rooms, adding an element of authenticity to the virtual escapade.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Beginning Of Story:</strong></h2>Henry’s wife and colleague, Alina, was a fearless Russian civil rights and anti-corruption activist campaigner and an investigative journalist. She was known for her unwavering commitment to uncovering the truth and exposing corruption, no matter the cost. One day, Alina received a tip about a powerful group called Wagner PMC that was involved in illegal activities. Despite the dangers, she decided to pursue the story and gathered evidence to support her claims. Wagner PMC was determined to keep its activities secret and saw Alina as a threat to their operation. Despite being threatened, Alina refused to give up her information or back down. She kept her resolve, knowing that her story was bigger than her safety. In the end, Alina's courage and tenacity caused her to be targeted. She died on January 21st, 2023, after a mysterious 14-day illness. Henry's world was turned upside down when his wife was found dead, and he was framed for her murder. Despite being innocent, Henry was convicted and sentenced to life in prison. He was devastated but refused to give up hope. One day, the warden approached Henry with an offer of help. He told Henry that his wife had uncovered evidence of the Wagner PMC and had sent the information to someone she trusted. The warden offered to help Henry escape from prison if he agreed to retrieve the evidence and expose the truth. Henry agreed and therefore he was transferred to a certain cell. With the help of the warden, he sets out to escape from the prison and find the evidence to clear his name and bring the corrupt members of the Wagner PMC to justice. The journey is filled with danger and obstacles, but Henry refuses to give up. Help Henry to escape from the prison so that he could continue his wife's legacy by speaking out against corruption fighting for the truth and proving that unwavering spirit and determination can be served, even when the odds seem insurmountable.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melia Keys In... Quantum Decade</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2717950/Melia_Keys_In_Quantum_Decade/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717950/extras/QDsteamgif.gif?t=1703696423"><br/><br/>"I, Kelsey Burton, am on a mission to finally grow up and forget my embarrassing adolescent alter-ego - but it's gonna be tough while still navigating friendships with clueless childhood pals &amp; a goofy alien fangirling over my old made-up persona." <i>...Hey now, I take offense to this. I am grown up - and what is this about a made-up alter ego? I have no idea what that's talking about... Should I just keep reading these off? Alright.</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>55K+ Words : "Six content-packed Episodes make for 6+ hours of gameplay on a first playthrough!"<br/></li><li>4th Wall Breaks : "I'm narrating to YOU..." <i>I guess?</i> "Answer choices your own way to unlock three possible endings!" <i>...Just don't tick me off.</i><br/></li><li>Animation/CGs : "Sprites blink and speak! CGs and animations for key scenes make the story really pop!"<br/></li><li>CG Gallery : "40 images and other items to unlock in the Gallery!"<br/></li><li>Bonus Content : "Join Moonie for some 'Out Of This World' content at the end of every episode!"<br/></li><li>Original Soundtrack : "Poppy, toe-tapping music courtesy of acclaimed VN composer Melia Keys!" <i>...Yes, that Melia Keys. I don't get it either.</i></li></ul><br/><i>There. That's it. I read the whole thing. Yes, I purposely skipped the part about Melia Keys being "best girl" and the "real star of the game." No, I'm not going back and saying that. I'm going home. Bye.</i> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repurpose</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1862430/Repurpose/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1862430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1862430/extras/steam_page_03.png?t=1703690729"><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2>You and several others have passed away.<br/><br/>Rather than being sent to Heaven or Hell, the powers that may be are unable to decide where you should go. You wake up in the Garden of Eden who's new home has been made in Limbo. You have three options: either take the trials to earn your place in Heaven, live it up in Hell, or remain lost in Limbo for eternity.<br/><br/>It's a lot to take in fresh off your death bed... but maybe you find can find your peace along with your new friends in the afterlife.<br/><br/>---<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1862430/extras/steam_page_01.png?t=1703690729"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1862430/extras/steam_page_02.png?t=1703690729"><h2 class="bb_tag">About</h2>Repurpose is an LGBT+ positive dating sim about death, love, and finding your purpose. We offer the ability to play as the gender that suits you best be it cis, trans, or anything else on this beautiful mess of a spectrum! The cast and staff of Repurpose are majority queer identifying so our stories are written with our community's experience at the very heart.<br/><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>Features:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Ability to play as cis, trans, or various other genders with unique interactions based on it.<br/></li><li>Eccentric queer/LGBTQA+ characters<br/></li><li>Partial voice acting from a talented cast.<br/></li><li>400K words of funny, dramatic, and touching story to go through.<br/></li><li>60+ CGs, 100s of unique sprite work, and dozens of backgrounds. This game puts the VISUAL in visual novel!<br/></li><li>Catchy soundtrack<br/></li><li>Secrets that lie underneath the surface....</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirates vs Ninjas</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735260/Pirates_vs_Ninjas/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pirates vs Ninjas  -  Ninjas and Sea Creatures are attacking Pirate Island.<br>
You and Your crew must take out ALL of them to Save Your Booty.<br>
<br>
This is a Fast Paced RPG Style Looter Shooter.<br>
<br>
The game includes a Multiplayer &amp; Single Player system.<br>
PvP OR CO-OP.<br/>
You can Invite Your Steam Friends with the ' + ' Icon on the Main Menu !<br/>
<br/>
The Game is packed with a complete inventory management and looting system, swimming system, level-ups, AI, combat mechanics, and many more features.<br/>
It has been tested online with clients under server-load.<br/>
Directly Compatible with the Steam online subsystem.<br/>
<br/>
* NOTE : You should have a Stable &amp; Fast Internet Connection for Best Results *<br/>
<br/>
Features:<br/>
<br/>
Advanced Inventory System<br/>
Inventory Quickslots<br/>
Item Durability<br/>
Fully Host System-based Saving System<br/>
Entity and Loot spawning system<br/>
Advanced Skill and Level Up system<br/>
Percentual Reward Division (Based on Damage)<br/>
Player Lobby and Menu system<br/>
Dynamic Crosshair System<br/>
Range and Melee weapons with damage, ammunition handling, and FX.<br/>
Throwable Grenades, Molotovs, etc<br/>
Advanced Enemy AI<br/>
Advanced Damage System<br/>
Advanced Player knockout and death system<br/>
Full SFX + Music<br/>
Interaction system<br/>
Fully interactable Water system with Swimming and Diving<br/>
Sniper Rifle scoping (zooming) mechanics<br/>
<br/>
Large Map<br/>
Lots of Enemies to battle<br/>
Pirate Ships to Travel around in<br/>
** { ONLY HOST CAN CAPTAIN THE SHIP } **<br/>
<br/>
. . . and More !						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valuable Cargo</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731090/Valuable_Cargo/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Valuable Cargo is an addictive game where you get the chance to become a forklift master and drive a powerful forklift.<br>
<br>
A difficult task awaits you - to transport goods across different levels and deliver them to the required places. The game features a variety of territories and each location will require special attention and skills from you, as various obstacles await you on the way to delivering goods.<br>
<br>
Delivery of goods requires precision and dexterity from you. You have to load various materials, boxes and other items. Be prepared for a variety of challenges that will require your attention! Embark on an exciting adventure where your forklift driving skills will lead you to success!<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br/>
- Different difficulty levels<br/>
- Beautiful graphics<br/>
- Pleasant music						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Demon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731080/Small_Demon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Small Demon - An exciting roguelike game that immerses you in the dark world of hellish labyrinths. As a small but powerful demon, you will face countless different enemies who are trying to destroy you!<br>
<br>
Use a varied arsenal of weapons, including blasters, guns and other weapons. Make your way through increasingly challenging stages of the maze to become the best sleeper in the business!<br>
<br>
The game is a 2D action roguelike. You need to move around the location, pick up more powerful weapons and destroy enemies.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br/>
-Pixel graphics<br/>
-Different types of enemies and weapons<br/>
-Great soundtrack						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REGULAR FIT</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731070/REGULAR_FIT/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							REGULAR FIT - As a tramp, you embark on a dangerous and mysterious journey through a dense forest full of amazing creatures and unseemly obstacles. Your main goal in this game is to survive in this cruel world. You will face various challenges such as jumping over cliffs, weaving through dangerous chasms and fighting aggressive creatures that inhabit the forest.<br>
<br>
The graphics in the game are done in an attractive pixel style, which adds some nostalgic appeal to the game. The soundtrack also creates a great atmosphere of the game, reflecting its mystery and danger.<br>
<br>
The game is a 2D platformer. You need to go through various levels, destroy many enemies and complete assigned tasks.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br/>
- Nice pixel graphics<br/>
- Lots of levels<br/>
- Good soundtrack						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racing Go</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731060/Racing_Go/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Racing Go is a car game where you have to use your driving skills on exciting tracks! In the game you will find a lot of different tracks and several types of cars! Overcome unusual obstacles, maneuver, and get to the finish line within a certain time! Immerse yourself in this exciting world and prove that you are the best racer, capable of overcoming any difficulties on the way to victory!<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
- Different difficulty levels<br>
- Several cars<br>
- Lots of tracks						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infected Bunker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713870/Infected_Bunker/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Infected Bunker - You will encounter exciting adventures in a forgotten bunker, where the main character finds himself completely alone. In a dark and gloomy environment, you have to use your ax in battles against creepy zombies and aggressive bugs to survive and get free from this mysterious place.<br>
<br>
The game is a 2D platformer. You have to go through one level after another, destroying enemies in locations.<br>
<br>
However, the bunker itself is a dangerous place, full of secrets and horrors. Be careful: danger lurks around every corner, and even familiar spaces can become fraught with traps.<br>
Will you be able to overcome all obstacles and find a way out of this nightmare?<br>
<br/>
Game Features:<br/>
- Nice pixel graphics<br/>
- Various enemies<br/>
- Good soundtrack						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Karoshi Club</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2624950/Welcome_to_the_Karoshi_Club/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624950/extras/Store_Image_03.png?t=1703667932"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624950/extras/Store_Image_06.png?t=1703667932"><br/><i>"Welcome to the Karoshi Club"</i> is a free visual novel set in the Japanese horror business punk in black and white manga style. The story follows Kenji Haishima, a former game developer, as he tries to find a new job and land an interview for the sales specialist position at a new company. As the player, you will face the consequences of your choices. Explore the <i>"Karoshi Club"</i> world and uncover the terrifying truth. Enjoy a thrilling experience and immerse yourself in this unique visual novel.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624950/extras/Store_Image_05.png?t=1703667932"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624950/extras/Store_Image_13.png?t=1703667932"><br/>It is a fact that we are keen on expanding the universe of <i>"Karoshi Club"</i> in collaboration with the gaming community. Therefore, <i>"Welcome to the Karoshi Club"</i> is a free showcase of our primary product. We are looking to get feedback on the game to determine whether we are heading in the right direction and identify what we did well and what needs improvement.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624950/extras/Store_Image_02.png?t=1703667932"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624950/extras/Store_Image_07.png?t=1703667932"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong><i>Job Interview Horror Simulator:</i> Experience the fear of job searching in a new reality</strong><br/></li><li><strong><i>Art:</i> This game's visual style is reminiscent of other famous horror manga artists</strong><br/></li><li><strong><i>Setting:</i> The crisis in Japan during the 90s is relevant to modern times</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624950/extras/Store_Image_01.png?t=1703667932"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624950/extras/Store_Image_09.png?t=1703667932"><br/>Our multinational indie team is a group of game developers impacted by layoffs in the gaming industry in 2023. However, we refused to give up and used this to create something of our own. We are determined to develop games and create specific worlds we are passionate about, and we hope you will love them just as much as we do.<br/><br/>Listen to the stories from Kamishibai while you sit back.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624950/extras/Store_Image_04.png?t=1703667932"><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FmNmJ7auHVc" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624950/extras/Store_Image_14.png?t=1703667932"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Fables: The Magic Snowflake Collector's Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2718140/Christmas_Fables_The_Magic_Snowflake_Collectors_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2718140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game consists of the best mini-games and item search scenes from DominiGames! Santa's Toy Factory is on holiday overload (happens every year, get used to it). In an effort not to let his co-workers down, one of the elves has refused to take a sick day (elves getting colds, imagine that), and now there's a vexed 10-year-old kid walking the streets of the city with a very (very!) dangerous artifact in his tiny sweet hands. Now what do a common cold and an impending catastrophe have to do with each other, you may ask? That is something to be kept just between you and the aforementioned elf! Above all, please-please-please don't tell Santa! Gather your wits for an unforgettable love story in this pulse-pounded new Hidden-Object Puzzle Adventure!<br>
<br>
This Collector's Edition includes: <br>
<br>
🎄   Bonus Chapter!<br>
Go through the main story to unlock the bonus chapter and relive the best Christmas ever as a kid! Go on an adventure to save the holiday from a sugar crash, and learn some exciting new details about the characters! Follow the jingle bells and get energized by the Christmas spirit!<br>
<br/>
🎄   Magic puzzles!<br/>
Look for new items, solve confusing puzzles, find answers, castigate and open boxes and mystery chests. This will all help move you further along in the storyline and even unlock new Christmas trails. Be on the lookout!<br/>
<br/>
🎄  Think twice!<br/>
You have the ability to choose the characters' phrases for a particular action. Your decision can affect the plot of the Christmas story. Don't forget, by making tough choices, you can affect people's fates. Save Christmas!<br/>
<br/>
🎄  Exclusive collections!<br/>
This enchanting story is filled with various magical items and mysterious artifacts that you can get as you progress through the episode. You'll have to be very careful to collect the whole collection. Hurry up and start playing to fully immerse yourself in the magical atmosphere!<br/>
<br/>
🎄   Unravel all the mysteries! <br/>
Put your intellectual skills to the test with a variety of Christmas puzzles and unwind with a collection of relaxing mini-games timed to the winter holiday, aiming for a variety of game achievements! This will enhance your gaming experience in this collector's edition!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rumble Fish +</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2499990/The_Rumble_Fish/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Rumble Fish, a game developed in 2004 by DIMPS, renown for its smooth animation and deep game mechanics, has returned as The Rumble Fish +, packed with new features.<br>
<br>
From online PvP with rollback netcode to a training mode with features such as CPU recording and playback, everything you need as a fighting game lover is here!<br>
<br>
Main Game Modes:<br>
Arcade<br/>
Local PvP<br/>
Online PvP<br/>
Training<br/>
<br/>
New feature: A CPU recording and playback feature has been added as an enemy behavior setting in training mode. Now you can record inputs for CPU and play them back to practice against.<br/>
<br/>
Selecting character colors:<br/>
When selecting a character in the character selection screen, you can choose different character colors depending on the button you press (LP, LK, SP, SK, D, START). Default color is LP.<br/>
<br/>
How to play as Greed:<br/>
On the character selection screen, input the following command.<br/>
1. RIGHT x2 with your cursor on Orville<br/>
2. LEFT x1 with your cursor on Typhon<br/>
3. LEFT x3 with your cursor on Boyd<br/>
4. RIGHT x2 with your cursor on Zen<br/>
Finally, press UP and Greed will appear as a selectable character.<br/>
<br/>
The Story:<br/>
It is the end of the 20th century... A large-scale natural disaster struck the eastern area of a nation. It wiped out the financial sector and resulted in a staggering loss of life.<br/>
<br/>
At the dawn of the 21st century, the conglomerate PROBE-NEXUS, commonly known as Probe, began reconstruction efforts in that eastern area. Colossal capital and cutting-edge technology was poured into rebuilding it. Skyscrapers that put the old high-rises to shame along with the world's biggest shopping mall and recreational facilities. This was the dazzling birth of a symbol for the new century. It was christened Zone Prime.						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stinky and Loof in Wonderland</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2135210/Stinky_and_Loof_in_Wonderland/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2135210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Stinky and Loof in Wonderland redefines action puzzle games! Solve more than 350 ingeniously designed levels in 350 different ways while evading a wide variety of enemies from UFOs to ghosts.   Guide four quirky characters, collect coins, and find (or build!) the way to each level's exit.   Test your logic and reflexes with a wide variety of levels that tell compelling stories.  Explore spooky dungeons, discover the mysteries of the Rainbow Spirits, drive the UFOs from Wonderland, rescue the captured Stinkers - and more!<br>
<br>
The game includes a fully integrated level editor allowing you to create, modify and distribute levels to both the Steam game and its companion mobile game.   As well as Stinky and Loof in Wonderland's own levels, the Editor can import levels designed for the beloved original trilogy on which it's based.  This gives you access to thousands of new levels and to a thriving online community of fellow Wonderland players.<br>
<br>
With its unlimited replay value and hundreds of mind-bending puzzles, Stinky and Loof in Wonderland is sure to become one of your favorite games						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NONOTOWN: Nonogram Logic Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2240720/NONOTOWN_Nonogram_Logic_Puzzle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2240720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							NONOTOWN is a fun and challenging puzzle game that puts your problem-solving skills to the test. In this game, you are presented with a grid of squares that are either filled in or empty. Your goal is to fill in the empty squares according to the given clues in order to reveal the hidden image.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2240720/extras/gif-nonotown-luuavv.gif?t=1703635409"><br/><br/>To play, you simply use your cursor to fill in the empty squares on the grid. As you fill in the squares, the hidden image will gradually take shape, and you will need to use logic and deduction to figure out which squares to fill in next. The game includes a variety of different nonogram puzzles of varying difficulty, so there is always a new challenge waiting for you.<br/><br/>NONOTOWN is a great game for fans of puzzles and logic games, and it is suitable for players of all ages. So why not give it a try and see how many nonogram puzzles you can solve?						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seal World</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1684410/Seal_World/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684410/extras/Discord.png?t=1703627693"><br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684410/extras/Arrow.png?t=1703627693"> <u><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fnjes7Bp" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Seal Discord</a></strong></u><br/><br/><strong>Meet MANY SEALS, unlock hats and glasses, eat lots of fibsh and take a nice break!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684410/extras/1.png?t=1703627693"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684410/extras/Meet_Seals.png?t=1703627693"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684410/extras/talk.gif?t=1703627693"><br/><strong>Talk to other friendly seals! Make simple choices!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684410/extras/Swim.png?t=1703627693"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684410/extras/swim.gif?t=1703627693"><br/><strong>Swim! Inspect interesting objects, and relax in peaceful spots!</strong><br/><br/>Become part of this silly world full of seals!<br/><br/><strong>Cool Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore<br/></li><li>Talk to Seals &amp; Make Choices<br/></li><li>Unlock Hats and Glasses<br/></li><li>Collect Fibsh<br/></li><li>Simple Platforming<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684410/extras/Patreon.png?t=1703627693"><br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684410/extras/Arrow.png?t=1703627693"> <u><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FSealDev" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Support The Development!</a></strong></u></img></img></li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Speed Run</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2419730/Ultimate_Speed_Run/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2419730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FkXCqedxQY5" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2419730/extras/Discord_Link.png?t=1703619097"/></a><br/><br/>Use your skill and determination to navigate through each course in your fastest time possible. Each level will test your precision skills as a gamer and push you to your limits. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2419730/extras/Always_Keep_a_Look_Out.gif?t=1703619097"> <br/><br/>Some of the levels are relaxing, but don't let your guard down, some of these courses may give you a false sense of security.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2419730/extras/Bonus_Round_1.gif?t=1703619097"><br/><br/><strong><u>Ragdoll Physics</u></strong><br/>Have fun with Ragdoll Physics. You'll find yourself messing up on purpose, just to have a giggle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2419730/extras/True_Ragdoll_Physics_2.gif?t=1703619097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2419730/extras/True_Ragdoll_Physics.gif?t=1703619097"><br/><br/><strong><u>Dodge 'Em's</u></strong><br/>It's not all running and jumping! Use your dodge-ball skills to get through the Dodge 'Em's where your jump is disabled!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2419730/extras/Beat_The_Dodge_Em_s.gif?t=1703619097"><br/><br/><u><strong>Balancing</strong></u><br/>How are you with heights? You will have to get good and refine your balancing skills!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2419730/extras/Refine_Your_Balancing.gif?t=1703619097"><br/><br/><strong><u>Many Obsticles</u></strong><br/>Ultimate Speed Run has many obsticles to have fun with. There is no random chance, you will have to decide where and when to make your moves.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2419730/extras/Bounce_and_Multi-Jump.gif?t=1703619097"><br/><br/><strong><u>Leaderboards</u></strong><br/>Every level has a Steam Leadboard associated with it. Compete against others to be the best, and show off your highest scores to the world and your friends to see!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2419730/extras/Leaderboard_1.png?t=1703619097"><br/><br/><strong><u>Store</u></strong><br/>Customize your character with clothing items. Spend your hard earned coins and stand out from the crowd.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2419730/extras/Customize_Character.gif?t=1703619097"><br/><br/><strong><u>Collections</u></strong><br/>There are four collections to complete. These special pickups are worth more coin, and once a collection is complete, you will unlock special clothing items that can be found in the store.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2419730/extras/Collections_1.png?t=1703619097"><br/><br/><strong><u>Achievements</u></strong><br/>There are around 45 achievements to obtain. Including a '100% Complete' achievement! But it will take a certain type of gamer to achieve this one!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2419730/extras/45_Acievements.gif?t=1703619097"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ninja Attack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2718060/Ninja_Attack/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2718060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You play as a ninja fending off waves of various types of ghosts, each getting increasingly difficult from the last. <br/><br/>How many waves can you last before the ghost onslaught overwhelms you.<h2 class="bb_tag">Coming Soon</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Classic mode: 40 waves, survive as long as you can without dying. Leave before you die to collect your rewards or battle on for a chance at more or to lose it all. Completing classic mode unlocks endless mode<br/></li><li> Endless mode: Seperate from the classic mode, endless mode lasts beyond the standard 40 waves of classic mode and can get you greater rewards for lasting past the standard 40 waves.<br/></li><li> Skills: Using the rewards you get from classic and endless mode you can upgrade certain skills to imrpove your chances at surviving.<br/></li><li> Bosses: Every 10 waves you will have to face a boss ghost who will be more challenging than normal, once defeated a greater reward will be given and you'll advance to the tier of ghost</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tharaba</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2729370/Tharaba/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dive into the exhilarating world of Tharaba, a thrilling score-chasing Arcade game that challenges players to master the art of precision and timing. Immerse yourself in a fast-paced and dynamic gaming experience as you face off against randomly generated enemies, aiming to achieve the highest score possible. Become the ultimate Motharib by showcasing your skills and outperforming your friends getting the highest score on the leaderboard in this adrenaline-fueled Arcade Game.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729370/extras/Tharabagifff.gif?t=1703607745"><br/><br/>Gameplay:<br/>Tharaba revolves around the concept of precision and timing, where each hit must be perfectly executed to score. Players engage in battle against randomly generated enemies, each with unique characteristic and attack pattern. The goal is to defeat enemies by strategically timing your attacks and dodges.<br/><br/>Key Features:<br/><br/>Precision-Based Combat: Tharaba's gameplay focuses on precision and timing, requiring players to execute each move perfectly to achieve the highest score. Master the art of well-timed strikes and flawless maneuvers to secure the highest score.<br/><br/>Randomly Generated Enemies: Encounter a diverse array of enemies, each with its own set of challenges and behaviors. Adapt your strategy on the fly as you face unpredictable foes, keeping the gameplay exciting every time.<br/><br/>Score-Chasing Mechanics: The primary objective is to attain the highest score possible, while not losing health. Each precise move contributes to your overall score, encouraging players to continuously refine their techniques and strive for perfection in every battle.<br/><br/>Tharaba offers an exhilarating gaming experience, combining time precision combat with the thrill of chasing high scores. Dive into this action-packed world and emerge as the ultimate Motharib in the quest for glory!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divine Journey: The Life of Jesus</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2721090/Divine_Journey_The_Life_of_Jesus/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2721090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Devine Journey - the Life of Jesus unfolds the extraordinary life of Jesus Christ across 25 compelling chapters. <br>
<br>
Begin at the miraculous birth in Bethlehem, witness transformative miracles, and delve into the profound teachings that have shaped civilizations for centuries.  As you progress, engage in 10 distinct types of minigames that add layers of interactivity to the experience. As you complete each level, be inspired by carefully selected quotes from the Bible, providing a spiritual reflection on the themes explored in the game. <br>
<br>
Whether you're decoding ancient scrolls, finding hidden objects, or solving interactive puzzles, the biblical quotes punctuate each level, deepening the connection between the gameplay and the spiritual journey. <br>
<br>
Devine Journey is more than a game; it's a meditative experience, inviting players to reflect on the words that have inspired generations.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Spider to A Fly</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2259530/A_Spider_to_A_Fly/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2259530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							90's Horror inspired Point &amp; Click — a Dark and Emotional journey of a man looking for his missing son while facing his hidden demons. Enjoy an Atmospheric &amp; stylized world, haunting and memorable audio, and piece together a story that will stay with you long after it ends.<br>
<br>
Ian Comes Home to Find His Son is Missing, Quickly Throwing Him into a Downward Spiral of Betrayal, Grief, Hatred, and Despair as He Searches, Not Only for His Missing Child, but for Himself.<br>
<br>
- A short (1-3 hours) 2D solo-made adventure/horror story with mature themes.<br>
<br>
- Inspired by Games/films such as "Silent Hill", "Jacobs Ladder", "A Tale of Two Sisters", and "The Cat Lady".<br/>
<br/>
- "Point &amp; Click" style adventure gameplay.<br/>
<br/>
- A Unique "Pixel-Photobash" Art Style.<br/>
<br/>
- Dark and Oppressive Music with a Haunting Atmosphere.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fighting</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2715260/Fighting/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							PS: This is a game developed by me alone, and I am looking for a job. My previous salary was about 70000 US dollars per year. So I hope to find a similar job. Proficient in UE3, 4, and 5, with over 15 years of C++experience. <br/>    This is a link to my work from a long time <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fago.https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fchannel%2FUClAbc9s_g2X7DaIn4aUvMOQ" rel="noopener" target="_blank">ago.https://www.youtube.com/channel/UClAbc9s_g2X7DaIn4aUvMOQ</a><br/>    This is my previous game link from <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2F2017.https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DAYt1GNYxeX0%26amp%3Bt%3D14s" rel="noopener" target="_blank">2017.https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AYt1GNYxeX0&amp;t=14s</a><br/>    This is a game that I led the development of in <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2F2022.https%3A%2F%2Fstore.steampowered.com%2Fapp%2F2473100%2FNull_Sequence%2F" rel="noopener" target="_blank">2022.https://store.steampowered.com/app/2473100/Null_Sequence/</a><br/><br/>    This is a common MMPRPG game.<br/>    Players control a character, wielding a sword or axe, to defeat monsters and obtain spoils of war, including experience and coins, through attacks and skills.<br/>    Experience can be used to level up, coins can be used to unlock more weapons and skills, and drugs can be purchased to increase survival opportunities.<br/>    Gameplay:<br/>    1. Explore the World<br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715260/extras/ExploreWorld.png?t=1703748876"><br/>    2. Defeat monsters and upgrade<br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715260/extras/DefeatMonsters.png?t=1703748876"><br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715260/extras/LevelUp.png?t=1703748876"><br/>    3. Learning equipment and skills<br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715260/extras/PurchaseWeapon.png?t=1703748876"><br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715260/extras/PurchaseSkill.png?t=1703748876"><br/>    4. Challenge Boss<br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715260/extras/Boss.png?t=1703748876"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Puzzle 5</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2706250/Christmas_Puzzle_5/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Next chapter of Christmas Puzzle awaits!<br/>Complete matching puzzle levels and create a gingerbread holiday decoration telling the story of Hansel and Gretel's journey.<br/><br/>Embark on a whimsical adventure and tackle a series of quests to tidy up, decorate, and build a fantastical world inspired by classic fairy tales. From cleaning cookie crumbs to creating a gingerbread house, from building a castle for mischievous witch to the chocolate factory grand opening. <br/><br/>Solve puzzles, light up decorations, and navigate challenges to guide the characters through their enchanting journey. Creative tasks and a touch of humor promise a magical and visually stunning experience for players of all ages. Get ready for a heartwarming conclusion as the characters find their way home.<br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>	225 match-3 levels to play <br/></li><li>	Complete dozens of quests<br/></li><li>	Follow the winter story<br/></li><li>	Create Hensel and Gretel decoration </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
