<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Dominions 6 - Rise of the Pantokrator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2511500/Dominions_6__Rise_of_the_Pantokrator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2511500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are a God! You are master and ruler of a loyal nation. You have unimaginable powers at your disposal. You have claimed this world as yours. But there are others who stand in your way. You must defeat and destroy these pretenders. Only then can you ascend to godhood and become the new Pantokrator.<br>
<br>
Dominions 6 is a turn based 4x strategy game suitable for both play vs AI, player vs player.  Team play vs AI or players also works great as everyone can do their turns at once.  The game has a huge variety of units, spells, magic items and different nations to play.<br>
<br>
In Dominions you take control of a powerful being that rules a nation and aspires to godhood. The type of Pretender Gods can vary from magically powerful arch mages to huge titans or large monuments. The pretender gods have different strengths dependent on what kind of god you choose and what nation you play.<br>
<br>
When you start the game you decide what kind of god you are and how your Dominion affects your lands, followers and sacred soldiers. It is an expression of your divine might and the faith of your followers. If your dominion dies, so do you. Your dominion also inspires your sacred warriors and gives them powers derived from your dominion.<br/>
<br/>
In order to win and become the one true god you have to defeat your enemies one of three different ways: conquer their lands, extinguish their dominion or claim the Thrones of Ascension.<br/>
<br/>
Dominions is set in a fantasy world that draws inspiration from historical nations, cultures and myths. You will not encounter the elves of conventional fantasy in this game. Instead you might lead a nation of vanir from old norse myth. Aztecs, romans, israelites, greeks, kievian rus and lovecraftian horrors are just a few of the inspirational sources of the game.<br/>
<br/>
The first Dominions game was released in 2002 and was well received by strategy gamers. Since then Dominions has been much refined and Dominions series is still actively played making it one of the longest running 4x turn based strategy games.<br/>
<br/>
----------<br/>
<br/>
Dominions 6 is scaled up compared to Dominions 5 and armies are larger. We wanted to tweak the balance between conventional armies and magic. To accomplish this a couple of changes are introduced. Incomes and resources are increased, while mages are more expensive. Battlefield-wide spells are more difficult to cast and there are instead more mid-tier spells. There are some other changes with the same aim.<br/>
<br/>
The second and probably most influential change is the addition of a new magic path. No longer are illusions the domain of Air magic. Instead illusions, phantasms, dreams and the stuff of forgotten legends are manipulated with the path of Glamour. This has resulted in many new spells, items and sites being added to the game. <br/>
<br/>
A third massive change is the separation of mounts and riders. Riders and mounts now have separate stats and can be targeted individually. This change probably has less impact on gameplay than the previous one, but will still have an impact on cavalry and nations using mounted units.<br/>
<br/>
Dominions 6 features a number of new nations as well. The addition of the Glamour path has also affected several of the old nations. <br/>
<br/>
There are also a number of changes intended to ease gameplay.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cult of the Lamb: Sinful Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2646130/Cult_of_the_Lamb_Sinful_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2646130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Sin to your heart’s content with Cult of the Lamb: Sinful Pack. This pack is the perfect way to indulge for those who enjoy a gluttonous aesthetic befitting kings and queens. Vanity might be a sin, but there’s nothing wrong with that!<br/><br/><strong>Cult of the Lamb: Sinful Pack includes;</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>5 brand new Follower forms: Hammerhead, Ladybug, Tiger, Llama, Sphynx<br/></li><li>6 new Follower outfits<br/></li><li>6 new base decorations<br/></li><li>A sinful new Fleece for the Lamb!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Safety Hotline</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2357910/Home_Safety_Hotline/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/RuntimeLabel-HSH-Dark.png?t=1705432881"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/ShinyLogoOnlyGIF.gif?t=1705432881"><br/><br/><strong>Hearing noises? Seeing things? Call Home Safety Hotline! Our operators are standing by, waiting to give you the answers you need to protect your home from all manner of pests and household hazards.</strong><br/><br/>Home Safety Hotline is an analog horror inspired telephone operator simulator where you answer incoming callers' questions about what's inside their home. Read through a vast catalog of common pests and household hazards, and do your best to become an expert in home safety. You will be held responsible for what happens.<br/><br/>A new horror experiment from Nick Lives, the creator of <i>NiGHT SIGNAL</i> and <i>A Wonderful Day For Fishing</i>. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Navigate a vast catalog of safety information using the latest in 90's technology.<br/></li><li> Listen to original jazzy lo-fi music by David Johnsen while you place callers on hold.<br/></li><li> Correctly deduce what's in your callers' homes or else leave them to suffer the consequences.<br/></li><li> Learn about the various untold horrors that live inside your home.<br/></li><li> "Phobia Toggles" - An accessibility option that allows you to disable in-game images for common phobia triggers including arachnophobia and more.<br/></li><li> Unlockable Art Book detailing the game's development history.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/NumberOnlyGIF.gif?t=1705432881"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingsvein</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2276830/Kingsvein/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2276830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							All contact with the city of Kingsvein has been lost. As Wisp Slayer, your role is to investigate and exterminate whatever evil lurks there.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2276830/extras/castleBanner_616x152.gif?t=1705404781"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adventure through the castle and its outer reaches as you see fit - secret treasures and skulking beasts hide around every corner! <br/></li><li>Dynamic and deep tactical combat - toss your enemies into spikes then electrify their blood, or cover the battlefield in flames <br/></li><li>Customize your team by mixing and matching 15 different classes, each with upgradeable abilities and equippable passives <br/></li><li>Use your abilities to explore - freeze rivers with your magic, blast through cave walls, and throw chains to topple statues <br/></li><li>Ride your loyal steed in and out of combat, and train it to be as fierce as any Knight <br/></li><li>Set in the realm of Graven, a weird subterranean world of living soil and half-stone Diecast <br/></li><li>From the maker of the highly-rated <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1224290/Horizons_Gate/" rel="" target="_blank">Horizon's Gate</a>, <a href="http://store.steampowered.com/app/415920/Voidspire_Tactics/" rel="" target="_blank">Voidspire Tactics</a> and <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/643900/Alvora_Tactics/" rel="" target="_blank">Alvora Tactics</a></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2276830/extras/voidbeam616x152.gif?t=1705404781"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Builder</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1244630/House_Builder/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1244630/header_alt_assets_12.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Become one man construction crew and build houses like a simple African mud hut and as complex as a super modern energy-saving architectural marvel.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1244630/extras/20232.gif?t=1705430976"><br/><br/>Let us take you on a trip to various spots on the globe and experience true architectural variety. You will try to build a mud hut in Africa, an igloo in the Arctic, a Canadian house, a log cabin in Siberia, a traditional house made of bricks, airbricks, or concrete, and many, many more…<br/>Every house consists of hundreds of elements you need to match according to the rules of construction.<br/><br/><strong>Learn new technologies</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1244630/extras/4.gif?t=1705430976"><br/><br/>See how construction technologies differ from each other. Learn how to apply proper materials and procedures during the building process.<br/>Build houses brick by brick, element after element, down from the foundations and up to the roof.<br/>Learn different structures of buildings, construction materials, their features, and their properties. Build simple constructions made of primitive materials, but also ultramodern buildings featuring the latest technological discoveries.<br/><br/><strong>Use unique mechanics</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1244630/extras/3.gif?t=1705430976"><br/><br/>Use various tools depending on the situation and requirements. Improve your skills, and use better equipment to be able to build complex structures quickly and efficiently.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1244630/extras/1.1.gif?t=1705430976"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1244630/extras/8.gif?t=1705430976"><br/><br/><strong>Demolition</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1244630/extras/6.gif?t=1705430976"><br/>Sometimes there is no way out. Demolish everything in your path and start again!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1244630/extras/7.gif?t=1705430976"><br/><br/>ABOUT HOUSE BUILDER<br/><br/>The building is your hobby? Thanks to the House Builder you will become a one-man construction crew! Find a perfect piece of land and create something amazing there! Constructing is only limited by your imagination and bank balance… So control your resources, keep up with construction standards and raise buildings that everyone will love!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1244630/extras/2.2.gif?t=1705430976"><br/>HOUSE BUILDER – MAIN FEATURES:<br/><br/>To build a first-class house, start with choosing the perfect location. You can select every place in the world! Boiling Africa, frosty Siberia, or tropical Amazon Rainforest? It’s up to you! <br/>Next, let’s focus on the project - you can create different types of buildings - from miserable little sheds to exclusive mansions. This will depend also on the materials you will use. Each of them has different properties. Using the wrong material will cause unpleasant consequences. Prove your cleverness and knowledge to prevent any glitches in construction. Over time your skill will be better and buildings more advanced. When all the pieces are set, it only takes a moment to finish and give a unique look to your house. The buyers will be delighted! <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1244630/extras/5.gif?t=1705430976"><br/>MAIN FEATURES<br/><br/>Build all over the world - Learn more about the architectural style of the region and let your imagination run wild!<br/>Learn new technologies - With every building your skill improves and new technologies will expedite your work.<br/>Demolish! - Some of the houses must be cleaned up and rebuilt from scratches. <br/>Go back in time - Travel across many periods in history and try to build all iconic designs<br/>Diverse climate - scorching and freezing temperatures can be a challenge to sustain. Be aware of dangerous fauna.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1244630/extras/2023.gif?t=1705430976"><br/>Home Builder.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1244630/extras/grafika_1.png?t=1705430976"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sovereign Syndicate</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1674920/Sovereign_Syndicate/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1674920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1674920/extras/TitleLogo.png?t=1705355459"><br/><br/><strong><i>Explore an open world in this Victorian steampunk cRPG.</i></strong> Play as three characters with branching stories that intertwine. Investigate, interact, and take action to leave your mark on the world and its inhabitants. No random stat points here, use your skills to level them up, and trust your fate to our tarot card chance system. <br/><br/>So, how will you solve your problems? <strong><i>Combat, persuasion, magic, explosives?</i></strong> The choice is yours and all your cards are on the table; but be careful, the docklands aren’t for the faint of heart. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1674920/extras/Tarot.png?t=1705355459"><br/><br/><strong>Tarot Card Chance System</strong> – Leave your dice at home as you interact with a variety of characters. NPC’s react to your gender, race, appearance, and choice of dialogue, so you’d better look and act the part if you want the “right” results. But not everything is certain, luck plays a role and it’s all in the cards with our tarot card chance system. <br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1674920/extras/Stats.png?t=1705355459"><br/><br/><strong>Skill and Etiquette System</strong> -  The skills you use will improve your ability, while ignoring others will cause them to stagnate. Master the skills you choose and learn more about the world and its inhabitants to unlock special dialogue and skill-check options.<br/><br/>So go, see, do! And don’t be afraid to try the unconventional. Drown yourself in gin? Sure, provided you’ve got the constitution for it. Smoke that opium? Certainly, but be careful not to doze off— it might not be safe here. Put it all on black? You only live once, as they say. Even in failure you learn something…<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1674920/extras/Map.jpg?t=1705355459"><br/><br/><strong>A Rich Open World to Explore</strong> - A steampunk fantasy-inspired Victorian London awaits; filled with interesting characters and locations. Explore the back alleys, opium dens, brothels, and more at your peril, or relax and enjoy their simple pleasures. Investigate, interact, and take action to forge your own path.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1674920/extras/ThreeCharacters.png?t=1705355459"><br/><br/><strong>Three Characters, Three Different Stories</strong> – Play as three characters with stories that intertwine through the city’s docklands and unfold based on your choices.   <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Atticus Daley</strong>, an orphaned minotaur magician crawling out of the bottom of a bottle to find a sense of belonging, and his next fix. <br/></li><li> <strong>Clara Reed</strong>, a corsair with a checkered past, and a cunning woman with a rebellious streak. Follow her on a search for vengeance, and the courtesan killer.   <br/></li><li> <strong>Otto</strong>, the trusty automaton and companion of engineer Theodore Redgrave. More than just the sum of his parts, Otto wants more to life than servitude and utility.</li></ul><br/>Each character has their own mix of skills, equipment, and expertise, and they might just have to work together to succeed. Will you trust your companions, and should they trust you? Not everyone is a hero after all. <br/><br/><br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A large open world to explore, 20 different locations spread over the city’s east docklands<br/></li><li>Three playable characters<br/></li><li>Three intertwined stories to experience<br/></li><li>Branching narrative and dialogue system<br/></li><li>Character customization <br/></li><li>Tarot card chance system<br/></li><li>Single-player</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Momodora: Moonlit Farewell</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1747760/Momodora_Moonlit_Farewell/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1747760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Momodora: Moonlit Farewell" is the latest installment in the Momodora series. Join Momo, High Priestess of the village of Koho, as she embarks on a divine mission to save her people from imminent destruction at the hands of the demon hordes summoned by a malevolent bellringer.<h2 class="bb_tag">Story:</h2>Momodora: Moonlit Farewell presents the account of the greatest calamity to befall the village of Koho, five years after the events of Momodora III.<br/> Once the toll of an ominous bell is heard, the village is soon threatened by a demon invasion.<br/>The village's matriarch sends Momo Reinol, their most capable priestess, to investigate the bell and find the bellringer responsible for summoning demons. It is their hope that by finding the culprit, they will also  be able to secure the village's safety, and most importantly, the sacred Lun Tree's, a source of life and healing for Koho...<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Gorgeous pixel art and animation<br/></li><li> Action-packed gameplay focusing on melee combos, dodging enemy attacks, and firing arrows at enemies<br/></li><li> The "Sigil" system, which allows for greatly customizable play styles<br/></li><li> Intense and core-shaking boss battles<br/></li><li> Deep exploration into a world rich in lore and atmosphere<br/></li><li> Freely adjustable difficulty levels, allowing you to relax and explore the alluring world at your own pace or take on mighty foes for a real challenge</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Developer's Voice:</h2>Hello!<br/><br/>This is rdein, creator of the Momodora series. Recently my team and I have announced the latest installment in the series, “Moonlit Farewell”. This is a concluding story, following through from the events of Momodora 3. With this new tale, I also intend to close the book on many of the past games’ mysteries and questions.<br/><br/>I’m aware that many players are more familiar with the story of Kaho, which is set in a distant past. As such, I’m designing “Moonlit Farewell” to be as enjoyable as possible without prior knowledge of Momodora 1 to 3’s stories. Moreover, the series has always been focused on action and minimal stories. So please, don’t worry too much about “catching up”!<br/>Lastly, we hope to bring you our best game with this new title, using all the knowledge we’ve learned in the past 10 years. Please look forward to it!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frostrain</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735630/Frostrain/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/01_Thumnail.png?t=1705033707"><h2 class="bb_tag">Roam the frozen world</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Roam_the_frozen_world.gif?t=1705033707"><br/>Climate change has turned the world white and frozen, and the only thing moving on the planet is you, your passengers, and your train. It's a dead world, but ironically, it's all the more fascinating for it. A vivid landscape awaits you to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Keep your passengers happy</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Keep_your_passengers_happy.gif?t=1705033707"><br/>The passengers on your train will work diligently at your command, but be careful: if you don't manage their happiness properly, they might throw you off the train.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build your own train with card decks</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Build_your_own_train_with_card_decks.gif?t=1705033707"><br/>Each time you pass through a city, you'll be able to add new train cars by launching a heavy lift drone. Be careful with each choice you make. If you are lucky, you'll be able to build a better, more synergized, happily-ever-after train deck, but it won't always go as you planned.<h2 class="bb_tag">Reach the Promised Land</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Reach_the_Promised_Land.gif?t=1705033707"><br/>Lead your passengers in search of the Promised Land, somewhere on the eastern edge of the world. But the journey to the Promised Land isn't all smooth and pleasant. You'll have to pass through toxic areas, and a severe storm is brewing behind you. Pay attention to your passengers' happiness levels and lead them safely to the Promised Land. The journey is in your hands.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoardLand</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735620/BoardLand/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Create your own strategy with the dice</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/extras/Cardnals_1.gif?t=1705310503"><br/><br/>The dice is rolled!<br/>Are you going to move? Are you going to act?<br/>Different effects are applied to each die, and the numbers determine your behavior.<br/>How do you combine numbers to get the best results?<br/>Every time you pick a number, you'll have to choose carefully.<h2 class="bb_tag">Make a powerful board by strengthening the tiles.</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/extras/Cardinals_2.gif?t=1705310503"><br/><br/>Tiles get more and more powerful!<br/>Every time you act on a tile, the tile gains experience, and the tile with enough experience is upgradeable.<br/>Combine tiles with multiple properties to create the best strategy, your own board<h2 class="bb_tag">Defeat the monsters and bosses</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/extras/Cardinals_3.gif?t=1705310503"><br/><br/>Monsters disturb you!<br/>Monsters can summon Fireballs, or they can curse and cause obstacles to certain tiles.<br/>You have to move and act with the dice, avoiding these patterns every time.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Flame: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517810/The_Last_Flame_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_1.png?t=1705280390"><br/>The Last Flame is a roguelike auto-battler which focuses on build creation, strategy and decision making. Recruit special heroes, fight deadly encounters, loot and craft powerful gear, discover and create unique synergetic builds! Every run, you will need to create powerful builds that will take down your foes!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_A3.gif?t=1705280390"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_2.png?t=1705280390"><br/>The Last Flame offers an incredible amount of build diversity. Combine heroes, items, relics and origins together to create amazing builds! Hero and team building have been designed with flexibility and freedom at their core which allows you to discover and create unique synergetic builds every single run!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Builds.gif?t=1705280390"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_3.png?t=1705280390"><br/>In between the automated combats, you will have to cleverly guide your heroes through the adventure by making the smart decisions! Manage your resources, choose the optimal path in the map, make powerful builds, and strategically position and plan the combat phase!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Tactical.gif?t=1705280390"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/comingToFullVersion.png?t=1705280390"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get access to a lot more stuff! Make amazing builds with over 250 items, 55 heroes, 120 relics and 55 origins.<br/></li><li>Continue the adventure in the third act, and meet the final boss in a special act!<br/></li><li>Face 30 challenging enemies and 10 bosses!<br/></li><li>Progress through 5 difficulties which will challenge your knowledge and strategy!<br/></li><li>Push your builds to their limit in the endless mode, a mode where you try to reach the highest floor!<br/></li><li>Experience the game in diverse and fun new ways with the challenge modes!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_ENDLESS.gif?t=1705280390"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summoners War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2426960/Summoners_War/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2426960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>▶Features</strong><br/><strong>[Tactical RPG play]</strong><br/>Witness the dazzling display of each monster 's unique skills.<br/>23 different Rune sets to pick and choose additional abilities for your monsters!<br/>Come up with the best strategy to win battles in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[Endless Fun]</strong><br/>Decorate your Village, battle other summoners , explore dungeons , fight in PvP battles , expand your collection, train monsters , and more.<br/><br/><strong>[The Key of Colletion RPG : Massive Collection]</strong><br/>Fire, Water, Wind, Light and Dark!<br/>5 different attributes, and 1500 different monsters!<br/>Collect as many monsters as you can and win battles with your own decks .<br/><br/><strong>[Real-time Raid]</strong><br/>Battle as a team with your greatest monsters !<br/>A real-time battle with 3 users!<br/>Defeat the boss with your fellow Summoners using various tactics.<br/><br/><strong>[Homunculus]</strong><br/>The Forbidden Summoning Magic has finally been revealed!<br/>You can Evolve the skill of your choice with this special monster.<br/>Summon Homunculus and show off your strategy in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[All about Turn-Based RPG : World Arena]</strong><br/>Enjoy a real-time battle with Summoners worldwide!<br/>Experience a breathtaking battle that starts from Pick &amp; Ban.<br/>Reveal your unique strategy to the world and win battles .<br/><br/><strong>[Guild Content]</strong><br/>A sensational Guild PvP battle in the Isle of Conquest!<br/>Explore the Tartarus' Labyrinth and dungeons with Guild Members.<br/>Make your Guild the greatest of all.<br/><br/><strong>[Dimension Hole]</strong><br/>Fight against the ancient power emerged from a new dimension!<br/>Defeat the Ancient Guardians and meet the powerful monsters with new awakening power.<br/><br/><strong>[Artifact]</strong><br/>Artifacts are now dropped with MAX power-up levels!<br/>Summoners , fight against the powerful bosses and acquire Artifacts!<br/>Enhance your monsters with various sub properties of Artifacts.<br/><br/><strong>[Progression and Farming Structure Revamp]</strong><br/>Summoner progression structure renewed and content reward greatly improved!<br/>Dive into Summoners War and experience the enhanced progression system!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portal: Revolution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/601360/Portal_Revolution/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Portal: Revolution is a fan-made mod for Portal 2 which plays before the events of Portal 2 in the dead and decaying Aperture facility.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/ezgif-7-f507c3c464_1_.gif?t=1705083406"><br/><strong>Over 40 new puzzles</strong><br/>The campaign contains 40 brand new puzzles making use of new test elements and presents existing mechanics in a new way not seen in Portal 2.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resurrected "Pneumatic Diversity Vent" element<br/></li><li> New laser cube variant<br/></li><li> Over 15 puzzles using only the blue Portal-Gun<br/></li><li> Gel Cleansing Field</li></ul><br/><strong>Difficulty</strong><br/>Portal: Revolutions puzzle difficulty starts where Portal 2 stops, but fear not. All new mechanics and advanced portal tricks are taught to you. We have ensured through rigorous playtesting that every player can solve the puzzles. Although very few chambers require portals to be fired mid-air, no puzzles require advanced tricky movement.<br/><br/>Depending on your experience with Portal 2 mechanics, you can expect about 5 to 7 hours of playtime.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/banner_story_2.gif?t=1705083406"><br/>Set inbetween Portal and Portal 2, Portal: Revolution tells a brand new story using new characters. You play as a test subject who is awoken by a personality sphere called Stirling and join his mission to find a powerful device capable of restoring Aperture to its former glory.<h2 class="bb_tag">ENGINE</h2>Portal: Revolution uses a modified version of Portal 2: Community Edition's engine, which is a custom version of the Counter-Strike: Global Offensive Source Engine branch using licensed source code provided by Valve Software.<br/><br/>This allowed us to introduce many mechanics and improvements to the engine to create an experience which would be impossible in Portal 2.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pesticide Not Required: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2480450/Pesticide_Not_Required_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The free prologue for Pesticide Not Required, a game that combines auto-attacking bullet heaven roguelites with farming game mechanics to create an expansive set of strategies and build combinations. Destroy huge hordes of evil insects, grow tons of crops, create your own build path, and unlock unique characters to play with!<br/><br/>This prologue version contains similar mechanics to the main game, but has less achievements, progression unlocks, unlockable characters, weapons, maps, and enemy varieties.<h2 class="bb_tag">Create Overpowered Builds</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/extras/CombatChaosFisher.gif?t=1705210453"><br/>You are the bullet hell! Grow an arsenal of ridiculous weapons and craft your own unique build with a combination of 40+ stats. Additionally, each character has their own unique traits that keep runs fresh.<h2 class="bb_tag">Farm, Fish, and Mine</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/extras/FarmFishMineWinterGif.gif?t=1705210453"><br/>Earn vital gold and experience from growing crops, catching fish, and mining. Expand your plot to harvest huge quantities of crops and build carefully to enhance your farming, fishing, and mining capabilities.<h2 class="bb_tag">Automate Your Farm With Pets</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/extras/PetsGifAutumn.gif?t=1705210453"><br/>Recruit friendly pets that will enhance your farm, collect loot, and kill enemies.<br/><br/>Other Features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Season-themed map variations with multiple difficulty levels<br/></li><li>Many unlockable characters with special traits<br/></li><li>Persistent skill tree upgrades<br/></li><li>Quick ~20-minute play sessions<br/></li><li>Tons of achievements to unlock<br/></li><li>Full gamepad and keyboard support<br/></li><li>Go WUMBO!</li></ul><br/>Pesticide Not Required: Prologue is inspired by awesome games like Brotato, Vampire Survivors, and Atomicrops.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Esports Godfather Origin</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2739460/Esports_Godfather_Origin/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/游戏简介英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>"Esport Godfather" is a management simulation card game that revolves around the theme of MOBA esports. In this game, you will assume the role of a coach in an esports club and personally build your own team! Starting from scratch, what kind of playstyle will you devise for your team? In a constantly evolving meta, can you derive a unique understanding of what it takes to win? How will you unlock the potential of your handpicked athletes and mold them into superstars?<br/><br/>Ultimately, will you be able to become a legendary figure in the esports industry, crafting your own esports story and lifting the championship trophy?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/选手培养英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>Each athlete is unique! They all have their own strengths and weaknesses.<br/>If an athlete's efficiency in earning money increases over time, they are undoubtedly a skilled late-game specialist.<br/>Successful ambushes can unlock hidden potential, propelling some athletes onto the path of godlike.<br/>As a coach, it's your responsibility to analyze each athlete's characteristics, devise training plans tailored to their needs, and guide them on their journey to becoming superstars!<br/><br/>· Every athlete possesses distinct abilities that will impact their performance on the battlefield!<br/>· An athlete's hero pool is crucial for Ban &amp; Pick strategies!<br/>· The tactic cards utilized by athletes in matches serve as the foundation of all strategies!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/版本变更英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>The meta environment is ever-changing!<br/>Changes in the equipment pool, the structure of economic income, and the source of decisive advantages, even slight alterations to the rules can drastically shift the priorities of Ban &amp; Pick and alter the strategic approach!<br/><br/>· Equipment will be added or removed as the versions change!<br/>· The timing of crucial team fights will shift with each version update, making team composition crucial!<br/>· Does harassment grant more gold? Do kills damage towers? Each gameplay rule brings a fresh experience!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/指挥战斗英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>You have the power to command the battlefield, with athletes attentively listening to your orders.<br/>Should you play it safe and focus on farming under the towers, or launch aggressive assaults and initiate attacks?<br/>Perfect team composition requires perfect leadership! The game is ever-changing, and you must face your opponents head-on!<br/><br/>· Each hero and athlete possesses their own tactic cards. It is through creative combinations and strategic application that they become unstoppable!<br/>· Offense or defense? Aggression or caution? The outcome rests in your hands. Formulate strategies and implement tactics!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/其他内容英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>· Over 50 unique heroes in the starting lineup, each with their own special abilities!<br/>· 200+ tactic cards, granting you control over the battlefield!<br/>· Diverse athlete training options! As a mentor, it's important to tailor your teachings to each individual!<br/>· Unearth young talents and cultivate new forces in the youth training camp!<br/>· Choose sponsors, a top-tier club deserves the support of top-tier sponsors!<br/>· Trash-talking sessions, asserting dominance is a must before crucial matches!<br/>· Abundance of events, includes unexpected occurrences, athlete communication, team pep talks!<br/>· Training match plans, knowing your opponents inside out ensures victory after victory!<br/>· Regular season, playoffs, transfer periods—different decisions await you at different times!<br/>· When athletes reach their limits, you must help them break through and reach new heights!<br/>· Create a custom team logo for your club!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/工作室LOGO英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>kings call</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674290/kings_call/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Kings call is a free-to-play, trading-card  . Playable through a browser, the game allows players to take the role of the Lord of Silver Heron Ridge, and obtain and use cards to summon creatures, cast spells, and defeat monsters as they battle through different regions and protect their kingdoms.<br>
Card-Based Battles | Choose from hundreds of different monster and spell cards, and fuse them together to make them more powerful.<br>
Protect Your Kingdom | Manage your kingdom's resources to obtain better cards, weapons, and equipment for your character.<br>
Player-vs-Player | Engage in Kings call' 1v1, 2v2, and 4v4 PvP arenas, or test your tactics against AI opponents.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703868247"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1705428302"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1705428302"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1705428302"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1705428302"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1705428302"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1705428302"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1705428302"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1704804364"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1705439381"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1705439381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1705439381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1705439381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1705439381"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1703186631"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1705229288"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1705229288"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1705229288"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1705229288"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1705229288"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1705229288"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1704392583"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1704392583"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1704392583"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loddlenaut</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1644940/Loddlenaut/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1644940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Loddlenaut is an ocean cleanup adventure set on a vibrant alien planet. Play as an interstellar custodian who is tasked with cleaning up the pollution left behind by spacefaring mega-corporation. Befriend local axolotl-like creatures and explore sunken corporate ruins as you revive the planet’s lush ecosystems.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1644940/extras/MarchHeroGif_Steam.gif?t=1705401427"><br/><br/>🚀 <strong>Explore</strong> an open-world alien planet<br/>🐠 <strong>Raise</strong> aquatic critters called “loddles” that grow based on what they eat<br/>🔫 <strong>Clean up</strong> icky goop and floating debris with your bubble gun<br/>🌟 <strong>Unlock</strong> special gadgets to clean different types of ocean pollution<br/>🛠️ <strong>Recycle</strong> collected trash to craft useful items and upgrades<h2 class="bb_tag">BRING GUP-14 BACK TO LIFE</h2>Your mission: Clean up the ocean planet of GUP-14 after it was abandoned by GUPPI, a mega-corporation that makes and sells everything from soda to spaceships. When you first arrive on the planet, you’ll find yourself amid murky waters, oil spills, and scattered junk.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1644940/extras/MarchCleanupGif_Steam.gif?t=1705401427"><br/><br/>Within the polluted environments, you’ll find remnants of GUPPI’s buildings, ships, and machinery all sunken to the ocean floor. Discover clues about the planet’s past inhabitants as you clean up the mess they left behind using an assortment of high-tech gadgets.<h2 class="bb_tag">BEFRIEND ALL THE LODDLES</h2>As you clean up the planet, you’ll run into axolotl-like aliens known as “loddles.” Protect them from the polluted waters and feed them aquatic fruits while you make their planet habitable again. Depending on their diet, loddles will grow in different ways and develop unique traits and abilities that will further enable them to survive on this polluted planet.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1644940/extras/LoddleEvoGif_BestBorder.gif?t=1705401427"><br/><br/>When the loddles are strong enough and the waters are cleaner, release them back into the wild and watch them thrive! You may even come across eggs that you can incubate to raise more loddles.<br/><br/><i>0.05GBP per sale on Steam is donated to WDC, Whale and Dolphin Conservation. WDC is a UK registered charity no. 1014705.</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1705031379"> </img></a><br/><br/>Vegas Infinite is for players aged 18+ only.<br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Click The Button</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2577760/Just_Click_The_Button/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FW9p6sm2ByZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577760/extras/discrodforsteam.png?t=1705507143"/></a><br/><strong>Just Click The Button takes the clicker genre and combines it with the arena shooter-reverse bullethell genre.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577760/extras/gif1.gif?t=1705507143"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577760/extras/gif2.gif?t=1705507143"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577760/extras/gif3.gif?t=1705507143"><br/><br/>Just Click The Button is a game about clicking on a button. The more you click the button, the more the game evolves. Level up, acquire new abilitites, choose your playstyle, and build a powerful button!<br/><br/>The game can be played idefenetly, allowing you to aquire (almost) every single ability, which will then cause there to be way too much stuff going at once. Or attemt to beat the game. The game can be beated via 1 of 4 endings. Some builds will make certain endings easier than others, which encourages you to choose specific abilities for whatever ending you will attempt.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577760/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter__3_.gif?t=1705507143"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577760/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter__2_.gif?t=1705507143"><br/><br/>Also check out Treasure Chest Clicker!<br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422090/Treasure_Chest_Clicker/?curator_clanid=43674917" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422090/Treasure_Chest_Clicker/?curator_clanid=43674917</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autumn Spirit</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2462830/Autumn_Spirit/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2462830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2462830/extras/title_synopsis.png?t=1705506499"><br/><br/>The world is slowly crumbling and you are falling apart with it. In an attempt to find a semblance of peace and to rethink your future you go into exile in a remote corner to enjoy the calm of nature. But you are not alone on these mountains, another soul in pain is on your land, a ghost grounded on earth by regrets. Deciding to free him of his curse, you might find peace yourself in the process.<br/><br/>Autumn spirit is a melancholic story about love and the modern anxiety of feeling powerless in this chaotic world. Featuring a dog. A very good boy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2462830/extras/title_characters.png?t=1705506499"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2462830/extras/clarisse_bio.png?t=1705506499"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2462830/extras/Nathan_bio.png?t=1705506499"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2462830/extras/title_features.png?t=1705506499"><br/><br/>- Star-crossed lovers, lonely together and more cute relationship tropes to chill on a rainy day.<br/><br/>-  A beautiful modern and melancholic love story tinted by humor. <br/><br/>- Plenty of  personality and bickering choices! <br/><br/>- Around 30,000 words (approximately 2h per playthrough)<br/><br/>- Burtonesque art style and soft atmospheric music <br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><i>Autumn spirit was made in one month for Spooktober 2022</i> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distant Sun</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2276140/Distant_Sun/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2276140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Distant Sun is a singleplayer, story-rich, sci-fi game based on character dialogue, puzzle solving, the choices you make and the impact of its results. <br/><br/>Set in the late 2100s, there's not much space in space. Under the backdrop of rising tension between the nations of Earth, Pioneer Research has embarked on the noble task of figuring out how to expand humanity throughout the cosmos but something odd happened there.<br/><br/>What happened in Pioneer Station? Puzzle together and save the lives of those that remain and uncover a conspiracy on a solar scale. Sift through corporate emails, hack administration rights, and talk with research personnel to unravel the mysteries, but do mind that the saying "ignorance is bliss" applies.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features of the game</h2><br/>- Choose your story<br/>The decisions you make advance the story in unique ways. Whether through dialogue with other characters, avoiding confrontation, or outsmarting your adversaries, this will effect the ending of the game.<br/><br/>- Dialogue tree<br/>The dialogue tree guides player conversations and is an essential part of the story. Talk with NPCs and discover more about what happened in Pioneer Station and the conspiracies that lies beneath.<br/><br/>- Companions<br/>You do not have to go in alone. Your crewmates Wonglei and Hailey will be there to back you up with firepower and advice.<br/><br/>- Character creator<br/>Customize your character's appearance with the game's in depth character editor.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitty Knight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2751370/Bitty_Knight/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2751370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bitty Knight is a fast-paced, challenging 2D top-down mini-roguelike with random levels and 30+ powerups. No two plays are ever the same and it is completely free-to-play. The game centers on a tiny knight stuck in a small dungeon and you have to reach the final boss to escape.<br/><br/>Collect upgrades to survive as you make your way to the final level, there are no saves and if your character dies you will have to restart. Collect keys, unlock chests, find gems, kill enemies and shop to upgrade or smash power-up blocks to find loot and your way to the end.<br/><br/>Be warned, some loot has negative effects and collecting loot blindly can have consequences that will make the game much harder.<br/><br/><strong>Note:</strong> <i>if you have issues, find a bug or have something to say then please post in the Community Hub for assistance</i> <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Completely free-to-play <br/></li><li>Random dungeons &amp; loot - no game is ever the same<br/></li><li>2D Top-down retro pixel graphics<br/></li><li>30+ Power-ups to collect with stacking<br/></li><li>Permadeath - no character upgrades or saves<br/></li><li>Hardcore mode if you prefer a real challenge<br/></li><li>Low system requirements - should run on most PCs</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2751370/extras/BittyKnight.jpg?t=1705505857"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renovation Plan</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2638900/Renovation_Plan/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Come and immerse yourself in this relaxing and leisurely home decoration game!The lovely cartoon art style and soothing background music will bring you a relaxed and pleasant game experience. <br>
<br>
Dear decorator, a task full of challenges and fun awaits you.According to the design drawing, put various furniture in the proper place, showing your aesthetics and skills.Each room has different usage scenarios, from bedroom to living room, from kitchen to bathroom, you need to choose the appropriate furniture and decoration style according to different scenarios.Not only that, there are also gorgeous large apartments waiting for you to challenge.<br>
<br>
Come and try it, let's find the fun of decoration in this game together!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VRidge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2677750/VRidge/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							VRidge connects your mobile device to your PC, transforming it into a powerful SteamVR-compatible virtual reality headset. It will then stream SteamVR apps to your mobile device as a high-performance video with full head and controller tracking. All you need is a mobile or cardboard VR viewer to enjoy the experience!<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677750/extras/connect-bg.png?t=1705504764"><h2 class="bb_tag">Getting started</h2><ol><li>Install RiftCat client application on your computer via Steam.<br/></li><li>Install VRidge on your mobile device and place it inside your mobile VR viewer.<br/></li><li>Launch both apps.<br/></li><li>Follow the built-in instructions in the RiftCat application to connect them via WiFi.<br/></li><li>Enjoy!</li></ol><h2 class="bb_tag">Test your setup first</h2>Try out your <strong>VRidge hardware setup</strong> with the <strong>Demo version</strong> to ensure everything works correctly before making a purchase.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677750/extras/lab_cat.png?t=1705504764"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little Elf Tanks</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2330780/Little_Elf_Tanks/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330780/extras/title_crop.gif?t=1705504525"><br/><br/>Embark on an exciting journey in this thrilling bug blasting adventure! Choose one of four playable characters and join the battle to free your fellow elves from the grasp of a wicked spider army. Each playable character comes with their own set of unique abilities and strengths, giving you the freedom to tackle obstacles in your own way. But beware, your foes won't make your mission easy. In addition to the hoards of gross creepy crawlies, several big boss fights lie in wait to test your skills!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fast paced overhead shooting gameplay.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 60 enemy encounters spanning 5 levels.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>4 playable characters.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Three difficulty settings. Easy, Normal, and Hard.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Several challenging boss battles.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Unlockable boss rush mode.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Charming pixel art and cartoon graphics.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>An amazing soundtrack.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The bugs bleed green goo and it's super gross.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Case Should Remain Unsolved</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2676840/No_Case_Should_Remain_Unsolved/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i>"I remember how surprised I was when I first saw this case. Everyone involved was lying, for one reason or another."</i></strong><br/><br/><strong>#No_Case_Should_Remain_Unsolved</strong> is a detective game where players uncover and piece together memory fragments to solve a long-forgotten case. Follow former police detective Jeon Gyeong as she acquires clues and testimony relating to the case of a missing girl.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676840/extras/MainPic.gif?t=1705503627"><h2 class="bb_tag">#No_Case_Should_Remain_Unsolved</h2>February 5, 2012. A little girl named Seowon is reported missing from a playground. Police launch an investigation and question witnesses and suspects, but Seowon's case is never solved.<br/>Twelve years after Senior Inspector Jeon Gyeong's retirement, she is visited by a young police officer: a woman who pleads with her to reexamine Seowon's case.<br/>But with each uncovered memory, only one thing becomes clear: everyone in Seowon's vicinity was lying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676840/extras/Ending_2.gif?t=1705503627"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Experience an imaginative reasoning system where players connect memories like pieces of a jigsaw puzzle.<br/></li><li>Uncover passcodes, keys, 54 conversations, and two hidden truths.<br/></li><li>Over the course of a 2-3 hour playthrough, players will learn why Seowon's disappearance is the only case Jeon Gyeong has left unsolved.<br/></li><li>Also featuring an original soundtrack by Seongyi Yi, composer of Legal Dungeon and The Wake!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yuuna and the Haunted Hot Springs The Thrilling Steamy Maze Kiwami</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2436340/Yuuna_and_the_Haunted_Hot_Springs_The_Thrilling_Steamy_Maze_Kiwami/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Want to dive into a bath? Or into a dungeon?</strong><br/><strong>"Yuuna and the Haunted Hot Springs" is now an RPG that's pushing all sorts of boundaries!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/extras/dungeon.gif?t=1705503627"><br/><br/>Yuuna and the Haunted Hot Springs makes its video game debut as a genuine roguelike RPG!<br/>In order to save Kogarashi, search through expansive dungeons that change layout every time you enter!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/extras/onsen2.gif?t=1705503627"><br/>Jump in the hot spring to power up! Watch out for damage to your clothes!<br/>A new story of hauntings, hot springs, and high adventure awaits you!<h2 class="bb_tag">Adventure, apparitions, and a hot spring... A brand-new story that's quite literally bursting at the seams!</h2><br/>Featuring a story unique to the game with special event images that can't be seen anywhere else<br/>and character interactions fully voiced by the star-studded cast of the animated series!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/extras/adv_en.png?t=1705503627"><br/><br/>One weekend-<br/>After hearing a strange noise coming from the Yuragi Inn's storage, Kogarashi and the rest of the Inn's residents decide to do a bit of spring cleaning,<br/>but they accidentally knock over a chest they find inside.<br/>From inside the miniature garden they find within, a girl's voice can be heard.<br/>"Kogarashi...! You've come back!"<br/>At that moment, a powerful gust plucks Kogarashi off his feet, and sucks him into the miniature garden!<br/>Will the others be able to rescue Kogarashi?!<h2 class="bb_tag">Anything could happen! Push through dungeons that'll push you to the limit!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/extras/dungeon2_jp.png?t=1705503627"><br/>Conquer the dungeons' challenges!<br/>Jump into battle with Yuuna, Sagiri, Yaya, and even more playable characters!<br/>Bring your favorite characters and rescue Kogarashi!<h2 class="bb_tag">You can push the limits of bathing too... Refresh yourself and get powered up in the Resonant Spring!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/extras/furo2_en.png?t=1705503627"><br/>A relaxing soak in the hot spring might relieve the exhaustion of your adventure, but could evil spirits be drawn in too?!<br/>Team up with Koyuzu to clear out both the steam and the spirits!<br/>As you do, you might even notice some characters have changed!<h2 class="bb_tag">From adorable to...alluring?! Change freely between over 15 kinds of costumes!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/extras/costume2.png?t=1705503627"><br/>More than 15 kinds of both familiar and brand-new outfits appear!<br/>Dress Yuuna and friends up in your favorite costumes!<br/>Of course, both the in-game sprites and the character illustrations will change to match!<br/>Each costume has different abilities, so make use of them when delving into dungeons!<h2 class="bb_tag">"It's too difficult... I can't beat this..." No worries! The storage is stuffed fit to burst with helpful items!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/extras/kura_en.png?t=1705503627"><br/>For any players who don't relish challenging dungeons,<br/>you can make use of handy support items right from the start!<br/>Naturally that includes costumes too, so get dolled up in your preferred outfits and conquer the dungeons!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's Up There?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2756610/Whats_Up_There/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2756610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>What's Up There?</strong> is a unique meditative platformer game. Your only goal is to climb the ladder as far as you can. Jump over the steps again and again to reach the top eventually. But one mistake and you can fall to the very bottom losing all your progress. But use a simple blink system if you smart or fast enought to undo a fatal mistake.<h2 class="bb_tag">GAMEPLAY</h2>Calm and cozy journey at the beginning but with insane risks as you become closer to the top<h2 class="bb_tag">GRAPHICS</h2>Nice neon style graphics with minimalistic environment so nothing distracts you from your goal<h2 class="bb_tag">THE JOURNEY</h2>Climb thousands of steps to unravel the mystery of what is happening. Find out the reasons for everything that is happening here<h2 class="bb_tag">SECRETS AND ENDINGS</h2>Reach the top and find a true game end. Or stuck here forever halfway to the goal						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nephenthesys</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2660400/Nephenthesys/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2660400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Blast off on a treacherous mission to recover an unidentified energy source amidst an alien onslaught!</h2><br/><br/>Nephenthesys is a vertical scrolling shoot’em up presented in widescreen top-down 3D style. Blast through a huge variety of enemy ships, collect power-ups for wider shot spreads and special bombs, then face off against screen-filling bosses. This mission will take you through caverns, waterways, cityscapes and more. Do you have the skills to see it through?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2660400/extras/Nephenthesys_gif_01.gif?t=1705494750"><br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Experience old-school shoot’em up action inspired by arcade genre classics!<br/></li><li>Choose from a variety of ships with unique stats and shot types.<br/></li><li>Face off against enemy swarms and collect power-ups!<br/></li><li>Navigate caverns, waterways, cityscapes and other unique environments.<br/></li><li>Take on screen-filling bosses at the end of each stage.<br/></li><li>Enjoy a light story conveyed through comm dialogue!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2660400/extras/Nephenthesys_gif_02.gif?t=1705494750"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2660400/extras/Nephenthesys_gif_05.gif?t=1705494750"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twizzle Puzzle: Reptiles</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2757530/Twizzle_Puzzle_Reptiles/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Twizzle Puzzle: Reptiles - is the perfect puzzle game for a fun and rewarding pastime.<br/>Your goal is to assemble a picture of cool reptiles that has been cut into an equal number of pieces.<br/>Rotate the pieces to create the full picture, but think logically about the connections and solve the puzzle. <br/>There are 50 levels to complete, and the challenge becomes increasingly difficult as you progress.<br/>Enjoy a relaxing time connecting the pieces to create a beautiful picture of reptiles<br/><br/>In Twizzle Puzzle: Reptiles:<br/><br/>•50 levels<br/>•Beautiful art<br/>•Simple controls (mouse)<br/>•Achievements<br/>•Relaxing music<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757530/extras/3.png?t=1705494741"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757530/extras/1.png?t=1705494741"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757530/extras/2.png?t=1705494741"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757530/extras/4.png?t=1705494741"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trupki</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422310/Trupki/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Most simple puzzle game ever possible.<br/>Sliding tiles by rows or columns so that the final shape, made of tile elements, appears!<br/>Game guides you step by step from super simple one turn easy levels through more comprehensive up to almost insane difficulty.<br/>Variability of the game is modified by logical obstacles which may limit or completely distort basic workings of tile movement.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422310/extras/DividersV301.png?t=1705508864"><br/><br/>Many players claim that out of the box approach for every level is a must and so Trupki is great tool for developing this ability!<br/>Game plays with total minimalism but insist on aesthetic even in case of level design. However game is not short on levels.<br/>Offers over 300 levels in all difficulties and expected tens of hours of struggle and a-ha moments.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422310/extras/DividersV302.png?t=1705508864"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creature Summon: Showdown Moment</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2751800/Creature_Summon_Showdown_Moment/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2751800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A creative first-person card game that mimics VR perspective and operation. Combining science fiction and magic, it features a non-traditional card game mode and a 3D spatial UI. Players can throw cards to any position (with physics system) by using the mouse quickly.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2>· Unique gameplay mechanism: The game mimics the way VR throws objects. In this game, players can drag and throw cards with the mouse. Cards use physical systems, and where they are thrown depends entirely on player operations. The game also comes with 10 dance actions, and players can dance and throw cards for high immersion.<br/><br/>· Gameplay: You can only summon up to 5 creatures on the field at the same time. Once your creatures reach 5, throwing cards again will not summon more creatures. You need to wait for the number of monsters to drop below 5 before picking up cards and throwing them again. After the creature is summoned, it will prioritize attacking or occupying flags against the creatures it restrains. (Ranged creatures will not actively occupy flags, only melee creatures will occupy flags).<br/><br/>· Creature factions: There are currently 5 factions, which will increase to 9 in the future. Each faction has more than 10 creatures, and the total number of creatures will exceed 100.<br/><br/>· Realistic models: Further enhance immersion.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer Online</h2>Play with friends in the Steam lobby and enjoy multiplayer mode, it's even more fun and free!<br/><br/>· PS:<br/>The gameplay of this game may be unique. Players who play for the first time should take a look at the text description in "Tutorial" to understand the game rules and mechanism before playing. Due to budget issues, no professional translation experts were hired. Except for Chinese, all localized languages of this game are translated by translation software. If there are any translations that are difficult to understand, please send me an email for correction.<br/>For more fun, please experience it in the game personally. Many fun cannot be expressed in words. :P<h2 class="bb_tag">Thanks</h2>I hope everyone likes the creative gameplay of this game.<h2 class="bb_tag">Finally, please forgive me</h2>This game is developed by only one person, all the assets are purchased from the store, and the style is not consistent. If you have any gameplay suggestions, please email me. I might not be able to handle the art aspects, as I have no knowledge in that area. Apologies for the inconvenience...						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominions 6 - Rise of the Pantokrator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2511500/Dominions_6__Rise_of_the_Pantokrator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2511500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are a God! You are master and ruler of a loyal nation. You have unimaginable powers at your disposal. You have claimed this world as yours. But there are others who stand in your way. You must defeat and destroy these pretenders. Only then can you ascend to godhood and become the new Pantokrator.<br>
<br>
Dominions 6 is a turn based 4x strategy game suitable for both play vs AI, player vs player.  Team play vs AI or players also works great as everyone can do their turns at once.  The game has a huge variety of units, spells, magic items and different nations to play.<br>
<br>
In Dominions you take control of a powerful being that rules a nation and aspires to godhood. The type of Pretender Gods can vary from magically powerful arch mages to huge titans or large monuments. The pretender gods have different strengths dependent on what kind of god you choose and what nation you play.<br>
<br>
When you start the game you decide what kind of god you are and how your Dominion affects your lands, followers and sacred soldiers. It is an expression of your divine might and the faith of your followers. If your dominion dies, so do you. Your dominion also inspires your sacred warriors and gives them powers derived from your dominion.<br/>
<br/>
In order to win and become the one true god you have to defeat your enemies one of three different ways: conquer their lands, extinguish their dominion or claim the Thrones of Ascension.<br/>
<br/>
Dominions is set in a fantasy world that draws inspiration from historical nations, cultures and myths. You will not encounter the elves of conventional fantasy in this game. Instead you might lead a nation of vanir from old norse myth. Aztecs, romans, israelites, greeks, kievian rus and lovecraftian horrors are just a few of the inspirational sources of the game.<br/>
<br/>
The first Dominions game was released in 2002 and was well received by strategy gamers. Since then Dominions has been much refined and Dominions series is still actively played making it one of the longest running 4x turn based strategy games.<br/>
<br/>
----------<br/>
<br/>
Dominions 6 is scaled up compared to Dominions 5 and armies are larger. We wanted to tweak the balance between conventional armies and magic. To accomplish this a couple of changes are introduced. Incomes and resources are increased, while mages are more expensive. Battlefield-wide spells are more difficult to cast and there are instead more mid-tier spells. There are some other changes with the same aim.<br/>
<br/>
The second and probably most influential change is the addition of a new magic path. No longer are illusions the domain of Air magic. Instead illusions, phantasms, dreams and the stuff of forgotten legends are manipulated with the path of Glamour. This has resulted in many new spells, items and sites being added to the game. <br/>
<br/>
A third massive change is the separation of mounts and riders. Riders and mounts now have separate stats and can be targeted individually. This change probably has less impact on gameplay than the previous one, but will still have an impact on cavalry and nations using mounted units.<br/>
<br/>
Dominions 6 features a number of new nations as well. The addition of the Glamour path has also affected several of the old nations. <br/>
<br/>
There are also a number of changes intended to ease gameplay.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lab and Dungeons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658960/The_Lab_and_Dungeons/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Summary</h2>The Lab and Dungeons is a blend of roguelike action and shooter RPG, set on an island ruled by robots during a human-robot war. You play as a small robot that has mysteriously powered up recently. Your mission is to mine ores, forge weapons, and confront aggressive robots in the unpredictable, procedurally generated dungeons. Collect items to invent more unique weapons and boost your abilities. From light skirmishes to intense bullet storms with physics enabled, play solo or online co-op with friends, are you ready to take on the challenge and unravel the island’s secret?<h2 class="bb_tag">“Never the same dungeon twice”</h2>Explore 6 major procedural dungeons and extra boss rooms! New explorations intensify challenges in old dungeons.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658960/extras/SixDungeons560220rev2.gif?t=1705485652"><h2 class="bb_tag">Weapons</h2>Defeat enemies your way: use ranged, melee, deployable weapons, or even a tiny black hole!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658960/extras/Weapons450140.gif?t=1705485652"><h2 class="bb_tag">Physics</h2>Newton’s laws apply! Take advantage of physics reactions!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658960/extras/Physics200160.gif?t=1705485652"><h2 class="bb_tag">Collection Room</h2>Display your favorite items and make it your own style!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658960/extras/CollectionRoomGif.gif?t=1705485652"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Modes</h2>Play solo or online / LAN co-op!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658960/extras/Coop.gif?t=1705485652"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrades</h2>Upgrade your abilities and unlock weapons to become stronger!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658960/extras/UI430240.gif?t=1705485652"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>6 major dungeons filled with countless varieties of procedurally generated floors.<br/></li><li>40+ unique enemies that challenge your exploration.<br/></li><li>Exciting physics-enabled combat where enemies can take ores and items, and even damage each other.<br/></li><li>Single player mode, Steam Online or LAN co-op for up to 4 players.<br/></li><li>3 categories of 60+ weapons: ranged, melee, and deployable.<br/></li><li>130+ levels across 9 specs to upgrade.<br/></li><li>3 difficulty levels.<br/></li><li>5 save slots with Steam Cloud supported.<br/></li><li>Steam achievements.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat Warrior</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2640520/Cat_Warrior/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2640520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Cat Warroir</strong> is an action-platformer of retro and cute style about a cat knight on his way to recapture his stolen treasure.<br/>Deep into the exciting and dangerous fantasy world,defeat the challenging big boss with your slash, dash, jump, walljump and other skills to find the treasure back!<h2 class="bb_tag">Feature</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Addictive gameplay</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>4 unique challenge worldsand 30 handmade levels.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Beautiful pixel-art graphics;</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A cute cat</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlas Wept</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1699260/Atlas_Wept/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1699260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1699260/extras/Atlas_Wept_Glee_Forward_Walking.gif?t=1705465582"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1699260/extras/Atlas_Wept_Dezi_Forward_Walking.gif?t=1705465582"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1699260/extras/Atlas_Wept_Charlie_Forward_Walking.gif?t=1705465582"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1699260/extras/Atlas_Wept_Gigi_Forward_Walking.gif?t=1705465582"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1699260/extras/Atlas_Wept_Main_Cover_Cute_Pixel_Goat_Robot_Dog_Kids_Statue_Landscape_.png?t=1705465582"><br/><br/>A Humanist retro-style RPG game about sincerity and empathy, featuring friendly robot dogs and evil smiley faces.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1699260/extras/Atlas_Wept_Silk.png?t=1705465582"><br/><br/>Explore the worlds of two separate casts of characters embarked upon their own unique quests, alternating back and forth as their seemingly unrelated stories creep closer and closer together.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1699260/extras/Atlas_Wept_Hive.png?t=1705465582"><br/><br/>Engage with a wide variety of unique and unusual enemies in turn based combat mixed with bullet hell style dodge mechanics.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1699260/extras/Atlas_Wept_Grin.png?t=1705465582"><br/><br/>Fight to unconver the mystery of he whom holds the ground up to our feet...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1699260/extras/Atlas_Wept_Stomp.png?t=1705465582"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panda Go</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626360/Panda_Go/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a turn-based board puzzle game in which a variety of unexpected levels are combined through a simple guard mechanism! You need to skillfully operate your character to pass through guards and various obstacles to finally reach the end! In addition, You can also use the level editor to create your own levels and share them with the community, or download levels created by other players for a greater challenge!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hexagoner</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2513640/Hexagoner/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2513640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You're the mastermind behind a team of lovable yet fierce battlers, each with their own abilities. From crafty wizards with a twinkle in their eyes to valiant knights and enchanting creatures, your squad is as charming as it is formidable. Imagine moving them across a unique hexagonal grid, where every step is a chance to outmaneuver your opponents and claim victory.<br>
<br>
But here's the catch - it's all about smart moves and smarter resource management. You've got to think on your feet, juggling energy and movement points to pull off those game-changing moves. Whether it's unleashing a powerful attack, calling in reinforcements, or nimbly navigating the battlefield, your decisions shape the course of the clash.<br>
<br>
And the ultimate goal? To outsmart your opponent and take down their king. With nine different pieces to spawn, each with their own cost, pattern, and skills, the possibilities are endless. You'll need to adapt your strategy, exploit weaknesses, and sometimes even turn the tide of battle when the odds are against you.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landlords &amp; Tax Evasion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594400/Landlords__Tax_Evasion/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Landlords &amp; Tax Evasion, a multiplayer boardgame where you compete against your friends and/or bots on owning all the land and having all the gold in the kingdom. Play games of up to 8 players and wear different accessories.<h2 class="bb_tag">Things you can do in this game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Own land and become a landlord</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Buy land from other landlords</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Collect taxes on your land</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Develop your land with 4 unique buildings</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Evade taxes</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Run from other landlords you owe tax to</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Catch landlords that evade your taxes</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play with friends and/or bots</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Use items to gain an unfair advantage</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explode</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Be the last landlord standing to win the game</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Things you can't do in this game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Buy endless micro transactions</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Buy a battle pass</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get an AI generated response to your negative review</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Arson</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cutlass Call</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2739180/Cutlass_Call/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Rookie State of the Seas: The Beginning of a New Pirate!<br>
"Get ready to embark on an adrenaline-fueled adventure! In Cutlass Call, you start as a rookie pirate who doesn't know how to swim. As you master the land with W, A, S, D keys, it's up to you to develop your skills on the seas."<br>
<br>
Mysterious Island Courses and Tasty Discoveries!<br>
"At the beginning of the game, explore the deserted island's courses as a rookie pirate who doesn't know how to swim. Overcome obstacles, find mysterious foods, and test your skills to survive on the island. Navigate with W, A, S, D, and Shift keys as you embark on your adventure as a new pirate."<br>
<br>
Overcome Obstacles, Rule the Seas!<br/>
"In this exciting adventure where you start as a rookie pirate who doesn't know how to swim, overcome obstacles, find delicious foods, and become the ruler of the seas! Cutlass Call offers unique experiences as you witness the rise of a true pirate. Get ready; this adventure awaits you!"						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Evolution: Drive to Divinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2111360/Extreme_Evolution_Drive_to_Divinity/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2111360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2111360/extras/LoopBanner6_JauntyJourney.gif?t=1705434836"><br/><i>EXTREME EVOLUTION: Drive to Divinity</i> is an expressive platformer where every obstacle has countless, overlapping solutions.  Set free in sprawling spaces, the experiment evolves and grows.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2111360/extras/demoDoubleUI.gif?t=1705434836"><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Use § to transform between known forms at any time; invent movement combos.<br/></li><li> Discover new evolutionary forms, often in temples... at greater § costs.  <br/></li><li> Collect raw § to permanently increase max §.<br/></li><li> Enter holes to unlock new Sites.<br/></li><li> The experiment hustles, hurtles towards Earth.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2111360/extras/demoTransformingLonger_fixed.gif?t=1705434836"><br/>String transformations together, performing extreme combos through the environment.  Take big jumps as <i>Car</i>, fling junk as <i>Pump</i>, ricochet as the bouncy <i>Bomp</i>, cling upside down as <i>Spide</i>, fling thyself as <i>Tire</i>, etc... in <i>Extreme Evolution</i>, explorative biology demands exploitation.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2111360/extras/JumpJumpJump2.gif?t=1705434836"><br/><strong>EEE: the Extreme Evolution Experiment. The Gods capitulate and call out, driving <i>Extreme Evolution</i>.  The nutrient rich Body, the perfect Digital Way, the abject Nothing, Infinite Spirits, Lies, and the Ouroboros: essential stopgaps along the Drive to Divinity. Inside each a Subjective! divine seal; these six seals lock away the last/first known (Human) planet (Earth).</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2111360/extras/runLoopGif.gif?t=1705434836"><br/>Movement as the original power; the ultimate story of mitochondrial evolution concludes in <i>Extreme Evolution: Drive to Divinity</i>.<br/><strong><br/>Photosensitivity warning: This game features many procedural visual effects &amp; post-processing, including multi-color rapid flashing and/or strobing.  The most extreme effects can be reduced with settings in-game, but cannot be turned off fully.<br/>Configure visuals with Sharp mode, Reduced Animation, and Simplified Backgrounds. </strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2111360/extras/demoGraphics2.gif?t=1705434836"><br/><br/>the 4th game by Sam Atlas<br/>music by DL Salo						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starlight Scouts</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2753420/Starlight_Scouts/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2753420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2753420/extras/ShipsFlying.gif?t=1705434472"> <br/><strong>An Ex-Rocket-Hero, waiting for the stars to call again...</strong><br/>You were a fighter pilot in the early days, when rockets were tin cans with thrusters bolted onto every side. Battles were waged constantly in the name of newfound resources. You were one of the best...<br/><br/>Now Rocket-Heroes are a thing of the past. All that's left is your desire to get beck behind the throttle...<br/><br/>Suddenly, your old Auto-Log chimes to life with an open broadcast message...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2753420/extras/DescHeader.png?t=1705434472"><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FXDqkFuB9BX" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2753420/extras/DiscordSmall.gif?t=1705434472"/></a><br/><strong><i>Join the Starlight Scouts today, the most elite space explorers in the solar system.<br/><br/>Venture forth into unknown worlds. Discover the future.<br/><br/>Become one of the galaxies elite.<br/><br/>Become an expert pilot.<br/><br/>Become, a <u>Starlight Scout...</u><br/><br/>It's gonna take hard work, dedication, and a whole lot of fun, but- I think you've got what it takes...</i></strong><br/><br/>The transmission ends. Will you answer the call?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2753420/extras/Hazard_Lines.png?t=1705434472"><br/><br/><br/><strong>Unlock 5 badges per level to boost your total score through the atmosphere. Speed through levels at blistering paces. Crawl across the floor like a limp dog just to conserve enough fuel. Skim past obstacles that would otherwise knock the teeth out of a lesser pilot. Get through a level without a single scratch on your rocket. Get all four and you've earned yourself the Scout's Medal...</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2753420/extras/MedalsDesc.png?t=1705434472"><br/><strong>Now get lost. Go find your ship and fly to your heart's content...</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2753420/extras/ShipStreak.png?t=1705434472"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychopath Hunt Chapter two</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2570150/Psychopath_Hunt_Chapter_two/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2570150/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A butcher has captured you and taken you to his house.<br>
<br>
Try to escape before it's too late. Explore the terrifying house, solve puzzles, and uncover hidden secrets. Goodluck..<br>
<br>
Theres three different escape routes!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portal 2: Confinement</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2716490/Portal_2_Confinement/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Confinement is a co-op focused Portal 2 mod centered around the confinement concept. Rather than introducing any new mechanics or test elements, confinement puzzles are simply a special type of co-op map where one player is always trapped to allow the other to roam free, requiring swapping out the confined partner. Sometimes referred to as “1.5 player,” these puzzles still utilize all 4 portals, but in a limited manner, creating challenging situations to set up portal states for the active partner to utilize to achieve the objective. Only once both players are freed from their prison can the exit be reached (usually).<br>
<br>
Features 28 challenging co-op puzzles offering around 20-30 hours of playtime. Currently available only in split-screen (online is planned, though difficult to implement and requires Valve's help, so it will come later).<br>
<br>
This is a remaster of the Confinement map series available on the Portal 2 workshop. They can already be played online there, but the difficulties in finding a partner/ setting up for split-screen/ getting online co-op to function at all has proven problematic for many people; therefore, this mod exists as an easy way to play all the best maps in a neat and tidy collection. All the gimmicky/ bad maps have been excluded, and many visual and puzzle enhancements have been implemented, leaving only the highest quality puzzles for a streamlined experience. This is Confinement: Definitive Edition.<br>
<br>
By default, pressing the "1" key will turn cheats on, and R will swap between players. But you can customize this with the instructions below:<br>
<br>
IMPORTANT: Portal 2's built in split-screen control sometimes has issues. To swap between players, you will most likely have to force the command. Here is what to do. Open the developer console and type in the following: BindToggle key in_forceuser. Replace "key" with whatever key you wish; that will swap between the 2 players. Additionally, this command only works when cheats are turned on. To do this, type sv_cheats 1. To bind to a key, type bind key "sv_cheats 1", again replacing "key" with whatever key you wish.<br/>
<br/>
Although not strictly necessary, you may sometimes wish to have one partner's view take up the whole screen. The command for this is BindToggle key ss_force_primary_fullscreen, which will make player 1's view fullscreen. To do the same for player 2, enter the following into the console (all as one command): ss_pipsplit 3; ss_pipscale 1; ss_pip_bottom_offset 0; ss_pip_right_offset 0. This will toggle each player as fullscreen each time the key is pressed.<br/>
<br/>
Music is from the talented Mikeastro.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Purgatory Salvation</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2706230/Purgatory_Salvation/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706230/extras/download.gif?t=1705427970"><h2 class="bb_tag">Escape From The Purgatory</h2><br/>Purgatory Salvation is a multiplayer horror game where one player takes on the role of the Keeper of The Purgatory (Killer), and the other players play as Survivors, trying to escape from Purgatory and avoid being caught and killed.<br/><br/>Survivors  and The Killer plays in third-person.<br/><br/>The Survivors' goal is run away from The Killer and try to find The Ashes in order to unlock their graves. When they unlocked their graves they can transform to spirit form and finally escape from The Purgatory.<br/><br/>The Killer's goal is prevent that scenario and kill them in order to turn them into a Purgatory Creature to help him.<br/><br/><br/><strong>WARNING: PHOTOSENSITIVITY/EPILEPSY SEIZURES - READ THIS NOTICE BEFORE PLAYING</strong><br/><br/><i>A very small percentage of people may experience epileptic seizures or blackouts when exposed to certain kinds of flashing lights or light patterns. These persons, or even people who have no history of seizures or epilepsy, may experience epileptic symptoms or seizures while playing video games. If you or any of your relatives has an epileptic condition or has had seizures of any kind, consult your physician before playing any video game.<br/><br/>IMMEDIATELY DISCONTINUE use and consult a physician if you or your child experience any of the following symptoms: dizziness, altered vision, eye or muscle twitching, involuntary movements, loss of awareness, disorientation, or convulsions. Parents should watch for or ask their children about the above symptoms.<br/><br/>You may reduce risk of photosensitive epileptic seizures by taking the following precautions: sit farther from the screen, use a smaller screen, play in a well-lit room, do not play when you are drowsy or fatigued.</i> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room231</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2737100/Room231/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2737100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Room231</h2><i>Backroom: Room231</i> is a single player horror game, which is based on the famous creepy pasta called "Backrooms". In this game, you will need to find an exit of level231 while hiding from dangerous environments and entities. However, you will need to find every "<i>objects</i>" from other levels of backrooms to open the exit of level231.<h2 class="bb_tag">Uncanny Rooms</h2>Currently, <i>Room231</i> has 8 levels. Level231 is a main level, which is the beginning and end map for the player's escape. It is a familiar place, but becareful. Uncanny experiences are waiting for you. There are 6 more levels that have "objects" which must placed in the right location in level231. While collecting these objects, player will be able to reach the truth of level231 and exit to live. Each levels contain various of puzzles and mechanics which requires both physically and mentally. <br/>These are current levels:<br/><strong>1</strong>- Level 231<br/><strong>2</strong>- Level 6<br/><strong>3</strong>- Level 7<br/><strong>4</strong>- Level 19<br/><strong>5</strong>- Level 34<br/><strong>6</strong>- Level 69<br/><strong>7</strong>- Level Maze(Original level)<br/><strong>8</strong>- Level Forest(Original level)<h2 class="bb_tag">Entities</h2>During your uncanny adventure, you will meet several entities. Some of them are based on the original backrooms, others are this game's original entities. Each entities have different patterns and gimmicks, so you would better to know that and find best way to esacpe from those.<h2 class="bb_tag">Puzzles&amp;Items</h2>You will need to solve lots of puzzles during your journey for reach to every exits of backrooms. Each puzzles have unique and interesting gimmicks which requires you to think creatively. And to solve puzzles, to live, to hide from entities, you can use lots of items and tools. You can save them in their inventory, or hold them with hand.<h2 class="bb_tag">Future Updates</h2>Since I am a solo developer, it is hard to guarantee fast updates and reponses, but I will keep update <i><br/>Room231</i> and communicate with you guys for best creepy experience.<br/><br/>If you encounter any issues&amp;bugs feel free to send me: <strong><a href="mailto:dudwlstldud@gmail.com">dudwlstldud@gmail.com</a></strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Safety Hotline</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2357910/Home_Safety_Hotline/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/RuntimeLabel-HSH-Dark.png?t=1705432881"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/ShinyLogoOnlyGIF.gif?t=1705432881"><br/><br/><strong>Hearing noises? Seeing things? Call Home Safety Hotline! Our operators are standing by, waiting to give you the answers you need to protect your home from all manner of pests and household hazards.</strong><br/><br/>Home Safety Hotline is an analog horror inspired telephone operator simulator where you answer incoming callers' questions about what's inside their home. Read through a vast catalog of common pests and household hazards, and do your best to become an expert in home safety. You will be held responsible for what happens.<br/><br/>A new horror experiment from Nick Lives, the creator of <i>NiGHT SIGNAL</i> and <i>A Wonderful Day For Fishing</i>. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Navigate a vast catalog of safety information using the latest in 90's technology.<br/></li><li> Listen to original jazzy lo-fi music by David Johnsen while you place callers on hold.<br/></li><li> Correctly deduce what's in your callers' homes or else leave them to suffer the consequences.<br/></li><li> Learn about the various untold horrors that live inside your home.<br/></li><li> "Phobia Toggles" - An accessibility option that allows you to disable in-game images for common phobia triggers including arachnophobia and more.<br/></li><li> Unlockable Art Book detailing the game's development history.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/NumberOnlyGIF.gif?t=1705432881"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Trains</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2494440/Toy_Trains/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494440/extras/STEAM_GIF_1.gif?t=1705426110"><br/><br/>Open a long forgotten, dusty suitcase in your grandpa’s attic, rediscover your old toys and even older memories. As soon as you start playing, it’s both rails and memories that start to click together. In this creative space, where all depends on you, you can feel child-like joy and fulfillment of building tracks and solving brain teasers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494440/extras/STEAM_GIF_2.gif?t=1705426110"><br/><br/>Toy Trains land is yours to shape. The challenges are open-ended and each board has multiple possible solutions, so you can let your imagination loose and never feel stuck. After you solve a board, get creative with decorating it, progress with every step and set up more and more complex routes each time!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494440/extras/STEAM_GIF_3.gif?t=1705426110"><br/><br/>The warm, colorful world keeps you nice and cozy throughout the journey. There is no timer, no score, no rush. Play at your own pace and take time to step back and admire your work. Toy Trains brings nothing but satisfaction and pleasure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494440/extras/STEAM_GIF_4.gif?t=1705426110"><br/><br/><strong>In Toy Trains you can:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Be creative - try various options to solve open-ended challenges<br/></li><li>Express yourself - decorate the land in your individual style<br/></li><li>Play with the world itself - splash some water, move the trees or melt over the cuteness of little Railies!<br/></li><li>Go back in time - experience child-like joy and live through a nostalgic storyline<br/></li><li>Relax - there is no rush and no stress in the Toy Trains land<br/></li><li>Immerse - feel all that and more in the most captivating way - VR!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494440/extras/STEAM_GIF_5_small.gif?t=1705426110"><br/><br/>Are you ready to hop on board and take a ride with Toy Trains?						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Glitch Prison</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2756700/The_Glitch_Prison/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2756700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About this game</strong>.<br/>This game is a single player escape adventure game.<br/>You are a prisoner who has been trapped in this prison for a long time.<br/>But you have noticed some bugs in the world and you have decided to use them to escape from prison.<br/>Now is the time to break out!<br/><br/><strong>Game Overview</strong>.<br/>The goal of the game is to verify various bugs and break out of a small prison.<br/>Manipulate objects that can physically interfere, transparent walls, and uncomfortable behavior to achieve the fastest jailbreak possible.<br/><br/><strong>Play Time</strong>.<br/>30 minutes to 1 hour<br/><br/>b]Controls[/b][/b<br/><br/>Camera:Mouse<br/>Move:WASD<br/>Jump: Space<br/>Interact:E<br/>FPS/TPS:V<br/>Move object:Drag&amp;Drop<br/>Crouch:Ctrl<br/>Flash light:F<br/>Wave:H<br/>Restart:P<br/>Rolling:Alt<br/>Game Menu:Tab<br/>Main Menu:Esc<br/><br/>There are no restrictions on video streaming.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLeM: The First Attribute</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2722310/CLeM_The_First_Attribute/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>CLeM: The First Attribute is a free prologue that offers the first loop of <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1861440/CLeM/" rel="" target="_blank">CLeM</a>, a narrative-driven puzzle adventure game with a dark twist.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722310/extras/Experience_a_dark_adventure_full_of_mystery.png?t=1705421127"><br/>You awaken in a cold, dimly lit room, your senses slowly adjusting to the surroundings that, oddly, feel familiar. A strange sensation lingers in you, reminding you that something is not quite right. As you find your bearings, your attention is drawn to a peculiar item on the ground. A notebook labeled "CLeM" lies before you. As you delve into its pages, covered with intricate sketches of insects accompanied by vague symbols, you find a note containing a cryptic message: “Bring me BEAUTY.” Lost in deciphering the contents, a voice interrupts your focus.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722310/extras/1.gif?t=1705421127"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722310/extras/Solve_puzzles_and_find_your_way.png?t=1705421127"><br/>Puzzles intertwine with exploration, weaving a unique narrative experience we call “Puzzlevania” with a shadowy story to unravel and countless challenges to overcome.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722310/extras/CLeM---Puzzles-Improved-v2_1.gif?t=1705421127"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722310/extras/Craft_enchanted_toys_and_uncover_secrets.png?t=1705421127"><br/>Craft magic toys to unveil hidden secrets, access unreachable spots, and reclaim items from the past as you uncover new revelations in familiar spaces. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722310/extras/3.gif?t=1705421127"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722310/extras/Discover_a_cute_and_dark_world.png?t=1705421127"><br/>Investigate a seemingly desolate house accompanied only by an obscure voice and a notebook full of annotations and drawings on alchemy, insects, and other creepy crawlies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722310/extras/4.gif?t=1705421127"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722310/extras/Embrace_your_destiny.png?t=1705421127"><br/>Choose your fate in this dark story of manipulation, pride, forgiveness, and redemption.<br/><br/><u><strong>Features:</strong></u><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A new genre, “Puzzlevania,” intertwines puzzles and exploration. Discover hidden secrets in each room as you delve deeper into the mysteries with every crafted magical toy.<br/></li><li>Unique and beautiful art style with hand-drawn elements.<br/></li><li>2D graphics with 3D environmental navigation.<br/></li><li>Challenging and diverse puzzles to solve.<br/></li><li>An enigmatic story with a dark turn.</li></ul><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1861440/CLeM/" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1861440/CLeM/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos Sisters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2664300/Chaos_Sisters/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2664300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2664300/extras/ICover.gif?t=1705503767"><br/>Chaos sisters is a beat'em up of demon girls fighting their way through monsters and heroes.<br/><i>Puna &amp; Sini are two demons slacking on guard duty, when a party of heroes invades their home dungeon! Now surrounded by furious former allies, the sisters have to slay each hero... or The Master will have their heads!</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2664300/extras/combo5.gif?t=1705503767"><br/>Play in two completely different fighting styles: Fiery Puna fights up close and personal with her quick melee combat. Set the battleground ablaze and wreak havoc!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2664300/extras/CombatS3.gif?t=1705503767"><br/>Sini barrages enemies with heavy hitting spells. Store spell-charges and combine spells into powerful invocations to utterly annihilate your foes!<br/><br/>Features:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight your way through a prologue and 6 unique stages.<br/></li><li>Encounter over 20 unique monsters and conquer 6+ bossfights, not a single recoloured enemy!<br/></li><li>Play as two demons with completely different fighting styles.<br/></li><li>Talk with the monsters and heroes with character specific dialogue and jokes.<br/></li><li>Collect secrets, and uncover the truth of the fateful night.<br/></li><li>Over 20 illustrated cutscenes!<br/></li><li>Appreciate the wonderful soundtrack.<br/></li><li>Enjoy the hand-drawn 2D animation combat-a-palooza!</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rexy 360</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2278150/Rexy_360/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2278150/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							Plays full 360 videos and capture at traditional screen aspect ratios. Frame your shots and tailor the perfect capture for later playback.<br>
<br>
As your 360 video plays, you control the pan, tilt and zoom of the view to reframe in real-time. This empowers you to take control of virtual camera using the mouse, keyboard or joystick.<br>
<br>
We have partnered with Rexy Wheels which can be used with this application to practise and train for geared head camera work.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2631710/Strange_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2631710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Come and sweep slime! You will experience the thrill of slaying slime in this game!<br>
Let's break out of the enclosure and face a new round of challenges!<br>
<br>
Strange Survivors is a survivor like game that continuously allows characters to enter dungeons and receive rewards from monsters to make them stronger and stronger. Even in dangerous situations, they can move forward bravely!<br>
<br>
Strange Survivors is a time racing game that combines the top-down perspective of a meat pigeon in 3D, with a simple gameplay.<br>
Slimes are rampant, and you are constantly being chased. You cannot escape their pursuit, there is no place to hide!<br/>
And the only thing you can do is to bravely kill the enemy, do everything possible to survive until you finally face inevitable death.<br/>
Of course, you need to use the coins obtained in each battle to strengthen yourself, purchase attributes, and make the next survivor stronger and go further!<br/>
Independent game, taking you to experience unlimited barrage output and good mood!<br/>
<br/>
Recommended genres<br/>
·Speed stacked to 1500<br/>
·Choose weapons at the beginning of the game<br/>
·The only way you can regain health is through the wooden spell card<br/>
·Note that there are two types of cards: attribute cards and skill cards<br/>
·You have mastered two skills that are almost CD free since birth: "Gold Attraction Technique" and "Swift Wind Step"<br/>
·Using the Gale Step in front of enemies with high movement speed can make your survival more friendly, but as time passes, the enemy will become stronger and faster, and you need to use attributes to have a better advantage in survival.<br/>
·Trying to use the "Gold Attraction Technique" will make it easier for you to obtain the experience required for upgrading, and of course, there will be good profits in the later stage!<br/>
·Explore other content to the fullest!<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Follow me!<br/>
Let's improve this game together!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingsvein</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2276830/Kingsvein/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2276830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							All contact with the city of Kingsvein has been lost. As Wisp Slayer, your role is to investigate and exterminate whatever evil lurks there.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2276830/extras/castleBanner_616x152.gif?t=1705404781"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adventure through the castle and its outer reaches as you see fit - secret treasures and skulking beasts hide around every corner! <br/></li><li>Dynamic and deep tactical combat - toss your enemies into spikes then electrify their blood, or cover the battlefield in flames <br/></li><li>Customize your team by mixing and matching 15 different classes, each with upgradeable abilities and equippable passives <br/></li><li>Use your abilities to explore - freeze rivers with your magic, blast through cave walls, and throw chains to topple statues <br/></li><li>Ride your loyal steed in and out of combat, and train it to be as fierce as any Knight <br/></li><li>Set in the realm of Graven, a weird subterranean world of living soil and half-stone Diecast <br/></li><li>From the maker of the highly-rated <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1224290/Horizons_Gate/" rel="" target="_blank">Horizon's Gate</a>, <a href="http://store.steampowered.com/app/415920/Voidspire_Tactics/" rel="" target="_blank">Voidspire Tactics</a> and <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/643900/Alvora_Tactics/" rel="" target="_blank">Alvora Tactics</a></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2276830/extras/voidbeam616x152.gif?t=1705404781"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
