<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Soak &amp; Splash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2051500/Soak__Splash/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2051500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the Soak &amp; Splash! Get ready to sweat, socialize, and have a blast with your friends in this unique game that combines the best of traditional sauna culture with modern party fun.<br>
<br>
First, step into the steamy sauna and feel the heat and humidity envelop your body.<br>
<br>
Once everyone is inside, it's time to start the fun. You can start by whisking each other with broom.<br>
<br>
Feeling competitive? You can also fight with other players with sauna equipment. Or you can simply relax and enjoy the company of your friends, chatting, singing, or telling jokes.<br>
<br/>
Finally, when you've had enough of the sauna, you can cool off in the nearby pool or shower.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, this game is all about having fun, bonding with your friends, and experiencing the unique benefits of sauna culture. So why wait? Download game and get ready to sweat, laugh, and enjoy life to the fullest!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egg</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2784840/Egg/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2784840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><h2 class="bb_tag">About this game!</h2></strong><br/><br/>&gt; <strong>Egg</strong> is an interactive clicker game where you need to click egg to earn more eggs.<br/><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Features!</h2></strong><br/><br/>&gt; This game supports mouse and keyboard.<br/>&gt; This game supports gamepad (use <strong>A</strong> button on joystick to click).<br/>&gt; This game uses best HD quality textures that is possible to create.<br/>&gt; Runs on every hardware. Even on BESM.<br/>&gt; Supports all screen resolutions.<br/>&gt; Supports Windows 10/9/11 and so on.<br/>&gt; If you don't like the game you can always easily refund it.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/315210/Suicide_Squad_Kill_the_Justice_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Rocksteady Studios, the creators of the Batman: Arkham series, Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is a genre-defying third-person action shooter where the ultimate band of misfits must do the impossible to save the world: Kill the Justice League.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/SSKTJL_Intro.gif?t=1706907136"><br/>Join the newly “recruited” members of Amanda Waller’s infamous Task Force X (aka the Suicide Squad), Harley Quinn, Deadshot, Captain Boomerang and King Shark, as they set out on an impossible mission to Kill the Justice League. Drop into an expansive and dynamic open-world Metropolis ravaged by Brainiac’s invasion and terrorized by the heroes who once protected it. <br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/Traversal_2.gif?t=1706907136"><br/>Each Squad member brings their own traversal mechanics to help them navigate a sprawling and battle-torn Metropolis, combining free-roaming exploration and combat verticality for an unforgettable experience. Players are free to experiment with a variety of different play styles to unleash maximum damage on their enemies. Whether in single player or online with up to three of your friends, players can take on this suicide mission their own way.<br/><br/>Post-launch, players can expect a continuously evolving Metropolis with free new playable villains, environments, weapons, in-game events, and more, all included with purchase of the base game.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Hoplite</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1479810/Legendary_Hoplite/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1479810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Ft.co%2FY2Qab5oiFi" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1479810/extras/LEH-61_3_Discord.gif?t=1707080619"/></a> <br/> <br/>Play as Dio, a young commander inspired by the old heroes from Greek mythos like Achilles, Hector, and Perseus. He uses spears, swords and shields to slay thousands of monsters attacking the city of Ithaca. Dio has yet to discover his true power with a wide selection of gear to be used, godlike powers to be summoned and entire new armies to be drafted for battle. This is a war for the fate of mankind.<br/> <br/>The monsters that will try to breach your defense are many and varied. You'll need to think carefully about combat tactics and power balance, especially when dealing with legendary bosses.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1479810/extras/LEH-13_1_Slay_monsters_and_defend_the_gate.png?t=1707080619"><br/>The most important goal is to not let the enemy pass through the gate. Fight against the beasts and legendary tribes from Greek mythology. They will use all their might to break through your ranks and shatter the line of defense. <br/> <br/>In battles, you must lead your army and think of the right strategies to face different enemies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1479810/extras/LEH-50_2.gif?t=1707080619"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1479810/extras/LEH-13_Dividing_Line.png?t=1707080619"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1479810/extras/LEH-13_2_Get_the_best_gear.png?t=1707080619"><br/>The mundane weapons of the world are not enough to repel the attacks of the mighty monsters. Dio needs the weapons with deadly power, the artifacts blessed by the Gods themselves. <br/>Besides strategically arranging the armies, you'll need to upgrade them through battles to match the stronger and more unusual enemies. The classic skill tree upgrade system combined with the sets of war technique provide the required versatility. Changing them will open up tactical options and let your defenders vanquish the ever-changing monster waves.<br/>Make your own build with a combination of skills and become a powerful adversary for your enemies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1479810/extras/LEH-50_1.gif?t=1707080619"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1479810/extras/LEH-13_Dividing_Line.png?t=1707080619"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1479810/extras/LEH-13_3_Fight_your_foes.png?t=1707080619"><br/>Your enemies are the beasts and legendary races from Greek mythology who conflicted with humans since the dawn of time and have long wanted to exterminate them. The legions of the dead started this war, gathered the army and attacked Ithaca in great numbers. The beasts and monsters from around the region took advantage of the opportunity to advance their forces. <br/>Pay special attention to the bosses. They are creatures of legend that caused much suffering to mankind. Now, they will use their impetuous primordial strength to break through our defenses.<br/>Stop them from destroying our homeland and killing our people at any cost.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1479810/extras/Fight_your_foes.gif?t=1707080619"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1479810/extras/LEH-13_Dividing_Line.png?t=1707080619"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1479810/extras/LEH-13_4_Find_out_the_truth.png?t=1707080619"><br/>The Trojan War is over.<br/>Odysseus, king of Ithaca, became a legend because of his trick with the Trojan horse. Having returned from Troy, Odysseus regained the throne of Ithaca, but peace did not last long...<br/>An unexpected event led to Odysseus’s death at the hand of his illegitimate son. This incident revealed a critical secret and brought an endless horde of monsters to the gates of Ithaca.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1479810/extras/Find_out_the_truth_1.png?t=1707080619"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1479810/extras/LEH-13_Dividing_Line.png?t=1707080619"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 40 levels where ARPG meets Tower Defense.<br/></li><li>Over 150 types of monsters with hundreds of variants.<br/></li><li>Many bosses from the original Greek mythology, including Cerberus, Hydra, Gorgon, Minotaur, etc.<br/></li><li>Plenty of items to collect and equip in your endless hunt.<br/></li><li>Various armies with dozens of special skills that enable countless strategies.<br/></li><li>And many more secrets tied to the achievement system waiting to be discovered.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161700/Persona_3_Reload/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a transfer student thrust into an unexpected fate when entering the hour "hidden" between one day and the next. Awaken an incredible power and chase the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fight for your friends, and leave a mark on their memories forever. <br/><br/>Persona 3 Reload is a captivating reimagining of the genre-defining RPG, reborn for the modern era.<br/><br/>Key Features: <br/>- Experience the pivotal game of the Persona series faithfully remade with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, and signature stylish UI. <br/><br/>-Fully immerse yourself in an emotional, gripping journey with new scenes, character interactions, and additional voiceover.<br/><br/>- Choose how to meaningfully spend each day through various activities, from exploring the Port Island to forging genuine bonds with beloved characters.<br/><br/>- Build and command your optimal team to take down otherworldly Shadows and climb closer to the truth.<br/><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Deluxe Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook: Filled with 64 pages of character art, concept art, backgrounds and other illustrations from the game!<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack: Listen to newly arranged tracks from the original Persona 3 plus all-new tracks from Persona 3 Reload, presented by the Atlus sound team for a total of 60 new songs.</li></ul><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Premium Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack<br/></li><li>Persona 3 Reload DLC Pack:  P5R Phantom Thieves Costume Set, P5R Shujin Academy Costume Set, P5R Persona Set 1, P5R Persona Set 2 , P5R BGM Set, P4G Yasogami High Costume Set, P4G Persona Set</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonbreaker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/845890/Moonbreaker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/845890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Moonbreaker is a turn-based strategy, tactical skirmish game developed by Unknown Worlds, the team behind the Subnautica series. It is designed to be a true digital miniatures experience, set in an expansive sci-fi universe crafted by best-selling sci-fi and fantasy author, Brandon Sanderson. Through approachable turn-based competitive gameplay, immersive art, captivating lore, and deep customization, Moonbreaker offers a variety of gameplay experiences for all types of players.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/845890/extras/MB_GIF_1_TableTop@615x200.gif?t=1706814698"><br/><br/><strong>TURN-BASED, TABLETOP TACTICS:</strong> Lead your Units in fast-paced, turn-based strategic skirmishes. Play against other players, against AI, or in the single-player roguelike adventure mode “Boss Run.” It’s quick to pick up, hard to put down.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/845890/extras/MB_GIF_3_Roster@615x200.gif?t=1706814698"><br/><br/><strong>BUILD YOUR ROSTER:</strong> No two Units are alike and no two Rosters play alike. Each Unit has its own special set of abilities, playstyle, personality, and more. Create various Rosters of diverse Units to experience fresh dynamics and build the ultimate team. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/845890/extras/MB_GIF_2_Paint@615x200.gif?t=1706814698"><br/><br/><strong>PAINT YOUR CREW:</strong> Harness your creativity with Unit painting, designed to capture the feel of real miniature painting – without the real-world limitations. Professional digital painting tools go beyond what is traditionally possible (undo! mask! zoom!), creating the perfect space for blissful player expression.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/845890/extras/MB_GIF_4_Reaches@615x200.gif?t=1706814698"><br/><br/><strong>DISCOVER THE REACHES:</strong> Crafted by beloved fantasy author Brandon Sanderson, The Reaches is filled with vibrant, diverse characters and cultures. Unravel the vast world of Moonbreaker through Audio Dramas by award-winning author Dan Wells, fully-voiced in-game dialogue - performed by renowned voice actors - and an unlockable Codex full of lore.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boxes: Lost Fragments</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2019810/Boxes_Lost_Fragments/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2019810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FggGzdma9mA" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2019810/extras/discord.png?t=1706879962"/></a><br/><br/><strong>As a legendary thief, your next assignment lures you into a grand and lavish mansion. There you find a series of puzzle boxes, designed for an unknown purpose.</strong><br/><br/>Suddenly, you realize that this is no ordinary building and that you are no longer in control of what is unfolding, and perhaps never were. What should have been a quick in-and-out, turns into your own harrowing struggle for freedom and answers. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2019810/extras/clockworkDivider.png?t=1706879962"><br/>Inspired by the cryptic atmosphere, intricate machinery, and smooth controls of the best room escape games, we have created a diverse set of original puzzle levels that will test your resolve and skills to navigate this mysterious and compelling journey. Each level is beautiful, unique, and a true delight to explore and figure out.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLCARD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1201540/HELLCARD/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Hellcard</strong> is a <strong>cooperative roguelike deckbuilder</strong> that can be played in both <strong>Singleplayer </strong>and <strong>Multiplayer </strong>modes. The game takes place in the paper dungeons known from Book of Demons, and its main mechanics revolve around deckbuilding and fast-paced tactical card battles. <br/><br/>If you are excited about <strong>HELLCARD</strong>, be sure to <strong>wishlist </strong>the game on Steam. Otherwise, consider wishlisting anyway - who knows, we might surprise you yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif5_600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/>What makes <strong>HELLCARD</strong> unique and different from other deck-building games is that <strong>monster placement actually matters</strong> and can be used to your advantage.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif4_600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>HELLCARD</strong> supports <strong>co-op battles</strong> with up to three heroes facing the Archdemon's hordes. In <strong>singleplayer mode</strong>, you can descend into the dungeons solo or recruit computer-controlled companions. In <strong>multiplayer mode</strong>, your friends or strangers can help you battle the hordes of hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif1-2-3-600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/r2g_logo_fixed.png?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>Return 2 Games</strong> is a series of unique mid-core games inspired by the golden days of PC gaming. Each R2G title is a tribute to a single hit game from the '90s: a reimagining of a single universal story for a brand-new audience, using modern means and innovative, often vastly simplified gameplay mechanics.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/pillars.png?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>HELLCARD</strong> was first envisioned as a new game mode inside the Book of Demons universe, but we soon realized that its design is huge and that it should be executed as a stand-alone spin-off game. If you want to learn more about Return 2 Games or support us in the development of the series, visit the <strong>Supporter Pack</strong> store page. On release, <strong>HELLCARD </strong>will be a part of it.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/706770/Return_2_Games_Supporters_Pack/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/706770/Return_2_Games_Supporters_Pack/</a><br/><strong>Book of Demons</strong>, the first part in the series is already here, be sure to check it out as it includes a free demo. <br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/449960/Book_of_Demons/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/449960/Book_of_Demons/</a><br/>Also, be sure to check out <strong>Book of Aliens</strong>, the second book in the series and a tribute to MicroProse’ UFO: Enemy Unknown that’s also in the works:<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1196230/Book_of_Aliens/" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1196230/Book_of_Aliens/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1131620/Dominion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Expand a small kingdom to a mighty Dominion!  <br/><br/>Play the Spiel des Jahres winning boardgame beloved by millions around the world. This is the officially licensed implementation.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Reigning.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Discover the game that defined a genre, Dominion was first to popularize deck-building and remains a staple of tabletop. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/GrowYourKingdom.png?t=1707010484">Collect as many Victory Points as you can by building a powerful deck. Your deck starts out a small sad set of Estates and Coppers, but you hope that by the end of the game it will be brimming with Gold, Provinces, and the inhabitants and structures of your kingdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/BuildEngine.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Choose wisely among the 10 cards available in the tableau to create the strongest combos to dominate your opponent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CollectAllExpansions.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Make your games more exciting with additional cards and rules from up to 15 expansions including the recent Plunder expansion! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/NearInfiniteVariety.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Over one hundred thirty-two septillion possible Kingdom combinations, 500+ cards, 15 and counting expansions, and ongoing promo packs make Dominion one of the most extensive and replayable boardgames in the hobby. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CompeteComputer.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Sharpen your skills with solitaire style solo play against a robust AI, with four levels of difficulty. Our innovative AI learns through self-play. Earn Achievements and win in Recommended Sets against each AI level. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/PlayWithFriends.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Join up to 6 players online through your device or pass and play among your friends. Play ranked or unranked matchmaking, with realtime and asynchronous modes. Set up a private table for a family game, challenge a stranger in the lobby, or invite a friend!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Daily.png?t=1707010484"><br/>A daily ritual to relax with over a cup of coffee. Try the Daily Dominion, a free puzzle level available to players around the world. Practice your strategy to keep up a winning streak and climb the leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CrossPlatform.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Play from any supported device, whenever you want, after verifying your email in-game. Join games with opponents on platforms other than your own to enjoy the largest possible multiplayer pool and speedy matchmaking. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/JoinCommunity.png?t=1707010484"><br/>With an active Discord and online community, make new friends or challenge new people to a game. Export and share kingdoms and game summaries to compare strategies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/FreeToPlay.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Download the game that started it all for free! The base set of Dominion is available at no charge. Try the rotation of expansion cards in the Daily at no cost once per day. Jump into a lobby game with expansions enabled to try before you buy. Only the host needs to own the expansions.    <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Intro.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Learn the ropes in this easy to pick-up, hard to master title. Play one of the most highly regarded strategy tabletop games of all time through our simple tutorial.  The core loop is easy to follow, but offers a wealth of strategy to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>1-6 player</strong> support<br/></li><li><strong>500 </strong> plus <strong>cards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Solo play</strong> against four AI difficulties<br/></li><li><strong>Async </strong>&amp; <strong>real-time</strong> multiplayer<br/></li><li><strong>Ranked</strong> &amp; <strong>unranked</strong> matchmaking<br/></li><li><strong>Lobby</strong> &amp; <strong>Private game</strong> tables<br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform multiplayer</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform purchases</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Daily challenge</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Challenging AI</strong> that learns through self-play<br/></li><li><strong>Recommended Sets</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Customize</strong>, save &amp; share <strong>Kingdoms</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Achievements</strong>, <strong>Stats </strong>&amp; <strong>Leaderboards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Pass &amp; Play</strong> mode<br/></li><li>Automated <strong>score-keeping</strong> &amp; hints<br/></li><li><strong>Smart-play</strong> options to streamline gameplay<br/></li><li><strong>Jumbo mode</strong> for readability on phones<br/></li><li><strong>Turbo mode</strong> to zoom through games quickly<br/></li><li><strong>Tutorial</strong> &amp; <strong>Rules</strong><br/></li><li><strong>4 languages</strong>: English, Japanese, German, French<br/></li><li><strong>15 expansions</strong> plus three promo packs </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Awards for the Boardgame</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Awards.png?t=1707010484"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kādomon: Hyper Auto Battlers Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1985320/Kdomon_Hyper_Auto_Battlers_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Enter_a_new_world!.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/enter_new_world_final.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>Welcome to the world of Kādomon, a mysterious land where cute and quirky monsters roam freely. Journey through randomly generated regions, battling and collecting Kādomon on your quest to be the best.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Over_180_Kadomon.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/dex_final.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>There’s 180+ monsters to add to your Kādodex, and each Kādomon has 2 super rare misprints to discover! Find over 60 of these monsters and their misprints to build the ultimate unstoppable team in the Kādomon prologue!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Battle_with_Unique_Monsters.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/unique_mon_final.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>All Kādomon have special characteristics, such as activated abilities, passive abilities and different typings (there’s 12 types in total!). Synergise your Kādomon’s attacks and create a super effective combo of monsters. Grow even stronger with every battle by levelling-up and evolving your team!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Experience_Hyper_Evolutions.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/exp_hyper.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>Once fully evolved, every Kādomon has the chance to get HYPER! Acquire very rare items that allow your Kādomon to break their limits and discover a hyper-powerful 4th form! With brand new designs and souped-up stats, you’ll be able to tackle the greatest of challenges, in the Kādomon prologue you will be able to discover Hyper Evolution for every starter Kādomon! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Fight_BIG_bosses!.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/big_bosses.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>Battle your team against elite enemies and bosses. Get your team ready to fight against MEGA opponents, and unlock brand new Kādomon if you win! Remember, there is always a greater foe to test your strength!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Discover_Secrets_.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Discover_Secrets_final.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>The Kādomon world is bustling with secrets, including random events that will change the tide of battle! In the Early Access release, experiment with different items and monsters, Kādomon might evolve in different ways, and if you’re lucky you might just encounter a Legendary Kādomon to join your team…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/shonnkknk.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/shonnka.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>In between battles, take a mosey around Shonkka's Shop! Here you can use the Money Berries you’ve earned to buy new Kādomon and items. Held items are incredibly useful to have as they give you permanent buffs or powerful single use effects when used wisely!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/881020/Granblue_Fantasy_Relink/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/881020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Story<br/>
Granblue Fantasy takes place in the Sky Realm, a world where myriad islands float in a great blue expanse. Take your role as captain of a skyfaring crew, joined by a scrappy little dragon named Vyrn and a young girl with mysterious powers named Lyria. Together you sail with a colorful cast of crewmates, including kings and misfits alike, for Estalucia, a fabled island beyond the end of the skies.<br/>
<br/>
In the Zegagrande Skydom, islands are guarded by powerful creatures known as primal beasts and winds carry tales of a secretive organization known as the Church of Avia. Unveil a web of intrigue reaching far beyond the borders of Zegagrande and engage in a battle for the fate of the Sky Realm itself.<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay<br/>
Engage in real-time combat with a party of four in this character action RPG—choose from a diverse roster of skyfarers, each with their own unique weapons, skills, and combat styles. Teamwork makes the dream work with party-based mechanics such as Link Attacks and Chain Bursts to help you crush foes in spectacular fashion. Tackle quests solo or with the help of others for up to 4-player co-op and take down treacherous foes to score rare loot to further enhance your gear. Every enemy and party formation has its own strengths and weaknesses—the key to victory lies in working out how these pieces fit together.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced combat not your thing? Assist modes can provide accessibility for gamers of all skill levels. Toggle on Full Assist to have all actions performed automatically during battle!<br/>
<br/>
The Sky Realm is rich in lore and history. Browse Lyria's journal at any point during the game to access a trove of writings on the world's peoples, places, and more. In addition to the wealth of side quests available, Fate Episodes allow you to delve into the backstories of each member of your crew!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlazBlue Entropy Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2273430/BlazBlue_Entropy_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/原创声明-英语.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗EN_.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>Charismatic character designs with unique aesthetic styles and dramatic animations create a flamboyant, awesome combat experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快的动作连招EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快动作连招.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>Smooth controls, infinite possibilities of combos, and realistic combat feedback. This is the roguelite game with the best action experience yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超多角色豪华制作EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/全员图618x346.jpg?t=1706765621"><br/>Ten playable characters with vibrant personalities, unique combat styles, and immersive voice-acting.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式自由定制EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式，自由定制en.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>There are hundreds of moves for you to build around, plus countless elemental effects and legacy skills passed between characters. The possibilities are infinite. Time to make the best fighter of your own!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/抉择拯救世界EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/GIF-抉择拯救世界EN.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>In the future where the world has been plunged into chaos, people enter a cyberspace called ACE, seeking their last chance to resolve the crisis.<br/>If you are the only person in this world who knows the truth, how will you react?<br/>The ending is also the beginning. Your decision will decide humanity's future.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poppy Playtime - Chapter 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2555190/Poppy_Playtime__Chapter_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2555190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							A decrepit orphanage known as Playcare sits beneath the once magical toy factory. You must make your way through this haunted place, solving new puzzles and avoiding the nightmares that lurk within the dark. Answers lie between the blood-stained bedsheets and screaming echoes... If you can survive.<br/><br/><strong>This is Poppy Playtime's biggest and most terrifying chapter yet. More lies ahead than you might expect...</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>New monsters await, and they're much more than just simple toys.<br/></li><li>Playcare is Playtime's own massive, fantastical orphanage. And you get to explore it.<br/></li><li>The GrabPack gets an upgrade!<br/></li><li>New hands permit new and creative ways to explore.<br/></li><li>A Gas Mask is the only way to safely explore through the red smoke that fills the air.<br/></li><li>Answers will finally be revealed. Lies can only stay buried for so long...</li></ul><br/>There is so much more to see, with further details coming very soon. <br/><br/>Much awaits you in the chapter ahead... a bit of playtime never hurt anyone, right?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Dorado: The Golden City Builder - Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2410890/El_Dorado_The_Golden_City_Builder__Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1451470/El_Dorado_The_Golden_City_Builder/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1451470/El_Dorado_The_Golden_City_Builder/</a><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1505940/Orc_Warchief_Strategy_City_Builder/" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1505940/Orc_Warchief_Strategy_City_Builder/</a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>This is the prologue of our upcoming El Dorado: The Golden City Builder - the prologue is just part of the full game that will let you get to know the game before its official release and it's completely free.</strong></h2><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F2YPZ6fDBsh" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/extras/ElDorado-Discord.png?t=1706714077"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build the mightiest and most expansive empire of Yucatan</strong></h2>Your aim in the game of El Dorado: The Golden City Builder - Prologue, is to create the mightiest empire of the whole Yucatan peninsula. Develop your early small settlement into a city bustling with life and dripping with gold. Build, develop, manage your resources and appease the Gods. Dominate other newly rising or existing settlements of other families through conquest or peaceful talks. Diplomacy or blood… it is your choice.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/extras/El-Dorado-GIF_1-Build_the_mightiest_and_most_expansive_empire_of_Yucatan.gif?t=1706714077"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Become the architect of your mythical city</strong></h2>As the Leader, you will be responsible for every building built on your territory, such as sawmills, temples, housing, barracks and many more. Skillfully plan your city as every path may play a vital role in managing your city. Well-planned zones of your empire will have a special impact on the proper and quickly develop your city. The fate of the citizens depends on you.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/extras/El-Dorado-GIF_2-Become_the_architect_of_your_mythical_city.gif?t=1706714077"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Gather resources</strong></h2>There are many resources on your territory crucial for the development, conquest and keeping your empire stable. Some will be used for daily life, other resources will have a chance to become part of a variety of weapons – so vital to plan your skirmishes.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/extras/El-Dorado-GIF_3-Gather_resources.gif?t=1706714077"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Offer sacrifices to the Gods to earn their favor…</strong></h2>Without sacrifices, there is no game based on a mythical ancient tribe, right? God's favor is one of the basic and important quests in the game. Thanks to their approval your city will not only develop freely but also expand its borders and acquire greater military and political capabilities. Satisfy your Gods to avoid their wrath. You can make sacrifices through your Priest in places of worship such as temples. Choose an appropriate slave, organize a grand festival in honor of the chosen Deity and perform secret dark rituals to the delight of the audience. In return, you can expect divine protection from different cataclysms or an increase in yields from your farms and fields.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/extras/El-Dorado-GIF_4-Offer_sacrifices_to_the_Gods_to_earn_their_favor….gif?t=1706714077"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>… or prepare for their wrath</strong></h2>Gold, riches, extraordinary development… it can’t be that easy. Each repeating or grand one-time festival requires sacrifices. If you happen to forget about worship, the Deities will send many cataclysms to your empire or other problems that will hinder your development. Some will be more or less taxing, but it is always better to evade a lone lightning bolt striking your home and setting the city ablaze or a huge tornado wreaking havoc in your city. Plan well what and when you offer your Gods as no mortal has survived their wrath.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/extras/El-Dorado-GIF_5-…_or_prepare_for_their_wrath.gif?t=1706714077"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Conquer and enslave neighboring people</strong></h2>Every gold is paid for in blood and war is the easiest way to get rich fast. Plunder resources, earn slaves and conquer new land needed for development. Gods are not the only worry, there are other peoples and tribes aiming for the same goal as you. Organize military expeditions, and reinforce the war front or defense lines with resources, which will help in your skirmishes with the enemy. Skillful resource management during war will have an impact on whether your people will come back as victorious conquerors bearing gifts or losers. Fight for the title of the mightiest ruler of the Golden City, El Dorado!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/extras/El-Dorado-Last.png?t=1706714077"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Do not lose yourself in pride.</strong></h2> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcast Tales: The First Journey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/882590/Outcast_Tales_The_First_Journey/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/882590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F7hSuXNCpMP" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/882590/extras/Discord_button_update.png?t=1706789517"/></a><br/><br/>The First Journey is just the beginning of a much grander experience (as the name sort of implies!). So, for now, familiarize yourself with the wasteland - you'll spend a lot more time in it when Outcast Tales is out!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Be tactical</strong> (or mash buttons;  might work just as well)!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/882590/extras/OT-GIF-Intro.gif?t=1706789517"><br/><br/>Robots, mutants, desert raiders: almost all enemies have something up their sleeve. So do your characters: some abilities are most effective in combination with others. Find your opponents' weaknesses, humiliate them on the battlefield, and never ponder the moral implications of your actions!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Use your strengths</strong> (if you can find any)!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/882590/extras/OT-GIF-Personas.gif?t=1706789517"><br/><br/>Combine class and personality types to give each of your characters a unique set of abilities. A Preacher Mercenary and an Antihero Mercenary will behave quite differently. Create a balanced crew, or just try out the wildest combinations to see how they turn out!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Overcome challenges</strong> (or mess everything up)!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/882590/extras/OT-GIF-Events.gif?t=1706789517"><br/><br/>Your characters will encounter dozens of unique situations that test their skill and wits. The Pacifist might talk his way out of trouble, the Egghead might try setting up traps, and the Daredevil will most likely just start blasting! In Outcast Tales, there are no wrong answers.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Develop relationships</strong> (like in a dating game, but not quite)!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/882590/extras/OT-GIF-Relations.gif?t=1706789517"><br/><br/>Your characters can develop deep bonds or even fall in love - but can also come to despise each other, all depending on your actions. Your journey can become a wholesome story about newfound friendship, or a gruesome tale of three strangers constantly at each other’s throats. Whatever sounds more fun…<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Let the chat join the action</strong> (or, more realistically, set you up)! </h2><br/>Connect the game to your Twitch account so that your viewers can influence the gameplay! The Twitch Integration feature will enable your chat to make crucial decisions during events, as well as choose your next destination or ability upgrade. And don't worry, your viewers won't ever try to harm you. They love you. Right..?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2772560/Supermarket_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This Prologue is a limited version of the full game to stop waiting and jump into running your supermarket already. Don't forget to wishlist the full game to continue your most fun supermarket experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Design your store, optimizing for efficiency and aesthetics. Determine where products are displayed, manage your aisles, and ensure a smooth shopping experience for your customers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Order stock using an in-game computer and anticipate the arrival of your next delivery. Unpack goods, organize them in your storage room and display them on shelves, fridges, and freezers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Read product barcodes, handle cash and credit card transactions, and ensure customers leave satisfied with their shopping and checkout experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier_Raw.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Navigate the complexities of a real-time market. Buy products when prices dip and determine the best-selling prices to balance customer satisfaction with profit margins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><br/>Wishlist the full game "Supermarket Simulator" where every decision matters. Will you rise to the occasion, transforming a modest establishment into a retail powerhouse, all while balancing customer satisfaction, finances, and mafia expectations?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Lily - Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2220360/Paper_Lily__Chapter_1/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Something terrible has happened. You can’t bear to think about it - but you can’t live like this anymore. You stopped attending school, you haven’t left your house in months, you have no reason to get out of bed anymore. There are no choices left.<br/><br/>No choice except... that strange golden letter.<br/><br/>It’s time to get your life back together. <br/><br/>One last try.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/divider.png?t=1706724298"><br/><br/>Paper Lily is a story-driven, psychological horror RPG where each puzzle has multiple solutions and outcomes. <strong>There is always another way.</strong><br/>Follow Lacie's story as you explore a dangerous hidden world, solve puzzles in multiple different ways, and face strange enemies. The game is playable in about 4 hours and contains multiple endings depending on your actions.<br/><br/>Paper Lily - Chapter 1 is the continuation to the prologue, <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1698960" rel="" target="_blank">Project Kat</a>, but it can also  be enjoyed without having played it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/lacie_sai_walk.gif?t=1706724298"><h2 class="bb_tag">Out of Context Features</h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple ways of solving puzzles!<br/></li><li>Touch grass, and trees<br/></li><li>Minigames where you press buttons and push boxes around<br/></li><li>Call your mother<br/></li><li>Harmless Snack™<br/></li><li>Various things made of paper<br/></li><li>Bunnies (or whatever those things are)<br/></li><li>Demons<br/></li><li>Fast demons<br/></li><li>Social anxiety simulation<br/></li><li>Table salt<br/></li><li>...Is that Kat? Nah, probably not<br/></li><li>Bathroom etiquette<br/></li><li>Death</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707126915"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707126915"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707126915"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707126915"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707126915"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707126915"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707126915"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707126915"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707126915"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707126915"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707126915"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707126915"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNDERDOGS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2441700/UNDERDOGS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_Title.gif?t=1707036172"><br/><br/>Wrap yourself in 5 tons of metal and go smashing through a dark scene of UNDERGROUND MECH FIGHTS! Bash, crush, maul and rip apart enemy bots and mechs.<br/><br/><u><strong>IT’S FULL-ON METAL-ON-METAL VIOLENCE IN THIS PHYSICS-BASED MECH BRAWLER!</strong></u><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_Smooch.gif?t=1707036172"><br/><br/>But rampaging through the pits ain’t all - <u><strong>THIS IS A ROGUELIKE.</strong></u><br/>Gear up with 120+ items including power tools to customize your mech, meet 30+ characters, hire hackers and saboteurs, hustle and deal with the gangsters and psychos who run these streets as you claw your way up the food chain.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_DF_Pan.gif?t=1707036172"><br/><br/>This city is a dog-eat-dog shit show, but luckily you ain't alone.<br/>Your little bruv King is in your corner - calling out threats and giving you lip while you fight like a wild animal, smashing car sized pit bots that wanna kill you dead to the deafening roars of the blood thirsty crowds.<br/><br/><strong>This is New Brakka - The Mech Fighting Capital of the World.<br/>This is UNDERDOGS.<br/><br/>Welcome to the jungle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_Dem_Clean.gif?t=1707036172"/></strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2072450/Like_a_Dragon_Infinite_Wealth/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/Accolades_616.png?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>EPIC EMOTIONAL DRAMA</strong><br/>Two larger-than-life heroes brought together by the hand of fate, or perhaps something more sinister…<br/><br/>Ichiban Kasuga, an unstoppable underdog who’s no stranger to crawling up from rock bottom, and Kazuma Kiryu, a broken man facing down his last days.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/2_Epic_Emotional_Drama.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>BEST-IN-CLASS RPG ACTION</strong><br/>Experience one-of-a-kind combat with dynamic, fast-paced RPG battles where the battlefield becomes your weapon, and anything goes. Adapt your party’s skills to the situation with outlandish jobs and customizations to strategically subdue enemies with over-the-top moves. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/3_Best_In_Class_RPG_Action.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>INFINITE ADVENTURE</strong><br/>Live it up in Japan and explore all that Hawaii has to offer in an adventure so big it spans the Pacific. Unforgettable moments await at every step of the journey with a unique mix of quests and activities to enjoy at your leisure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/4_Infinite_Adventure.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Deluxe Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Ultimate Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/>- Assorted Outfit Bundle: Customize your party's look with outfits &amp; swimwear<br/>- Sujimon &amp; Resort Bundle: Get legendary Sujimon, resort guests and special boosters<br/>- Yakuza CD Collection Set: Increase your in-game playlist with classic karaoke tracks						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apollo Justice: Ace Attorney Trilogy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2187220/Apollo_Justice_Ace_Attorney_Trilogy/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2187220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2187220/extras/13_Apollo_CustomImages_600x338.png?t=1706177279"><br/><br/>Apollo Justice's Legal Journey Begins Anew!<br/><br/>Join rookie attorney Apollo Justice and his mentor, the legendary Phoenix Wright, in this collection of 3 games! This title features the 14 episodes of "Apollo Justice: Ace Attorney", "Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney - Dual Destinies", and "Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney - Spirit of Justice", and the 2 previously DLC-only Special Episodes for a total of 16 episodes!<br/><br/>Also included is a mountain of extra goodies that's sure to satisfy any Ace Attorney fan!<br/><br/>Orchestra Hall - Listen to the in-game background music and select orchestral arrangements!<br/><br/>Art Library - View illustrations, design specs, commissioned pieces, and even the special Spirit of Justice Prologue anime!<br/><br/>Animation Studio - Play around with character animations and recreate your favorite scenes!<br/><br/>This collection supports Japanese, English, French, German, Korean, and Traditional and Simplified Chinese. Mix and match to play in whichever languages you'd like!<br/><br/>Immerse yourself in this beautiful collection as you shout "Objection!" in these newly renovated halls of justice!<br/><br/>Some of the contents of the games in this collection are presented as initially released to preserve the games as originally created.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summon Masters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2100140/Summon_Masters/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2100140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a card and board game with the following features:<br>
<br>
Deck Building: Players can build their own decks to battle with. Depending on different strategies and opponents, players can choose different cards to counter.<br>
<br>
Tactical Gameplay: The game uses a 3x10 chessboard, and players can freely place cards to fight. Players need to develop tactics and arrange card positions and usage order within limited space.<br>
<br>
Different Professions: Players can choose freely from four professions - swordsman, mage, monk, and archer. Each profession has different characteristics and skills, and players can choose according to their preferences and tactical needs.<br/>
<br/>
Competitive Battles: Players can battle with other players after building their decks, and it is fun to fight with other people. Through battles with other players, players can improve their strength and tactical skills.<br/>
<br/>
Team Dungeons: In addition to fighting against other players, players can also team up with others to challenge high-difficulty dungeons. Players need to defeat powerful bosses through cooperation and strategy to get more rewards and cards.<br/>
<br/>
Special Challenges: Players can participate in special rules challenges and use their intelligence to defeat other players. These special rules make the game more interesting and challenging, and players need to constantly think and try new strategies.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced: Each game is fast-paced (within 5 minutes), and can be played in short fragments of time. The fast pace of the game allows players to enjoy the game in a short time, while also being able to play at any time and anywhere.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2248950/TransSiberian_Railway_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take the helm of a classic Russian locomotive, discover the raw beauty and wildness of Siberia and try to survive on the longest railway line in the world. This is the Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator. A game for real adventurers!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/drinking1.gif?t=1707121961"><br/><br/>Complete the tutorial and the first kilometers of the route for free.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/explosion_gif.gif?t=1707121961"><br/><br/>The Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator offers amazing rail and survival challenges on real Russian dangerous routes. Feel what it is like to put your hands at the helm of a powerful freight locomotive and explore the untouched natural landscape that is sure to delight you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/shooting_gif.gif?t=1707121961"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Prologue features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Detailed simulation of driving a VL10 locomotive - the locomotive control is slightly simplified.<br/></li><li> Locomotive repair system - Manage and replace locomotive parts that are constantly wearing out.<br/></li><li> Train traffic simulation - Follow rail signs and signals to avoid derailment or damage to a part of the locomotive.<br/></li><li> Work system - Earn by completing transport orders. <br/></li><li> Game modes (Survival) and (Simulator). It is recommended to play in the (Survival) mode. This is the leading game mode that is constantly being developed. <br/>For players who are not interested in survival mechanics, a simple Simulator mode is available. <br/></li><li> Mafia system - Complete missions for the mafia to earn extra money.<br/></li><li> Survival system with statistics of hunger, thirst, alcohol, hangover, disease and hypothermia - Eat and drink to avoid death. <br/>Keep the right temperature so you don't freeze.<br/></li><li> Shooting system - Use your weapons for hunting and self-defense.<br/></li><li> Purchase and sales system - Buy various items, food, tools, weapons and ammunition.<br/></li><li> Locomotive inspection mode - Inspect the condition of locomotive parts and replace them in time to avoid damage.<br/></li><li> Dynamic weather system with day and night cycle - Survive extreme weather conditions.<br/></li><li> Route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Novosibirsk-Main) - scale 1:1. Buy the full version with the route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Krasnoyarsk).<br/></li><li> Police system - A corrupt militia watches over your movements.<br/></li><li> Much more to discover.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Universim</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/352720/The_Universim/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>WHAT WOULD YOU DO WITH THE POWER?</strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Play God!</strong> </h2>Guide your fledgling sentient species (lovingly called “nuggets”) from Stone Age cave painters to star-faring explorers.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-1-2d869427c7.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Wield godly power</strong></h2>Command more than 15 godly powers to guide, protect — or discipline — your followers. Create devastating tornadoes, smite naughty followers with lightning bolts, or shake and sunder the very earth. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-1-998341a4ac.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Watch your Nuggets grow and thrive</strong></h2>Observe Nuggets' every move as they work and fight to survive. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-537928a55b.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Evolve and advance through the ages</strong></h2>Research more than 200 technological and societal advancements. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-daca04b5ec.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Expand your power and colonize the galaxy</strong></h2>Discover and colonize a galaxy of procedurally generated planets, each with  unique ecosystems and challenges to conquer.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-be2f66969b.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Manage delicate ecosystems</strong></h2>Manage the delicate balance of planetary ecosystems to help nuggets thrive. Your decisions and your followers’ ' actions influence global climates and have real environmental consequences. (Try not to kill them in an ecological disaster — well, unless you want to, of course.)<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-0095b39c11.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Delve into the deeper mystery of your existence</strong></h2>Unravel the layers of a deeper cosmic story that challenges your perception of who and what you are — and reveals unexpected twists!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-4830f44913.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>About This Game:</strong></h2><br/>The Universim is a strategy city builder game with “God” elements where you guide a civilization (Nuggets) from the Stone Age to the Space Age. Manage resources, dynamic challenges, and ensure your Nuggets can survive, thrive, and spread to the stars. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Animated_Planet_3.png?t=1705993770"><br/><br/>The Universim  features more than  200 research perks that will help you to shape your civilization. Be as benevolent or malevolent as you like to drive nuggets to evolve, advance, and expand. (Even the best civilizations need an occasional smiting).  <br/>Every planet in The Universim is procedurally generated and offers unique characteristics  and challenges, ensuring  that every world and every game is unique and engaging.  Ecological balance and resource management are critical to success. Nuggets have their own needs and behaviors you must attend to. Your guidance will shape how they deal with conflicts, natural disasters, alien creatures, and other civilizations. Their growth and evolution depends on you!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FSymAzCGWsk" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Crytivo_Discord.png?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FgUt5N68" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Discord_join.jpg?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://twitter.com/crytivo" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Twitter.png?t=1705993770"/></a> <br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Feepurl.com%2FbKnqM1" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/News.png?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><br/>This game published by <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/franchise/Crytivo" rel="" target="_blank">Crytivo</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Capitalist Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743080/100_Capitalist_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779640/100_Capitalist_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_6" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779640/100_Capitalist_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱💼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 CAPITALIST CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆💰💵</h2>🤑 Join the cutest adventure in the Wall Street, New York, heart of capitalism! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/600x200.png?t=1706062420"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level of Wall Street location<br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Capitalist Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779640/100_Capitalist_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100CapitalistCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Extra.png?t=1706062420"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779660/100_Capitalist_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100CapitalistCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1706062420"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779650/100_Capitalist_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=100CapitalistCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Artbook.png?t=1706062420"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/600x1.png?t=1706062420"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1706062420"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot" id="dynamiclink_7" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743080/100_Capitalist_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot" id="dynamiclink_8" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743080/100_Capitalist_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intravenous 2: Mercenarism</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2651330/Intravenous_2_Mercenarism/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Wishlist_Game.png?t=1705699394"><br/><br/>Step into the shoes of Gideon, a ruthless mercenary who cares about nothing but his wealth. Set two months before the events of Intravenous 2, you will take on seemingly simple jobs, the effects of which will ripple out and affect the main game's protagonist. But why should Gideon care? He's just in it for the money.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Stealth_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Stealth or Firepower:</strong> the choice is yours. Sneak through shadows, turn off the lights, pick doors, or unleash a hail of bullets. The game will adapt to your play style.<br/></li><li> <strong>Customize Your Skills:</strong> develop your skills the way you want to, whether it's mastering the art of stealth or becoming a gunslinging virtuoso.<br/></li><li> <strong>Bullet Time:</strong> Gideon is no stranger to stimulants that enhance his cognitive abilities - bending time to give him the edge in tense situations.<br/></li><li> <strong>Vast Arsenal:</strong> choose from firearms, gadgets, and a variety of ammo types to creatively tackle the challenge<br/></li><li> <strong>Weapon Modification:</strong> personalize each firearm with suppressors, laser sights, and more, tailoring your arsenal to the task at hand.<br/></li><li> <strong>Responsive AI:</strong> engage in intense combat with enemies that react to your actions, take cover, use tactics and call for backup.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Action_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominions 6 - Rise of the Pantokrator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2511500/Dominions_6__Rise_of_the_Pantokrator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2511500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are a God! You are master and ruler of a loyal nation. You have unimaginable powers at your disposal. You have claimed this world as yours. But there are others who stand in your way. You must defeat and destroy these pretenders. Only then can you ascend to godhood and become the new Pantokrator.<br>
<br>
Dominions 6 is a turn based 4x strategy game suitable for both play vs AI, player vs player.  Team play vs AI or players also works great as everyone can do their turns at once.  The game has a huge variety of units, spells, magic items and different nations to play.<br>
<br>
In Dominions you take control of a powerful being that rules a nation and aspires to godhood. The type of Pretender Gods can vary from magically powerful arch mages to huge titans or large monuments. The pretender gods have different strengths dependent on what kind of god you choose and what nation you play.<br>
<br>
When you start the game you decide what kind of god you are and how your Dominion affects your lands, followers and sacred soldiers. It is an expression of your divine might and the faith of your followers. If your dominion dies, so do you. Your dominion also inspires your sacred warriors and gives them powers derived from your dominion.<br/>
<br/>
In order to win and become the one true god you have to defeat your enemies one of three different ways: conquer their lands, extinguish their dominion or claim the Thrones of Ascension.<br/>
<br/>
Dominions is set in a fantasy world that draws inspiration from historical nations, cultures and myths. You will not encounter the elves of conventional fantasy in this game. Instead you might lead a nation of vanir from old norse myth. Aztecs, romans, israelites, greeks, kievian rus and lovecraftian horrors are just a few of the inspirational sources of the game.<br/>
<br/>
The first Dominions game was released in 2002 and was well received by strategy gamers. Since then Dominions has been much refined and Dominions series is still actively played making it one of the longest running 4x turn based strategy games.<br/>
<br/>
----------<br/>
<br/>
Dominions 6 is scaled up compared to Dominions 5 and armies are larger. We wanted to tweak the balance between conventional armies and magic. To accomplish this a couple of changes are introduced. Incomes and resources are increased, while mages are more expensive. Battlefield-wide spells are more difficult to cast and there are instead more mid-tier spells. There are some other changes with the same aim.<br/>
<br/>
The second and probably most influential change is the addition of a new magic path. No longer are illusions the domain of Air magic. Instead illusions, phantasms, dreams and the stuff of forgotten legends are manipulated with the path of Glamour. This has resulted in many new spells, items and sites being added to the game. <br/>
<br/>
A third massive change is the separation of mounts and riders. Riders and mounts now have separate stats and can be targeted individually. This change probably has less impact on gameplay than the previous one, but will still have an impact on cavalry and nations using mounted units.<br/>
<br/>
Dominions 6 features a number of new nations as well. The addition of the Glamour path has also affected several of the old nations. <br/>
<br/>
There are also a number of changes intended to ease gameplay.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Safety Hotline</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2357910/Home_Safety_Hotline/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/RuntimeLabel-HSH-Dark.png?t=1706120817"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/ShinyLogoOnlyGIF.gif?t=1706120817"><br/><br/><strong>Hearing noises? Seeing things? Call Home Safety Hotline! Our operators are standing by, waiting to give you the answers you need to protect your home from all manner of pests and household hazards.</strong><br/><br/>Home Safety Hotline is an analog horror inspired telephone operator simulator where you answer incoming callers' questions about what's inside their home. Read through a vast catalog of common pests and household hazards, and do your best to become an expert in home safety. You will be held responsible for what happens.<br/><br/>A new horror experiment from Nick Lives, the creator of <i>NiGHT SIGNAL</i> and <i>A Wonderful Day For Fishing</i>. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Navigate a vast catalog of safety information using the latest in 90's technology.<br/></li><li> Listen to original jazzy lo-fi music by David Johnsen while you place callers on hold.<br/></li><li> Correctly deduce what's in your callers' homes or else leave them to suffer the consequences.<br/></li><li> Learn about the various untold horrors that live inside your home.<br/></li><li> "Phobia Toggles" - An accessibility option that allows you to disable in-game images for common phobia triggers including arachnophobia and more.<br/></li><li> Unlockable Art Book detailing the game's development history.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/NumberOnlyGIF.gif?t=1706120817"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2744170/Artifact_SeekerPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/DS.png?t=1706492908"/></a><br/>The difference between the prologue version and the official version<br/>There is a special artifact in the prologue<br/>Characters: 2 in the prologue, at least 5 in the official version<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 3 in the final version.<br/>Systems: Tavern, Marketplace, and Endless Mode will be added to the game.<br/>Artifacts: More artifacts will be added to the game.<br/>Skills: More skills will be added in the official version.<br/>Affixes: More Affixes will be added in the official version.<br/>Events: There will be more interesting Events in the official version.<br/>Progress: No need to worry, all progress will be carry into the official version.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/11y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1z.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/2y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/gif1.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong>[/b]<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><strong><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </img></img></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frostrain</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735630/Frostrain/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/01_Thumnail.png?t=1706325941"><h2 class="bb_tag">Roam the frozen world</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Roam_the_frozen_world.gif?t=1706325941"><br/>Climate change has turned the world white and frozen, and the only thing moving on the planet is you, your passengers, and your train. It's a dead world, but ironically, it's all the more fascinating for it. A vivid landscape awaits you to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Keep your passengers happy</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Keep_your_passengers_happy.gif?t=1706325941"><br/>The passengers on your train will work diligently at your command, but be careful: if you don't manage their happiness properly, they might throw you off the train.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build your own train with card decks</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Build_your_own_train_with_card_decks.gif?t=1706325941"><br/>Each time you pass through a city, you'll be able to add new train cars by launching a heavy lift drone. Be careful with each choice you make. If you are lucky, you'll be able to build a better, more synergized, happily-ever-after train deck, but it won't always go as you planned.<h2 class="bb_tag">Reach the Promised Land</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Reach_the_Promised_Land.gif?t=1706325941"><br/>Lead your passengers in search of the Promised Land, somewhere on the eastern edge of the world. But the journey to the Promised Land isn't all smooth and pleasant. You'll have to pass through toxic areas, and a severe storm is brewing behind you. Pay attention to your passengers' happiness levels and lead them safely to the Promised Land. The journey is in your hands.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696480/Nothing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2696480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play. Or is it?<br>
<br>
Just do Nothing as the timer goes up. If you do Something, you lose.<br>
<br>
If you don't like doing Nothing, go play Something instead.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KinitoPET</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2075070/KinitoPET/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Join the Discord!</strong></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FGZfJqdM7au" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/GZfJqdM7au</a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enter the Everlasting Fun!</strong></h2>Would you like a friend? Yes? Well, I have something special for you.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075070/extras/BoxSpin.gif?t=1706703007"><br/>KinitoPET invites you to their wonderfull world of fun and excitement!<br/>Where he will be your very own virtual friend and personal helper! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075070/extras/KinitoWelcome.png?t=1706703007"><br/>Kinito is able to walk, talk, browse, adapt, and play games as Kinito is like no other with its adaptive technology! Kinito is h̶i̶d̶i̶n̶g̶ ̶a̶ ̶d̶a̶r̶k̶ ̶s̶e̶c̶r̶e̶t a friend you'll never forget with its critically acclaimed react respond algorithm to make your experience in̶d̶e̶f̶i̶n̶i̶t̶e truly unique. Where d̶i̶d̶ he ̶g̶o else can you find a friend like Kinito with its multitude of great features and friendly love! <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075070/extras/SteamImageLowerRes.png?t=1706703007"><br/>Kinito will be your friend and you can s̶t̶o̶p̶ ̶i̶t be there's! <br/>So why wait as with your new virtual assistant and friend you can have f̶o̶r̶e̶v̶e̶r everlasting fun!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summoners War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2426960/Summoners_War/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2426960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>▶Features</strong><br/><strong>[Tactical RPG play]</strong><br/>Witness the dazzling display of each monster 's unique skills.<br/>23 different Rune sets to pick and choose additional abilities for your monsters!<br/>Come up with the best strategy to win battles in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[Endless Fun]</strong><br/>Decorate your Village, battle other summoners , explore dungeons , fight in PvP battles , expand your collection, train monsters , and more.<br/><br/><strong>[The Key of Colletion RPG : Massive Collection]</strong><br/>Fire, Water, Wind, Light and Dark!<br/>5 different attributes, and 1500 different monsters!<br/>Collect as many monsters as you can and win battles with your own decks .<br/><br/><strong>[Real-time Raid]</strong><br/>Battle as a team with your greatest monsters !<br/>A real-time battle with 3 users!<br/>Defeat the boss with your fellow Summoners using various tactics.<br/><br/><strong>[Homunculus]</strong><br/>The Forbidden Summoning Magic has finally been revealed!<br/>You can Evolve the skill of your choice with this special monster.<br/>Summon Homunculus and show off your strategy in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[All about Turn-Based RPG : World Arena]</strong><br/>Enjoy a real-time battle with Summoners worldwide!<br/>Experience a breathtaking battle that starts from Pick &amp; Ban.<br/>Reveal your unique strategy to the world and win battles .<br/><br/><strong>[Guild Content]</strong><br/>A sensational Guild PvP battle in the Isle of Conquest!<br/>Explore the Tartarus' Labyrinth and dungeons with Guild Members.<br/>Make your Guild the greatest of all.<br/><br/><strong>[Dimension Hole]</strong><br/>Fight against the ancient power emerged from a new dimension!<br/>Defeat the Ancient Guardians and meet the powerful monsters with new awakening power.<br/><br/><strong>[Artifact]</strong><br/>Artifacts are now dropped with MAX power-up levels!<br/>Summoners , fight against the powerful bosses and acquire Artifacts!<br/>Enhance your monsters with various sub properties of Artifacts.<br/><br/><strong>[Progression and Farming Structure Revamp]</strong><br/>Summoner progression structure renewed and content reward greatly improved!<br/>Dive into Summoners War and experience the enhanced progression system!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portal: Revolution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/601360/Portal_Revolution/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Portal: Revolution is a fan-made mod for Portal 2 which plays before the events of Portal 2 in the dead and decaying Aperture facility.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/ezgif-7-f507c3c464_1_.gif?t=1705968827"><br/><strong>Over 40 new puzzles</strong><br/>The campaign contains 40 brand new puzzles making use of new test elements and presents existing mechanics in a new way not seen in Portal 2.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resurrected "Pneumatic Diversity Vent" element<br/></li><li> New laser cube variant<br/></li><li> Over 15 puzzles using only the blue Portal-Gun<br/></li><li> Gel Cleansing Field</li></ul><br/><strong>Difficulty</strong><br/>Portal: Revolutions puzzle difficulty starts where Portal 2 stops, but fear not. All new mechanics and advanced portal tricks are taught to you. We have ensured through rigorous playtesting that every player can solve the puzzles. Although very few chambers require portals to be fired mid-air, no puzzles require advanced tricky movement.<br/><br/>Depending on your experience with Portal 2 mechanics, you can expect about 5 to 7 hours of playtime.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/banner_story_2.gif?t=1705968827"><br/>Set inbetween Portal and Portal 2, Portal: Revolution tells a brand new story using new characters. You play as a test subject who is awoken by a personality sphere called Stirling and join his mission to find a powerful device capable of restoring Aperture to its former glory.<h2 class="bb_tag">ENGINE</h2>Portal: Revolution uses a modified version of Portal 2: Community Edition's engine, which is a custom version of the Counter-Strike: Global Offensive Source Engine branch using licensed source code provided by Valve Software.<br/><br/>This allowed us to introduce many mechanics and improvements to the engine to create an experience which would be impossible in Portal 2.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IFU</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2666080/IFU/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2666080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Immerse yourself in a world where every step you take could be your last, where the tension grows with every passing moment.  The IFU invites you to guide your character, Alexander, through loops of uncharted mysteries and dark secrets.</i><br/><br/><strong>Discover a story that takes your breath away:</strong>.<br/>You are Alexander, a computer programmer who finds himself at the center of an unimaginable nightmare. Your reality turns into a struggle for survival when you follow an invitation that promises to be the gateway to a new life, but becomes the entrance to hell. Meet the mystical Droseries and uncover Dr. Hatcher's story, which is shrouded in sinister secrets.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2666080/extras/1.gif?t=1707132192"><br/><br/><strong>FEEL THE FEATURE OF THE COUNTRY:</strong>.<br/>In IFU, every element of the environment contributes to the frightening atmosphere. From an ominous rustle to the flickering light of a lantern, your heart will beat in rhythm with every step in an abandoned mansion where every corner could be hiding your enemy... or a clue... Or a clue.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2666080/extras/2.gif?t=1707132192"><br/><br/><strong>EXPERIENCE THE BORDERS OF REALISM:</strong>.<br/>IFU raises the bar on realism with thoughtful gameplay that forces you to look at simple walking from a new angle. Discretion and attention to detail are your main allies in the search for the truth.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2666080/extras/3.gif?t=1707132192"><br/><br/><strong>OPEN the veil of secrets:</strong>.<br/>Every item, every document in the IFU is a piece of the puzzle that you must assemble to understand the full picture of the horror taking place. Put them together to uncover stories that are only whispered in the shadows.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDLE Animal Anatomy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2778360/IDLE_AnimalAnatomy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Have you ever dreamed of raising an animal with your own hands? Feel like a scientist in this game and grow your favorite pet cage by cage right on your device!<br>
<br>
In this game<br>
- a lot of interesting facts about animals<br>
- learn how the internal organs of animals and humans look like<br>
- can you raise cute animals<br>
- plunge into anatomy like a real scientist.Grow all the living creatures from the collection!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delicious Donut</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2791620/Delicious_Donut/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Solve the world most delicious donut puzzle reduced to it's simplest form right here in front of you, ready to be taken to other planets, and spread the words about how delicious these donuts are.<br>
<br>
To solve the puzzle, you have to move the donuts to the correct spot just like sokoban puzzle.<br>
<br>
WASD move<br>
Z undo<br>
X redo						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>黄毛漂流记</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2535770/_/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2535770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2535770/extras/45645.png?t=1707135101"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Player Discussion Group</strong></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/chat/invite/ZdEEZDZi" rel="" target="_blank">https://steamcommunity.com/chat/invite/ZdEEZDZi</a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Main Plot:</strong></h2>Due to a maritime accident, you unexpectedly find yourself on this island and receive a warm invitation to settle here. The village chief enthusiastically introduces you to other residents of the island: Ping, Aunt Lin, the carpenter, and others. Everyone is excited about your arrival. Your mission is to develop the island and embark on a series of exciting explorations.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Gameplay:</strong></h2>Maintain good relationships with NPCs through various distinctive tasks. Each NPC, with their unique personality, has different storylines. In your leisure time, you can earn island currency through mechanisms like fishing, planting, and selling. Use these earnings to purchase more building blueprints for island construction. <br/>You can also take a speedboat from the pier to visit other unique islands, meet more characters, and invite them to join in building the small island.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Character Introductions:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Aunt Lin: A kind and gentle housewife who, along with her daughter, runs a martial arts gym for a living.<br/></li><li>Ping: Aunt Lin's daughter, passionate about martial arts.<br/></li><li>Xiao Ai: The somewhat laid-back owner of a shop.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Gunner Wukong</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2270750/Black_Gunner_Wukong/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2270750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Black Gunner Wukong is a Rougelike type shooting game.<br/>In the game, the player takes on the role of Wukong , who enters a U.S. military base to rescue his master who has been captured by Diden.<br/>In the game, all creatures are identified as armed helicopters and supermarket shopping bags, not as female and male!<br/>Demo:<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2095890/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2095890/</a><h2 class="bb_tag"> Game Features: </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2270750/extras/Shot.gif?t=1707120191"><br/>A very rare TPS+Vampire survivor!<br/>Can use 6 big guns to crush your enemies! <br/>Can fly using the Nimbus Cloud! <br/>Rich build options, gun bonds combinations.<br/>Play as different forms of Wukong, with various active and passive skills. <br/>Bullet storms, a true bullet hell! <br/>Collect peaches from each round of battle, purchase enhancements, and ultimately engage in a showdown with the boss. <br/>A comically themed background storyline.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2270750/extras/Fatian.gif?t=1707120191"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTuber Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2098560/YouTuber_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2098560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2098560/extras/gifgif.gif?t=1707129951"><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2>A super popular fitness YouTuber with over 5 million subscribers... The protagonist, Beom-<br/>tae, is happily running a YouTube channel, receiving tremendous love from fans. <br/><br/>Can it be this intense?!! This is... dangerous!! <br/><br/>Survive from the fans...!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2098560/extras/2023-10-23_15-59-22_3.gif?t=1707129951"><br/><strong>Youtuber Survivors</strong> is a BEAT 'EM UP + Rogue-like action game. A unique "One button combo system" makes complex technical movements in a breeze.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>2D BEAT 'EM UP + Rogue-like!<br/></li><li>A cartoon-like story filled with humor!<br/></li><li>Easy One button combo system!</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Unlock permanent trait for your character!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detective Ridelle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2172490/Detective_Ridelle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2172490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FhDP85fYRsC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2172490/extras/discordLink.png?t=1707131233"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Solve the Clues. Unravel the Mystery.</h2><br/>Ridelle receives an anonymous letter inviting her on a luxury train. On board, she's already suspicious - but when someone is found <u>dead</u> it's up to her to catch the killer.<br/><br/>Detective Ridelle is a first-person puzzle game with visual novel style storytelling.<br/><br/>Explore a unique, handcrafted world filled with suspects, clues, and hidden secrets.<br/>Can you uncover the truth and bring the killer to justice?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2172490/extras/steamDivider.png?t=1707131233"><h2 class="bb_tag">On board you will find:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Escape Room Puzzles</strong><br/>Featuring unique puzzles by a real escape room designer. You'll need to keep your wits about you to solve them all.<br/></li><li><strong>A Cast of Crazy Characters</strong><br/>Why are all these people on the train? Where were they at the time of the murder?<br/>Why does everyone seem to have something to hide?<br/>It's up to <u>you</u> to find out.<br/></li><li><strong>Unique Handcrafted Environments</strong><br/>Enjoy uncovering and exploring the many locations handcrafted with a unique visual style.<br/></li><li><strong>A Thrilling Mystery</strong><br/>There's a murderer on board and you're the only one who can stop them. Unravel the web of clues to find the killer before it's too late.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>消失的妹妹(The Vanished Sister)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2778320/The_Vanished_Sister/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Developed independently by a Bilibili horror game anchor for two and a half years<h2 class="bb_tag">Background story:</h2>My younger sister mysteriously disappeared, and the protagonist followed her trail to a mysterious sea building. As night fell, the terrifying secrets buried here gradually became apparent.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay:</h2>In this game, players need to avoid the capture of "spiritual bodies" that may be hidden in any corner, stimulate all intelligence, and use various props found along the way to find ways to escape. Even the most tenacious players must give their all in harsh environments, do their best to survive, and escape into the sky.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game features:</h2>-Typical design of traditional horror escape games<br/>-Innovatively adding an emotional system to artificial intelligence, accumulating anger points while chasing players. With each stage of anger, AI's various abilities will be improved to varying degrees<br/>-Carefully building advanced artificial intelligence systems<br/>-All props are randomly generated, with multiple escape methods and a permanent death mechanism, providing a brand new experience in each game<br/>-The game is divided into multiple levels of difficulty, each with its own unique design						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Contract</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/907940/Defense_Contract/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/907940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Grapple hook racing</h2><br/>Speed through challenging race levels using grappling hooks in VR. Defense Contract is built for virtual reality and provides a unique and exciting experience aimed at VR veterans but still enjoyable to those without their "VR legs" for short periods.<br/><br/>Defense Contract will appeal to players looking for more intense, fast paced VR content. While it does contain a level editor that is surprisingly fun and low-key, the majority of the content is exhilarating, superhero-feeling racing game play.<h2 class="bb_tag">Current features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Grapple hook racing<br/></li><li> Over 20 built in levels (with more being added)<br/></li><li> Fully VR level editor for creating your own challenges</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abyssmare</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2437870/Abyssmare/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i>Abyssmare </i></strong>is a near future science fiction world view based on the Cthulhu Mythos world view, and an action game based on<i> Roguelite+first person shooting</i>.<h2 class="bb_tag">gameplay：</h2><strong>1.Old-School FPS</strong><br/>With ultra-high movement speed and sustainable output of powerful firepower, all you need to do is attack and explode all the living creatures.<br/>Your goal is to explore the dungeon and find the elevator that leads to the lower level. During this process, you can search for resources in the maze to strengthen yourself, such as ammunition, medical kits, energy crystals, and various weapons and equipment.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437870/extras/s1.gif?t=1707102947"><br/><br/><strong>2.Manual random maze</strong><br/>On the surface, it is a randomly generated maze, but in reality, all changes in the maze are artificially designed.<br/>This game aims to achieve randomness while ensuring a maze exploration experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437870/extras/s4.gif?t=1707102947"><br/><br/><strong>3.Weapons and Equipments</strong><br/>More than 30 completely different firearms.<br/>More than 20 sub weapons with different functions.<br/>Each profession has a melee weapon.<br/>More than 40 different equipment components, each with unique functions and effects.<br/>The quantity of these items will continue to be updated.<br/>I hope this can enhance your enjoyment of exploring the maze.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437870/extras/s2.gif?t=1707102947"><br/><br/><strong>4.Roguelite game</strong><br/>This game has two growth cycles.<br/>Growth in a single adventure: includes acquiring weapons and equipment, improving personal attributes, obtaining random buffs, and shopping in temporary stores.<br/>Growth through multiple adventures: The protagonist can obtain a certain amount of resources for each adventure, regardless of victory or death. After completing a single adventure, they can consume resources and permanently enhance the character's strength.<br/><br/><strong>5.Action-RPG game</strong><br/>This game has certain RPG elements, such as custom characters, equipment, and random entries on equipment, character professions, character attributes, etc.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437870/extras/s3.gif?t=1707102947"><br/><br/><strong>6.Enemies</strong><br/>16 regular enemies+10 bosses, and will continue to be updated.<br/>Except for human enemies, they are all based on the classic Cthulhu Mythos series novels.<h2 class="bb_tag">Cthulhu Mythos elements:</h2>In this game, monsters and old dominators in the Cthulhu Mythos, whose size is approximately similar to that of human beings and may be destroyed by human weapons, are selected as enemies, and a new image is designed for them.<br/>Most enemies have undergone physical modifications and are wearing "ShenWei" exoskeletons, hoping these will make you feel interesting.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jousting in January</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2768520/Jousting_in_January/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2768520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Jousting in January is a g̶̶̶o̶̶̶o̶̶̶f̶̶̶y̶̶̶ ̶̶̶s̶̶̶i̶̶̶d̶̶̶e̶̶̶ ̶̶̶p̶̶̶r̶̶̶o̶̶̶j̶̶̶e̶̶̶c̶̶̶t̶̶̶ ̶̶̶I̶̶̶ ̶̶̶t̶̶̶h̶̶̶r̶̶̶e̶̶̶w̶̶̶ ̶̶̶t̶̶̶o̶̶̶g̶̶̶e̶̶̶t̶̶̶h̶̶̶e̶̶̶r̶̶̶ ̶̶̶t̶o̶ ̶e̶n̶t̶e̶r̶t̶a̶i̶n̶ ̶m̶y̶s̶e̶l̶f̶ ̶̶̶s̶̶̶i̶̶̶n̶̶̶c̶̶̶e̶̶̶ ̶̶̶m̶̶̶y̶̶̶ ̶̶̶m̶̶̶a̶̶̶i̶̶̶n̶̶̶ ̶̶̶p̶̶̶r̶̶̶o̶̶̶j̶̶̶e̶̶̶c̶̶̶t̶̶̶ ̶̶̶h̶̶̶a̶̶̶s̶̶̶ ̶̶̶h̶̶̶i̶̶̶t̶̶̶ ̶̶̶s̶̶̶o̶̶̶m̶̶̶e̶̶̶ ̶̶̶d̶̶̶e̶̶̶l̶̶̶a̶̶̶y̶̶̶s̶̶̶  free for all arcade game in which you must strike the enemy before they get you. 1 hit kill. 1st hit wins. Game features include:<br>
<br>
- 8 levels randomly selected at the start of each round<br>
- 2+ players in local multiplayer<br>
- An easy access Quit Game button so you can go run conveniently timed errands before your friends catch up to your score<br>
- Melee weapon that can be thrown as a projectile (or left on the ground like a spike trap in one of those dimly lit parts of the map)<br>
- Movement in 8 directions<br/>
<br/>
P.S. You will be unarmed after throwing your lance. You'll have to go pick it up or lead the enemies to your lance sitting on the ground.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SE VR World Demo</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1142180/SE_VR_World_Demo/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1142180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a playable technology showcase that introduces game mechanics, in this VR project. This game (technology showcase) will serve as the basis of the VR game system for separate new game.<br/>Game will be <strong>adventure game with a story</strong>, only single player.<br/>A lot of game stuff like models, textures, sounds are from original game <strong>Space Engineers</strong>.<br/><br/>Player will playing with 2 characters alternately, one as Engineer and second as Policeman on space station.<br/><br/>The Engineer will mainly manually repair various devices. The Policeman will assist the Engineer and have weapons available to protect them from infected Engineers.<br/><br/><br/><br/>This technology showcase is created on <strong>Unreal Engine 4</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Compatibility of VR head sets</strong>: I'm doing it on <strong>Oculus Rift</strong> but it's also compatible with Vive (teleport).<br/><br/><strong>Movement</strong>: In technology showcase is teleport and free movement. Free movement is still WIP. On Vive can be problem with free movement.<br/><br/>This technology showcase is still WIP.<br/><br/><br/>Music in Bar map is from: <strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bensound.com" rel="noopener" target="_blank">www.bensound.com</a></strong><br/><br/><br/><br/>Original <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/244850/Space_Engineers/" rel="" target="_blank"><strong>Space Engineers</strong></a> game<br/><br/><br/>Many thanks to <strong>Remethep &amp; The Tiamat Gaming Community</strong> for support of realization the final release phase.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXIT KUN</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781370/EXIT_KUN/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a game of finding differences and observing. Our game challenges players to carefully observe and spot the distinctions that lead them to the elusive "Exit KUN."<br>
<br>
Game Overview:<br>
<br>
You find yourself trapped in an enigmatic underground labyrinth, and your only goal is to reach "Exit KUN." The journey demands keen observation of your surroundings. Every detail matters, and anomalies could be your key to progress.<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br>
<br/>
Observe Carefully: Scrutinize your surroundings to uncover anomalies that may guide your way or pose a threat.<br/>
Turn Back if Needed: If anomalies are detected, swift decision-making is crucial. Turn back immediately to avoid unforeseen consequences.<br/>
Forward Momentum: Should your observation reveal no anomalies, press forward. <br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Developer Notes:<br/>
This game is inspired by Exit 8. You are free to create, upload, and monetize videos and other content featuring Game on platforms such as YouTube, Twitch, and other video-sharing websites. The characters, places, and elements involved in the game are fictitious. Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, or events is purely coincidental.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Path</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2736350/Home_Path/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Home Path is a rogue-like Game where you have to help the Slime to Reach her Home. You have to survive 10 floors and help the little girl to not be hungry.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736350/extras/gif1.gif?t=1707048493"><br/><br/>Get Random power-ups when you travel to the next Floor.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736350/extras/gif2.gif?t=1707048493"><br/><br/>The floors are randomly generated so every playthrough has a new layout.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Lone Wolf</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684410/Star_Lone_Wolf/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							To learn more about 'Interstellar Lone Wolf' and its game information and benefits, join the official QQ group: 219926703.<h2 class="bb_tag">Craft Your Own Genre</h2>      Spaceships, modules, talents, and items come together to create this world of endless possibilities. The spaceship determines the foundation, modules define the framework, and items flesh it out. Talents empower your genre to take shape smoothly. You'll need to combine your own genre by choosing the ship model, equipped talents, purchased items, and upgrading different modules.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684410/extras/角色选择短.gif?t=1707046756"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684410/extras/模块选择短.gif?t=1707046756"><h2 class="bb_tag">Battle</h2>       In 'Interstellar Lone Wolf,' your spaceship will automatically search for and engage enemies in combat. Your primary task is to evade enemy collisions and incoming fire. Upon defeating enemies, they will drop crystals, which you can collect to gain experience points. When your experience bar is full, random module upgrade options will appear. Upgrading different modules will yield vastly different effects, and these upgrades shape the framework of your genre.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684410/extras/升级选择短.gif?t=1707046756"><h2 class="bb_tag">Side Quests</h2>       To embark on side quests in 'Interstellar Lone Wolf,' you must become familiar with the map and follow the building indicators at the screen's edges to locate your desired destinations. By visiting various buildings, you can accept different side quests and complete them to earn gold coins, which are crucial for your path to victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684410/extras/击杀任务短.gif?t=1707046756"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684410/extras/缓速任务短.gif?t=1707046756"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gold Factory and Crystal Factory</h2>       For experienced players, it's essential to learn how to utilize your existing economy to secure future economic growth opportunities. Within the game, you'll encounter two buildings, the 'Gold Factory' and the 'Crystal Factory.' The Gold Factory periodically provides players with gold coins, with production capacity increasing with each upgrade. Similarly, the Crystal Factory periodically supplies crystals, and its production capacity also increases with each upgrade. Each factory can be upgraded to a maximum level of 10. Players must make strategic decisions based on their predictions for the game's progression, determining which factory to upgrade and to what level.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684410/extras/购买道具短.gif?t=1707046756"><h2 class="bb_tag">Main Quests</h2>       Your main objective in 'Interstellar Lone Wolf' is to defeat four Bosses, and the only way to achieve this is by empowering yourself through all the elements discussed above. If your genre isn't well-constructed or you're not earning money quickly enough, progressing through the later stages can become extremely challenging.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684410/extras/金币工厂短.gif?t=1707046756"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684410/extras/晶石工厂短.gif?t=1707046756"><h2 class="bb_tag">主线任务</h2>       击杀四个Boss是您的主线任务，通过上述所有内容，强大自己，是通关的唯一方法。如果流派搭建的不够完善，或者钱赚的不够快，就很难通过后续关卡。<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684410/extras/主线任务短.gif?t=1707046756"><h2 class="bb_tag">GameOver and GameWin</h2>       When you first enter the game, you'll typically face challenges and might fall in battle as early as the second Boss. If you have gaming experience, even the third Boss can pose a significant challenge. Don't worry, whether you win or lose, the game features an evaluation system that assesses your performance and grants you corresponding experience points. Each time you level up, you will randomly receive a talent or unlock a new spaceship. The number of talents you can carry into battle is limited, so you'll need to choose them wisely based on your strategy. Players will gain an additional talent slot at levels 1, 4, and 7, and then every 10 levels thereafter, up to a maximum level of 100.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684410/extras/胜利升级短.gif?t=1707046756"><h2 class="bb_tag">Challenge</h2>       Once you've crafted your own genre and successfully defeated all four Bosses, you can attempt to take on even higher difficulties. The game offers 26 difficulty levels, labeled from A to Z, and it's recommended to start with the lower difficulty levels before progressing to the higher ones. Difficulties can be stacked, allowing you to challenge multiple levels simultaneously. Each selected difficulty level adds a 20% bonus to the final experience earned. If you choose all 26 difficulties, you'll face a monumental challenge that might even turn your previous gaming experiences upside down. The specifics are left for you to explore, and we wish you the best of luck in your endeavors.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684410/extras/难度选择短.gif?t=1707046756"><h2 class="bb_tag">Module Synthesis</h2>       When specific modules reach their corresponding levels, new modules will become available for synthesis. You can check the specific synthesis formulas by clicking the 'Synthesis' button on the pause menu. Module synthesis can even lead to a profound transformation of your genre, but the details are left for you to explore on your own.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684410/extras/合成词条短.gif?t=1707046756"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frog Story : The Power Tongue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2208130/Frog_Story__The_Power_Tongue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2208130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a captivating adventure with a small frog and its powerful tongue, on a quest to gather scattered fireflies and, crucially, seal the shadows of the Dark Toad King. Navigate through a delightful puzzle-platformer world, mastering pushing and jumping mechanics across 96 intricately designed levels.<br>
<br>
Explore the lush Green Marsh, venture into the abandoned Quarry, traverse the icy Watershed, and unravel the secrets within the fortress of the enigmatic Dark Toad King. Each location presents its own challenges and puzzles, adding layers of depth to your quest. Learn new and exciting gameplay elements, and face increasing challenges.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soak &amp; Splash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2051500/Soak__Splash/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2051500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the Soak &amp; Splash! Get ready to sweat, socialize, and have a blast with your friends in this unique game that combines the best of traditional sauna culture with modern party fun.<br>
<br>
First, step into the steamy sauna and feel the heat and humidity envelop your body.<br>
<br>
Once everyone is inside, it's time to start the fun. You can start by whisking each other with broom.<br>
<br>
Feeling competitive? You can also fight with other players with sauna equipment. Or you can simply relax and enjoy the company of your friends, chatting, singing, or telling jokes.<br>
<br/>
Finally, when you've had enough of the sauna, you can cool off in the nearby pool or shower.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, this game is all about having fun, bonding with your friends, and experiencing the unique benefits of sauna culture. So why wait? Download game and get ready to sweat, laugh, and enjoy life to the fullest!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shop Legends</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/982300/Shop_Legends/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/982300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pick up where your adventures left off and embark on a journey of legends...<br>
<br>
Upon your graduation from the most prestigious shopkeeping academy, you received an invitation from your uncle’s best friend, Jacque. Your uncle has mysteriously vanished, leaving the once most renowned shop unattended. Now, it’s time for you to step up and inherit this shop by applying your business acumen to reclaim the shops' status as the most preeminent across the lands. Do you have what it takes to go from zero to hero?<br>
<br>
Immerse yourself in an Idle Simulation Tycoon RPG like no other, where you are tasked with simultaneously expanding a profitable item shop, crafting legendary equipment to gear up visiting customers as well as commanding mighty heroes you've recruited to loot rare artifacts &amp; blueprints to challenge the top ranked shopkeepers!<br>
<br>
~~~~~~~~~<br/>
BECOME A MASTER SHOPKEEPER<br/>
~~~~~~~~~<br/>
◆ CREATE and DESIGN your fantasy item shop with endless possibilities<br/>
◆ CRAFT and FUSE powerful items to sell to visiting adventurers<br/>
◆ TRADE with other shopkeepers to build your fame and wealth<br/>
◆ CUSTOMIZE your shopkeeper avatar to express your own style<br/>
<br/>
~~~~~~~~~<br/>
EXPERIENCE AN EXCITING ADVENTURE<br/>
~~~~~~~~~<br/>
◆ RECRUIT and equip mighty heroes, each with their own unique abilities<br/>
◆ COLLECT epic loot across time limited dungeons and themed events<br/>
◆ TEAM UP with your friends or make new ones to build a prosperous city<br/>
◆ BATTLE bosses and slay titans together to amass fame and fortune<br/>
<br/>
What are you waiting for? All of these adventures and more awaits you–join the millions of players that have already made Shop Legends their home. Prepare yourself for endless adventure as Aragonia anticipates your awakening!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>my eyes deceive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2700780/my_eyes_deceive/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Set over the course of roughly a week, you play as a young girl who has been living in a shelter all her life. The outside world is infected with a deadly disease. Society is in chaos. Fortunately, your papa is protecting you.<br/><br/>my eyes deceive is a first-person psychological horror experience that makes players question their perception and consider whether they can blame themselves in retrospect.<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURING</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A twisted, dark, and engaging narrative that gradually unravels itself over the course of the experience.<br/></li><li>An experience where you uncover and interpret the story as you play.<br/></li><li>The power of deciding the child's fate. (multiple endings)</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">ADDITIONAL INFORMATION</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Average playtime: 45 minutes (longer if both endings are desired)<br/></li><li>It is recommended to carefully pay attention to your surroundings and every word spoken.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">DISCLAIMER:</h2>Includes sensitive and distressing subject matter, including highly triggering elements such as suggested sexual abuse. It may be deeply unsettling to some players. Individuals who find disturbing content distressing or have experienced trauma related to these triggers are advised to refrain from playing.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Princess Polly</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713560/Princess_Polly/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ahoy, ye daring buccaneers and landlubbers alike! Ready yer sea legs for the legendary saga of "Princess Polly," a thrilling escapade bound to shiver yer timbers! Ye'll join the ranks of a breakdancing ninja, skulking through the shadows of a haunted pirate ship to reclaim the esteemed Princess Polly and her royal kin from the clutches of Captain Pegleg and his peculiar crew—part undead, part lively dancing pirates.<br>
<br>
But beware, me hearties! Venture forth into this eerie vessel teeming with chattering parrots, a fearsome Panther, and Pegleg's menagerie of peculiar creatures:<br>
<br>
Deck 1: Cargo Holds: Shadowy recesses hiding secrets of yore and mysteries unknown.<br>
Deck 2: Bunkhouse: Revelry reigns in the quarters where pirates revel and plot.<br>
Deck 3: Artillery: Beware the newfangled laser security system guarding treasures untold.<br/>
Deck 4: Ballistics: A majestic battle awaits with a mighty Panther and sights of creatures rare.<br/>
Deck 5: Main Deck: Princess Polly awaits in her cage amidst the heart of the ship's turmoil.<br/>
Deck 6: Captain's Quarters: The lair of Pegleg, harboring danger at every turn.<br/>
Deck 7: Pegleg's Perch: Prepare for the ultimate duel with Pegleg himself, a fight to the death!<br/>
<br/>
But 'tis more than a mere rescue! High-maintenance Princess Polly seeks chests brimming with gold to capture her heart. Plunder the treasure, duel with pirates, and ascend the gold leaderboard to claim victory!<br/>
<br/>
Pirate Pegleg, with a taunt upon his lips, challenges ye to try and wrest Princess Polly from his clutches! Can ye navigate the haunted decks, showcase breakdancing ninja prowess, and win Polly's heart? Face peril and outsmart danger in this riveting adventure or find yerself at the mercy of the briny deep! Haha!<br/>
<br/>
Controls:<br/>
Move: A, W, S, D or Arrow Keys<br/>
Sprint: Shift<br/>
Combat: Left/Right Mouse Clicks for sword combos<br/>
Roll: Q<br/>
Interact: E (with chests and doors)<br/>
Walk/Run: 1/2<br/>
Pause: P<br/>
Mute Audio: M<br/>
Quit: Escape key<br/>
<br/>
Remember, should ye lose Stealth, stand motionless for 3 heartbeats to melt back into the shadows. But beware the undead, parrots, and the Panther—eyes sharper than a cutlass! Embark on this perilous voyage, defy Pegleg, and seize victory in the race for Princess Polly's heart! Haha! And don't forget, ye've got nine lives and health packs stashed about each deck to aid yer perilous journey. Aye, onwards, brave souls, for adventure awaits!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Stock Trading Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2612800/Simple_Stock_Trading_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the world of high-stakes finance with our brand-new game, 'Simple Stock Trading Simulator.' Dive into the exciting realm of stock trading, where strategic decision-making is the key to reaching challenging goals and experiencing the thrill of the market.<br>
<br>
In this immersive game, we've designed an experience that's not only thrilling but also incredibly accessible. Whether you're a seasoned trader or new to the world of stocks, our gameplay is simple, easy to learn, and straightforward, making it perfect for all skill levels.<br>
<br>
Harness your inner financial genius as you embark on a journey to test your trading skills. Every move you make matters, and each decision could be the turning point in your pursuit of success. Will you buy low and sell high? The fate of your virtual fortune is in your hands.<br>
<br>
But beware, the stock market is a challenging arena, and it won't always play by your rules. You'll need to adapt, learn from your mistakes, and refine your strategy as you progress. The thrill of the market is in its unpredictability, and that's what makes our 'Simple Stock Trading Simulator' an exhilarating adventure.<br>
<br/>
So, are you up for the challenge? How long will it take for you to reach your financial goals and become a trading master? Only time will tell in this exciting yet straightforward simulation that offers a taste of the real stock market without the risks.<br/>
<br/>
Experience the rush of trading, make wise decisions, and navigate the volatile world of stocks in 'Simple Stock Trading Simulator.' Get ready to embark on an engaging journey that will put your trading skills to the test, all while having a blast in the process. Dive in now and discover the captivating world of stock trading like never before!<br/>
<br/>
Developers Message:<br/>
This is my official first game that I've made. While this is very simplistic, this game did take me awhile to make by myself as an Indie Dev. I hope you enjoy my game and good luck trading.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neocon Tower Defence 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2705900/Neocon_Tower_Defence_3/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2705900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Neocon Tower Defense 3 is a finger-blisteringly action-packed, fast-paced tower defense game that progressively intensifies with each level.<br>
<br>
While the initial stages serve as a gentle introduction to the game mechanics, later levels become increasingly challenging, inundating you with enemy forces from all directions. You'll need split-second decisions to figure out how to counter the relentless and nameless enemy hordes.<br>
<br>
With a selection of 20 towers and 10 add-ons and 24 perks to choose from, there's always a new strategy to try out against the escalating threat.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Owner</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/946670/School_Owner/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/946670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/946670/extras/description_banner.jpg?t=1706990330"><br/><br/><strong>School Owner</strong> is a construction and management simulation game where you manage an entire school, from pre-school to college. It is your job as the owner of the school to build it from the ground up and make sure that the students, employees, parents and even the government are satisfied with your work.<h2 class="bb_tag">BUILD</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/946670/extras/steamgif3.gif?t=1706990330"><br/>You will start with a flat land and random trees that you can chop. From there, you can start designing and developing your school the way you like it.<h2 class="bb_tag">EXPAND</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/946670/extras/steamgif1.gif?t=1706990330"><br/>Expand your lot and have the largest school!<h2 class="bb_tag">Other Key features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hire employees that will build, research, assist, teach, cook, clean, and guard your school.<br/></li><li>Complete control over the schedules of the staffs and students.<br/></li><li>Buy TV advertising, set up a school website, and do other marketing stunts that will help make your school popular.<br/></li><li>Day and Night, Season, and Weather system are integrated into the game.<br/></li><li>If needed, you can take out loans from the bank.<br/></li><li>Keep your students happy and satisfied by tending to their needs.<br/></li><li>Do your "to-do" list and get rewarded.<br/></li><li>Campaign and Sandbox mode</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egg</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2784840/Egg/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2784840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><h2 class="bb_tag">About this game!</h2></strong><br/><br/>&gt; <strong>Egg</strong> is an interactive clicker game where you need to click egg to earn more eggs.<br/><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Features!</h2></strong><br/><br/>&gt; This game supports mouse and keyboard.<br/>&gt; This game supports gamepad (use <strong>A</strong> button on joystick to click).<br/>&gt; This game uses best HD quality textures that is possible to create.<br/>&gt; Runs on every hardware. Even on BESM.<br/>&gt; Supports all screen resolutions.<br/>&gt; Supports Windows 10/9/11 and so on.<br/>&gt; If you don't like the game you can always easily refund it.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Son Of Killwa</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2526270/Son_Of_Killwa/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2526270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2526270/extras/fight.gif?t=1706960565"><br/><br/>Embark on an epic journey of bravery and mystery in "Son of Killwa," an enthralling adventure game that will keep you on the edge of your seat. Immerse yourself in a gripping narrative-driven 3D world, where every twist and turn unfolds a thrilling tale of courage and resilience. Take on the role of a determined protagonist, navigating through a stunning third-person perspective, as intense action and mind-bending puzzles await your skillful hands. Prepare for heart-pounding encounters with formidable foes and delve into challenging enigmas that will put your wit to the test. "Son of Killwa" promises an unforgettable quest where your decisions shape the destiny of the journey. Will you rise to the challenges that lie ahead, or will the shadows of doubt hinder your path to glory? Embark on this unforgettable odyssey, where a myriad of surprises awaits, and let your adventure begin!<h2 class="bb_tag">Riddles</h2><br/>Embark on an enthralling journey of survival, where the power of your mind holds the key to unlocking the secrets of sustenance. “Son of Killwa" beckons you to think smart, think fast, and think sharp, as you decipher spoken riddles to navigate through the treacherous wilderness in search of food and water. The challenges may be daunting, but your intelligence will guide you, providing the crucial edge to overcome obstacles and seize victory. Will you dare to test your limits and conquer the unknown? The adventure awaits, where survival and intelligence unite in an unforgettable quest for triumph.<h2 class="bb_tag">Stealth</h2><br/>Embrace the shadows and hone your stealth in the ultimate test of survival. In “Son of Killwa" every step you take is shrouded in danger as the battle-hardened enemy lurks nearby, keenly attuned to any sound or movement. Engaging in brute force is a perilous gamble against their deadly close-combat rebels and long-range snipers, leaving only the savvy few to consider the art of calculated attack or strategic retreat. The odds are against you, but with nerves of steel and a mind that weighs every move, the possibility of survival beckons. Will you evade their watchful eyes and escape into the night, or will you seize your moment and rise as the elusive victor in this enthralling game of wits and wiles? The fate of your life rests in your hands.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2526270/extras/caught.gif?t=1706960565"><h2 class="bb_tag">Fight Rebels</h2><br/>Prepare to dive into an exhilarating world where every choice is a matter of life and death. In “Son of Killwa" we refuse to strip you of your power; wield the enemy's weapons with deadly precision, from snipers that cut through the darkness to swords that clash in close combat. But be warned, the path of confrontation is fraught with danger, and only the skilled will emerge unscathed. Your journey will force you to confront harrowing decisions: to fight and risk it all or to suffer the slow embrace of starvation. Can you navigate this treacherous tightrope of survival, balancing between life and demise? Your fate lies in your hands, and the world awaits your every move with bated breath.<h2 class="bb_tag">Find Food and Water</h2><br/>In the midst of this gripping tale of survival, you are thrust into a world where every morsel counts. As an ordinary civilian, untrained in the art of hunting and wilderness survival, your lifeline lies in the scarce remnants left behind by the rebels. Tables become your treasure troves, holding the key to sustaining your fragile existence. Yet, the haunting twist of fate in this war-torn realm comes in the form of an IBS stomach condition, a merciless adversary that siphons away your sustenance before it can fortify your body. Time becomes your foe as food slips through your grasp, urging you to embrace resourcefulness and cunning. Every bite is precious, and every decision holds the power to dictate your destiny. Can you muster the strength and intellect to endure this grueling dance with hunger, or will the relentless war within your body overwhelm you? The battle for survival commences, and only the craftiest minds will emerge triumphant in this unforgettable journey of resilience and determination.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build And Craft</h2><br/>Embark on a thrilling adventure where your past expertise as an engineer becomes your secret weapon for survival. Crafting in " Son of Killwa: The Ingenious Quest" is second nature to you, for your engineering prowess unlocks the secrets of resourceful ingenuity. No axes or pickaxes required, for the treasures you seek lie hidden amidst the rebel-held territories. Sharpen your wits, as your imagination and intelligence guide you to unearth the elusive resources needed to build your way to sustenance. Tables, abandoned structures, and concealed caches hold the keys to your salvation, and with every carefully fashioned creation, you inch closer to defying the odds. Can you engineer your path to survival, turning the remnants of a war-torn world into tools of hope, or will the challenges crush your aspirations? The journey of resilience and invention awaits, where the genius of your mind will carve the path to your very existence.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steel Echoes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713390/Steel_Echoes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a chilling odyssey in "Steel Echoes," where a quest for aid takes a nightmarish turn. Stranded with no fuel, you stumble upon a contemporary structure, hoping for sanctuary in the dark expanse. However, as the doors creak open, the illusion of normalcy crumbles, exposing a realm haunted by eerie steel beasts that stealthily pursue your every step. Welcome to a descent into terror where the line between safety and horror blurs.<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br>
<br>
A Desperate Quest for Light: Navigate through the haunted halls of an enigmatic gallery, cloaked in shadows and filled with unsettling whispers. Armed only with a flickering flashlight powered by elusive batteries, uncover the dark secrets that bind you to this malevolent place.<br>
<br>
Steel Statues of Dread: Encounter frozen steel statues that come to life when you gaze away from their eyes. Every step forward is a step deeper into the chilling unknown, where survival depends on mastering the art of avoiding the relentless pursuit of these eerie adversaries.<br>
<br/>
Unravel the Dark History: Piece together the haunting history of the gallery as you traverse rooms adorned with paranormal occurrences. Ghostly apparitions and unexplained phenomena weave a tale of lost souls and unresolved tragedies, intensifying the atmospheric horror that engulfs you.<br/>
<br/>
Multiple Endings: Face the consequences of your choices as "Steel Echoes" offers multiple endings, each with its own brand of horror. Will you escape the clutches of the gallery, or will the nightmarish cycle persist, ensnaring you in its inescapable grasp?<br/>
<br/>
Eerie Atmosphere and Immersive Storytelling: "Steel echoes" weaves a tale of supernatural torment with atmospheric environments, spine-tingling soundscapes, and a narrative that unfolds like a waking nightmare. Every room is a puzzle, and every encounter a test of your courage as you strive to break free from the gallery's relentless grip.<br/>
<br/>
Can You Escape the Unending Night? Challenge yourself to confront the malevolent forces that lurk within the gallery's walls. "Eternal Loop" invites you to experience a harrowing night of horror where your choices shape your destiny. Will you escape the unending night, or will the loop endure for eternity? The answer lies within the darkness – if you dare to seek it.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Strider</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2669210/Space_Strider/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Space Strider is a 2D Sidescroller Shoot 'em up with Roguelite elements, where you beat hordes of enemies and defeat unique bosses. Unlock, upgrade and level up your Spaceships to become the ultimate Space Strider!<h2 class="bb_tag">Introduction</h2><br/>In an unknown galaxy in the distant future, many hostile creatures and renegade factions have controlled and steadily expanded their sphere of influence over the past few centuries, posing an ever-increasing threat to galactic peace. As the elected Admiral of the Alliance for Galactic Peace (AGP), it is your job to hunt down and defeat these creatures and renegade factions to restore galactic peace.<br/><br/>Face off against the Vultures in Blue Horizon, the Red Rebels in the Red Cluster, and the Crawlers in Viridius.<br/><br/>Unlock powerful upgrades and expand your fleet with unique Spaceships.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669210/extras/spaceships_previewtext.png?t=1706954605"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669210/extras/spaceships_animated.gif?t=1706954605"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Unlock and play with up to 10 different Spaceships with each having their own unique weapons</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Level up your Spaceship during a run and choose a PowerUp to make it stronger</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Upgrade your Spaceships with 20 different global Talents</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play in three different levels and beat different enemies and unique bosses</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Increase the challenge with 5 different danger levels</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Roadmap:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>More levels and enemies</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>???</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Ask The Cube Where To Go</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2789060/I_Ask_The_Cube_Where_To_Go/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2789060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(Using translator)<br/>*Photosensitive epilepsy warning: This Game has high brightness or rapidly changing lens effects.<br/><br/>I Ask The Cube Where To Go is a suffer parkour game, you will face brief falls and repetitive, lengthy, bumpy roads.<br/>-When you start the game, you will see a cube, which is very common.<br/>-When you press WASD or rotate the joystick, you can see the cube moving, which is a very common operation.<br/>-The goal of the game is on the mountain in front of it, which is a very common design.<br/>The cube is actually just rotating, using its own edges to pry and move itself.<br/>You can view the cube from a third or first perspective, or any other way you wish, but it's not that important, just like you don't care what the cube will see you as.<br/>This game should not be as difficult or interesting or good as other similar games.<br/><br/><br/>-----------------------------------<br/><i> <strong> Self rating: 8/10 </strong> </i><br/><br/>—— Bilibili：危途异客						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labyrinthian Lockdown</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2778230/Labyrinthian_Lockdown/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Lay down your Defences.<br>
Summon the Militia from the other side to assist you.<br>
Collect scrolls from the enemy and turn the tables with the power within them.<br>
Upgrade your Defences both inside the Labyrinth and out.<br>
Further increase your capabilities of your arsenal with the Masteries.<br>
<br>
Labyrinthian Lockdown is a Tower Defence based game that revolves around a Labyrinth that suddenly broke through the surface in a village in the Kingdom of Klondor and now dispenses forces from within in an attempt to claim the land around it's entrance. The Labyrinth will change upon each and every delve, never being the same as previous entries. <br/>
<br/>
Dive into the Labyrinth and protect the Kingdom by defending your Mana Crystal as it is what powers your means of defence that being the power of the elements, one means of defence will be your towers, each one capable of manifesting an elemental projectile allowing you to defeat your foes, another one being the ability to summon units from the Militia from the surface that are mainly used to slow down the enemy while the towers handle the damage, lastly the spell scrolls that have a chance to drop from enemies may be a game changer if applied correctly.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marmargee Fighter Girl vs. Zombies &amp; Monsters!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2784590/Marmargee_Fighter_Girl_vs_Zombies__Monsters/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2784590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Marmargee Fighter Girl and her best friend Matmateo Fighter Boy are Astral Undine, Masters of the Vortex.<br>
Zombies and monsters have launched a surprise attack from space devastating the blue planet of Taetania, their homeworld! <br>
Luckily Marmargee and Matmateo were able to escape...<br>
Other worlds are now being invaded by these zombies and monsters and are crying out for help! Will Marmargee be able to stop them? Perhaps with the help of Matmateo?<br>
<br>
In this simple low-poly runner style game, you can rerun through 10 unique worlds at 3 speed difficulty levels and have fun destroying different types of Monsters and Zombies... Watch out though for obstacles and traps!<br>
Replay to increase your level or overall score!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cargo Duty</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2766480/Cargo_Duty/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							'Cargo Duty' is a goofy horror resource management game. Keep an eye on your ship and don't let any creatures in.<br>
<br>
Cargo Duty is a multiplayer game up to 6 players. You and your friends go from moon to moon collecting cargo. There are creatures that will try and stop you. Use the countermeasures on the ship to get rid of any unwanted attention.<br>
<br>
How long will you survive ?						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abandoned Village Walking Group</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2644840/Abandoned_Village_Walking_Group/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2644840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"There I saw ----<br>
something that shouldn't be there, or I saw what I've always wanted."<br>
<br>
Takanori Nagami is a college student who goes to an abandoned village that has recently become the subject of rumors as part of his circle's activities.<br>
He discovers a strange torii gate with his junior student Mine Honnoji.<br>
What appears there is a young girl in a strange atmosphere, dressed in a Chihaya costume.<br>
<br/>
The two of you are candidates for sacrifice .......<br/>
<br/>
However, he was also a freak who wanted to desecrate the mystery.<br/>
The village custom and the mystery of the sacred tree. An arson attack on the village for no particular reason. The day of the festival is approaching. Arson. The battle for the salvation of mankind by the cursed village begins now.<br/>
<br/>
The game is a horror story in the form of a visual novel.<br/>
This is a horror adventure game in a visual novel style.<br/>
The estimated playing time is about one hours.<br/>
The main character can set fire to the village at any time he likes!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance Work | 監視業務</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2793240/Surveillance_Work/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2793240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Overview</strong><br/>"Surveillance Work" is a horror spot-the-difference game where you monitor surveillance camera footage <br/>to discover and report anomalies.<br/>There are two things you do:<br/>・Monitor by switching between multiple surveillance cameras installed in the facility.<br/>・Report any anomalies you find.<br/><br/>There are two reporting methods:<br/>'Direct Report', which reports by clicking on an object, and <br/>'Situation Report', which reports the type and location of the anomaly.<br/><br/>Anomalies can range from objects increasing, disappearing, or moving.<br/>Some anomalies may interfere with surveillance systems such as surveillance cameras and reports, <br/>or may attempt to destroy surveillance cameras, so a calm response is required.<br/><br/>There are two conditions for game over:<br/>・Excessive anomalies appear within the facility.<br/>・Even one surveillance camera is destroyed by an anomaly.<br/><br/>Work starts at 0:00 and ends at 6:00 in the morning.<br/>Please carry out the work until the end time.<br/><br/><strong>About Story</strong><br/>You have been appointed as an observer for "Specific Facility Surveillance Work".<br/>Your ability to work as an observer will be assessed through a five-day probation.<br/>After the work is completed, we will pay you according to the number of anomaly reports and false reports.<br/>Please manage your expenses such as housing and food expenses based on your salary.<br/>Your future will be determined by your work ability and other factors.<br/><br/>In Story, you will monitor five facilities in order.<br/>You can continue the story even if the game is over.<br/>You can see the ending after completing probation.<br/>More than 20 different endings are available.<br/>Some endings give you information about the main character, work, and anomalies.<br/><br/><strong>Postscript</strong><br/>・You can select 30 minutes (default) or 15 minutes (half) for the work time.<br/>・There are about 90 anomalies in each facility.<br/>・Once you finish the story, you can select the difficulty level, adjust the frequency of anomalies, <br/>　and retry. You can also play Training mode.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subluminal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1594110/Subluminal/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1594110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Subluminal</strong> is a 3D car driving platformer about gaining speed and going fast.<br/><br/>Vehicles have precise maneuverability allowing you to jump in the air and manipulate your orientation to drive on all surfaces.<br/><br/>All vehicles are equipped with a space displacing mechanism known in Subluminal as a space displacing mechanism or SDM to propel the vehicle forward.  This not only allows you to gain speed, but provides aerodynamic control and the ability to conquer any imaginable path.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Free To Play</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Single Player:</strong> Achieve the fastest time possible, in an elaborate course, with elements that allow you to traverse off the conventional path and  into the air.  As you complete more courses, the difficulty rises; forcing you out of your comfort zone in order to use all your skill to complete these untraditional courses as fast as you can.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIvolution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668280/AIvolution/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Your base is attacked by rebel robots. Repel them by building defensive towers and a fortified defensive wall. Be smart and distribute resources between installing protective structures and improving them.<br>
<br>
AIvolution is a 3D tower defense game. Show off your real-time strategy and tactics skills in this sci-fi action game. Your task is to survive the attack of hordes of cyborgs until the timer expires.<br>
<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
- Low poly graphics<br/>
- Lots of robots<br/>
- Real-time strategy and tactics						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruction</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2774240/Instruction/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2774240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2774240/extras/Aboutdevelopment.png?t=1706909482"><br/><br/>Instruction is a story based clicker game where you, an employee of a power plant, are tasked with generating power for your city. The powerplant's built in intelligence mentor program, or I.M.P. for short, will help you generate the necessary amount of voltage to fulfill your quota. I.M.P may have developed a little too much of a personality for the powerplant's liking, but don't worry! It's still more than capable of keeping you on track. <br/><br/>In this game you'll be tasked with using different systems to generate power. Each system works differently and can be upgraded to increase your efficiency. Discover each of the power plant's mechanisms, and uncover the story behind your less than friendly companion. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2774240/extras/Gamefeatures.png?t=1706909482"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 300 unique lines of dialogue<br/></li><li>5 different systems to generate power<br/></li><li>Secrets and hidden interactions</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2774240/extras/Aboutdevelopment.png?t=1706909482"><br/><br/>This game was developed as a student project at DigiPen Institute of Technology and was created for educational purposes only. Please check out our publisher page for more information.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
