<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Call to Arms - Gates of Hell: Liberation</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2447590/Call_to_Arms__Gates_of_Hell_Liberation/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<strong>“Soldiers, Sailors, and Airmen of the Allied Expeditionary Force: you are about to embark upon the Great Crusade!”<br/>This DLC introduces the western front action in 1944, featuring the US faction, as well as German western front content.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/01Sherman.gif?t=1701279518"><br/><br/>Be among the first to scale the Atlantic wall and fight your way through the Bocage. <br/>Be the spearhead that breaks the stalemate in the battle of the Bulge. <br/>Re-live the rush to the Rhine bridge, on the road into the heart of Germany!<br/><br/>Or, fight for the Wehrmacht and be the one that leads the counterattacks, the one that stops the breakout. In other words; be the one that defends “Fortress Europe” facing all the classic dilemmas that come with it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/02Beach.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Single Player</h2>The single player campaigns focus on four legendary western front units: the “Liberation” campaign has the 2nd Rangers and the 3rd Armored Division on the US side. Beside 6 single player missions, this DLC also offers 4 skirmishes for the US faction, which are part of the campaign storyline.<br/>In all of the missions, you will find yourself in intense battles on iconic battlegrounds, recreated to the last detail; get a taste of the bitter fighting against fanatical opposition, liberating western Europe step by hellish step. The action will be intense and the immersion will be up there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/03Nebel.gif?t=1701279518"><br/><br/>The German campaign,  “Festung Europa”, has the 3rd Fallschirmjäger division and 116th Panzer division on the German side in 6 intense and compelling missions.<br/>Be the one that commands the Wehrmacht forces on the western front from Normandy to the last battles in the Ruhr pocket. In the German campaign you will enjoy a lot of new content as well! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/04Maps.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer</h2>“Liberation” adds the USA to multiplayer with 20 brand new western front MP maps, and all of the new weapons, vehicles and tanks; it also adds a new German late war doctrine.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/05Mist.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Conquest</h2>For conquest, 25 western front maps are included. These, like other maps, use the unique set of assets we have created to immerse you in the western front atmosphere. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/06wespe.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Visuals</h2>Liberation pushes the boundary of the visuals of the Gates of Hell universe to a new standard, with hundreds of highly detailed environment models, improved destruction for buildings and beautiful environments. To ensure the historical accuracy of our content, we have collaborated with WW2 Armor in Florida, who provided us with vast amounts of valuable documentation and knowledge.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/07Logo.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Content</h2>The Liberation DLC contains:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>10 US single player missions, including 4 US skirmishes<br/></li><li>6 German single player missions<br/></li><li>150+  new US and German vehicles, cannon, ships, aircraft and tanks<br/></li><li>50 new small arms<br/></li><li>500+ new humanskins<br/></li><li>20 new MP maps<br/></li><li>25 new DCG (Conquest) maps<br/></li><li>500+ new editor assets for the western European theater.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MULLER-POWELL PRINCIPLE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2155770/THE_MULLERPOWELL_PRINCIPLE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FeY9JWyTaAm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_discord.png?t=1701271403"/></a><br/><br/>It is a sci-fi story that takes place in the near future. You are Harry Herman, an employee of Delta Laboratories who researches interdimensional traveling. You had been participating in a project that was supposed to benefit all humanity, but something went wrong. Through the gameplay, you will solve various physics-based puzzles using an energy-manipulating weapon, travel across space and time to explore surrealistic universes and find out the dark truth about this project and your connection to it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_gameplay.png?t=1701271403"><br/>Solve various puzzles and trick enemies using physics interactions and your special tool - the Portable Energy Manipulator. <br/><br/><strong>PHYSICS PUZZLES &amp; INTERACTIVE ENVIRONMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/gameplay_physics.gif?t=1701271403"><br/><br/>Many objects in the game can be picked up, brought somewhere, or manipulated in other ways. Whether it's a computer terminal, a box you can carry, or a simple mug on a table. Explore various interactive environments to find clues and return to the riddle with a solution, which in some cases may be several. Nothing was made for you to solve, there's no cube dispenser or an obvious exit door at the end. It's all for you to figure out.<br/><br/><strong>PORTABLE ENERGY MANIPULATOR</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/gif_photongun.gif?t=1701271403"><br/><br/>The device you carry throughout the game can absorb different energy types from the environment and use them to perform various tasks.<br/><br/>Absorbing energy from a particular source will give the gun its’ properties. The heat energy from fire and radiators will melt glass, security cameras can be blinded by a beam of light, and for powering generators, you can take hazardous radiation from toxic puddles scattered across Delta Labs facilities. And of course, you will make an encounter with the quantum entanglement energy - the mysterious power capable of opening rifts between worlds. <br/><br/>Apart from solving environmental puzzles, your device can also be used against various creatures you'll meet in parallel dimensions. Most of the time you can't defeat your enemies; instead, you can use the Manipulator to outsmart or suspend them. Some enemies can be frozen in place using the force field energy, while others are sensitive to light and can be distracted by shooting a beam at it in the distance. You will require more advanced strategies and combining various energy types to pass them.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_story.png?t=1701271403"><br/>You find yourself in one of Delta Labs' off-world research facilities in an unknown dimension that looks more like a crashing-down laboratory. Your old friends Eugene and Alex try to connect with you shortly, and with their help, you start a journey through various dimensions. You will learn different physics interactions and meet unusual creatures on your way home. Along this, you have to unveil the mysteries of this project and your past. <br/><br/>Experience a non-linear story where your choice always matters. Can you get to the bottom of this, or just try to escape? Who to listen? Who to trust? Which side will you take? And will you finally “break the Principle”? That depends entirely on you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_setting.png?t=1701271403"><br/>Make your way back to Earth through mysterious parallel dimensions littered with puzzles and secrets, uncover mysterious connections between the worlds you visit, and reveal the dark truth about Delta Labs and your involvement with them. Dare to explore?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_features.png?t=1701271403"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Solve various physics-based puzzles<br/></li><li>Unique gameplay mechanics that involve an energy-manipulating weapon <br/></li><li>A mix of sci-fi with surreal and esoteric themes makes the game setting a unique design. Most of the time you'll spend in bizarre alien dimensions<br/></li><li>Deeply thought-out story and lore. Each location and each character in the game has its own story revealed through various notes, environmental narratives, and characters' conversations.<br/></li><li>The game features multiple endings that can be achieved through different choices </li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn around immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Other</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destiny 2: Season of the Wish Silver Bundle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2218002/Destiny_2_Season_of_the_Wish_Silver_Bundle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2218002/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Purchase the Season of the Wish Silver Bundle and receive the 'Brave Explorer' Legendary Emote along with 1700 Silver (1,000 + 700 bonus Silver) which you can use to purchase Season of the Wish, cosmetics, and more! <br>
<br>
Visit the Seasons tab in-game to use your Silver and buy Season of the Wish.<br>
<br>
To unlock your new Emote, visit the Special Deliveries Terminal in the Tower.<br/>
<br/>
One-time purchase only available during Season of the Wish. Silver is an in-game currency used at the Eververse store.<br/>
<br/>
Season of the Wish not included with purchase.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead by Daylight - Chucky Chapter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2656010/Dead_by_Daylight__Chucky_Chapter/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Main_Banner.png?t=1701272232"><br/> <br/>Meet your new best friend ‘til the end. Dead by Daylight: Chucky brings an iconic horror legend into The Fog with a new Killer: <strong>The Good Guy - Chucky</strong>. Purchasing this add-on unlocks an <strong>exclusive Charm: Good Guys Box.</strong> <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Killer_Power.gif?t=1701272232"><h2 class="bb_tag">CHUCKY</h2>Viciously cruel with a cutting sense of humor, Chucky is a brutally effective killing machine. Using his diminutive frame to his advantage, he’ll pop up when Survivors least expect it, chasing them down and introducing them to his trusty weapons.<br/> <br/><strong>Chucky’s Power: Playtime's Over </strong><br/><br/>The Good Guy is the first Killer in Dead by Daylight to feature a third-person camera.   <br/><br/><strong>Special Ability – Hidey-Ho Mode:</strong> When Chucky enters Hidey-Ho Mode, he becomes Undetectable and generates Map-wide footfalls, disorienting Survivors. Though Hidey-Ho mode can be entered at any time, it does have a cooldown.   <br/> <br/><strong>Special Ability – Scamper:</strong> While in Hidey-Ho Mode, Chucky can Scamper under a downed Pallet or through a Window, allowing him to quickly gain ground.   <br/><br/><strong>Special Ability – Slice &amp; Dice:</strong> While in Hidey-Ho Mode, Chucky can sprint and lunge forward to Slice &amp; Dice Survivors. This attack can be held, but Chucky will be unable to do anything else during this time. If a Survivor tries to Vault a Window or Pallet while you’re charging a Slice &amp; Dice attack, Chucky can quickly chain into a Scamper.   <br/> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Killer_Perks.png?t=1701272232"><br/><br/>Chucky comes with <strong>3 new perks.</strong><br/><br/> <h2 class="bb_tag">Hex: Two Can Play</h2>When a Survivor Stuns or Blinds you a number of times, a Dull Totem becomes a Hex Totem. When that Hex is active, Survivors who stun or blind you are Blinded for 4 seconds. The Hex effects persist as long as the related Hex Totem is standing.<h2 class="bb_tag">Friends ‘Til the End</h2>You become Obsessed with one Survivor. When you Hook a Survivor that is not the Obsession, the Obsession becomes Exposed and reveals their Aura for a brief duration. If you Hook the Obsession, a random Survivor will scream, reveal their position, and become the Obsession.<h2 class="bb_tag">Batteries Included</h2>When within the vicinity of a completed Generator, gain Haste. The movement speed boost lingers for a brief duration after you leave the Generator’s vicinity.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Exclusive_Item.png?t=1701272232"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXCLUSIVE CHAPTER ITEM: GOOD GUYS BOX</h2>The Chucky Chapter includes an exclusive item, the <strong>Good Guys Box Charm</strong>, only available as part of the DLC. Please note that this item cannot be purchased separately.<br/><br/><br/><i>His name is Charles Lee Ray. Chucky to his friends... You’ll be his friend ‘til the end, right?</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1701242352"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1701242352"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1701242352"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noctuary</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2143680/Noctuary/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/英文_大标题.png?t=1701172317"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/1奇光异彩_英文.png?t=1701172317"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/英文_主角介绍.png?t=1701172317"><br/><br/>Noctuary is a dual-protagonist Visual Novel. Players can play the role of the duo, Fancia Dream and Alina Nightsong who have dreams of "becoming Arborangers who protect and serve everyone." Travel through the fairy-tale-like world as the duo, experience their lively daily adventures, and gradually encounter the life story of a mysterious girl who came down from the sky.<br/><br/>Meanwhile, don't forget to fight against the everpresent monsters—"Darkritters!" These dangerous enemies threaten the life of Illuminators constantly. Sharpen your fighting skills, defeat ferocious monsters and ensure peace in your community!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/2华丽战斗_英文.png?t=1701172317"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/ARPG01_英文.gif?t=1701172317"><br/>During your adventure, you will fight against various enemies. You can defeat them with a cascade of powerful combo attacks!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/ARPG02_英文.gif?t=1701172317"><br/>The two main characters master different skills and present various fighting styles, which allows you to win a battle in whichever method you choose. Switch between the two girls in battles to cope with enemies' attacks and finish them off with the powerful On-field Switch skill and the Synergy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/3任务选择_英文.png?t=1701172317"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/Quest01_英文.gif?t=1701172317"><br/>Embark on various missions within Inlixaland and become a unique "Arboranger."! In addition to the main storyline that spans several tens of hours, there are also over 20 side routes and quests featuring different stories and characters to explore. Join forces with diverse Illuminators as companions, cultivate relationships, and earn adventure rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/4祝福标题_英文.png?t=1701172317"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/Blessing01_英文.gif?t=1701172317"><br/>The friendships and blessings you harvest along the journey will strengthen you in battle. Feel free to combine the "Blessing Petals" that are embedded with features of different characters to customize your battle style. In addition, there are many other well-designed cultivation systems that are ready for you to explore!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/感谢尾图_英文.png?t=1701172317"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retro Commander</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/338820/Retro_Commander/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/338820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/338820/extras/icon_and_text_v05_-_600x195px.png?t=1700862195"><br/>Retro Commander is a <strong>post-apocalyptic</strong> real-time strategy wargame (RTS). Take command and fight it out in a world where a cataclysmic timeline has transpired on Mother Earth. Wage wars solo, against the AI, or take on your gaming comrades and friends in cross-platform multiplayer matches. Form teams and clans and fight co-op style with the AI and other players for ultimate victory.<br/><br/>As opposed to other real-time strategy game, Retro Commander tries to focus on both, a fun <strong>single player</strong> and a thrilling <strong>multiplayer</strong> experience. The game strives to be easy to learn with a modern user interface. Single player comes with skirmish matches against the AI as well as a comic-based <strong>story campaign</strong>. Multiplayer can be played cross-platform and includes a ranking and rating system.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u>Post-Apocalyptic</u>: Real-time strategy (RTS) played in a post-apocalyptic timeline on Mother Earth. The environment includes day-night cycles, rain, snow, wind and solar flare activity.<br/></li><li><u>Story Campaign</u>: Deep campaign and story line of humanity after a cataclysmic event. Factions come with their own specialized <strong>technologies</strong> such as stealth, robots, drones or shields.<br/></li><li><u>Single &amp; Multiplayer</u>: A challenging AI for both single and multiplayer matches with co-op play. Cross-platform multiplayer including <strong>LAN</strong>/internet. ONLINE play comes with an award and rating system.<br/></li><li><u>Play Modes</u>: In addition to regular skirmish matches, the game supports missions such as elimination, survival, <strong>capture the flag</strong>, defense and <strong>battle royale</strong>. Available in both single and multiplayer also are escort and rescue missions.<br/></li><li><u>Structures &amp; Troops</u>: Common troops for land, sea and air warfare is available to all factions. Specialized elements such as stealth, shields, <strong>EMP</strong> weapons, nukes, <strong>portals</strong>, orbital weapons, assimilator and other troops and structures provide for additional variety.<br/></li><li><u>Research</u>: A <strong>tech tree</strong> and research options enable to build specialized structures and troops. A <strong>Tech Snatcher</strong> can be used to steal enemy technology.<br/></li><li><u>Modding</u>: A map editor is included allowing for player-modded maps including player-modded campaigns. All elements including troops, structures, as well as graphics and sound effects, can be modded if desired.</li></ul><br/>Although some troops are shared, the game is trying not to be a generic RTS-games. There are <strong>faction-specific technologies</strong> each with their strengths and weaknesses.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u>GRA Technology</u>: gives access to <strong>stealth</strong> and cloaking. Included are cloaked agents and spies as well as bombers with EMP and nuclear weapons. Available also are snipers and heavy airlifts. Can build uranium fabricators.<br/></li><li><u>ELC Technology</u>: provides <strong>robots</strong>, <strong>airships</strong> and robo dogs. Available also are a mechanic and heavy airlift. Can build stationary EMP-field generators.<br/></li><li><u>IDB Technology</u>: provides <strong>hovertanks</strong>, <strong>drones</strong> including EMP-field drones and drones equipped with napalm weapons. Can build fusion generators for power.<br/></li><li><u>Mayan Technology</u>: consists of <strong>decoy</strong> capabilities. Included are hologram tanks, transformers, dogs and dolphins. Can build <strong>portals</strong>.<br/></li><li><u>Ancient Technology</u>: provides <strong>shields</strong>, EMP soldiers, assimilators and napalm tanks. Can build matter fabricators.</li></ul><br/><strong>Free vs Paid (DLC or in-game)</strong>: The free version includes unlimited access to over 12+ multiplayer scenarios and Chapter 01 of the single player campaign. Purchasing the DLC <strong>"All Maps &amp; Modding"</strong> grants full access to the game. It includes everything for single player including the story campaign, skirmishing against the AI, ONLINE multiplayer or LAN-play with friends and family.<br/><br/><strong>No DRM</strong>: There is no DRM in the game. You <strong>don't need to connected to the internet</strong> to play single player games or the campaign. You don't need to be logged in to play LAN games either. You don't need to login either for WAN games (locally hosted games over the internet), but you will have to work out your router settings and do the appropriate port-forwarding so your friends can connect from remote.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Stars And Time</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1677310/In_Stars_And_Time/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FZzFSRUBXEC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/discordbanner620.gif?t=1701180941"/></a><br/><br/><strong>What would you do if you were forced to relive your failures over and over again?</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam5_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> tells the story of Siffrin and their adventurer friends—a found family bound together by fate in order to end the tyrannical reign of an evil king. But as victory is just within the party’s grasp, a tragedy occurs, the clock resets, and <strong>they have to do it all again</strong>. <br/><br/>As Siffrin’s the only one who notices this loop, each new start wears away at his cheerful veneer, yet he keeps going in hopes he can end this temporal tragedy once and for all.<br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> is a <strong>time-looping RPG adventure</strong>. With each loop, Siffrin gains a new perspective on the world around them, opening up new solutions to puzzles and allowing them to make better choices in conversation. Equip memories as armor, pray to the Change God to improve your team’s capabilities each loop, and challenge deadly foes to Rock, Paper, Scissors as Siffrin seeks the truth.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam4_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Our Adventurers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Siffrin (he/they):</strong> Stressed, depressed, and under duress. (Don’t worry about it. They’re doing fine.) The punmaster protagonist of our neverending tale.<br/></li><li><strong>Mirabelle (she/her):</strong> A caring and nervous housemaiden mysteriously blessed by the god she so ardently follows.<br/></li><li><strong>Isabeau (he/him):</strong> Defender with a heart of gold. Cares dearly for his people and his friends.<br/></li><li><strong>Odile (she/her):</strong> The mature and nonsensical researcher studying…something. (No, she will not tell you what it is.)<br/></li><li><strong>Bonnie (they/them):</strong> Wait a minute, who brought this kid along???</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Save the world through the power of Rock, Paper, Scissors in <strong>strategic turn-based RPG</strong> combat encounters.<br/></li><li>Ignore the limits of time and space to <strong>fix your past mistakes</strong> by repeating the same two days over and over again.<br/></li><li>Equip the <strong>memories you have of your friends</strong> to make your party stronger in combat. <br/></li><li><strong>Watch the fate of this world unfold</strong> as you escape the twists and turns of this endless(???) loop.<br/></li><li>Eat <strong>samossas</strong> with your friends!<br/></li><li>Get heckled by a <strong>cheeky ethereal being of infinite starlight</strong>.<br/></li><li>Pray to a god for good luck in your travels. <strong>You’re gonna need it.</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam2_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/>If any of this interests you, you might also want to play the game’s initial prototype, <u><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1691420/START_AGAIN_a_prologue/" rel="" target="_blank">START AGAIN START AGAIN START AGAIN: A Prologue</a></u>. While you don’t need to play it to understand In Stars and Time, it’s fun to see the game’s roots.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucky Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2404510/Lucky_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2404510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Lucky Hero: A Fantasy Adventure Weaving Wisdom, Exploration, and Strategy! <br/><br/>Welcome to the world of "Lucky Hero"! This is a deckbuilder game that perfectly combines roguelike adventures and strategy. Engage in battles with a variety of enemies by spinning the wheel of fortune, collecting, and combining various symbols and skills!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2404510/extras/Character.gif?t=1701073211"><br/><br/><strong>Character：</strong><br/>3 distinct characters: the hefty Warrior, the elusive Assassin, and the enigmatic Summoner, offering varied gameplay experiences.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2404510/extras/En战士_9个片段2023108181391.gif?t=1701073211"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2404510/extras/En召唤师_6个片段20231081848273.gif?t=1701073211"><br/><br/><strong>Symbol：</strong><br/>Over 300 enigmatic symbols are to be collected. By purchasing and deleting them, you build your strategies against enemies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2404510/extras/2023-10-08_11-50-4920231081851524.gif?t=1701073211"><br/><br/><strong>Skill:</strong><br/>Over 30 active &amp; passive skills. When matched with appropriate symbols, skills leads to different builds.<br/><br/><strong>Enemy:</strong><br/>Unique enemies and Bosses with diverse abilities are to be challenged! They will relentlessly assail you. Some may hinder you in ways you are unable to expect. Observe, study, then beat them with your wisdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2404510/extras/2023-10-08_11-50-492023108185705.gif?t=1701073211"><br/><br/><strong>Area Effect:</strong><br/>Over 10 effects for different areas provide unique experiences for every run! Some positive area effects may lead to a less bumpy road, but a negative area effect often has rewards in store for the brave The decision is in your hands.<br/><br/><strong>Random Event:</strong><br/>The game teems with random events, providing a plethora of surprises and unforeseen developments. Will you stumble upon overnight riches or get stripped to bare bones? Are you daring enough to take a punt?<br/><br/>Navigate your journey with deliberation, collect gold, strategize your builds, vanquish formidable enemies, and liberate your kingdom! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2404510/extras/lkho_steam_store_asset_spin_effect_en.gif?t=1701073211"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Saga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1320140/Small_Saga/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Venture below the streets of London, and you will find the medieval kingdom of rats, mice, moles, squirrels, and shrews known as Rodentia.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G8.gif?t=1700830017"><br/><br/>If the rodents have a cardinal law, it is this: never attack a god. But Verm never had much respect for the rule of law. His tail was stolen by the Yellow God of Death, and now the mouse will have to fight all manner of beasts and titans on his quest to get it back.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G5.gif?t=1700830017"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G1.gif?t=1700830017"><br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Team up with a colorful cast of misfit rodents.<br/></li><li>Encounter awe-inspiring titans. Clash with a swashbuckling water vole, a pious lab rabbit, a poetry-spewing kraken, and many more.<br/></li><li>Meet the hideous vermin who run society, then overthrow them.<br/></li><li>Brandish your tiny weapons in strategic, turn-based combat. <br/></li><li>There is no grinding. Small Saga is a tightly-focused and boss-oriented adventure.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero's Adventure: Road to Passion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1948980/Heros_Adventure_Road_to_Passion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FFPnrtuXddA" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/JOIN_OUR_DISCORD.png?t=1700823813"/></a><br/><br/>In <i>Hero's Adventure:Road to Passion</i>, you commence your journey as an underdog in the tumultuous Jianghu - a vibrant world teeming with martial artists - and are met with a wide array of choices as you navigate your heroic saga. Whether it’s training under a battle-hardened warrior to become a master of martial arts, or following Taoist rituals to reach self-enlightenment, you’re the hero, and this is your adventure.<br/><br/><br/>Play 1.0 Now!<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>[Unexpected Encounters Await]</strong><br/><br/>Throughout your journey, you will run into scripted and unexpected encounters. Perhaps you'll cross paths with an ambitious lieutenant amidst a power struggle at a humble inn, or you’ll run into a retired kung fu master in a nameless village. These will be the experiences you will learn to expect in the ever-changing Jianghu.<br/><br/>Beware, each encounter might associate and change your relationship with the 30+ factions involved in the power struggle in this chaotic Martial World. And remember: every choice you make, every person you befriend (or offend), and every faction you engage will leave a mark.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/Sparring.gif?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[Become the Master of Martial Arts]</strong><br/><br/>Whether you're decoding ancient techniques off a forgotten scroll, or prefer training with a battle-hardened warrior, there’s no correct solution for mastering martial arts. Choose from a variety of weapon types and explore 300+ martial arts skills, the Jianghu will be yours to conquer.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/High-level_Martial_Arts.gif?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[Explore a Living, Breathing World]</strong><br/><br/>In this Wuxia simulator, you'll get to explore 80 cities and villages that bring wuxia to life. Witness how villagers go about their daily routines, and experience the rhythms of ancient Chinese cities.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/Nameless_Village.gif?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[Craft Your Narrative]</strong><br/><br/>To provide an experience where you can embody your own martial spirit, Hero’s Adventure has over 10 distinct endings. Whether you choose to be a noble swordsman, a guardian of the nation, or an agent of chaos, you'll find an ending that aligns with your chosen path in Hero's Adventure. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/武林霸主_1_.png?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[New features that are added in v1.0:]</strong><br/>- New bondable female characters, boosting the total number to 18<br/>- A Homestead system to better manage your recruited characters, inherit your Martial Art and weapons to another playthrough<br/>- 200+ new narrative encounters, and adjusted 400+ of the existing encounters<br/>- New Jianghu Event system ensures your adventure doesn’t end prematurely with major events<br/>- Added duel option against high-rank NPCs for a test of mettle.<br/>- Enhanced customization and upgrades for team characters.<br/>- Early supporters will discover a special accessory as a token of gratitude.<br/>- Controller and steam deck support.<br/>- Steam Workshop 2.0</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Faith</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1274600/The_Last_Faith/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The wicked and the blessed will be judged the same - let nothing stand in your way.<br/><br/>Often brutal, always empowering, The Last Faith is an unholy alliance of metroidvania and soulslike. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/extras/GIF_5.gif?t=1701261553"><br/><br/>The Last Faith thrives on merciless and precise combat, with a huge range of custom executions to perform.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/extras/GIF_4.gif?t=1701261553"><br/><br/>Discover a formidable arsenal of melee weapons, arcane spells, and long-range firearms, allowing you to carve a path your own way. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/extras/KUMISOULS_THELASTFAITH_GIF_02.gif?t=1701261553"><br/><br/>Nonlinear exploration is at the core of The Last Faith. Gorgeous pixel art depicts an imposing gothic landscape. Journey along snow-dusted mountains and castles bathed in moonlight. Discover and upgrade a formidable range of tools for destruction.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/extras/GIF_8.gif?t=1701261553"><br/><br/>Step into The Last Faith’s ravaged world as Eryk, who awakens with no recollection of his immediate past. Soon he will discover he is in a race against time as his mind and conscience begins to deteriorate. His desire for salvation from this affliction sets him on a cursed mission that crosses paths with ancient religions and divinities. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/extras/KUMISOULS_THELASTFAITH_GIF_01.gif?t=1701261553"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naheulbeuk's Dungeon Master</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2005160/Naheulbeuks_Dungeon_Master/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/Reivax_poster_H_en.gif?t=1700585599"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your mission, should you choose to accept it!</h2><br/>Embody Reivax, the servile (or not) steward of the Dungeon of Naheulbeuk. Years before the first incursion of fearless adventurers, you are tasked to build, develop, and populate the wobbly tower. Above all, try not to upset your master, the evil sorcerer Zangdar. Are you up to the task?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_1_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Ascend to days of glory and build the dungeon of your dreams!<br/></li><li>Decorate each room with lots of objects and furniture to attract new patrons and employees!<br/></li><li>Raise your reputation to new heights to become the world-devious dungeon!<br/></li><li>Level up your Tripe adviser reputation to attract new customers to your tavern!<br/></li><li>Display your most precious treasures to earn their benefits! Protect them from jealous neighbors!<br/></li><li>As you grow, unlock new dungeon levels to expand and diversify!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_2_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/></img></li><li>Hire less useless personnel to work, defend, raid, and serve the evil Zangdar.<br/></li><li>The world of Naheulbeuk is inhabited by various and unusual species, each with perks and skills – can you manage them?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_3_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/></img></li><li>Manage the expectations and the needs of your fellow minions to reveal the best or worst of their capabilities!<br/></li><li>Upgrade them to improve their workflow and their satisfaction!<br/></li><li>Deal with strikes and other acts of insubordination the way you like!<br/></li><li>Handle Zangdar frustration to secure your fragile position!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_5_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/></img></li><li>As your dungeon grows and improves its reputation, defend it against adventurers!<br/></li><li>Build treacherous traps and artifices to catch raiders and seal their fate!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_6_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/></img></li><li>Offense is the best defense – send your minions to loot and raid neighboring dungeons!<br/></li><li>Want to eliminate the competition? Send your mercenaries and guards on incursions all around the land of Fangh!<br/></li><li>Many factions exists in Naheulbeuk, try not to frustrate them to much or face reprisals!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_4_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/></img></li><li>Production is key to thriving and achieving a monopoly, so you will need to generate numerous resources to flood the market!<br/></li><li>Tools, weapons, compost, intel, astral energy, and more! Stock or sell them to gain advantages!<br/></li><li>Use the Crac 40 wisely to prosper! <br/></li><li>Unlock the market, giving you access to new items and artifacts!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header_alt_assets_2.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astral Ascent</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1280930/Astral_Ascent/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Astral Ascent is a 2D platformer rogue-lite game set in a modern fantasy world. As one of 4 Heroes with very different personalities, you must escape from <i>the Garden</i>, an astral prison guarded by 12 powerful and vicious bosses, the Zodiacs.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CREATE YOUR OWN PLAYSTYLE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Gif_playstyle.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Unlock dozens of unique spells for your 4 distinct characters. Optimize your own build or try out new ones to take down 12 powerful bosses. Get stronger with time to match up with your foes. Each run will test your skills and your reactivity.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TWELVE ALMIGHTY BOSSES TO FACE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Zodiacs.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The Zodiacs are 12 experienced guardians dispatched over 4 gorgeous worlds. They’ll bring to the battlefield unique attacks, abilities, and patterns, backstories to uncover, and reasons to be fighting you. Get yourself warned!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>4 PLAYABLE CHARACTERS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/4_Character_banniere_steam7.png?t=1700851162"><br/><i>Unique characters. Unique weapons. Unique ways to play.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Ayla:</strong> The sole survivor of her guild of assassins, she uses her twin daggers to eliminate her enemies before they can react. Her speed and proficiency are unmatched.<br/></li><li><strong>Kiran:</strong> This orphan learned life the hard way. He uses his strength to deliver attacks powerful enough to create shockwaves. Brutal.<br/></li><li><strong>Calie:</strong> This talented sculptor wants her freedom back. She will use her magical gemstones to pierce enemy defenses and shred them to bits. She is unforgiving.<br/></li><li><strong>Octave:</strong> Trained by a powerful witch, this young fighter summons ethereal guns to attack his foes. When needed, he can conjure bigger weapons as well. Lethal in all cases.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A STORY THAT OPENS UP, ONE PIECE AT A TIME</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/ZimZim2.png?t=1700851162"><br/>Astral Ascent is a rogue-lite infused with narration. Replayability is part of our story which will be unraveled piece by piece. As you get stronger, you will discover more about the characters, their motivations, and the secrets of the world they’re trapped in.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>LOCAL CO-OP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Coop.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The weight of destiny is too heavy to carry by yourself? Don’t worry and bring a friend to play in our <strong>two-player co-op</strong> mode. Fight and crush your enemies together in local co-op or online using the <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/remoteplay?snr=1_614_615__1601" rel="" target="_blank"><strong>Steam's Remote Play Together</strong></a> feature.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A VAST, COLORFUL FANTASY WORLD WAITING TO BE EXPLORED</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Panning.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Dash across gigantic landscapes. Explore original and hand-crafted areas. Discover the world created by our artists, with a gorgeous art and frame-by-frame animation.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refind Self: The Personality Test Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2514960/Refind_Self_The_Personality_Test_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							All players approach games in varied ways, making different choices.<br/>No one ever plays in exactly the same way. Indeed, how a person plays can be an indicator of their personality...<br/>And Refind Self is a game where you can learn all about that personality.<br/><br/>One play is about one hour.<br/>Just enjoy this simple test during your busy time.<br/>And the third time test will show all your personalities, where the end of the story is also not far away.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/NormalScene.gif?t=1700145463"><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2>You are an android. The story begins with you standing at the grave of the Doctor who created you. The world is populated by robots in various forms, created for numerous purposes.<br/><br/><br/>Travel to places key to your memories of the Doctor, interact with the robots, and unravel the secrets behind the future the Doctor sought and what you were entrusted with.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/ConversationWithRobot.gif?t=1700145463"><h2 class="bb_tag">Important Characters</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/CR_Player_Normal.png?t=1700145463"> <strong>[Protagonist]</strong><br/>The player, a robot created by the Doctor as an EAI: an AI that can take action based on emotions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/CR_Daru.png?t=1700145463"> <strong>[Dull]</strong><br/>A robot clerk at the café. Always lazy due to misconfiguration by the Doctor.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/CR_GOGOscrap.png?t=1700145463"> <strong>[GoGo Scrap]</strong><br/>A robot that collects scraps. Sociable and boylike.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/CR_Inori.png?t=1700145463"> <strong>[Inori]</strong><br/>A shepherd robot created to carry out orders.<h2 class="bb_tag">How to Play</h2>Go wherever you feel like, converse, investigate, play minigames... Simply play as you please. There are no game overs, and there's no right or wrong way to progress.<br/><br/>With each action you take, your personality will be analyzed. Once analysis is 100% complete... Congratulations, you've beaten the game! Your personality results will then be revealed.<br/><br/>If you want to know more about your personality, you can go back to play again and again. Of course, this also goes for those who want to know the truth of the story.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/HowToPlay.gif?t=1700145463"><h2 class="bb_tag">Personality Comparison and Sharing</h2>Your test results are stored in an online database, and you'll be issued a unique results ID. You can share your results ID, and view others' results to compare them with your own.<br/><br/>Perhaps similar personalities mean good compatibility? That's another way of having fun with your results.<br/><br/>*Test result data does not include any personal identifiable information.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/PersonalityComparison.gif?t=1700145463"><h2 class="bb_tag">Examples of Possible Personalities</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/seikakuichirei_en.png?t=1700145463"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirate Fighting Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186400/Pirate_Fighting_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pirate Fighting Simulator is a free multiplayer PVP game developed in Unreal Engine 5 in which you fight other players using typical pirate weaponry. There are also cosmetics that you can unlock, these cosmetics can be either hats, weapon skins or in the form of a title that sits underneath your username. The game also includes emotes so you can absolutely boogie down silly style after destroying an enemy gamer. There are also two gamemodes one being TDM (Team Death Match)) and the second being FFA (Free For All).						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1699642767"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1700646226"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons 4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1643310/Dungeons_4/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Once upon a time in a realm far, far away, everything was lush and green. The unicorns mingled among the trees and the elves and humans lived peacefully in harmony with their surroundings. Yet somewhere at the edge of a clearing half-hidden among the trees, obscured by a rising veil of fog in the hazy half-darkness of a weather-beaten hut, a shape huddles over a large and ominously glowing crystal ball. A mumbling voice sings ancient formulae, urging the swirling glowing mists inside the crystal to part and give an insight into the future.<br/><br/>“All is in flux, nothing seems certain. Come, oh vagaries of space and time, separate the veil and show us what is yet to come”, the voice grumbles with the hint of an eye faintly reflecting the glow in front of its hood. The shape’s audience, only barely visible in the dim light, leans in closer and listens intently. “Time ebbs and flows, forming pools and wrinkles… but when the mists part only vague images rise from beyond the veil. Shhhh—don’t come too close, you don’t want to disturb my delicate magical weavings do you?” The shape, still bent over the orb, mutters and shoos the other back a bit more into the shadows. “Ah, now it seems to be clearing a little. I can see… something… several somethings, hints of voices echoing in the haze. A baby, something happening on Hill Doom and the coming together of the Council of Snots – what could all this mean?”<br/><br/>In a flash, the light reflected in the eye turns red and a distant evil laughter echoes through the woods. Stay tuned for the return of the Soothsaying Evil!</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/dungeons-4.gif?t=1700659806"><br/><br/>The Absolute Evil and its trusted *cough* servant, the Dark Elf Thalya, return in <strong>Dungeons 4</strong> after the events of its fabulous predecessor to bring about their triumph over the forces of good once more.<br/><br/><strong>Build a cozy and comfortable Dungeon</strong> to suit your creatures’ needs and rule over them, then send them out into the Overworld to kindly remind the good people living there that the Absolute Evil rules over their lands. <strong>Gather your Evilness</strong> in new and dynamic ways <strong>and unleash it upon</strong> the lush green forests and plains of <strong>the Overworld</strong> to turn them over to the dark side. But make sure that <strong>your Dungeon is well-secured</strong> by traps and defended by your creatures, for those pesky Overworlders won’t just twiddle their thumbs while you <strong>turn their land into the Absolute Evil’s most pleasurable holiday paradise</strong>.<br/><br/>But what is that noise? <i>“Gold, gold, gold and gems, gold and gems and gold!”</i> The ancient song echoes throughout the underworld, accompanied by the clanging steel of hammers and axes. <strong>The Dwarves have arrived</strong> to claim their share of the abundant resources and together with the Elves and Humans of the Overworld, they send out their raiding parties to find the Dungeon’s heart.<br/><br/>Dungeons 4 keeps the spirit of its predecessor, but everything is now <strong>bigger, better, and with even more dynamic Evilness™</strong>.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-1_EN.png?t=1700659806"><br/><strong>Everything is better with Dwarves™:</strong> The Dwarves have arrived to build their underground strongholds and the hardy little fellows (although they don’t like being called that) compete with the Ever-Expanding Evil for space and resources.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-2_EN.png?t=1700659806"><br/><strong>It makes your Dungeon great again:</strong> Dungeons are up to four times larger than before and there are many more creatures who wait for the All-Commanding Evil’s orders to conquer the Overworld. Now the time has come for massive armies and truly sprawling dungeons!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-3_EN.png?t=1700659806"><br/><strong>Ripe for the taking:</strong> The Overworld is bigger than ever before. Gain Evilness by beating Mini Bosses like the obsessively harmonious Unicorn and use it to transform the Overworld into stunning biomes of pure evil.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-4_EN.png?t=1700659806"><br/><strong>New and shiny:</strong> An ability-based Perk system for Thalya, the Absolute Evil’s trusted *cough* and most loyal subordinate, grants her impressive new powers. The Absolute Evil can now enjoy taking over the world, governing the creatures and slapping subordinates even more with the customizable Evil Hand.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-5_EN.png?t=1700659806"><br/><strong>Minions, everywhere:</strong> The Horde, the Undead and the Demons wait to do the Absolute Evil’s bidding, with more creatures than ever eagerly following the gesturing Evil’s orders, and Snots will play a much more prominent role this time.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-6_EN.png?t=1700659806"><br/><strong>Many ways to tell the story:</strong> A long campaign, narrated by the beloved English Narrator from previous titles, as well as several skirmish maps all to challenge your rule as the Absolute Evil.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-7_EN.png?t=1700659806"><br/><strong>Change the world:</strong> Spread your Evilness across the Overworld to bring lush and green environments over to the dark side, now shining even more vibrantly and beautifully evil as you spread your evilness across many new biomes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-8_EN.png?t=1700659806"><br/><strong>Work together, slay together:</strong> 2-player co-op multiplayer with both players managing one Dungeon together. All maps from the skirmish mode and the campaign are playable in co-op.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colony Ship: A Post-Earth Role Playing Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/648410/Colony_Ship_A_PostEarth_Role_Playing_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/voyage.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/><i>It is the Year of Our Lord 2754…<br/><br/>You will never feel the sun’s warmth under a blue sky, never hear the wind in the branches of a tree, and never swim in the ocean, all because you had the misfortune to be born on the Ship, chained to a fate you didn’t choose. You have never seen Earth and you’ll never see Proxima Centauri either. You’re doomed to live and die on the Ship in the name of the Mission, like your father before you, like his father before him.<br/><br/>The Ship is old. She had already been twenty years in service when she was rechristened Starfarer - a pretty name for a retrofitted interplanetary freighter. No one is certain the Ship will actually reach its destination, and nobody much cares, since no one alive now will live to see it. Might as well get on with your life and try to make the best of it.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/features_header.jpg?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>Colony Ship is an isometric, party-based RPG inspired by Heinlein’s Orphans of the Sky. Your character's world is a “generation ship,” a massive spacecraft on a centuries long voyage to colonize a distant planet. The Ship's original government has been disbanded following a violent mutiny and you must negotiate a treacherous path among your fellow passengers and the contentious factions striving to dominate the Ship. Your choices will determine who your friends and enemies are.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/explore.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/Pit.gif?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>Your adventure starts in the Pit - a sprawling heap of vacant cargo containers slowly getting filled up with those who couldn't afford to stay in the Habitat or needed to get away from its bosses and factions. Out here, folks live free and die fast...<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><i>You open your eyes to a grey hull-metal ceiling, one panel of which flickers yellow, indicating dayshift. You overslept, not that it matters. With a grunt you roll off your stained mattress and open the "window" to let some fresh air in. Like everything else around here, fresh is relative. The Ship does its best to recycle air and water, but cargo holds aren’t high on Her priority list. You breathe in metal and burning oil and look up. Four of the bridge's six projectors are still operational, shining dully down on the container towers of Cargo Hold 3, better known as the Pit, the Free City.<br/><br/>Calling the Pit a city is a bit of a stretch, but so is calling this reddish-brown liquid water. You've read that water is supposed to be clear and cities are supposed to be big, but no ship-born has ever seen either. Maybe in another hundred years water will look and taste like oil and people will be talking about the good old days when it was the color of rust and tasted refreshingly bitter and tangy. That's the kind of optimism that keeps you going.<br/><br/>The elevator crawls up a groove in the cargo hold's wall like a black steel bug that's worn a path traveling to the bridge and back. It’s time to get up there and earn a few credits, but first you need a drink.</i><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/Hydroponics.gif?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>Once tasked with adapting Terran plants and grasses to the alien environment of Proxima Centauri, Hydroponics was abandoned during the Mutiny. Quickly overwhelmed by out-of-control mutant vegetation, it more closely resembles deep jungle than a research complex. In addition to the abnormal plants, oversized pest control species –bioengineered to safeguard the colony's farmlands– are also on hand to punish the careless.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><i>Plants were sacred to the Founding Fathers. They represented our connection to Mother Earth, our sustenance, and our future. Picture rippling fields of wheat, rye, and barley to the horizon, mighty oaks and cedars, children eating apples right from the tree. That was the vision for Proxima.<br/><br/>But they didn't anticipate how many seedlings would fail in the Ship's simulated environments. And unless they found a way to make good those losses, it would be catastrophic. Alien fauna and poor soil were deemed the biggest threats, so they matched the most important plant species with customized, symbiont fungi. The latter were meant to act as pest killers. Unfortunately, the fungus did its job a little too well. We’re the pests now.</i><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/Habitat.gif?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>Before the Mutiny, the rooftops of the Habitat supported a sprawling amusement park. There, the people of the Ship could experience at least a few of the novelties they would never enjoy on Earth or Proxima: walk barefoot on real green grass – courtesy of Hydroponics – or soft, red-tinted 'Proxima' sand; sit under tall, artificial trees; and watch the sunrise on gigantic screens suspended all around. This last was said to be indistinguishable from the real thing, not that anyone aboard had ever seen it.<br/><br/>Nowadays, the three remaining rooftops are heavily fortified platforms, patrolled by armed guards. The sky-screens went dark long ago, a frivolous luxury in a decaying world. The grass underfoot and simulations of golden fields have likewise vanished, replaced by watchtowers and checkpoints. With enemies on all sides, cheap entertainment is a useless distraction from reality and its harsh demands.<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/Mixed.gif?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>The Armory - Among the stars, the children of Earth wish most of all for peace. Nevertheless, the wise prepare for every eventuality – we should not survive long without the means to protect our territory and interests, with violence if every other method is exhausted. To that end, the Ship launched with a wide assortment of peacekeeping weapons and armaments, most of it looted and spent during the Mutiny and the hundred lesser skirmishes that followed.<br/><br/>Mission Control - The century-old wreckage of the Ship Authority government complex that once controlled every aspect of life on the Ship. Now scavengers infest this ancient seat of power, a grim reminder that nothing lasts.<br/><br/>The Shuttle Bay - Noah relied on doves to find a landing place, the Ship carried twelve survey shuttles for that same purpose. Even though the Shuttle Bay survived the Mutiny intact, it was looted in the interim, the life support systems and emergency supplies stripped, and the shuttle interiors used by generations of squatters. <br/><br/>The Factory - An abandoned industrial complex that once worked 'round the clock to produce tools for the Ship and the future colony. Why squander your precious shekels on second-hand Earth machinery, when your captive workforce will have three hundred years to manufacture everything you need?<br/><br/>And many others.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/gain.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/Combat.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>Combat is difficult. You’ll be outnumbered and outgunned, so you’ll have to figure out how to even the odds or avoid fights you can't win. There are 3 main factors determining the difficulty of any combat encounter and your character's life expectancy: Accuracy, Evasion, Damage (both dealt and taken). To succeed in combat, you must learn to control these factors. <br/><br/>Accuracy = 50 + bonuses from (stat + skill + feat + implant + helmet/goggles + weapon). You can easily neglect a couple of items from this list and still be a competent fighter, meaning you don't need to min/max your stats because it's only 1 item out of 6. The attacker's accuracy is further modified by the attack type (different attacks have different pros and cons), the weapon's gun's effective range, and inflicted penalties.<br/><br/>Evasion = bonuses from (stat + skill + feat + implant + armor handling – armor penalty). The defender's evasion is further modifier by cover (the exact bonus depends on the angle), gadget bonus (i.e., using a Disruptor Field), and smoke/spore cloud (smoke grenades and certain critters). More detailed information can be found on the character and inventory screens (which show your accuracy and evasion), and in combat, where you can press ALT when targeting while targeting to learn what is affecting the accuracy of a particular attack.<br/><br/>The damage depends on both the weapon and the target's defense. Incoming damage is reduced by damage resistance (feat + implants + armor) and energy shield (gadget and/or energy armor). Weapons with good penetration and/or aimed attacks can reduce enemy's damage resistance, dealing more damage.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/Stealth.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>When you enter the stealth mode all tiles are automatically assigned detection values, determined by the distance from the guards, which way they're facing, their Perception, and thermal vision gear, if any. Green - safe (you remain undetected), yellow - risky (if you end your turn there, you'll be spotted), red - instant discovery. High sneaking ability (modified by skill, feats, gear) turns more tiles green and opens up more options, whereas a low level thief might see nothing but yellow and red tiles. <br/><br/>Each step and action (lockpicking, climbing, using computers, killing guards in stealth mode, etc) generates noise. Not a whole lot of noise to instantly alert the guards the moment you do something, but enough to add up over time and raise the guards' suspicions. The higher the guards' Perception, the faster the alert bar is filled. An alerted guard turns towards the last noise generated, meaning a lot of safe tiles will turn red and if you're in the line of vision you'll be instantly discovered. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/Dialogue.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>If fighting isn't you thing, you can avoid ALL combat by relying on speech skills: Persuasion, Streetwise, and Impersonate. Not every solution is in your face, but it is there. We check stats, skills, reputation, deeds, and track your choices to deliver appropriate consequences. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/friends.png?t=1701168231"><br/>Ten party members (max party size is 4) and well over a hundred different characters, some less friendly than others. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/001.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/002.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/003.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/005.jpg?t=1701168231"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/008.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/007.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/015.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/006.jpg?t=1701168231"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/harbinger.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/009.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/012.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/010.jpg?t=1701168231"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/016.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/013.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/004.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/017.jpg?t=1701168231"><br/><br/><i>Lord's Mercy was her given name. Though he wasn't a priest, her father had called himself a Man of Scripture, and never tired of reminding his only child of God's wrath, His vengeance, His untiring thirst for retribution. If that’s what her name meant, Mercy did her best to live up to it.</i><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><i>"Are you now?" Bartholomew looks at you with interest. "I assume you were on your way to the Habitat, but now you're stuck here...  Your odds aren't looking good, my friend,” he gives you a salesman's smile. “Attacking the Black Hand's stronghold is suicide, with or without our help. If Stanton loses...” He makes a pause, letting you work it out on your own.</i><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><i>“You may address me as Harbinger. I no longer have a name." The bitterness in her voice is unmistakable. She must not have been doing this Harbinger thing for long. One of the guards removes his helmet to reveal an oddly leathery face with deep-sunk eyes and a lipless mouth. He grins as he savors your discomfort.<br/><br/>“I wonder if the Neanderthals were as shocked by your outlandish appearance,” the woman says. “I wonder if they foresaw their own doom.”</i><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/join.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>A generation ship is a perfect ant-farm where different societies can coexist within a limited space, influencing and affecting each others' development while fighting for that limited space, which adds 'the end justifies the means' pressure. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/protector.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>The Protectors' one truth is the Mission, and the sole way to ensure successful completion of the Mission is to follow the Old Ways. The ways of the fathers, forefathers, and Founding Fathers are together the beam upon which the Ship travels to our ultimate destination. The mutiny, which through their steadfast and timely intervention was thankfully aborted, was the ultimate betrayal of the Old Ways, of everyone who had come before, the nullification of every sacrifice and every life dedicated to the Mission.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/brotherhood.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>The Brotherhood was formed to liberate the people from the iron shackles of the Ship Authority. Though their first sally -which the fossils of the old world denigrate with the term "mutiny"- failed to completely achieve this aim, the Brotherhood was successful in establishing themselves as a power to be reckoned with. The Brotherhood's initially pure goal, to free the enslaved wherever they may be, has unfortunately been sullied by the practical concerns of democracy. To bring freedom to the Ship entire must involve war, and no war may be won without sacrifice, nor may battles be managed by committee.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/church.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>As inevitably happens in dark and challenging times, some citizens turn to God for reassurance, the promise of an end to pain and hunger. Or failing an end, at least a purpose. The Church of the Elect rejected both the Protectors of the Mission and the Brotherhood of Liberty as worldly fools distracted by politics and their own egos. Teaching their adherents that they were chosen by God, the Church frames the journey of the Ship as a centuries-long test of faith. When the Ship arrives at her destination, Judgment Day awaits every citizen. The righteous will be welcomed into the Promised Land of Proxima Centauri, while the unrepentant will be returned to the Hell from which we fled - Earth - to suffer for all eternity.<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"/><br/>Plus lesser factions and groups: People of the Covenant (the mutants), the House of Ecclesiastes, formerly known as ECLSS - the Environmental Control and Life Support System, the Pit's Freemen, Thy Brother's Keepers, the Grangers, Jackson's Riflemen, and more!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"/> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobalt Core</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2179850/Cobalt_Core/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_1.gif?t=1700087396"><br/><br/>Cobalt Core is a sci-fi roguelike deckbuilder with a unique single-axis combat system that will throw you for a loop. Many loops! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_2.gif?t=1700087396"><br/><br/>Give orders to your crew by playing cards: Will you <strong>raise shields</strong> to protect your ship, <strong>dodge</strong> incoming missiles and cannon fire to avoid damage outright, or <strong>strike</strong> preemptively to disable your enemy’s weapons? Outmaneuver your foes to stay just ahead of impending calamity, and reach the Cobalt Core!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/characters.png?t=1700087396"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fresh new spin on tactics –</strong>  dodge attacks and target weak points in this unique single-axis take on tactics combat. Outwit the enemy in a high stakes game of cat and mouse!<br/></li><li><strong>Customize your deck –</strong> hundreds of cards and split upgrade paths means no two runs will be the same. Find that perfect combo that brings your deck from powerful to overpowered.<br/></li><li><strong>Get to know your crew –</strong> each character comes with a completely unique playstyle and their own personal story. Bring 3 along, mix and match their decks, and see how these little goobers get along with each other.<br/></li><li><strong>Tons of replayability –</strong>  hundreds of different character+ship combinations before you even hit “start run”. Crank up the difficulty and really test your skills!<br/></li><li><strong>Forward momentum –</strong> untangle a narrative and unlock more playstyles as you go. Is there any escape from this time loop?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/grandma_cookies.gif?t=1700087396"><br/><br/>By the makers of <i>Sunshine Heavy Industries</i>, recipient of IGF's <strong>Honorable Mention for Excellence in Design 2022</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nickelodeon All-Star Brawl 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2017080/Nickelodeon_AllStar_Brawl_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/ReviewScores.jpg?t=1700669221"><br/><br/><strong>Nickelodeon All-Star Brawl 2</strong> lets you duke it out with the biggest and best fighting character roster yet, including all new characters like SpongeBob SquarePants, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, Squidward Tentacles, Jimmy Neutron, and more!<br/><br/>Choose your favorite brawlers, master their unique move sets, and use all-new powerful Supers to land the finishing blow with friends or across a unique, roguelike player campaign!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/General_GIF-Optimized.gif?t=1700669221"><br/><br/>Featuring:<br/>• <strong>New Single-Player Campaign:</strong> Put your skills to the test as you fight to stop Danny Phantom archvillain Vlad Plasmius from taking over the Nickelodeon universe!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/Campaign_GIF-Optimized.gif?t=1700669221"><br/><br/>• <strong>All-New Gameplay:</strong> New and revamped visuals meets new audio, animations, modes, stages, mechanics, taunts and move sets for all levels of play!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/GameplayRevamp_GIF-Optimized.gif?t=1700669221"><br/><br/>• <strong>Cinematic Supers:</strong> Power up your fighters with incredible new animated supers to deal devastating blows to your opponents!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/CinematicSupers_GIF-Optimized.gif?t=1700669221"><br/><br/>• <strong>New &amp; Improved Brawlers:</strong> Nickelodeon All-Star Brawl 2’s roster is better than ever, with even more variety in how each unique character plays. Battle with brand new Nickelodeon fighters as well as returning fan favorites!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/NewBrawlers_GIF-Optimized.gif?t=1700669221"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stronghold: Definitive Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2140020/Stronghold_Definitive_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2140020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Relive the glory of Stronghold, the original BAFTA-nominated real-time strategy game, with this new definitive edition of the classic 'castle sim'. Witness the game that started it all, carefully rebuilt using the source artwork, remastered music, returning voice talent and veteran developers of the first entry in this legendary series.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2140020/extras/SH_DE_GIF_1.gif?t=1700750260"><h2 class="bb_tag">UNITE A BROKEN REALM</h2><br/>Welcome to the fractured, war-torn frontier of medieval England. With the King betrayed by his treacherous lords and a realm on the brink of collapse, take control of scattered forces and reunite your kingdom against the monstrous Rat, Pig, Snake and Wolf!<br/><br/>Strike down each villainous Lord in missions ranging from breaking sieges and capturing enemy castles to building epic fortresses and repelling enemy assaults. Test the limits of your strategic mind with castle assaults and grand banquets in military and economic campaigns.<br/><br/>Dive into classic RTS and city builder gameplay now elevated with remade graphics, community requested features and remastered music from series maestro Robert L. Euvino. Gather resources, construct mighty castles, protect your townsfolk, manage your gold, raise armies and wage all out war!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2140020/extras/SH_DE_GIF_2.gif?t=1700750260"><h2 class="bb_tag">A LEGEND RETOLD</h2><br/>Building on its 20 year legacy, <strong>Stronghold: Definitive Edition</strong> features two classic campaigns told across 26 missions, alongside fresh single player content in the form of a new narrative campaign designed by Firefly Studios founders Simon Bradbury and Eric Ouellette.<br/><br/>Exclusive to the definitive edition, this new 14 mission campaign sees players march across the devastated English hinterland in search of Sir Longarm's captured kin, before venturing beyond the story in a challenging new historical 'Castle Trail' of 10 unique scenarios.<br/><br/>With remade artwork, a higher fidelity soundtrack, full Steam multiplayer support for 8 players, Steam Workshop, modernised gameplay and more, <strong>Stronghold: Definitive Edition</strong> is the ultimate way to experience the game that started it all. Your kingdom awaits!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2140020/extras/SH1DE-Blacksmith.png?t=1700750260"><h2 class="bb_tag">NEW FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>ZOOM INTO NEW VISUALS</strong> remade by the original artists with improved animations, textures and lighting.<br/></li><li><strong>REMATCH CLASSIC VILLAINS</strong> as you hunt The Rat and The Snake in a challenging new 14 mission campaign.<br/></li><li><strong>BATTLE OLD FRIENDS</strong> on Steam with 8 player multiplayer support and extra maps on which to wage war!<br/></li><li><strong>RELIVE HISTORY</strong> in a new Castle Trail with 10 challenging siege scenarios and famous historical fortresses.<br/></li><li><strong>LOSE YOURSELF</strong> in a remastered soundtrack, with fresh recordings from some of the game's original voice actors.<br/></li><li><strong>CREATE, SHARE &amp; ENJOY</strong> new Stronghold community content with Steam Workshop support.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2140020/extras/addtowishlist.gif?t=1700750260"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2140020/extras/SH1DE-SiegeTent.png?t=1700750260"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658820/Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							10 possible fruits and one goal, reach the Watermelon.<br/>Your job is to combine matching fruits to evolve them to the next one and eventually reach the coveted Watermelon.<br/>To help you, you have 3 different abilities at your disposal. But watch out, using these will cost you some of your points. Be smart about when you use them to get the highest score!<h2 class="bb_tag">GET THE WATERMELON</h2>How many Watermelons can you combine before your basket overflows?<h2 class="bb_tag">USE YOUR ABILITIES</h2>Power, level up and destroy — These abilities will help you reach the Watermelon, using any of those will also allow you to angle your aim.<h2 class="bb_tag">GOLDEN FRUIT</h2>If luck is on your side, you might even see the mysterious Golden Fruit. Find it and witness its effect firsthand.<h2 class="bb_tag">STATISTICS</h2>Track your progress with in-depth statistics. Visit the menu to see the number of fruits you've combined, your ability usage, and much more.<h2 class="bb_tag"></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.codecks.io%2Fwatermelon-game" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/extras/Roadmap_Banner.png?t=1700532981"/></a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On The Brink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2347350/On_The_Brink/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2347350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use Capri's gravity manipulation to slingshot across the universe as she embarks on a mission to liberate a forgotten dimension from the clutches of an all-powerful being. Solve puzzles, uncover mysteries, and shatter space-time itself in this snappy sci-fi action platformer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2347350/extras/DescriptionBanner_01.png?t=1701285825"><h2 class="bb_tag">What lies in the dimensions above our own?</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> An original sci-fi narrative set in the far reaches of the universe following Capri's fight to right cosmic wrongs and save <strong>PROJECT: Almagest</strong>.<br/></li><li> High-speed movement is interwoven with unique puzzle mechanics sure to engage hypothalamuses and prefrontal cortexes alike.<br/></li><li> Galaxy distribution across the universe is dynamic and infinite. Stay conscious, or be lost in the infinite aether.<br/></li><li> <i>On The Brink</i> has subtitles available alongside controller support for both Windows and Mac OSX. <br/></li><li> Recommended for third-dimensional beings. Playable in the second dimension, with decreased performance.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stream Slugger</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2218430/Stream_Slugger/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2218430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							This desktop application is a transparent application.<br/>Which will entertain you while working.<br/>Together with an active Twitch account you can let friends spawn their 3D character on your desktop.<br/>Even when you aren't live on Twitch just use the chat.<br/>This can lead in hilarious situations and you will never feel alone when streaming or working for school.<br/>During a live stream the characters can fight or just hang out on your screen.<br/>Level them up  so the characters get super powers!<br/><br/><strong>Please note:</strong> that this program utilizes an API from Twitch.<br/>Before using the program, please review Twitch's API policies and guidelines at:<br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fsafety.twitch.tv%2Fs%2Farticle%2FCommunity-Guidelines" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://safety.twitch.tv/s/article/Community-Guidelines</a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2Fp%2Fen%2Flegal%2Fprivacy-notice%2F%23authentication-and-log-data" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.twitch.tv/p/en/legal/privacy-notice/#authentication-and-log-data</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kraken Odyssey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2112260/Kraken_Odyssey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2112260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2112260/extras/texte2.png?t=1701274360"><br/>Dive headfirst into this 3D action/racing game, run at full speed, jump to avoid dangers and hit the finish line! More than thirty different levels await you, with missions and medals to earn at each level. You won't be short of challenges!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2112260/extras/2023-05-17_16-19-20.gif?t=1701274360"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Help Voulpy in his adventure! </strong></h2>His little brother has been kidnapped and it's up to you to travel through various worlds to find him! Beaches, jungles, snowy mountains, flaming dungeons, but be careful not to end up as crab bait...<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2112260/extras/course.gif?t=1701274360"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Become the coolest kraken on the islands!</strong></h2>The game has a multitude of costumes to unlock, pirate or unicorn - it's up to you to choose.<br/>So if you love octopuses, the beach, and adventure, set out on an adventure in Kraken Odyssey!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2112260/extras/skins.gif?t=1701274360"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2112260/extras/essai.png?t=1701274360"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flat Spot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2459820/Flat_Spot/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the <strong>casual motorsport management</strong> game of the year!<br/><br/>Experience motorsport like never before: <i>very simple</i>. In this exciting, fast-paced management game you can be team principal of your own team, <strong>upgrade</strong> your car with newly built parts and <strong>sign new drivers</strong> to compete in races and win the championship. Use your drivers <strong>special abilities</strong> to gain an advantage over other drivers on track and leave them in the dust.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Build <strong>randomly generated car parts</strong> that suit your purpose! </li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459820/extras/FlatSpot_CreateCarPart_RearWing_480px.gif?t=1701272955"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Customize</strong> your car for each race! </li><li>Handle <strong>fun encounters</strong>off-track! </li><li><strong>Special abilities</strong> and strategy decisions, all in <strong>your hand</strong>!</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459820/extras/FlatSpot_UseSpecialAbility_AdrenalinRush_480px.gif?t=1701272955"><br/><br/><strong>See you on track!</strong> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All of Us Are Dead...</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2177170/All_of_Us_Are_Dead/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2177170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							All of Us are Dead - The Visual Novel<br>
An interactive, visual novel based on the hit webcomic series. <br>
<br>
◆ Story <br>
Summer. July. Zombie virus breaks out in Hyosan High. Friends and teachers become infected, and many can't bring themselves to take down the infected. They were friends and teachers, after all. Soon, the entire school is infested with zombies with no way of escape. <br>
Experience the struggles of ordinary students as they juggle extraordinary challenges. Join the jocks as they face overwhelming odds while fighting for their survival. Be wary of the terror that lies within the school for zombies were not the worst of their troubles. See how each and every one survives in their own, unique way.<br>
<br>
◆ All of Us are Dead: The Visual Novel <br/>
- Based on the hit webcomic of which the live-action drama series 'All of Us are Dead' is based on. Discover wholly new content untold in other adaptations! <br/>
- All new events, endings, and more! Watch where your decisions take you and see how they unfold. <br/>
<br/>
◆ Artworks <br/>
- All new character artworks are made to reflect every character's individual personality. <br/>
- Persistent artwork. Any encounters or events that affect the character persist in the artwork, even as the story progresses!<br/>
<br/>
◆ High Quality Illustrated Events<br/>
- 100+ high-quality illustrations for maximum drama.<br/>
- Animated events!<br/>
<br/>
◆ Fully voiced in Korean<br/>
- 12+ hours of fully voiced scenarios.<br/>
- Voice-over<br/>
Lee Bohee, Park Seongyeong, Ryu Seung Gon, Lee Kyung Tae, Song Harim, Mun Yujeong, Kim Na Yul, Seo Da Hye, Kang Si Hyun, Ahn Hyomin, Kim Young Sun, Kim Hye Sung, Jang Mi, Choi Seunghun, Jang Ye Na, Shin Beomsik, Park MinGI, Bang SiU, Kim Jin Hong, Lee Eun Jo, Jung Eui Jin, Lee Myounghwa, Sung Ye Won, Jung Ui Taek						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MULLER-POWELL PRINCIPLE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2155770/THE_MULLERPOWELL_PRINCIPLE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FeY9JWyTaAm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_discord.png?t=1701271403"/></a><br/><br/>It is a sci-fi story that takes place in the near future. You are Harry Herman, an employee of Delta Laboratories who researches interdimensional traveling. You had been participating in a project that was supposed to benefit all humanity, but something went wrong. Through the gameplay, you will solve various physics-based puzzles using an energy-manipulating weapon, travel across space and time to explore surrealistic universes and find out the dark truth about this project and your connection to it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_gameplay.png?t=1701271403"><br/>Solve various puzzles and trick enemies using physics interactions and your special tool - the Portable Energy Manipulator. <br/><br/><strong>PHYSICS PUZZLES &amp; INTERACTIVE ENVIRONMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/gameplay_physics.gif?t=1701271403"><br/><br/>Many objects in the game can be picked up, brought somewhere, or manipulated in other ways. Whether it's a computer terminal, a box you can carry, or a simple mug on a table. Explore various interactive environments to find clues and return to the riddle with a solution, which in some cases may be several. Nothing was made for you to solve, there's no cube dispenser or an obvious exit door at the end. It's all for you to figure out.<br/><br/><strong>PORTABLE ENERGY MANIPULATOR</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/gif_photongun.gif?t=1701271403"><br/><br/>The device you carry throughout the game can absorb different energy types from the environment and use them to perform various tasks.<br/><br/>Absorbing energy from a particular source will give the gun its’ properties. The heat energy from fire and radiators will melt glass, security cameras can be blinded by a beam of light, and for powering generators, you can take hazardous radiation from toxic puddles scattered across Delta Labs facilities. And of course, you will make an encounter with the quantum entanglement energy - the mysterious power capable of opening rifts between worlds. <br/><br/>Apart from solving environmental puzzles, your device can also be used against various creatures you'll meet in parallel dimensions. Most of the time you can't defeat your enemies; instead, you can use the Manipulator to outsmart or suspend them. Some enemies can be frozen in place using the force field energy, while others are sensitive to light and can be distracted by shooting a beam at it in the distance. You will require more advanced strategies and combining various energy types to pass them.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_story.png?t=1701271403"><br/>You find yourself in one of Delta Labs' off-world research facilities in an unknown dimension that looks more like a crashing-down laboratory. Your old friends Eugene and Alex try to connect with you shortly, and with their help, you start a journey through various dimensions. You will learn different physics interactions and meet unusual creatures on your way home. Along this, you have to unveil the mysteries of this project and your past. <br/><br/>Experience a non-linear story where your choice always matters. Can you get to the bottom of this, or just try to escape? Who to listen? Who to trust? Which side will you take? And will you finally “break the Principle”? That depends entirely on you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_setting.png?t=1701271403"><br/>Make your way back to Earth through mysterious parallel dimensions littered with puzzles and secrets, uncover mysterious connections between the worlds you visit, and reveal the dark truth about Delta Labs and your involvement with them. Dare to explore?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_features.png?t=1701271403"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Solve various physics-based puzzles<br/></li><li>Unique gameplay mechanics that involve an energy-manipulating weapon <br/></li><li>A mix of sci-fi with surreal and esoteric themes makes the game setting a unique design. Most of the time you'll spend in bizarre alien dimensions<br/></li><li>Deeply thought-out story and lore. Each location and each character in the game has its own story revealed through various notes, environmental narratives, and characters' conversations.<br/></li><li>The game features multiple endings that can be achieved through different choices </li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labrys</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2330210/Labrys/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Labrys</strong> is a multiplayer (up to 5v1) horror game where one player becomes the minotaur against the human prisoners, trying to escape the randomly generated labyrinth.<br/><br/>Humans can equip perks and find various equipment to aid them escaping the labyrinth.<br/><br/>The minotaur has access to various abilities and augmentations to upgrade his abilities.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><br/>• <strong>Be The Beast</strong><br/>You have the opportunity to play as the mighty minotaur, a fearsome creature with unparalled strength and cunning. Kill the humans as they try to escape the labyrinth, using your superior senses and abilities to hunt them one by one. <br/><br/>Smash through walls and use your abilities to corner your prey. You are the ultimate predator, embrace the power of the minotaur and let the hunt begin!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330210/extras/MinotaurGIF.gif?t=1701269935"><br/><br/>• <strong>The Ultimate Test Of Survival</strong><br/>As a human prisoner, your only goal is to escape the labyrinth before its sealed permanently. Use wits, equipments, agility and the environment to evade the minotaur's wrath. Team with other humans using the voice chat or be selfish to survive. Will you be able to outsmart the minotaur and escape the labyrinth?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330210/extras/HumanGIF.gif?t=1701269935"><br/><br/>• <strong>Face The Unknown</strong><br/>In Labrys the labryinth is randomly generated meaning every game is a unique and an unpredictable experience, keeping you on the edge of your seat every time.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330210/extras/facetheunknown.png?t=1701269935"><br/><br/>• <strong>Customize Your Playground</strong><br/>As the session host you have to ability to change many aspects of a session such as, the labyrinth size, room count, exit count, game length, loot amount, objective difficulty for both sides...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330210/extras/customizeyourplayground.png?t=1701269935"><br/><br/>• <strong>Single player and Co-op mode</strong><br/>Play versus Minotaur AI alone or with your friends!<br/><br/>• <strong>Level Progression System and Character Customization</strong><br/>Unlock perks and augmentations and character customization options.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wood Guy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2642860/Wood_Guy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2642860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In Wood Guy, you will be playing as a wooden puppet, exploring a world of handicrafts. <br>
<br>
With only your arms to move, climb (and fly?), you will face many challenges across more than 300 levels and bosses. Make good use of the weapons and shields you find along the way and hit those targets! Remember that gravity and physics are just a barrier that mean almost nothing to a living wooden toy trying to escape!<br>
Play alone to reach the end or ask a friend to join you and help. Also enjoy the Versus game mode where you can fight against up to 3 friends locally in a small arena to see who's the best puppet.<br>
<br>
<br>
More information :<br>
- It is recommended to play with a controller but playing with the keyboard and mouse is also possible.<br/>
- All multiplayer game modes (coop or versus) will require one controller per additional player as you will be playing on the same screen.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Velocity Ventures</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2607950/Velocity_Ventures/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Get ready for an adrenaline-fueled platforming adventure that will test your skills, reflexes, and combat prowess! "Velocity Ventures" is a thrilling 2D platformer that offers 20 action-packed levels of precision jumping, creative challenges, and heart-pounding excitement, along with a unique combat experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607950/extras/Screenshot_2023-09-16_1311143.png?t=1701267889"><br/><br/>🏃<strong> 20 Levels of Platforming Perfection:</strong> Embark on a journey through a colourful and dynamic world filled with meticulously designed levels. Each one presents a unique set of obstacles and puzzles that will keep you engaged and challenged.<br/><br/>🏹 <strong>Bow and Arrow Combat:</strong> Equip yourself with a trusty bow and arrow to take on enemies and overcome obstacles. Precision aiming and timing are essential as you engage in thrilling combat encounters throughout your adventure.<br/><br/>⏱️ <strong>Speedrun Mode:</strong> Are you a speed demon? Take on the ultimate challenge in our Speedrun Mode. Race against the clock to complete levels as quickly as possible, mastering the art of precise movement, perfect timing, and swift bowmanship.<br/><br/>🏆 <strong>Global Leaderboards:</strong> Compete with platforming enthusiasts from around the world! Climb the ranks and earn your spot on the global leaderboards, not only for your platforming skills but also for your combat prowess.<br/><br/>🎵 <strong>Dynamic Soundtrack:</strong> Groove to the beat of an electrifying soundtrack that perfectly complements the fast-paced gameplay. The music will keep you motivated as you navigate each challenge and face off against foes.<br/><br/>🎮 <strong>Controller Support:</strong> Whether you prefer a keyboard and mouse or a gamepad, "Velocity Ventures" offers full controller support for a seamless and immersive gaming experience.<br/><br/>"Velocity Ventures" is a love letter to classic platformers, combining modern gameplay mechanics with a nostalgic touch. It's not just about leaping through obstacles; it's about mastering the art of platforming and archery combat.<br/><br/>Join the platforming community, prove your skills, and aim for the top spot in the global rankings. Can you become the ultimate platforming hero and the sharpest archer in "Velocity Ventures"? Jump into the action and experience the thrill today!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pluto's Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1881290/Plutos_Island/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1881290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1881290/extras/pluto_ads_4.png?t=1701266420"><h2 class="bb_tag"> ~ FEATURES ~ </h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 8-12 hours of gameplay.<br/></li><li> Collect souls for the king of demons, Yaphett.<br/></li><li> Feed those souls into the volcano to gain power.<br/></li><li> Sling spells and magical abilities, strategize your upgrades, and survive explosive confrontations.<br/></li><li> Experience unforgettable NPCs painted with passion.<br/></li><li> Brave relentless waves of adversaries in roguelike flavored endless challenge zones.<br/></li><li> Collect Battlecrab TM cards! </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1881290/extras/pluto_ads_5.png?t=1701266420"><h2 class="bb_tag"> ~ BONUS FEATURES ~ </h2><i> ~ Based on the comic book, Pluto's Island ~ </i><br/><br/><i> ~ Exclusive soundtrack from Ark Patrol for maximum vibes ~ </i><br/><br/><i> ~ I tried my best to make it pretty good ~ </i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1881290/extras/pluto_ads_6.png?t=1701266420"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Cats 猫咪在哪里</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2685240/Where_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find 100 cats.<br>
A carefully hand drawn 4K scene filled with cute characters.<br>
The process is short and won't take up too much player time.<br/>
You can choose your favorite dyeing for the convenience of color blind players.<br/>
Extremely easy to achieve.<br/>
Automatically save and read files.<br/>
There is a local timer ranking.<br/>
No punishment, easy and enjoyable.<br/>
You can play games with family and friends on the same computer, suitable for all ages.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sugar Fruits</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2694480/Sugar_Fruits/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Sugar Fruits is the ultimate chill game for puzzle lovers! This is not just any ordinary matching game; it's a tranquil yet engaging escapade into a world of juicy goodness where strategy meets relaxation.<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay:</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694480/extras/Trailer.gif?t=1701260161"><br/><br/>With a simple tap, release a cascade of vibrant fruits from the tree tops. Watch as they tumble into a basket below, but be strategic! Your goal is to align similar fruits to create a chain reaction of delicious combos before the basket overflows.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probot Soccer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693360/Probot_Soccer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Probot Soccer is a third person soccer-style sports game where the player controls a robot. The aim of the game is to kick the soccer ball into the AI robot opponent's goal. The game includes various levels of difficulty which increase the number of rounds you must play against the AI robot opponent to win the game. The game has two maps: a daytime and a nighttime soccer field. You can keep track of how many wins and losses you have through the in-game scoreboard that can be reset if desired.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn around immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Other</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alice in Dinerland</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2476860/Alice_in_Dinerland/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2476860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Alive in Dinerland is a gripping garden game. Alice dropped through the rabbit hole, but in the end, she found herself in the role of a small diner owner. Now she needs to plant and grow some food to feed cute rabbits from the Dinerland. In this cozy building game, you will: <br/><br/>Features:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Build your own diner.<br/><br/></li><li>Plant a lot of different foods like tomatoes, pumpkins, carrots and more.<br/><br/></li><li>Travel through the Dinerland world, going between procedurally generated locations.<br/><br/></li><li>Fight characters from the original novel.<br/><br/></li><li>Craft weapons, hats, and glasses.<br/><br/></li><li>Meet some friends and foes.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jigsaw Advent Calendar</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2595930/Jigsaw_Advent_Calendar/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2595930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Surprise yourself every day leading up to Christmas with new challenging jigsaw puzzles in Jigsaw Advent Calendar</h2> <br/>There is more than enough puzzling to do for all of December – and longer – with 200 unique puzzles to complete. Lose yourself in Christmas cheer every day. Unlock each morning 8 new puzzles for 25 days until Christmas. Can’t wait? Don’t worry! In the play-immediately mode all days are unlocked and you can choose the puzzle you want to solve.<br/> <br/>Features:<br/>• 200 unique jigsaws, everyday 8 new puzzles<br/>• Choose the difficulty of your jigsaw puzzle (from 20 to 90 pieces)<br/>• Accessible controls (button- and touch controls)<br/>• Continue where you left off with to the automatic saving function						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orten Was The Case</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1785420/Orten_Was_The_Case/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1785420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FVsjgsyS6Sy" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1785420/extras/OrtenBanner.gif?t=1701260429"/></a><br/><br/>Get ready to step into the (non-existent) shoes of Ziggy - an unexpected hero from a fictional Swedish neighborhood. Together, you'll take on the daunting task of foiling a sinister scheme that could potentially devastate the entire world. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1785420/extras/Stuck__in_a_Time_Loop.png?t=1701260429"><br/><br/>Ziggy wakes up one day with a strange mark on his hand, clueless about what happened the night before. After a couple of minutes lost amongst the familiar streets of his suburb, Orten, an explosion brings him back exactly where he woke up moments before… He’s stuck in a time loop.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1785420/extras/ExplodeRewind600.gif?t=1701260429"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1785420/extras/Not_What_It_Seems.png?t=1701260429"><br/><br/>With no shoes or recollection of the past, he goes on a mission to discover what the hell is going on and how to avoid the destruction of his city. This won’t be easy though, cause the more he snoops in the wrong places, the more he learns that his hometown has a lot of secrets hidden. His weird neighbors become weirder, and he can only rely on his friends, and on his highly reliable brain.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1785420/extras/Friends600.gif?t=1701260429"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1785420/extras/Knowledge_is_Power.png?t=1701260429"><br/><br/>If the day repeats over and over, then how can one progress? That’s the catch: Knowledge is your key to progress in Orten. Each loop you go through, you will learn something new that will let you progress the story further. With this time loop mechanic, you’ll retain clues, notes, and timeline events, eventually knowing how you can change the future in just 12 minutes on a casual Sunday.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1785420/extras/LogBook600.gif?t=1701260429"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1785420/extras/We_Did_It.png?t=1701260429"><br/><br/>Who are they? The Midnight Council, I mean. They seem to be the only ones that are one step in front of you. What really happened in this town 40 years ago and how do you escape the time loop and death? <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1785420/extras/WeDidIt600.gif?t=1701260429"><br/><br/><strong> Follow the clues, solve puzzles, and explore the enigmatic suburb of Orten in this 2.5D hand-painted, adventure game! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1785420/extras/Running600.gif?t=1701260429"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where are my potatoes 2: Land Of Mystery</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2640640/Where_are_my_potatoes_2_Land_Of_Mystery/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2640640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Game story:</h2><br/>Kake potato character is back in this new third person platformer adventure. Kakes Ufo has crashed in Land of mystery. Kakes mission is to collect different fruits to get steam achievements and also main mission is to find missing potatoes which end kakes journey. There is different puzzles like player need collect bricks which is used to destroy wooden fences. Also player need use drain opener and fire to solve few other puzzles. There are also following enemies which can be killed only by using super smasher hand which weapons is hidden somewhere in map.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features::</h2>- Steam achievements.<br/>- Following enemies which can be killed with super hand<br/>- Puzzles<br/>- Collect bricks to destroy small fences. Fences need 4-7 bricks to destroy<br/>- Find fruits to get steam achievements						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beast Collector</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2691750/Beast_Collector/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2691750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Beast Collector - Your Ultimate Stylized Card Battler Adventure!</strong><br/>Welcome to the captivating world of "Beast Collector," a thrilling Trading Card Game (TCG) that seamlessly blends casual charm with competitive multiplayer excitement. Engage in epic card battles and craft your deck with style!<br/><br/><strong>Dive into Thrilling Card Duels!</strong><br/>Immerse yourself in dynamic card battles with stunning visuals and an immersive soundtrack. Challenge opponents worldwide in intense Player versus Player (PvP) card combat scenarios!<br/><br/><strong>Accessible to All Players!</strong><br/>"Beast Collector" is user-friendly, catering to players of all levels. Master the game mechanics through straightforward tutorials. Begin with a basic deck and expand your collection as you progress!<br/><br/><strong>Explore 300 Unique Cards!</strong><br/>Discover a diverse array of 300 distinct cards, featuring beasts, traps, spells, and enchantments. Each card presents unique strategies, empowering you to build decks that suit your playstyle.<br/><br/><strong>Command Strong Hero Cards!</strong><br/>Harness powerful Hero cards with unique effects capable of shifting battle dynamics. These Heroes wield abilities that can drastically alter tactics during combat.<br/><br/><strong>Synergize Different Classes for Battle Advantage!</strong><br/>Utilize distinct classes—Melee attackers, Magic attackers, Supporters, and Defenders—to create powerful synergies. Defenders boast high health points and a taunt ability, while Melee attackers wield strong attacking power and special abilities to bypass the defender's taunt. Magic attackers cast potent spells, swiftly annihilating enemies. Lastly, Supporters alter the battlefield with various abilities. Combine these classes for synergistic advantages in battles.<br/><br/><strong>Engage in Varied Modes!</strong><br/>Experience four distinctive game modes:<br/>* Explore Mode: Delve into the complexities of the "Beast Collector" world.<br/>* Dungeon Mode: Confront unique monsters found exclusively in dungeons, offering challenging Player versus Environment (PvE) encounters.<br/>* Normal Multiplayer Mode: Enjoy casual multiplayer battles, perfect for thrilling card duels.<br/>* Ranked Multiplayer Mode: Scale the ranks and engage in strategic multiplayer battles.<br/><br/><strong>Hatch Eggs for Random Beasts!</strong><br/>Navigate to your deck, select the egg tab, choose your egg card, and click the hatch button on the right panel. Access the Hatch screen to choose any egg and acquire a random beast!<br/><br/><strong>Evolve Your Beasts!</strong><br/>All beasts evolve through 3 stages. Begin at level 1, and by combining 5 identical beast cards, evolve to a much stronger stage, amplifying their abilities and prowess.<br/>"Beast Collector" offers an unparalleled experience in the competitive multiplayer TCG domain, featuring over 300 cards including a diverse collection of 270 unique beast cards, and traps, spells, and enchantments.<br/><br/><strong>Craft Your Winning Deck Strategy!</strong><br/>In "Beast Collector," devising your deck strategy is the key to victory. Explore multiple avenues to tailor your deck-building approach:<br/>* Prebuilt Decks: Dive straight into the Ranked ladder using pre-made decks designed for quick entry into battles.<br/>* Deck Crafting: Forge your deck from the ground up or take inspiration from a friend’s list to build a winning combination.<br/>* Tailored Customization: Fine-tune and personalize your decks, ensuring every card aligns perfectly with your battle tactics.<br/><br/><i>Recommended for</i><br/>Casual players seeking card gaming fun<br/>Enthusiasts of engaging deck-building adventures<br/>Multiplayer enthusiasts looking for competitive challenges						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final Resistance</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2482130/Final_Resistance/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2482130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Defend your castle! Kill all the monsters and welcome the dawn of victory! Final Resistance is a time-based defense strategy casual game, where you make your army stronger by making choices on talents and forging equipment, in order to hold onto the last fortress of humanity.<br>
<br>
There is no retreat, only a battle against the odds. Your only option is to fight with all your might, giving everything to defend your castle, which is also the last hope for humanity.<br>
<br>
The game consists of 2 phases:<br>
Preparation Phase: Within a limited time, collect resources, build defensive weapons, forge equipment, and arm your knights to the fullest.<br>
War Phase: Utilize the arrow towers of your castle, send out your soldiers, and do everything possible to defend your castle.<br>
<br>
An independent game that races against time, bringing you the experience of intense and thrilling castle defense battles!<br/>
<br/>
Game Features:<br/>
<br/>
Possess dozens of equipment, with different grades. Each legendary equipment has its unique special effect.<br/>
Each basic unit will bring you their special talent choices after a certain number of defense battles. Use different talent combinations to strengthen your knights in different ways.<br/>
Controls:<br/>
<br/>
Use W, A, S, D to control the game camera.<br/>
Use the number keys 1 and 2 to control basic units such as "peasants, instructors, chefs, blacksmiths" for resource collection and equipment forging						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drum Legend</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2685030/Drum_Legend/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							We proudly launch Drum Legend 2.0 !<br>
<br>
The game now support Custom Songs!<br>
Visit our Discord for Import Guide and get the Song Editor.（Click on the Discord bar at the bottom right）<br>
<br>
Drum Legend is a music rhythm game with multiple drumming gameplay options. In the 'Drum Maestro' mode,you can simulate a band drummer ,learn a variety of drumming skills, and play your favorite music.In the 'Rhythm Rush' mode, challenge yourself with more difficult tracks, aim for higher scores. <br>
<br/>
- Drum Maestro:<br/>
Simulate playing the drum kit and get a taste of being in a band!<br/>
This mode comes with a certain level of difficulty. If you haven't played the drum kit before, you can start practicing with the 'Practice Album' song pack.<br/>
Enjoy a refined drumming experience with professionally designed drum charts, gradually becoming a VR Soulful Drummer.<br/>
<br/>
- Rhythm Rush:<br/>
Don't make any miss, smash all notes accurately!<br/>
This mode is easy to pick up, but achieving SSS ranks or challenging level 9+ tracks requires continuous practice.<br/>
Every season, we release new featured song packs with meticulously designed music and charts for an exhilarating rhythmic experience.<br/>
<br/>
We are a pioneering team dedicated to exploring new music entertainment experiences in the XR world. 'Drum Legend' is our first music rhythm application, and we welcome your feedback to help us improve the product experience.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle Grid - Soundtrack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2453490/Battle_Grid__Soundtrack/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2453490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							The Soundtrack to Battle Grid. <br>
<br>
1 Intro<br>
2 Androidz<br>
3 Solar Flare<br>
4 Earth Anthem<br>
5 Distant Star<br>
6 Aquarium<br/>
7 Code Red<br/>
8 The Long Trek Home<br/>
9 Spirit Machine<br/>
10 Snow Intro<br/>
11 Your Darkest Hour<br/>
12 Prototype<br/>
13 Manic Bot<br/>
14 Interlude<br/>
15 Shards<br/>
16 Interplanetary Bureaucracy<br/>
17 Solar Flare (Demo Version)<br/>
18 Galaxy Cluster<br/>
19 March<br/>
20 Theme (Victory)						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wolf Sheep Cabbage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667480/Wolf_Sheep_Cabbage/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>"Wolf Sheep Cabbage"</strong> is a casual puzzle game where a single directional move affects all units simultaneously. Wolves eat sheep, sheep eat cabbage. Use your wits to safely deliver the wolf, sheep, and cabbage to their designated locations!<br/><br/><br/><strong>Deliver the wolf, sheep, and cabbage to the destination simultaneously</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667480/extras/1-1.gif?t=1701242654"><br/><br/><strong>Fences can protect the little sheep!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667480/extras/1-2.gif?t=1701242654"><br/><br/><strong>Beware of sharp traps!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667480/extras/1-3.gif?t=1701242654"><br/><br/><strong>Feel the anger of the little sheep!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667480/extras/1-4.gif?t=1701242654"><br/><br/><strong>Endless fun with teleportation gates!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667480/extras/1-5.gif?t=1701242654"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forest Grove</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1491390/Forest_Grove/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1491390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Forest Grove</strong> is a first-person mystery game where you uncover forensic clues, solve puzzles, and piece together a story using your own conclusions. Will you be able to solve the case?<br/><br/>Zooey Kunstmatigaard, the teenage heiress to a billion-dollar tech fortune, was reported missing by her stepmother Mary. She was last seen in her bedroom in Forest Grove, Oregon.<br/><br/>The Remote Forensics Bureau uses this as an opportunity to roll out their latest crime-fighting technology, the Nanodeck. You'll use it to investigate the scene, collect evidence, and unmask the truths behind Zooey's disappearance.<br/><br/>Relationships and secrets must be revealed. If foul play is suspected, those responsible must be brought to justice!<br/><br/><br/><strong>FORENSICS BASED EVIDENCE</strong><br/><br/>Explore a crime scene riddled with evidence such as DNA, fingerprints, perspiration metabolites and more. Can you associate these scattered pieces of evidence to reveal new leads and deduce the story within? It’s all up to you to find the truth.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1491390/extras/Feature_-_Forensics_Based_Evidence_resize.gif?t=1701234203"><br/><br/><br/><strong>INTERTWINED PUZZLES &amp; CLUES</strong><br/><br/>The Kunstmatigaard's are fond of puzzles. Discover hidden rooms and buried secrets all which lead to more clues to aid you in your investigation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1491390/extras/Feature_-_Intertwined_Puzzles___Clues_resize.gif?t=1701234203"><br/><br/><br/><strong>DEDUCTIVE REASONING</strong><br/><br/>Use your wit and intuition to piece together what really happened, knowing full well there's every chance you could get it wrong. There will be no hand holding here.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1491390/extras/Feature_-_Deductive_Reasoning_resize.gif?t=1701234203"><br/><br/><br/><strong>RICH CHARACTER BACKSTORY</strong><br/><br/>Uncover a cast of characters each with stories and conversation of their own. Perhaps someone knows more than they are willing to admit. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1491390/extras/Feature_-_Rich_Character_Backstory_resize.gif?t=1701234203"><br/><br/><br/><strong>INNOVATIVE EVIDENCE BOARD</strong><br/><br/>Solve the mystery like a real detective with the innovative evidence board. Collect an abundance of evidence which can be used to link to new leads, clues, or identifying persons of interest. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1491390/extras/Feature_-_Innovative_Evidence_Board_resize.gif?t=1701234203"><br/><br/><i>All characters appearing in this work are fictitious. Any resemblance to real persons, living or dead, is purely coincidental.</i> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>元素召唤 Summon Elemental</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2150310/_Summon_Elemental/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2150310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>This is an interesting tower defense (TD) Game.</strong><br/>You can use the mixed reactions among the seven elements of wind, thunder, water, fire, earth, light and dark to create a powerful element tower and defeat the invading enemy!<br/>At the same time, there will be plenty of dropped props and player skills in the game. With your unique element lineup, challenge the powerful monster leader!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Summon Elemental</li></ul>You can draw element cards by consuming gold coins each round, and you have a chance to get super rare elements!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Elemental Reaction</li></ul>Different elements in the field can react with each other to create more powerful elemental creations. At the same time, high-level creations will also react with elements, continue to synthesize upward, and create unparalleled powerful elements!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2150310/extras/hechengzhanshi.png?t=1701228167"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Strategy Matching</li></ul>Each element has different characteristics, and a reasonable combination of element towers is the key to victory!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Challenge BOSS</li></ul>There will be a variety of monster leaders with special abilities in the game. Players need to match reasonable element lineups according to monster characteristics to defeat them!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Magic prop</li></ul>Elite monsters may drop various magic props when they die. Equipping them to the element tower can strengthen various abilities of the element tower or bring special effects.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Summoning Skills</li></ul>When the player's Summoner level is upgraded, he will gain one skill point. The skill points consumed can be obtained from one of the three Summoning Skills.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Player Ranking</li></ul>In the follow-up of the game, infinite mode and player ranking will be launched, and the names of players and element lineups with the largest number of monsters defeated will be recorded.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One More Shooter Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2636490/One_More_Shooter_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This exciting third person shooting game. It consists of 10 levels full of action and challenges, where you will face a horde of enemies that threaten to invade the quiet desert.<br>
<br>
Objective of the game:<br>
<br>
Your mission is simple but crucial: you must eliminate a specific number of enemies in each level to advance. The planet relies on your shooting skills to prevent the plague of these enemies from expanding.<br>
<br>
"One More Shooter Game" will take you to exciting and action-packed levels, as you fight to keep the invasion of mutant enemies at bay in the vast and merciless desert. Do you have what it takes to face this challenge? Get ready to shoot and survive in this world full of enemies.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Coming</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2491050/Monster_Coming/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491050/extras/英01.png?t=1701222914"><br/>Hundreds of monsters are attacking you on the same screen, and you can only face it alone. The rich monsters will bring you the most exciting experience!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491050/extras/战斗1.gif?t=1701222914"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491050/extras/英02.png?t=1701222914"><br/>Different bosses have different attack skills, super fast movement speed, wall of beasts coming towards you, and position-locked sprint attacks. The attacks of each boss will be your nightmare!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491050/extras/boss.gif?t=1701222914"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491050/extras/英03.png?t=1701222914"><br/>You decide the upgrade route, which contains more than 20 props, and each prop has more than ten branch upgrade routes. Different routes determine different gameplay. No matter what choice you make, it will lead to victory!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491050/extras/升级.gif?t=1701222914"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491050/extras/英04.png?t=1701222914"><br/>Is it a summoning stream, a buff burst, or a large area of ​​high attack value crushing. Different genres have different gameplays. It all depends on your preference whether you want to move coquettishly or do violent output!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491050/extras/战斗2.gif?t=1701222914"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491050/extras/英05.png?t=1701222914"><br/>Is it a steel rider? Yue Yuan? Or the lonely-eyed swordsman? Each character has its own exclusive skills! A super long flying sword attack, a delayed explosive bomb, or a broken sword that kills at close range, your choice will determine your start!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491050/extras/角色.gif?t=1701222914"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491050/extras/英06.png?t=1701222914"><br/>Earn gold coins, continuously upgrade your talents, and with the blessing of buffs, you can kill ruthlessly and become unstoppable! The moment you start the game, victory is declared!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491050/extras/天赋.gif?t=1701222914"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucky Mayor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2659970/Lucky_Mayor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659970/extras/SteamHead.png?t=1701226602"><br/>In this roguelike mayor simulation game, you will become the leader of a city, taking on the role of a mayor. Your task is to recruit citizens, promote business prosperity, and establish a comprehensive industrial chain to meet the diverse needs of the population. Through wise planning and decision-making, transform your city into a thriving supercity that citizens take pride in, and become their admired leader!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659970/extras/steam2.png?t=1701226602"><br/>We have an extensive deck of cards, currently with over 150 citizens available for use, each with their unique abilities and preferences.<br/><br/>You need to meet the citizens' preferences to earn coins and, by the final deadline, obtain enough coins to prove that you are a capable mayor.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659970/extras/steam1.png?t=1701226602"><br/>We also have a wide range of items and different difficulty levels to enrich your gaming experience, and the development team will continue to provide updates for even more game content.<br/><br/>Please follow us on Discord, and we will be delighted to hear your thoughts and feedback on the game.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANDNAV</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1775460/LANDNAV/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1775460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							LANDNAV is an authentic simulation of military land navigation training.<br/><br/>LANDNAV is suitable as a training supplement for military and outdoors professionals. 1 to 1 parity with real world map and compass techniques. <br/><br/>Plan your route using authentic lensatic compass and 1:50,000 scale military topographic map.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Highly realistic forest terrain for immersive practice of terrain association techniques.<br/></li><li>Terrain association is more time consuming skill to train compared to dead reckoning - LANDNAV is the only 3d simulation that offers challenging and realistic environments in which terrain association plays a larger role compared to dead reckoning techniques. </li></ul><br/>The current version is the same version that has been used by many early testers to help prepare for many different military courses. It is marked as an early build work in progress because many fixes as well as new content is planned. Your support of the project helps me continue to improve the experience.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medville</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2656320/Medville/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Medville is an indie, single player, real time city builder game. It features individually simulated villagers, a money economy where prices can fluctuate, land and water transport and multiple towns. You start by managing a small town in randomly generated world of islands and mountains. You gradually need to build up an increasingly complex economy, first farming, then industry. After a certain level of development, you can start establishing new colonies and establish trade routes with each other.<br>
<br>
The economy of each town is centered around the marketplace. Citizens can sell their surplus goods and buy things that they need, such as food, clothes or inputs for their workshops. Each artifact has a price at a given marketplace, that can constantly change based on supply and demand. Traders can exploit price differences between different towns. Each city has a townhall, that taxes the households and can build new houses or fixes the roads and walls in return.<br>
<br>
All villagers have individual states and agendas. They can die because of starvation if the food supply chains break, or they can emigrate from the village if they are unhappy. They might join the outlaws, who live in separate communities and try to steal from your town, unless you keep them at bay with walls and soldiers.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weapon Shop Decillionaire</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2683960/Weapon_Shop_Decillionaire/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2683960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Weapon Shop Decillionaire</strong> invites you to embark on an epic journey where the realm of fantasy meets the allure of wealth. In this captivating idle game, you'll transform your dreams into reality as you immerse yourself in the world of equipment and trade.<br/><br/><strong>Build and Sell Equipment</strong>: Forge a fortune by creating and selling powerful equipment. As your coffers fill with profits, you'll have the opportunity to enhance your creations, forging a cycle of endless wealth.<br/><br/><strong>Strategic Equipment Placement</strong>: Hone your strategic skills as you master the art of efficiently packing as much equipment as possible into your shop's grid. Maximizing your earnings and achieving decillionaire status hinges on the meticulous arrangement of equipment within your store.<br/><br/><strong>The Path to Decillionaire</strong>: With incremental gameplay at its core, <strong>Weapon Shop Decillionaire</strong> offers an addictive and thrilling experience. One piece at a time, you'll ascend the ranks of wealth and influence.<br/><br/>Enter a world where fantasy and prosperity intertwine. Are you ready to become a decillionaire, shaping your destiny one piece at a time? Take your place in the annals of entrepreneurial legends with <strong>Weapon Shop Decillionaire</strong>.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pyrami Head</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2401450/Pyrami_Head/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2401450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>AVOID THE PYRAMIDS!</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2401450/extras/pyramikovala.gif?t=1701210450"><br/>We are trying to escape from a dark and extremely disturbing mysterious place. We are trying to rescue our character, who has lost his memory and is waiting to be sacrificed, without getting caught by the enemies around and open the hidden areas of the room by exploring the surroundings.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>DON'T GET LOST IN THE MAZE!</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2401450/extras/pyramibaslangıc.gif?t=1701210450"><br/>Keep an eye on your stamina bar and choose where to run your character!<br/>Make good use of the torch, which is our only friend and guide our way through the game, and try to explore the surroundings without getting caught by mysterious creatures! How long can you stay calm in this game that tests your stress and tension levels?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>COLLECT THE EYES</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2401450/extras/PyramiGoz.gif?t=1701210450"><br/>Fight against 3 different types of enemies that will stress you out even more in the dark atmosphere!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>GET RID OF THE CULT!</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2401450/extras/pyramiuclu.gif?t=1701210450"><br/>Enjoy replayability thanks to the key that spawns in different locations each time you play!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18 MINUTES</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2633200/18_MINUTES/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong></strong>18 MINUTES<strong></strong>Welcome to "18Minutes", the thrilling first-person shooter game that takes you back to 1984 and puts you in the shoes of a daring Eritrean commando operative on a mission to infiltrate and destroy an enemy airforce base. can you complete the mission in 18 minutes?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633200/extras/gif5__2_.gif?t=1701271368"> <br/><u>Stealth Mastery:</u><br/> Work you way in to the heart of a heavily guarded Asmara Air force base. Become a shadow as you slip through enemy lines with unmatched stealth. Infiltrate guarded areas, evade vigilant guards, and reach your targets undetected.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633200/extras/gif1__1_.gif?t=1701271368"><br/><u>Destructive Mayhem:</u><br/> Unleash chaos within enemy base! Race against the clock to destroy planes, vehicles, and fuel tanks before they can retaliate. Leave destruction in your wake and watch the enemy scramble to understand what just hit them.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633200/extras/gif6__1_.gif?t=1701271368"><br/><u>Fast-Paced Gunplay:</u><br/> Brace for intense, heart-pounding gun battles in Eritrean Commando. Engage in lightning-fast, close-quarters combat as waves of enemy soldiers swarm from all directions. Survive the onslaught and make a daring escape from the heart of the action-packed battlefield.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633200/extras/gif4__2_.gif?t=1701271368"><br/>18 MINUTES showcases stunning graphics and audio that bring every moment to life. From the realistic weapon mechanics to the explosive visual effects, every aspect of the game is designed to provide a truly immersive and cinematic experience. Feel the rush of adrenaline as you unleash an arsenal of weaponry, including assault rifle, RPG, explosives, and more.<br/><br/>But 18 MINUTES Eritrean Commandos isn't just about the explosive gameplay; it also pays homage to the courage, dedication, and heroism of the actual Eritrean commandos. Learn about their untold stories and the challenges they faced as you embark on these missions. Gain a deeper understanding of the sacrifices made by these brave warriors, and feel a sense of awe and respect for their extraordinary feats.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4Tacos</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608680/4Tacos/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>A cowardly goose against the whole dinosaur power mafia</strong>.<br/><br/>In a distant country called Tacotitlan, there exists the Divine Taco that is distributed among the people for their welfare. Everything was going well until the dinosaurs and their henchmen arrived, who moved by ambition, with deceit, took over the power of the Divine Taco creating many problems for the common people, who, fed up with the situation, with their singing, overthrew the dinosaurs from their throne and in their place placed a wise old man named Señor PG, who returned the benefits of the Divine Taco to the people of Tacotitlan.<br/><br/>But the dinosaurs would not stay with their arms crossed, they would attack with all their wiles to get the Divine Taco again. For this, Mr. PG opts to ask for help from the Legendary Heroes: Tlacuache and Ajolote, but upon arriving at his temple, Mr. PG finds it destroyed and inside there is only Cleto, a cowardly goose who had gone to leave a gift for his friends the Legendary Heroes. Cleto, lamenting for them, imagined the terrible things that Tlacuache and Ajolote would be going through, so leaving his cowardice for a moment he decides to join Lord PG to protect the Divine Taco and go to rescue his friends.<br/><br/>The battle begins in this video game based on the beat em up of the 90s.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight your way through the streets of Tacotitlan and learn about its folklore.</li><li>Use special powers against enemies.</li><li>Learn about the food in each zone of Tacotitlan.</li><li>Discover the secrets of its sacred millenary lands.</li><li>Defeat ruthless bosses.</li><li>Rescue your friends and prevent the dinosaurs from taking over the Taco Divino.</li></ul>.<br/>Languages: English and Spanish.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astro Planes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2645970/Astro_Planes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Astro Planes is set in the year 2074. Where you play as a lone pilot with advanced weaponry at your disposal. You are humanity's last hope, earth's finest. Defend earth from the unknown alien threat. As you travel across space, jumping through portals and engaging in fast paced battles with advanced aliens from many light years away. Your mission, Defend earth, locate the alien home world and bring this war to an end<br>
<br>
Astro Planes is a (single player) 3D side scroller space shooter with some 2.5D elements and many levels to play through. With a sci- fi themed fantasy atmosphere set in space and classic space shooter mechanics. Astro Planes is the modern day side scroller and space shooter of today.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2331710/Sky_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Sky Survivors</strong> is an arena shooter roguelite. Choose from a variety of skills, unlock unique characters and weapons. Build «stairway to heaven» — a sky tower, each floor of which gives your character a unique bonus. Create your own overpowered build to survive against hordes of monsters!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/1-st_eng.png?t=1701195497"><br/>Over 100 different skills will help you create a unique build every run. You can become an elemental mage, a weapon master, or summon magic books to destroy your enemies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/action.gif?t=1701195497"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/3-st_eng.png?t=1701195497"><br/>Each weapon has its own unique playstyle.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/chakram.gif?t=1701195497"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/4-st_eng.png?t=1701195497"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Bullet Hell — classic «roguelike». Increased speed of monsters and their projectiles. You and the monsters take more damage.<br/></li><li>Deckbuilder — the number of monsters and the amount of experience gained are increased.<br/></li><li>Standard Mode — perfect for the first time.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/5-st_eng.png?t=1701195497"><br/>Build a «stairway to heaven» — floors that grants your character a unique permanent bonus or a powerful temporary buff.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/obelisk.gif?t=1701195497"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/6-st_eng.png?t=1701195497"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><h2 class="bb_tag">Auto-aim mode for gamepads and PC.</h2></li><li><h2 class="bb_tag">Over 100 different skills to choose from.</h2></li><li><h2 class="bb_tag">«Stairway to Heaven» — each floor has its own unique bonuses.</h2></li><li><h2 class="bb_tag">Unique weapons that completely change your playstyle.</h2></li><li><h2 class="bb_tag">Diverse characters with unique abilities.</h2></li><li><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple game modes allow you to choose the playstyle to your liking.</h2></li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
