<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Distant Bloom</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1450250/Distant_Bloom/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to <strong>Distant Bloom</strong>, a <strong>cozy management and exploration game</strong> far away from home!<br/><br/>After a long expedition through space, you and your crew land on an alien planet with the critical mission of establishing a new home for your species. But this place is very different from the vision you saw through your telescope. What happened to the verdant life of this world? <i>And what will happen to you?</i> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/extras/DBGIF1.gif?t=1711545126"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Explore</strong> a desolate world and <strong>restore </strong>its blooming past with the power of plants!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/extras/DistantBloom_newGIF1.gif?t=1711545126"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Nurture new life by learning how to care for an amazingly varied alien flora.</strong> Play around with plant structures and create <strong>a thriving ecosystem!</strong><br/></li><li>Turn your harvest into<strong> recipes, tools, and items</strong> that you can use to build and <strong>improve your homebase.</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/extras/DistantBloom_newGIF2.gif?t=1711545126"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Reunite your scattered crew</strong> into a community where each member has their <strong>own story to tell.</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Explore the wilds to uncover the history of this strange planet.</strong> What <i>–or who–</i> left behind the puzzling ruins scattered across the land?<br/></li><li><strong>Change the world!</strong> Your actions will impact not only nature but also the <strong>future of your crew.</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/extras/DistantBloom_newGIF3.gif?t=1711545126"><br/><br/>Distant Bloom is an <strong>accessible and rewarding game</strong> that offers a <strong>warm, sheltered, and intimate experience.</strong> Explore, create, and bring nature <strong>closer to home!</strong><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FygVMn2Yser" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/extras/discord_banner_DB.png?t=1711545126"/></a> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE FINALS - Bank Rabbit Set</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2897810/THE_FINALS__Bank_Rabbit_Set/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2897810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							The Season 2 Bank Rabbit bundle includes:<br>
<br>
- Bunny Outfit<br>
- Hide Easter Egg Emote<br>
- 2 400 Multibucks						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>River Town Factory: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2847250/River_Town_Factory_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							River Town Factory: Prologue vs. Official Version Differences<br/>*Special Note: Prologue save data can all be transferred to the official version.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>In the Prologue version, players can increase the favorability of all romanceable NPCs up to 4 hearts.<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, players can increase the favorability of all regular NPCs up to 4 hearts.<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, players can access up to T1 node in the Oracle Temple.<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, 15% of buildings and technologies are available.<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, players can explore the Central Region, including martial arts and relic caves within the region.<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, players can reach a maximum of Level 2 on the SwordWay Sect and River Town Bounty Board (Somewhat Famous).<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, players can participate in the Spring Festival, including the Flower Festival and Qingming Festival.</li></ul><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FwNSHHEB2EJ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/discord.jpg?t=1711550847"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/en1.png?t=1711550847"><br/><br/>Create automated production assembly lines, from wooden planks to circuit boards, design every step of your production line.<br/>Unlock future technologies gradually, from silicon purification to photovoltaic power generation, and build your futuristic workshop.<br/>Use inter-district teleportation stations to receive products at various levels, expanding your factory's territory to the entire continent.<br/>From brewing and oil pressing to manufacturing ovens, even producing watches and antibiotics, astound ancient people with your futuristic goods!<br/>Reinforced concrete, rubber, and large-scale computers, these will be the mass-produced materials you use in the ancient times, a thousand years ago!!!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/steamgif.gif?t=1711550847"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/en2.png?t=1711550847"><br/><br/>There are 12 characters that can be pursued in the game - the royal, the martial arts world, the merchant, etc. Unlock the secrets of each character and pursue the friendships and romances you desire. Choose your partner and discuss marriage, and together move into the workshop where they will provide powerful assistance. Make connections with nearly 30 historical figures, each with their own changing schedules throughout the four seasons. Participate in their lives and use modern knowledge to solve their problems. In the River Town, everything happens naturally, and you have the final say on when to work, explore, and engage in romantic pursuits.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/rwall.gif?t=1711550847"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/rwstory.gif?t=1711550847"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/en3.png?t=1711550847"><br/><br/>A fast-paced combat system that is easy to pick up, combining evasion and offense to defeat your enemies through strategic maneuvers. Whether through formal training or adventures in the martial arts world, master more than 40 martial arts techniques including external skills, internal skills, light skills, and hard skills, allowing you to dominate the martial arts world.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/4zd.gif?t=1711550847"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/en4.png?t=1711550847"><br/><br/>Explore the four major villages on the map, complete village quests, and uncover their secrets.<br/>Explore the mystical realms left behind by ancient predecessors, delve deep into them, and defeat bizarre creatures.<br/>Explore the entire continent, discover treasures, explore bat caves, and punish bandits for the people.<br/>Sign contracts with mine owners throughout the entire map, allowing ancient people to work for you.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/5zddd.gif?t=1711550847"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/en5.png?t=1711550847"><br/><br/>Be a skilled craftsman or a social butterfly? Become the top martial artist or a versatile expert in everyday life? It's all up to you to decide.<br/>Craft spiritual medicines, weapons, and clothing, becoming a master of ancient craftsmanship.<br/>Create over 20 different dishes with various enhancements, such as Five Treasures Stew and Snowy Sunset Soup... Make them in your kitchen!<br/>Fill the Heavenly Workshop with the products you create, allowing ancient people to visit and witness modern technology.<br/>Utilize the power of future technology to repair the time machine and fulfill a mission that only you can accomplish.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/6zd.gif?t=1711550847"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulwark: Falconeer Chronicles</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/290100/Bulwark_Falconeer_Chronicles/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/titleBannerDescr.png?t=1711475617"><br/>Bulwark: Falconeer Chronicles is an open world builder with freedom and expression at its core, allowing players to build sprawling towns, spires, and fortresses that become hubs for trade, or rallying grounds for conquests. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/building.gif?t=1711475617"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_2-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Reforge a world shattered by the decisions of those who came before you, tower by tower, wall by wall, sculpting from the daunting cliffs and perilous waters of an unforgiving landscape that refuses to be tamed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_3-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Devastated by the aftermath of a war 40 years prior, you are in command of creating the last great settlement upon the Great Ursee - a vast, fantastical oceanic world filled with lost myths, breath-taking vistas and danger. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_4-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Starting with humble docks and wooden jetties, you will scavenge resources and grow your settlement as your population and creations grow ever grander, sculpting monumental stone towers and battlements that scrape the skies, where airships and giant warbirds rule.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_5-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Create trade routes and strike alliances with other factions scattered across the waves, acquiring powerful Captains and Commanders to protect your creations and utilise their aid in exploration -  or muster your own battlegroup to strike at them, waging war upon your ancient enemies. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_6-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>This world and its choices are yours to make - what legacy will you leave behind? What creations will bear your name?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/combat.gif?t=1711475617"><h2 class="bb_tag">Rediscover The Great Ursee </h2>The next instalment in the series which started with the award-winning 2020 aerial combat game, ‘The Falconeer’, taken into a completely new genre.<h2 class="bb_tag">A World of History and Violence </h2>An open world, full of opportunity. Explore the widest reaches of the Ursee in search of resources and engage with splintered factions - allying with them to acquire their aid, or sending your own warband to raid their settlements.<h2 class="bb_tag">Defend Your Bulwark </h2>Recruit powerful Captains and Commanders, used to provide powerful units, shore up your defences and adorn your settlement with their own architecture and style.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build Without Limits</h2>Enjoy a cosy ‘Freebuild Mode’, devoid of the conflict and challenges present in standard play, you can build without the need for resources or upgrades.<h2 class="bb_tag">Chaotic Creativity </h2>Immerse yourself in building mechanics inspired by 3D modelling software and kitbashing, for a building experience that focuses on experimentation.<h2 class="bb_tag">Transcendental Soundtrack </h2>Award-winning composer Benedict Nichols returns to craft an eclectic soundtrack like no other, sculpting the audible landscape of the Ursee along with your creations.<h2 class="bb_tag">Share Your Creations </h2>Utilise an intuitive, flexible camera mode and time lapse replay feature to watch your unique creations grow brick by brick, then share them with the world<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Ffalconeer" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/Bulwark-Discord.png?t=1711475617"/></a><br/><br/>Secret Code -&gt; 20TSFCBW24AW						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1268590/Millennia/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fmillennia" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/616x152.png?t=1711472688"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Store_Page_City_Growth_animation_Steam-Loop.gif?t=1711472688"><br/>Create your own nation in Millennia, a historical turn-based 4X game that challenges your strategic prowess across 10,000 years of history, from the dawn of humanity to our possible futures.  Set the course of history and experience different timelines in every playthrough as you write an epic story through your actions.  Lead your people through times of crisis and ages of discovery, face great challenges and opportunities, and build a civilization that prospers through the ages.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Guide_Your_Nation.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Dictate the course of history across ten ages, from the first cities to space travel.  Accomplish certain objectives and you can move time into a Variant Age - an alternate history with new rules, new technologies, and new units.  But beware Crisis Ages; following a path of chaos and disorder may plunge the world into a future filled with war, sickness or ignorance.  Then again, a wise ruler can always turn a crisis into an opportunity....  Choose the path with care, as the ages you pass through will have a lasting impact on your people and the world.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Choose_What_You.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Customize your nation by adopting unique Nations Spirits over the course of your game.  Will you be a nation of warriors or explorers?  Are your people lead by a Great Khan or a builder of monuments?  Are you known for defining  pop culture or for dominating global finance?  What parts of your culture will reverberate across history?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Master_a_Deep.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Manage your economy with care and create a juggernaut of growth and construction.  Start with basic resources to gain food, wealth, and production.  As your advance, decide how to best convert these simple goods into more valuable products through research and improvements.  Specialize your regions, turning iron into weapons or tools, wood into paper or lumber, gold into coin or jewelry.  Ship surplus goods where they are needed, allowing the breadbasket of your empire to feed far-flung colonies or your industrial heartland to supply troops near your enemy.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Unlock_Technologies.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Pursue knowledge to research scientific and cultural advances, unlocking new units, buildings, and improvements to grow your cities or strengthen your armies.  Research Defense to train the first archers, Smelting to master iron production, or Guilds for making wine.  Variant and Crisis Ages feature unique alternatives, introducing everything from Cloud Estates in the Age of Aether to underwater cities in the Age of Utopia.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Achieve_Victory.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Achieve your ultimate success through a Victory Age.  Toward the end of the game (or earlier if your strategy is sound), dominance allows a nation to dictate the winning conditions.  The rest of the world must decide if they will struggle to achieve victory before the leader ... or oppose the leader's attempt.  Risk everything to take victory in the Renaissance or carefully plan for triumph in the modern era.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Millennia: Premium Edition includes the following content:</h2><br/><strong>Wolfpack Warband &amp; Eagle Archers cosmetics</strong><br/>Elevate the presence of your units in Millennia with the exclusive Wolfpack Warband and Eagle Archers clothings. Available instantly with the Premium Edition, this clothes pack unlocks unique wolf skin clothing for your Warband. Your Archer Unit receives eagle-inspired clothes, symbolizing their precision and keen sight.<br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Ancient Worlds</strong><br/>Take your first uncertain steps in a new era for humanity in Millennia: Ancient Worlds. Take control of your people before their first settlement, while they still wander as nomads.  Includes a new nomadic game start option, a new National Spirit, a new economic Good, and new Nation starting bonuses. <br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Atomic Ambitions</strong><br/>Unlock the mysteries of the atom and change the world forever in Millennia: Atomic Ambitions. The Premium edition adds ways to harness the power of the atom for the good of all humankind, but, there are also ways to turn the planet into a fallout-filled wasteland if you aren’t careful. Includes two new Ages, a new National Spirit, and nuclear options for the Strategic Warfare System.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1268590/Millennia/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fmillennia" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/616x152.png?t=1711472688"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Store_Page_City_Growth_animation_Steam-Loop.gif?t=1711472688"><br/>Create your own nation in Millennia, a historical turn-based 4X game that challenges your strategic prowess across 10,000 years of history, from the dawn of humanity to our possible futures.  Set the course of history and experience different timelines in every playthrough as you write an epic story through your actions.  Lead your people through times of crisis and ages of discovery, face great challenges and opportunities, and build a civilization that prospers through the ages.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Guide_Your_Nation.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Dictate the course of history across ten ages, from the first cities to space travel.  Accomplish certain objectives and you can move time into a Variant Age - an alternate history with new rules, new technologies, and new units.  But beware Crisis Ages; following a path of chaos and disorder may plunge the world into a future filled with war, sickness or ignorance.  Then again, a wise ruler can always turn a crisis into an opportunity....  Choose the path with care, as the ages you pass through will have a lasting impact on your people and the world.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Choose_What_You.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Customize your nation by adopting unique Nations Spirits over the course of your game.  Will you be a nation of warriors or explorers?  Are your people lead by a Great Khan or a builder of monuments?  Are you known for defining  pop culture or for dominating global finance?  What parts of your culture will reverberate across history?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Master_a_Deep.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Manage your economy with care and create a juggernaut of growth and construction.  Start with basic resources to gain food, wealth, and production.  As your advance, decide how to best convert these simple goods into more valuable products through research and improvements.  Specialize your regions, turning iron into weapons or tools, wood into paper or lumber, gold into coin or jewelry.  Ship surplus goods where they are needed, allowing the breadbasket of your empire to feed far-flung colonies or your industrial heartland to supply troops near your enemy.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Unlock_Technologies.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Pursue knowledge to research scientific and cultural advances, unlocking new units, buildings, and improvements to grow your cities or strengthen your armies.  Research Defense to train the first archers, Smelting to master iron production, or Guilds for making wine.  Variant and Crisis Ages feature unique alternatives, introducing everything from Cloud Estates in the Age of Aether to underwater cities in the Age of Utopia.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Achieve_Victory.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Achieve your ultimate success through a Victory Age.  Toward the end of the game (or earlier if your strategy is sound), dominance allows a nation to dictate the winning conditions.  The rest of the world must decide if they will struggle to achieve victory before the leader ... or oppose the leader's attempt.  Risk everything to take victory in the Renaissance or carefully plan for triumph in the modern era.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Millennia: Premium Edition includes the following content:</h2><br/><strong>Wolfpack Warband &amp; Eagle Archers cosmetics</strong><br/>Elevate the presence of your units in Millennia with the exclusive Wolfpack Warband and Eagle Archers clothings. Available instantly with the Premium Edition, this clothes pack unlocks unique wolf skin clothing for your Warband. Your Archer Unit receives eagle-inspired clothes, symbolizing their precision and keen sight.<br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Ancient Worlds</strong><br/>Take your first uncertain steps in a new era for humanity in Millennia: Ancient Worlds. Take control of your people before their first settlement, while they still wander as nomads.  Includes a new nomadic game start option, a new National Spirit, a new economic Good, and new Nation starting bonuses. <br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Atomic Ambitions</strong><br/>Unlock the mysteries of the atom and change the world forever in Millennia: Atomic Ambitions. The Premium edition adds ways to harness the power of the atom for the good of all humankind, but, there are also ways to turn the planet into a fallout-filled wasteland if you aren’t careful. Includes two new Ages, a new National Spirit, and nuclear options for the Strategic Warfare System.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outpost: Infinity Siege</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1566690/Outpost_Infinity_Siege/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1566690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1566690/extras/ENGIF.gif?t=1711542896"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Outpost Building</strong></h2>Explore the world, gather resources, merge and upgrade outpost units to build your own outpost.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Unique Weapon</strong></h2>Fully exploit the value of the unique XEN Firearm with different protoslag attributes, and utilize ammunition with diverse performance.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Loot &amp; Farm</strong></h2>Enjoy the abundant difficulty levels, diverse gameplay features, and distinctive maps of the exploration mode. Venture deep into the brand new zones full of hazards and opportunities, and harvest powerful outpost units.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Feature</strong></h2>Fight alongside friends on Recovery Day, or strive together to survive infinite waves of monsters in Endless mode till the last moment.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arma 3 Creator DLC: Reaction Forces</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2647760/Arma_3_Creator_DLC_Reaction_Forces/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647760/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">More From Rotators Collective</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1681170/Arma_3_Creator_DLC_Western_Sahara/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1681170/Arma_3_Creator_DLC_Western_Sahara/</a><br/><br/>Fight fires from above in the Cougar medium utility helicopter or swerve from the beaten track in the MOOSE pickup truck to take on tier-1 operations with new weapons and equipment, from pistols and rifles to remote-controlled mortars and micro-drones. <br/><br/>Reaction Forces Creator DLC is the ultimate response to any situation on the battlefield.<h2 class="bb_tag">HOW TO LAUNCH</h2><br/>Once released, the Arma 3 Creator DLC: Reaction Forces will be optional to install and load. To play Arma 3 with this DLC enabled, please visit the DLC section in the Arma 3 Launcher, make sure Reaction Forces are owned and loaded, then launch the game by clicking the PLAY button.<h2 class="bb_tag">KEY FEATURES</h2><br/><strong>Cougar Helicopter</strong><br/>The Cougar is a four-blade, twin-engine, medium-sized, utility helicopter that has seen extensive military and civilian use over the years. In its civilian role, it is primarily used for transportation and offshore support, as well as public service missions, such as search and rescue. Some variants even come equipped with an emergency flotation device, which mitigates the risks of ditching at sea.<br/><br/>For military use, the Cougar comes with variable pylon mounts for external weaponry. Some variants are fitted with a 20 mm chin-gun, vastly increasing its striking power and versatility as a gunship.<br/><br/>Take advantage of extensive customization options featuring different pylon loadouts and over 30 skins, which allow you to outfit the helicopter for every imaginable mission.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647760/extras/banner_heli_v5.gif?t=1711461889"><br/><br/><strong>MOOSE Pickup</strong><br/>The MOOSE pickup is a light-duty vehicle with a wide range of configurations, serving military and civilian sectors worldwide. It is often used as a means of short-range transportation, or simply as a dependable weapons platform for special forces and non-state actors. <br/><br/>With 40 available texture variants, as well as a plethora of visual customization options and multiple different weapons modules, you can tailor your MOOSE to stand out amidst the chaos of battle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647760/extras/banner_pickups_v3.gif?t=1711461889"><br/><br/><strong>120 mm Twin Mortar and Commando Mortar</strong><br/>The 120 mm Twin Mortar is a container-sized emplacement that can launch HE, smoke, or laser-guided rounds accurately at incredible distances across the battlefield. The Commando Mortar is a lightweight one-man mortar that can be easily assembled in the field.<br/><br/><strong>RC-40 Micro-UAV</strong><br/>Keep an eye and an ear to the skies - although if you hear one of these drones, it is probably too late! This incredibly compact UAV can be equipped with explosive or smoke charges, which can be detonated remotely or via impact with a target. A scout variant can laser designate targets while maintaining a low profile.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647760/extras/banner_mortars_v2.gif?t=1711461889"><br/><br/><strong>Two Rifles, Two Handguns, and Four Aircraft Weapon Pods</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Mk26 L5</strong> - An American-made, semi-automatic pistol chambered in .50AE popularized through 80s action movies - and yes, a gold plated version is available!<br/></li><li><strong>HADES H6</strong> - Manufactured in Germany, the H6 is a modern, ultra-lightweight and easy-to-handle 5.56 mm bolt rifle.<br/></li><li><strong>Veles</strong>  - Russian-developed dedicated CQB bullpup rifle with a high stopping power.<br/></li><li><strong>G19</strong> - Often used by military and police, a full-automatic capable pistol, designed and produced in Austria.</li></ul><br/>Additionally, this CDLC features new suppressors, optics, and special 5.56 mm armor-piercing ammunition are available for extra firepower!<br/><br/>There is also a lethal selection of heavy-duty weapons for aircraft mounts, capable of turning an innocuous transport helicopter into a devastatingly effective gunship:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>12.7 mm machine gun weapon pod<br/></li><li>20 mm cannon weapon pod<br/></li><li>DAR/DAGR x19 missile pod<br/></li><li>Tratnyr HE/AP x16 missile pod</li></ul><br/><strong>Equipment</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Leather Jacket outfit<br/></li><li>Shape Breaker helmet variants for AAF, CSAT, and NATO<br/></li><li>Heavy Combat Helmet<br/></li><li>New sleek and lightweight Heli Pilot Helmet and Coveralls<br/></li><li>Wildland Firefighter Fatigues<br/></li><li>Full Brim Hard Hat to offer maximum protection in exposed environments<br/></li><li>Duffle Bag - spacious and with iconic Armaverse branding!<br/></li><li>TNVG-B night-vision goggles with color-enhanced thermal imaging and a special filter for low-light conditions<br/></li><li>Carrier Lite Rig and Tactical Vest Rig variants<br/></li><li>Colored steerable parachutes and backpacks for civilians and parachute display teams</li></ul><br/><strong>Modules and Mechanics</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hit Indicator effects module<br/></li><li>Wildfire mechanics module<br/></li><li>Water bombing waypoint types (collect and drop water for AI)<br/></li><li>The Advanced Helicopter Flight Model HUD gauges can be enabled in standard mode (Options &gt; Game &gt; Difficulty &gt; Category: Reaction Forces)</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647760/extras/banner_weapons_v1.gif?t=1711461889"><br/><br/><strong>Open-World Campaign Scenario: "Air Control"</strong><br/><br/>Take part in a combined arms offensive! Prioritize your tasks, transport special forces, and fly logistics as a helicopter pilot, influencing battles below from above in this vast, multi-hour open-world campaign scenario playable solo or in up to 12-players in multiplayer .<br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer Scenarios: Training Day and FireSeason</strong><br/><br/>Familiarize yourself with the Cougar helicopter, learn how to use a helicopter bucket, and take part in water bombing drills on Malden. Once trained, you can go on duty and help protect the island during the current fire season.<br/><br/><strong>COOP and Singleplayer Scenario: "QRF"</strong><br/><br/>Respond to an emergency call and protect the HVT until reinforcements arrive! As a Quick Reaction Force (QRF), defend against waves of enemies and fight for your life against overwhelming odds in this new co-op game mode. Conserve your ammo and pick your targets carefully while working closely with a team of up to six people.<br/><br/><strong>Multiplayer Mode: "Cashpoint"</strong><br/><br/>A series of cashpoint robberies are happening all across Malden and Tanoa — will you stop the criminals responsible, or are you one of them? This is a Team Deathmatch scenario for up to 12 players in two uneven teams.<br/><br/><strong>Additional Content</strong><br/><br/>Rounding out the Reaction Forces package, comes a set of additional items including new static props, as well as over 1 hour of newly composed ambient music tracks.<br/><br/>Included with the download is a specifically curated soundtrack in high-quality digital format. The soundtrack includes 11 tracks with a total duration of 38 minutes, curated from the Reaction Forces ingame ambient music for the best possible listening experience outside of the game.<h2 class="bb_tag">ABOUT THE DEVELOPERS</h2><br/>This DLC is published by Bohemia Interactive and developed by the Rotators Collective - a small group of like-minded developers loosely assembled from all around Europe with over a decade of experience in making mods for a wide variety of games, including the top-rated Arma 3 mini-campaigns Callsign Minotaur and Dunes, as well as their previous project, the highly praised Western Sahara Creator DLC.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTH PARK: SNOW DAY!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1214650/SOUTH_PARK_SNOW_DAY/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1214650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From South Park Digital Studios, the studio that brought you South Park: The Stick of Truth, South Park: The Fractured but Whole, and South Park: Phone Destroyer comes the next chapter in the journey of the New Kid.<br/><br/>Join Cartman, Stan, Kyle, and Kenny, in three-dimensional glory, to celebrate the most magical day in any young child’s life - a snow day! A massive blizzard has thrown the town into chaos and, more importantly, canceled school.<br/><br/>Play with up to three friends, use matchmaking, or solo the game with ally bots and battle through the snow-piled town of South Park. Engage in frenetic, action-packed combat against warring factions in an all-new story where you make the rules. Equip unique weapons and deploy devastating, upgradable special abilities on a new adventure to save the world and enjoy a day without school.<h2 class="bb_tag">It’s a snow day, dude!</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle your way through the snow-covered town of South Park in this all-new 3D co-op game.<br/></li><li>A blizzard of epic proportions has blanketed the town of South Park and it’s up to Cartman, Stan, Kenny, Kyle, and you, as the New Kid, to save the town from an endless winter.<br/></li><li>Experience cooperative gameplay for the first time ever in a South Park game with up to three friends or ally bots - unleashing powerful, coordinated attacks on your foes.<br/></li><li>Equip and upgrade devastating melee and ranged weapons. Deploy special abilities and powers that will bring hordes of enemies and epic bosses to their knees.<br/></li><li>Use a wide range of iconic cosmetics and customize your New Kid with endless possible combinations from beanies to Cheesy Poof T-shirts to chin balls.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DORONKO WANKO</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2512840/DORONKO_WANKO/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							『DORONKO WANKO』 is a <strong>DORONKO Action</strong> Game.<br/>In this game, you can become a cute, innocent pomeranian.<br/>And you can make your master's home messy and dirty.<br/>Let's explore this beautiful house and make it dirty and muddy at will!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Action_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Action.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>Pomeranian can get muddy by "rubbing"  against the "mud" spread on the floor.<br/>Spread out the mud with "splash"!<br/>Let's make the whole area muddy and messy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Goal_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Goal.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>Sometimes you can find "hidden pome" when you are spreading mud all over the house.<br/>When you find all the "hidden pome", the "Good Smell Room" 's door will open.<br/>(Let's go inside quietly before others notice!)<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Damage_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Damage.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>More mud, more damage!<br/>You can check the total amount of damage you have caused from the ending “Receipt”.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Present_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Present.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>When you cause enough damage, you will receive a “gift”?!<br/>They will help Pome’s exploration by making it easier to splash mud and obtain key items.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Gimmick_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Gimmick.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>A little action can cause a huge damage?<br/>Use personal appliances and toys to get even muddier.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Badge_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Badge_EN.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>The Pomeranian's adventures will remain as a "badge of memory".<br/>A random move may get an unexpected badge.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Customize_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Customize.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>"Put on" the "Goods" and make your Pomeranian more pretty.<br/>Don't forget the special goods that can release mud!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2510720/Artifact_Seeker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/DS.png?t=1711367082"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/11y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>The unique “Artifacts sharing code function” allows you to share the Artifacts you collect with your friends! !<br/>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/1y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/1z.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/2y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/gif1.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/3y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/3y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/4y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/4y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/5y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/5y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/6y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/6y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living With Sister: Monochrome Fantasy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2429860/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1711168850"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_1__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/>Living in a fantasy world, it's always been your dream to grow up to be a famous adventurer just like your father. Reality proves to be more boring than fiction, however, as your days are mostly spent doing odd jobs for the villagers. With your friends by your side, you enter the Tournament of the Eights and strive for something greater: the chance to become the top guild in the country. Will you realize your ambitions, or will your hopes slip through your fingers and doom you to a life of monochrome monotony?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_2__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/>As a member of your town's Adventurers' Guild, it's your job to protect the townsfolk. Go on hunts, kill dangerous beasts, and hone your abilities to better tackle whatever challenges tomorrow brings.<br/><br/>Once you get home from work, you'll have your sister to attend to. She's a very sickly girl who needs a lot of help. Manage your household finances well, build up your relationship with your sister, and who knows, perhaps you might even be able to solve the mystery behind her illness.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_3__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Big_Brother_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Little_Sister_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Kana_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Yui_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Kasumi_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Yukari_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Akatsuki_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_4__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><strong>Hand-Drawn Monochrome Art</strong><br/>Though it may lack color, this game's world is anything but colorless! The stunning black-and-white art is chock-full of personality and is sure to leave you with plenty of marvelous monochrome memories!<br/><br/><strong>Unique Combat System</strong><br/>With tons of bizarre and ferocious monsters to fight and dozens of unique skills to unlock, your adventures are sure to be full of challenge and excitement!<br/><br/><strong>Charming Characters</strong><br/>Build up your relationships with your guildmates and your sister to learn about what makes them tick and unlock character-specific abilities to further assist you in your quest to become the top guild in the country!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Chilla's Art] Shinkansen 0 | 新幹線 0号</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2793370/Chillas_Art_Shinkansen_0___0/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2793370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Shinkansen 0 | 新幹線 0号 is a game set in Japan where players are tasked with finding anomalies in the Shinkansen. (Japanese bullet train)<br/><br/><i><strong>Supporter content can be turned on and off at the title screen. (It is on by default) </strong></i><br/><br/><i><strong>Motion Blur and Headbob is turned off by default.</strong></i><br/><br/><strong>Controls:<br/><br/>WASD - Move<br/>Left Click - Interact　<br/>Right Click - Zoom<br/>Shift - Run<br/>ESC - Options</strong><br/><br/>Easy mode - There is an easy mode in the mainmenu available for everyone to enjoy<br/><br/>Auto-save: auto-save for each chapter<br/><br/>Endings: There are two endings<br/><br/><strong><i>If you encounter any technical issues, do the following:<br/><br/>-Update GPU driver<br/>-Lower the Graphics settings/Screen resolution<br/>-Update Windows OS<br/>-Check if your anti-virus software is blocking the game or its save data. (Save Data location: C:\Users\[YOURUSERNAME]\AppData\LocalLow\Chilla's Art, LLC\Shinkansen0)<br/>-Delete save, then try again (Save Data location: C:\Users\[YOURUSERNAME]\AppData\LocalLow\Chilla's Art, LLC\Shinkansen0)<br/>-Check if your PC meets the system requirements</i></strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears In Space</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1309620/Bears_In_Space/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FG6w3Zxbp8W" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/Steam_CTAbutton_Discord.png?t=1711123009"/></a><br/>Get ready to unleash your inner bear in Bears in Space, the over-the-top<br/>bullet-hell FPS that's bound to have you ROARING with excitement! Dive headfirst into hordes of oil-thirsty robots as you embody Maxwell Atoms, a Spacetronaut turned extraterrestrial castaway, whose DNA has been merged with Beartana, the She-Bear. <br/>Embark on a zany and humorous out-of-this-world adventure that'll have you blasting your way across exciting and varied locations, from wastelands to space carnivals to ancient hidden temples and more as you quest to find your way back to earth and if there’s time, save your crew.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fast-paced Mayhem</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/BulletHell_acid2.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Bears In Space offers non-stop, high-energy gameplay. Fight your way through waves of fiendish robots using an arsenal of outrageous weaponry and gadgets. Double jump, dash, and dodge enemy attacks in the tradition of the best old-school shooters.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Mighty As A Bear</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/BearMode.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Consume elusive honey pots and unleash your Ursine rage, transforming into a bear!  <br/>Use your unique DNA fusion to your advantage, carving up robot enemies with your mighty bear powers and masterful knowledge of the ancient art of Bear Fu and the fabled Kuma No Ken.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Upgrade Your Arsenal</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/UpgradeRadial.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Complete challenges and break open loot crates to purchase guns, choosing from a diverse range of over 25 weapons!<br/>Most weapons upgrade, with each kill gaining your equipped weapon XP until it evolves into its next evolution tier! So, get out there and let the lasers fly!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Varied Gameplay</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/Varied_Gameplay_BasketCube.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Venture beyond the ordinary FPS experience and discover Substories, secrets and collectibles across every level!<br/>Learn how to bake a cake, investigate a crime scene, battle a Rock God, play a round of Basketcube and even bust some ghosts! All while meeting a colourful cast of characters with their own quirks and stories to tell.<br/>Completing these exciting optional encounters brings with it a hefty loot pay off, making these encounters even more rewarding to search out as you save up for your next weapon!<br/><br/>Choose your difficulty and play the game your way!<br/>Modify your difficulty with independent sliders for incoming and outgoing damage. You can also engage our Platform Helper mode, making all platforming segments of our game significantly easier to conquer! Perfect for kids or gamers new to the FPS genre!<br/><br/><br/>Whether you're a seasoned gamer looking for a blast from the past or a casual player seeking a fun-filled adventure, Bears in Space promises a fun and absurd, action packed time. Get ready to shoot, chuckle, and unleash your inner bear in this one-of-a-kind bullet-hell FPS adventure that’s truly out of this world!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4D Golf</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2147950/4D_Golf/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2147950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>4D Golf</strong> is a mind-bending golf game unlike any other because it's set entirely in a 4-dimensional space. Complete fun and unique golfing challenges as you gain hands-on experience of the 4th dimension and beyond!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2147950/extras/SteamGIF_1.gif?t=1711121562"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 120 levels and 7 vibrant themed worlds<br/></li><li>Tons of visualization options to master 4D space<br/></li><li>Build your own 4D courses in the level editor<br/></li><li>Race the clock in Marble Platforming Mode<br/></li><li>Navigate hidden paths, moving platforms, shifting gravity, speed boosts, and more!<br/></li><li>Unlock custom accessories by completing challenges</li></ul><br/>Now open your third eye and unleash your full potential!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2054970/Dragons_Dogma_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Note: There are other sets that include this item.<br/><br/>Set forth on your grand adventure, Arisen!<br/><br/>Dragon’s Dogma is a single player, narrative driven action-RPG series that challenges the players to choose their own experience – from the appearance of their Arisen, their vocation, their party, how to approach different situations and more. Now, in this long-awaited sequel, the deep, explorable fantasy world of Dragon’s Dogma 2 awaits.<br/><br/>On your journey, you’ll be joined by Pawns, mysterious otherworldly beings, in an adventure so unique you will feel as if accompanied by other players while on your own adventure.<br/><br/>All of these elements are elevated further through physics technology, artificial intelligence (AI) and the latest in graphics, to create a truly immersive fantasy world in Dragon’s Dogma 2.<br/><br/><br/><strong><u>Action that challenges your creativity </u></strong> <br/><br/>Wield swords, bows, and chant magick.<br/>The vocations in Dragon's Dogma 2 give you the ability to approach combat the way you want.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_01.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Company in your single-player experience </u></strong> <br/><br/>Players can customize their own main Pawn, who will always accompany your Arisen, <br/>and enter a covenant with up to 2 additional Pawns from other players through the network. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_02.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Facing the monsters in this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Beyond the town borders, you will encounter diverse monsters that inhabit the lands. <br/>You will need to decide between engaging in battles or finding alternatives; <br/>so be aware of your party’s setup, the terrain around you, and the monsters you face.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_03.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Inhabitants of this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Travelers, merchants, soldiers and other folk go about their daily lives. <br/>Preoccupied by their own objectives and motives, they all exhibit different emotions.<br/>At times, they may lead you to a quest by approaching you and asking for a favor. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_04.gif?t=1711067553"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cureocity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2612680/Cureocity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							We are "Bread On Board," a collective of independent game developers spread across four countries, united by our passion and meeting during a GameJam. <br/>Our game demo was born in the "BOOOM CHALLENGE", a GameJam by GCORES. With only 21 days, we created a game based on a given theme. After the competition, we even won the "Most Popular Game" award at an Online Game Trial Event.<br/>The full playthrough of our game will take about an hour. We hope to give you a short, but super heartwarming and loving adventure❤️.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/1.奇幻而治愈（英文）.png?t=1711531628"><br/>A rookie adventurer fresh on the scene and a former mercenary who was transferred into an adventurer due to injury. Two protagonists with contrasting personalities will embark on an adventure of fantasy and healing together. In the mysterious ruins of an underground dungeon that lies in the depth of a jungle, what awaits them will be...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1711531628"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/2.两位冒险者（英文）.png?t=1711531628"><br/>According to the tavern's adventurer logs, the team heading into the dungeon features a rookie adventurer and an ex-mercenary who is now working as a healer. The adventurer looks as charming as a doll, and the enthusiasm never disappears; the healer is cool and a bit traditional, acting as a guiding figure for their adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1711531628"><br/><br/>What stories have unfolded between these two contrasting characters, and what challenges will they face together in this adventure? The continuation of this adventurous story is yours to discover.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/3.注重手法的回合制解谜（英文）.png?t=1711531628"><br/>"People think battles need powerful weapons, but strategy at hand is key." <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_3_en.gif?t=1711531628"><br/><br/>In "Cureocity," the power of your strategy is materialized as the numerical values of your hands in combat. You can swap different weapons or items held in your left and right hands to alter your character's attack and defense stats. You may also change "gestures" to focus attacks or land heavy blows on specific enemies.As you delve deeper into the dungeon, you will take the unique traits of monsters into consideration and discuss strategies with your allies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/4.你的选择决定冒险归途（英文）.png?t=1711531628"><br/>In this adventure, you'll discover not only the secrets hidden within the dungeon, but also the truths about the world and the  characters themselves. When faced with contaminated monsters, you can choose to either fight them or attempt to purify them. Of course, you also have the option to let things take their own course.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_4_en.gif?t=1711531628"><br/><br/>With each decision,the fate of the protagonists may change. The end of this adventure... is yours to decide.<h2 class="bb_tag">About the Publisher</h2>GCORES PUBLISHING is an independent game publishing venture formed by GCORES, committed to bringing you more outstanding indie games from the BOOOM CHALLENGE.<br/>Feel free to follow our <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/44750639" rel="" target="_blank">publisher webpage</a> for future updates.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midnight Ghost Hunt</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/915810/Midnight_Ghost_Hunt/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/915810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>MIDNIGHT GHOST HUNT IS A <i>PETRIFYING</i> PROP HAUNT GAME TO PLAY WITH PALS! </strong><br/><br/>Lying in wait across a series of cursed locations, relentless spirits stalk the halls. Assigned to eliminate them are the Ghost Hunters, armed to the teeth with the ghoul-busting tech to banish them to another realm! Play both Ghost and Hunter in a chaotic 4v4 struggle between the living and the dead.<br/><br/><strong>TONGUE-IN-CHEEK HIDE-AND-SEEK</strong><br/>As a Ghost, conceal yourself inside seemingly harmless pieces of furniture to evade preying Hunters… but when their backs are turned, turn the environment against them with telekinetic bombardment. No chair, lamp, or grandfather clock is innocent in this hijinks-heavy frenzy.<br/><br/><strong>MIDNIGHT MAYHEM</strong><br/>The fun isn’t over yet...when the clock strikes twelve, the witching hour begins, and the Hunters become the Hunted. The tables turn and Ghosts become supercharged, giving Hunters a limited amount of time to survive their vengeful wrath.<br/><br/><strong>MURDEROUS 4v4 MULTIPLAYER</strong><br/>Play together and communicate with your team and ensure a triumphant victory, giving each other pointers on the paths enemies tend to tread. Create synergies with your team's abilities to outthink and outwit your opponents.<br/><br/><strong>HARNESS SUPERNATURAL ABILITIES</strong><br/>The restrictions of reality don’t apply to Ghosts, of course. Claim your supernatural powers, which include turning invisible, causing furniture to float, and conjuring a dangerous Ghostly miasma. Ghosts can even hide in plain sight by masquerading as a Hunter’s doppelgänger!<br/><br/>Ghostly Perks include dramatically increasing your weight, extending your possessing range, the ability to see nearby Hunters through walls, and much more. <br/><br/><strong>ARMED AND READY</strong><br/>Hunters must choose their weapons from a full range of hi-tech gadgets designed to cast out Ghosts from our plane of existence. Detect ghostly presences with the Spectrophone, Radar and Pathfinder, capture them with a Trap, and suck up their spectral remains with the Vacuum – or just blast them to smithereens with the Spectral Cannon, sledgehammers, harpoons, salt-spewing shotguns, and more.<br/><br/>Hunters can also select Perks to give them a special boost. Choose from an extra burst of speed, health-replenishing capabilities and a host of other powers to get ahead of the game.<br/><br/><strong>A BEVY OF BLOOD-CURDLING MAPS </strong><br/>Explore ten unsettling locations, including an abandoned theatre, eerie mansion and cursed carnival. Each map brings with it different tactical considerations and items to throw about… as well as plenty of opportunities to play tricks on the enemy.<br/><br/><strong>FRIGHTENING NEW FEATURES</strong> <br/>As it crept through Steam Early Access, Midnight Ghost Hunt picked up a gaggle of game-changing features, built on the feedback of its community of Ghosts and Hunters.<br/><br/>Dedicated servers and host migration support make setting up matches a breeze, while the Progression Tier and Challenge systems bring added competition to the hunt. Looking for less of the silly and more of the scary? The Experimental Darkness game mode lends a chill to the chaos. Not to mention crossplay, full controller support, and even the GhostMaster minigame to pass the time during the van ride to your next match!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horizon Forbidden West™ Complete Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420110/Horizon_Forbidden_West_Complete_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/extras/horizon_forbidden_west_cinemagraph_610x610.gif?t=1711473066"><br/><br/>Join Aloy as she braves a majestic but dangerous new frontier that holds mysterious new threats. This Complete Edition allows you to enjoy the critically acclaimed Horizon Forbidden West on PC in its entirety with bonus content, including the Burning Shores story expansion that picks up after the main game.<br/><br/>Explore distant lands, fight bigger and more awe-inspiring machines, and encounter astonishing new tribes as you return to the far-future, post-apocalyptic world of Horizon.<br/><br/>The land is dying. Vicious storms and an unstoppable blight ravage the scattered remnants of humanity while fearsome new machines prowl their borders, and life on Earth is hurtling toward another extinction.<br/><br/>It's up to Aloy to uncover the secrets behind these threats and restore order and balance to the world. Along the way, she must reunite with old friends, forge alliances with warring new factions and unravel the legacy of the ancient past.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>See every gameplay detail with Ultrawide 21:9 and Super Ultrawide 32:9 resolutions, as well as 48:9 triple monitor support.*<br/></li><li>Witness the Forbidden West coming to life, with NVIDIA DLSS 3 upscaling and frame generation, image enhancing NVIDIA DLAA and latency reducing NVIDIA Reflex. AMD FSR and Intel XeSS are also supported.**<br/></li><li>Customize graphic settings to your preference, with the potential for unlocked frame rates.**<br/></li><li>Take control with full support for the DualSense™ controller, including haptic feedback and adaptive trigger functionality.*** </li></ul><br/>* Compatible PC and 4K display device required. <br/>** Compatible PC required. <br/>*** Wired connection required to experience the full range of in-game controller features.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age of Water: The First Voyage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2841350/Age_of_Water_The_First_Voyage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The First Voyage is the very beginning of your Age of Water experience. Jump right into the intense naval combat, craft your first boats, explore the waterworld and get a good idea of what Age of Water is about. Don’t forget to wishlist the full game now!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_ship_anim.gif?t=1711025025"><br/><br/>Become a sea captain on a post-apocalyptic Earth completely covered in water and go on an adventure in a huge open world. Sail through storms, fight and trade, capture other people's boats or build your own, extract resources from the bottom of the ocean, reveal the secrets of the Age of Water world.<br/><br/><strong>Water post-apocalypse</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_1.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>The ocean destroyed a once great civilization, but people survived and adapted. They built settlements on the roofs of tall buildings and the tops of other man-made structures. People travel across the ocean in tiny boats and huge combat vessels. The ocean provides everything they need, including extractable resources on the seabed. And yet, the dream of real land is still alive.<br/><br/><strong>True open world</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_2.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Explore the world at your own pace, discover new settlements and meet their inhabitants. Complete tasks, search for and extract valuable resources from the bottom of the ocean, earn money on trade or simply sell the artifacts you have obtained, and when you get the idea of how this world works, build your own base.<br/><br/><strong>Hundreds of unique ships</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_3.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Build boats from scratch or modify existing ones. Players have access to dozens of hulls and hundreds of parts, from which they can assemble anything ranging from a small boat to a hefty vessel 30 meters long, and then install equipment, armor and weapons. It’s important not to forget to gather a team of good crewmembers so that there is someone to stand behind machine guns and cannons or do other work on board.<br/><br/><strong>Fierce naval battles</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_4.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Pirates are always waiting for you at sea, and in some cases more aggressive players even start to chase you, so do not forget to install enough guns on your deck.  You can destroy an enemy vessel, or you can capture it in battle and take it for yourself forever. Adventures might also get you into storming enemy fortresses and defending allied settlements!<br/><br/><strong>Personal naval base</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_5.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>This shelter is reliably protected from enemies, and it allows a player to organize the production of everything that the captain may need on it. Build factories for the production of equipment, weapons, hulls for boats of all sizes, as well as the necessary resources.<br/><br/><strong>Flexible balance between PvE and PvP</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_6.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>At first, you will only meet computer opponents, but later you can challenge other players if you are confident enough in your skills and gear. Always be on the lookout: if your task is to transport illegal goods, then other players may well take the quest to hunt smugglers. In Age of Water, everyone decides for themself who they are today - a peaceful traveler or a bloodthirsty pirate.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slice &amp; Dice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1775490/Slice__Dice/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1775490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Slice &amp; Dice is a tactical dice battle roguelike.<br/><br/>Take control of 5 heroes, each with their own unique dice. Fight your way through 20 levels of monsters and try to take on the final boss. If you lose a single fight you have to start over so be careful/lucky!<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/>- 3D dice physics, choose which dice to reroll<br/>- Simple turn-based combat<br/>- Level up a hero or gain an item after each fight<br/>- Randomly-generated encounters<br/>- Ridiculous combos<br/>- Undo actions as much as you like<br/>- Each turn is like a mini-puzzle<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/>- 128 hero classes (+99999?)<br/>- 73 monsters<br/>- 473 items<br/>- Too many modes<br/>- ∞ curses<br/>- Weird modding<br/>- Online leaderboards<br/><br/><strong>Credits</strong><br/>- Created by tann (it took ~7 years)<br/>- Pixel art by a3um<br/>- Music by Ziggurath, Aleksander Zabłocki, Louigi Verona, Cold Sanctum, Ro'sø, Andrew Goodwin<br/>- Trailer by Everdraed<br/><br/>I plan to not participate in any sales/deals/bundles. No AI was used to make this game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone in the Dark</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1310410/Alone_in_the_Dark/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Alone in the Dark weaves a chilling tapestry of psychological horror and Southern Gothic charm, reimagining the iconic game that set the benchmark for the genre. We invite you to join us on a journey into madness, where each encounter could be your last. With each step you take closer to unravelling Derceto's mystery, the eyes that watch from the darkness grow hungrier. Every bullet means the difference between survival and an unthinkable end. The next door you unlock could lead to a nightmarish realm offering nothing but slashing claws, grasping tentacles, and frayed sanity.  Journey to interbellum Louisiana, where an era of decadence hides a darker tale - of escape from past traumas and an intolerant society, into the waiting grasp of something darker, something that has patiently lurked for impossible eons. This is Alone in the Dark as you've never seen it - a skillfully-woven narrative of Southern Gothic elegance and eldritch madness that pays homage to its legendary origins while taking the next step forward in survival horror storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_VIPIntro_2.gif?t=1711546287"><h2 class="bb_tag">A Haunting Tale of Mystery and Madness</h2>Step inside Derceto Manor, an asylum shrouded in intrigue, guarding a terrible secret. Client Emily Hartwood and private investigator Edward Carnby embark on a harrowing quest for answers; Emily to the mystery of her missing uncle, Edward to the toughest case he will ever face, and both to questions they dare not ask themselves. This re-envisioned classic invites you to explore an unforgettable single player adventure rich with suspense, frights, and revelations that will test the limits of your imagination.<h2 class="bb_tag">Featuring Hollywood Talent</h2>Experience some of the greatest acting survival horror has ever seen through the performances of award-winning actors Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow) in their first videogame roles. Jodie and David’s immaculately captured likenesses breathe life into Emily Hartwood and Edward Carnby, lending a deeply personal aspect to Alone in the Dark’s story that demands it be played twice to get the full experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Tribute to Horror Pioneers</h2>Rediscover the essence of psychological horror in a game that respectfully nods to its 1992 origin, the game that established the survival horror genre. Alone in the Dark is your gateway to an experience steeped in the atmospheric dread of classic horror, with next-generation storytelling and gameplay. A must-play for fans of twisted tales, nerve-wracking exploration, and desperate combat.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Story That Challenges Reality</h2>Envisioned by Mikael Hedberg, acclaimed writer behind modern horror classics “SOMA” and “Amnesia”, Alone in the Dark’s intricate web of mystery delves into themes of trauma, faith, evil, and abandonment. Whether you choose to brave the nightmare as Emily or Edward, you will uncover secrets that defy everything you thought about videogame storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Atrmo_2.gif?t=1711546287"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore Derceto Manor in this reimagination of Alone in the Dark, a love letter to the 90’s cult classic horror game.<br/></li><li>Return to the roots of psychological horror and experience an atmospheric journey worthy of the game that started the genre.<br/></li><li>Dive into a world full of sounds that make your skin crawl with a haunting, yet mesmerizing doom jazz soundtrack.<br/></li><li>Enjoy the thrill of desperate survival in a world where reality starts to crumble, evil lurks in every shadow and ammunition is scarce.<br/></li><li>Experience this nightmare from either Emily Hartwood’s or Edward Carnby’s perspective and unearth the dark secrets of a gothic mansion.<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in a deep psychological story that goes beyond the realms of the imaginable, by Mikael Hedberg, cult horror writer of SOMA and Amnesia.<br/></li><li>See Emily and Edward brought to live by the Hollywood talent of Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow), who lend their voices, their appearance, and their formidable acting skills to the protagonists.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Riddles_2.gif?t=1711546287"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Park Baseball 25</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384620/Out_of_the_Park_Baseball_25/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_banner_1.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/>We are incredibly excited to announce <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong> - the special 25th Anniversary edition of our award-winning baseball strategy series. Can you believe it's been a quarter of a century? Out of the Park Baseball is not just a game - it's a legacy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_henry.png?t=1710574531"><br/><br/>If it happens in real baseball, it happens in Out of the Park Baseball! Discover new talent, draft the next superstar, negotiate with free agents, enter trade talks with other teams, build your dynasty and guide a franchise into an infinite future! As a manager, dive into the more hands-on management and set your team's lineups, pitching staffs, in-game strategy and call the shots from the dugout. You can oversee your league at a high level, or play out each game in the gorgeous 3D game mode, managing play by play or even pitch by pitch. OOTP has it all covered!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_badge.png?t=1710574531"><br/>Here are just a few of the new features coming to <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong>:<br/><br/><strong>A game-changing new Player Development Lab!</strong><br/><br/>Shape the future of your upcoming stars! You can channel your inner Player Development Director like never before. A modern new Player Development Lab is here for every team that allows you to give players individual programs to work on, developing them how you like. Do you want your hitter to work on improving their baserunning? Bunting? Contact? Would you prefer your pitcher to work on building up their stamina? Developing a new pitch? Velocity? It's all up to you - for each of your upcoming future stars!<br/><br/><strong>Massive Player Ratings and AI Upgrade!</strong><br/><br/>It’s the most comprehensive player ratings upgrade in the 25 year history of Out of the Park Baseball! Batting, Pitching, and Fielding ratings have been painstakingly modified to capture the essence of baseball, with modifications to Contact and Power for hitters, Movement and Stuff for pitchers, the addition of Catcher Framing and Stealing Aggressiveness, and much more. BABIP is now front and center for hitters and hurlers, while new internal ratings updates allow for even more flexibility for Commissioners around the world to adjust the game to their detailed delight. Plus, the AI throughout the game has been improved dramatically to deliver the most challenging OOTP experience ever! <br/><br/><strong>Even More Detailed Player Development Control!</strong><br/><br/>Delegate how each and every player on your team will spend their time day in, day out with coaches at practice. Want your power hitter to worry less about avoiding strikeouts and put that time and effort into working on his home run swing instead? Want your aging starter to spend more time practicing his control instead of spending that time worrying about his stuff? By allocating their time and focus to the areas you want, over time you can influence how players develop, maintain their skillset, and fight the aging curve.<br/><br/><strong>2024 Rosters and Rules!</strong><br/><br/>As always, Out of the Park Baseball features up-to-the-minute 2024 MLB rosters that get updated all season long, with every franchise represented from its big league club all the way down to the low minors, and everywhere in between! Plus, OOTP 25 features officially licensed leagues from South Korea (KBO) and Europe.<br/><br/><strong>Improved Historical MLB Modes!</strong><br/><br/>Set up historical MLB games in an all new streamlined way - and benefit from vastly improved historical player ratings! It’s never been faster or easier to experience the entire history of Major League Baseball, now producing even more realistic outcomes thanks to those comprehensive ratings and simulation engine upgrades.<br/><br/><strong>New Retro Visual Immersion!</strong><br/><br/>Watch games with a variety of experiences, including retro-style black and white, ‘50s-era, and ‘70s-era television presentations. Choose from all of these to play games, watch highlights, or just catch a ballgame from a bygone era!<br/><br/><strong>New Licensed Leagues!</strong><br/><br/>For the first time ever, Out of the Park Baseball features an officially licensed Honkbal Hoofdklasse league from The Netherlands and the British Baseball Federation from the United Kingdom! Look for their official clubs, players, competitions, and more!<br/><br/><strong>For the first time ever - an official partnership with the Baseball Hall of Fame!</strong><br/><br/>What happens when you combine the only game that has the entire history of baseball and the the greatest Hall of Fame in sports? An incredible, year-long journey! Join us as we partner with the Baseball Hall of Fame all season - and beyond. Explore Hall of Fame Plaques, with the official, accurate text for each Hall of Famer. Discover incredible Hall of Fame artifacts, curated and released in fun "exhibits" over the course of the season in concert with the Hall - and more surprises too. It's going to be amazing! <br/><br/><strong>Dozens of upgrades big and small!</strong><br/><br/>--&gt; Updated in-game engine base advancement and camera movements<br/>--&gt; A new manager decision history screen gives you a look back on your best and worst trades and transactions<br/>--&gt; Improved trade packages for prospect packages <br/>--&gt; Updated two-way functionality with injured players<br/>And much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/pt_store_text_banner2.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/><br/><strong>Perfect Team is back - bigger than ever!</strong><br/><br/>It’s an all-new Perfect Team! There’s nothing in the world like the incredible online competitions of Perfect Team. Featuring by far the largest player pool ever, and taking advantage of all the player rating and balance upgrades, this year’s Perfect Team is a whole new ballgame.<br/><br/><strong>Brand New Perfect Team Combinator Series Cards!</strong><br/><br/>Pulled non-live cards have a chance to be a special Combinator Series version of the card! Use other cards that share a link (for example being teammates) with the player to get a chance to boost the raw ratings of the Combinator Series card.<br/><br/><strong>A Perfect Team Tournament Roster Builder!</strong><br/><br/>Want to design rosters for the incredible array of Perfect Team Tournaments - all on your own? For the first time ever, Perfect Team will feature a Tournament Sandbox! You can tinker to your heart's content with varying rosters for every type of tournament, with no pressure. This long-requested feature makes its debut in Out of the Park Baseball 25!<br/><br/>In addition to the brand-new Tournament Roster Builder and Combinator Series, Perfect Team 25 also features:<br/><br/><strong>Team Chemistry</strong> - Players who played together in real life will get extra bonuses when on your roster together. Players gain bonuses for seasons they played together, as well as simply being part of the same team or from the same decades<br/><strong>Perfect Team competitions starting on the first day</strong>, including a huge Opening Weekend of Tournaments with big prizes and Perfect Team Championship Series qualifying from Day One! <br/><strong>New content all season long - and beyond!</strong> All new programs, missions, competitions, and excitement await you every day.<br/><br/>Out of the Park Baseball 25 runs on PC/Mac and features the American League and National League logos, the World Series trophy, official logos and jerseys for all 30 MLB teams and 15 KBO teams, over 150 Minor League Baseball league and team logos, and historical MLB logos.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcast - A New Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1013140/Outcast__A_New_Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							20 years after the award-winning action adventure hit, Outcast, pioneered the genre of non-linear open-world games, the long-awaited sequel sees Cutter Slade return to the spectacular alien world of Adelpha. Resurrected by the almighty Yods, he has returned to find the Talans enslaved, the world stripped of its natural resources, and his own past intertwining with the invading robot forces. It's up to him to go on a mission and save the planet again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/flight_8mb.gif?t=1710511218"><br/><br/>The original team behind Outcast 1 has reunited to create this fascinating world, full of dangerous creatures and home to the Talan people – an ancient culture whose fate has become inextricably linked with earth since the events of the first game. You play as Cutter Slade, ex-Navy SEAL, sporting the same dry wit he had back in the 90s – however, the world around him has changed and eventually, so will he.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/combat01_6mb.gif?t=1710511218"><br/> <br/>To save Adelpha, you will … <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>use your jetpack to jump, air-dash, glide, and quickly traverse the fantastic in-game open world <br/></li><li>combine dozens of different modules to create your own personal weapon for taking down the robot invaders <br/></li><li>have total control to approach the story at your own pace in this non-linear world <br/></li><li>explore the world without boundaries, discover hidden temples and dangerous wildlife <br/></li><li>get familiar with the Talan culture while helping them free their villages and gain access to ancient Talan powers that use forces of nature to destroy your enemies <br/></li><li>experience a beautiful, hand-crafted world accompanied by an epic soundtrack by Outcast's original composer, Lennie Moore </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/combat02.gif?t=1710511218"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Shire: Room One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517850/Toy_Shire_Room_One/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FkhSxB2MSgD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/Toy_Shire_-_Discord_Banner.png?t=1710352808"/></a><br/><br/><br/>Play through the <strong>three levels in Kevin's Room</strong> and defend your room against your old toys. Face Memphis-X in the final level and put a stop to his assault as he crushes your soldiers in an attempt to get to your base.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyVengeance.png?t=1710352808"><br/>You received new toys from your family. Isn't that lovely? Oh, it's for sure... <br/>Your old toys, though, aren't getting along as well. They are no longer cared for and have been forgotten. So what follows next? They're going to join together against you and assault your brand-new toys, so be prepared. But never worry! You're in luck since your brand-new toys are troops of green soldiers. They still require your aid though! Control, strengthen, and defeat the opposing forces! However, focus with care, the enemies you encounter might not be your old playthings!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/InteractiveTowerDefense.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Tower building alone won't be sufficient to repel incoming attackers. Build up your own troops in the best feasible positions, then unleash attacks into enemy territory. Never abandon your towers, and deploy your troops in accordance with the traits of the enemy. First, the attacking forces will attempt to get past your defenses. Build and improve towers to aid your army. By using unique abilities, you can support your troops and towers as well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/EpicBattles.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Safeguard your base against waves of attackers. You need to pick the right troops if you would like to prevail. Clean the paths and guard any open routes. Upgrade your troops and unlock new ones to take down the waves and claim victory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyRealm.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Enter a world and a narrative built around the toys that enriched your youth, including toy soldiers, dinosaur sets, robots, building blocks, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_3.gif?t=1710352808"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dune: Imperium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1689500/Dune_Imperium/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Header.png?t=1710955211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body0_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Experience the ultimate blend of strategy and intrigue as you navigate the treacherous landscapes of Arrakis in the award-winning board game <i>Dune: Imperium</i>!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle online, locally with AI, or against the formidable House Hagal.<br/></li><li>Earn Achievements that showcase your prowess as a leader.<br/></li><li>Embark on more than a dozen Challenges that will test your wit and cunning.<br/></li><li>Compete for badges in the rotating Skirmish Mode where no two games are the same!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body1_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Arrakis. Dune. Desert Planet. Raise your banner above the vast wasteland before you. As the Great Houses of the Landsraad marshal their forces and their spies, whom will you influence, and whom will you betray? A tyrannical Emperor. The secretive Bene Gesserit. The shrewd Spacing Guild. The ferocious Fremen of the Deep Desert. The power of the Imperium can be yours, but war is not the only way to claim it.<br/><br/><i>Dune: Imperium</i> blends deck-building and worker placement in a deeply thematic new strategy game where the fate of the Empire hangs on your decisions. Will you seek political allies or rely upon military might? Economic strength or subtle intrigues? A council seat… or a sharpened blade? The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body2_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>In <i>Dune: Imperium</i>, you'll step into the role of one of the leaders of the Great Houses of the Imperium in a struggle to control the planet Arrakis and the invaluable Spice it provides.<br/><br/>The game plays out in a series of ten rounds, each of which is defined by a new Conflict on the surface of the planet; some award critical resources, and some provide Victory Points that will propel you to dominance. But choose your battles wisely: spread your forces too thin, and you'll find your enemies growing too strong to oppose.<br/><br/>Each round, you'll draw a hand of five cards from your deck, which will get stronger over the course of the game as you acquire new cards. Each card can be played in one of two ways: To send an Agent out into the Imperium to gather resources, or to Reveal at the end of the round to purchase new powerful cards. You must maintain a careful balance to get the most of the resources available to you. How will you find your path?<br/><br/>As your game progresses, you'll vie for Influence with four factions of the Imperium: The Emperor, the economically powerful Spacing Guild, the mysterious Bene Gesserit, and the ferocious Fremen of the deep deserts. Earning Influence among the various groups helps you to earn the Victory Points you need...but will you compete with your rivals for their favor, or abandon alliances to pursue other opportunities?<br/><br/>Many strategies are at your disposal, and many paths to victory. The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Footer.png?t=1710955211"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals Zero Hour</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732960/Command__Conquer_Generals_Zero_Hour/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals Zero Hour brings you closer to the enemy than ever before. Engage opposing forces at hot spots around the globe as you match strategies and arsenals against the new masterminds of modern war.<br/><br/><strong>Arsenal.</strong> Unleash the next generation of 3D new units and 20 new upgrades including China's ECM Tank, GLA's BattleBus and the USA's Spectre Gunship.<br/><br/><strong>Missions.</strong> Take on 15 new missions and make tomorrow's headlines. Root out a splinter cell in Cairo, steal deadly toxins from a U.S. lab and more.<br/><br/><strong>Generals.</strong> Match strategies and arsenals against 9 enemy commanders with unpredictable personalities and tactics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Tiberian Sun™ and Firestorm™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229880/Command__Conquer_Tiberian_Sun_and_Firestorm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Second Tiberium War begins in this legendary sequel to the original Command &amp; Conquer. <br/><br/>With his forces stronger than ever, arch villain and leader of The Brotherhood of Nod - Kane - is pitched in an epic battle against the world's war machine - the Global Defense Initiative. Now you must orchestrate the fate of mankind.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on Dynamic Battlefields. Nature itself provides tactical opportunities - destroyable and deformable terrain, forest fires, treacherous ice fields and many more surprises that help or hinder your strategies.<br/></li><li>Exciting New Strategies and Units. Jump Jet Infantry, Hover Tanks, Tunneling APCs, Hunter Seekers, Laser Fences, Mechanized Battle Units and many more.<br/></li><li>The "Veterancy" Factor. Units can become faster and stronger as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>New Kinetic Battlefields. Flying shrapnel, shock waves and crashing debris are just a few of the exciting new technologies developed to enhance the in-game experience.<br/></li><li>The mood and attitude of the battlefield comes alive like never before - covert night missions, searchlights and new defenses intensify the thrill and excitement.</li></ul><br/>Then take the battle further in <strong>Firestorm, the official expansion pack for the game</strong>. Includes all-new campaign missions, cinematics, and units to decide the future of mankind.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Renegade™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229890/Command__Conquer_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer gets up close and personal in this classic First Person Shooter for one of the most iconic franchises.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wreak Havoc</strong> - Experience the Command &amp; Conquer universe on foot as Havoc, wise-cracking GDI Commando.<br/></li><li><strong>Make Your Own Rules</strong>  - Take on the evil Brotherhood of Nod using your own mix of brute force, stealth, and strategy.<br/></li><li><strong>Assault at Ground Level</strong>  - Dish out the damage in either first or third person.<br/></li><li><strong>Total Access</strong>  - Sneak inside and explore full-scale structures, like immense Tiberium Refineries and the ominous Hand of Nod.<br/></li><li><strong>Grind the Gears</strong>  - Beef up your arsenal by commandeering lethal vehicles, such as Nod Buggies, Flame Tanks, and Mammoth Tanks.<br/></li><li><strong>Weapons of Mass Destruction</strong>  - Choose from a multitude of weapons, including the Tiberium Auto Rifle, Chemical Sprayer, and the devasting Personal Ion Cannon.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™, Counterstrike™ and The Aftermath™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229840/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_Counterstrike_and_The_Aftermath/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert</strong> pushed the envelope for the RTS genre in the mid-1990s and became one of the most iconic strategy games of all time. <br/><br/><strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert</strong>  gives you the opportunity to be more devious, cunning, and ruthless than ever before. Red Alert puts the fate of the world in your hands!<br/><br/><strong>Counterstrike</strong>, the exciting expansion pack to Red Alert, is full of clandestine activity, experimental technologies, and disavowed tactics. Includes 16 all-new missions, where you decide the ultimate fate of the struggle between the Allies and Soviets.<br/><br/><strong>In The Aftermath expansion pack</strong>, prepare for guerilla tactics, insidious strategies, and forbidden weapons. Includes 18 all-new missions and multiple units in a showdown that will test your mettle.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ and The Covert Operations™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229830/Command__Conquer_and_The_Covert_Operations/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The legendary RTS game which started it all. Will you side with the humanistic GDI or bring the world to its knees with Kane and the Brotherhood of Nod. Your adversaries are without mercy. And so are you.  <br/><br/>Includes the <strong>The Covert Operations</strong> expansion pack with a range of challenging new missions.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bot Patrol</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1800910/Bot_Patrol/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1800910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1800910/extras/header_game.jpg?t=1711553782"><br/>Prepare to dive headfirst into the quirky world of "Bot Patrol," where the daily grind takes on a whole new meaning! <br/>In this bustling asteroid station, life for bots is all about routine — wake up, punch in, push stuff around, and recharge. But one day, you notice something odd. There's a crack in the routine, something is off in all this monotony. And where did all those missing colleague bots vanish off to?<br/><br/>Embark on a truly riddled adventure through mind-bending puzzles spread across three different biomes.  Get ready for a roller coaster ride of old-school boulder dash mechanics with a large amount of extra spice. Maneuver through conveyor belt chaos, outsmart spinning guard bots with personalities bigger than their circuits, and dodge off laser barriers like a pro!<br/><br/>But beware! Every misstep could lead to disaster, from triggering contraptions gone haywire to pushing cargo drums just a tad too far. It's a race against mechanical mayhem as you uncover the secrets lurking in the station's walls. Who knew saving the day could be this much fun? There might even be freedom waiting at the end of the journey!<br/><br/>So grab your thinking cap and gear up for a quirky quest unlike any other. "Bot Patrol" is waiting for you to join the ranks of robot revolutionaries in the fight for freedom!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1800910/extras/header_play.jpg?t=1711553782"><br/>In traditional Sokoban fashion the player has to push all scattered cargo containers onto the right target spots to complete a level. Challenge comes from <i>only</i> being able to push, but not pull the barrels. This means every step has to be thought through to not end up in a scenario, where access to a container or its target is blocked.<br/><br/>Beyond the regular gameplay mechanics, Bot Patrol features an abundance of extended elements, that make achieving the goal a lot trickier. Conveyor belts, cranes, energy barriers and button triggers are added into the mix. Not to forget the evil control bots, that will perish the player upon contact.<br/><br/>And since playing the game is supposed to be a hard but fun puzzle challenge and not rage inducting repetition machine, Bot Patrol comes with a gracious infinite Undo, to take that one step back, that went to far. <br/>Or the one before. Or the one before that...<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1800910/extras/header_dev.jpg?t=1711553782"><br/>Bot Patrol has been developed by solo developer <i>a.mighty.dish</i> over the course of 3 years - as a hobby project next to a day job in AAA game development. <br/>It really started as a last big hobby project to finish before the birth of our first offspring. Natures deadlines are quite definite, so when the game was not really finished in time, development came to a halt between milk bottles and baby steps. <br/>Hot fast forward to two years later - with some small sabbatical time at hand - it seemed too much fun of a game to let it wither someone in the abandoned projects folder of ones hard drive and so Bot Patrol eventually saw the light of day!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Magical Mixture Mill</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1883800/The_Magical_Mixture_Mill/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FjZUUaZkUGP" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/extras/tmmm_store_discordbanner.png?t=1711555218"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/extras/Banner2.0.png?t=1711555218"><br/><br/>Any adventurer will tell you that <strong>Griselda’s Magical Mixtures</strong> is the go-to shop for travelers and heroes in search of performance-enhancing concoctions; be it to obtain mighty strength, incredible intelligence, enviable beauty or... less heroic needs.<br/><br/>Griselda, an elderly mushroom-loving witch, has always run the business with great dedication but time has taken its toll, and it's time to train someone who can replace her. In short, her knowledge must be handed down and <strong>YOU</strong> - a former adventurer whose career was cut short by mixture intolerance - <strong>will be the perfect candidate</strong>!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/extras/MMM-CLIP-Mix-1.gif?t=1711555218"><br/><br/>Together with your goblin assistant, <strong>build automated production lines of alchemical workstations</strong> to provide potent mixtures to the local heroes, assisting them in their epic quests, and making you their favorite potion supplier. <strong>Explore</strong> diverse biomes and use your remaining adventuring abilities to <strong>gather and research exotic ingredients</strong>, leading to new mixing opportunities. Get ready to face all the “<i>wax on, wax off</i>” challenges Griselda throws at you to bring the shop back to its former glory!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/extras/Magical_Features2.0.png?t=1711555218"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>• Accessible, automated potion brewing</strong></h2>Create fully automated production pipelines from a varied catalogue of workstations to produce potions. Balance liquid ratio, maximize potency, pick the right ingredients, balance flavors and pour it all on the fanciest bottle you can craft to create the potion!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>• A Vibrant, Cozy, and Colorful world!</strong></h2>A mix of colorful illustration designs with a pinch of cheeky classic fantasy humor but still an alchemically-cozy experience. Different environments to explore and gather your ingredients. But be careful! Some flora and fauna will fight back…<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>• Happy customers always come back! Especially if they are “hooked”</strong></h2>Not all heroes want the same potions, so take your time to get to know your customers. As they level up, their demand for stronger and more advanced mixtures grow, turning them into very loyal customers - and turning your pockets heavy with coins!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/extras/MMM-CLIP-Mix-2.gif?t=1711555218"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/extras/guide_mixedPotion_small.png?t=1711555218"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/extras/Bar2.0.png?t=1711555218"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEBEREKE Enjoy Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2869000/HEBEREKE_Enjoy_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2869000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2869000/extras/1_intro.png?t=1711551622"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2869000/extras/いんとろだくしょん用.gif?t=1711551622"><br/>Where am I pyooooo???<br/>HEBEREKE is back and so is his great and surreal adventure!<br/><br/>A mysterious little creature Hebe fell into a mysterious world.<br/>Discover a brand new world, explore every corner, find the treasures with your new wonderful friends, and use their skills to find new places.<br/><br/>The "Enjoy Edition" adds two new modes, useful features and challenging elements.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2869000/extras/2_EnjoyMode.png?t=1711551622"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2869000/extras/巻き戻し.gif?t=1711551622"><br/>You can rewind anytime by pressing the Rewind button.<br/>(*This function can be enabled or disabled)<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2869000/extras/クイックセーブロードふくりじ.gif?t=1711551622"><br/>You can save and load your play anytime. Up to 12 slots can be saved.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2869000/extras/あちーぶめんと.gif?t=1711551622"><br/> In Enjoy mode, the status of achievements can be displayed.<br/>(*Achievement display can be optionally switched ON/OFF.)<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2869000/extras/連射ふくりじ.gif?t=1711551622"><br/>Hebe's wall climbing and Jennifer's rapid ascent from underwater, can be made easier with continuous firing (jumping)!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2869000/extras/3_SpeedrunMode.png?t=1711551622"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2869000/extras/すぴらん切り出しこれ2.gif?t=1711551622"><br/>This is the mode to see how fast you can clear the game.<br/>In RANKING, you can compete with users all around the world by total time and challenge to set a new record! In addition to the total time to clear the game, the time to pass check points are also recorded.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2869000/extras/4_PickupEnjoy.png?t=1711551622"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2869000/extras/Steamx610.gif?t=1711551622"><br/><strong>1)Enjoy the story twice as much with Special Snaps.</strong><br/>Every time you discover a new event, you get a special snapshot! At any time during the game, you can enjoy comparative images and Japanese-English translations of the Japanese version of "HEBEREKE" and the Nordic version of "Ufouria: The Saga". You can see how that scene in "HEBEREKE" looks like in "Ufouria: The Saga"...!<br/>And the unique and expressive Hebe language in English translation! From core fans to international users, you can enjoy the story of "HEBEREKE" to the fullest. Two worlds with different characters and stories. Record every scene and discover the mystery of HEBEREKE. (Can you make it?)<br/>The in-game menu is available in Japanese and English, but the main story of "HEBEREKE" is only in Japanese. Please enjoy the English translation at Special Snap.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2869000/extras/資料.png?t=1711551622"><br/><strong>2) Extra</strong><br/>You can browse the package designs and instructions for the original versio of HEBEREKE.<br/>You can also view the package design and instructions for the Nordic version of 'Ufouria: The Saga'.<br/>(*Instructions can also be viewed from the menu in each game.)<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2869000/extras/アチーブメントen.png?t=1711551622"><br/><strong>3) Achievements</strong><br/>You can view all 35 achievements from the title screen.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2869000/extras/お楽しみ.png?t=1711551622"><br/><strong>4) Ranking</strong><br/>This is the mode to see how fast you can clear the game.<br/>In Ranking, you can compete with users all around the world by total time and challenge to set a new record!<br/><br/><br/><strong>★About HEBEREKE</strong><br/>HEBEREKE is a game developed by Sunsoft in 1991.<br/>The main character, Hebe, is a little creature with a unique manner of speaking. The comical universe of the game and its cute characters are what made it so popular back then.<br/>Another reason for its popularity is its action maze-like design. The player must explore every corner of the map to find their way in this surreal universe. The soundtrack is also to be mentioned: in contrast to the surreal world depicted, the music is more down-to-earth and straight to the point.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DYSCHRONIA: Chronos Alternate - Dual Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2023920/DYSCHRONIAChronos_Alternate__Dual_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2023920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Solve an impossible murder case in the far-flung future in this VR &amp; Non-VR investigation action adventure!<br/>DYSCHRONIA: Chronos Alternate has won multiple VR awards, including dominating seven categories at the NYX Game Awards and was a nominated finalist for Game of the Year in the 2023 VR Awards. The Steam version contains all three award-winning episodes in a single game. Now you can play each episode however you like in either <strong>VR or non-VR mode</strong>! <br/><br/>You are Special Supervisor Hal Scion, a detective with the ability to rewrite the past. Your mission: solve a theoretically impossible crime. Uncover the mysteries hidden in people and places, reality and dream. You'll need to keep your wits about you if you're going to survive the unexpected threats awaiting you!<br/>A premonition foretells of the city's destruction in seven days.<br/>Will you be able to uncover the truth and change the course of the future?<br/><br/><strong>■ Game System</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>[Memory Diving] Plunge into the past and alter reality as you try to crack the case.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2023920/extras/StoreGif_1.gif?t=1711551503"><br/></img></li><li>[Augmented Dreaming] Enter a stunning virtual world teeming with countless shoals of digital fish.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2023920/extras/StoreGif_3.gif?t=1711551503"><br/></img></li><li>[Trusty Companion] You may have one of the toughest cases the city has ever seen on your hands, but you don't have to go it alone. Lily, your navigation robot, is there to support you every step of the way. If you get stuck, just speak to Lily. You never know what you'll find out!<br/></li><li>[Puzzles] Clues lie hidden across the city for you to find, but the deeper you dig, the more mysteries you'll unearth. Search far and wide, high and low, for vital clues.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2023920/extras/StoreGif_2.gif?t=1711551503"><br/></img></li><li>[High-Stakes Stealth] Evade danger in life-or-death moments during your investigation.<br/></li><li>[Trial by AI] Reenact the crime with the evidence you collect and prove your theories beyond all doubt.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2023920/extras/StoreGif_4.gif?t=1711551503"/></li></ul><br/><strong>■ Story</strong><br/>Marine city, Astrum Close. Crime rate: 0.001%.<br/>Here, dreams are utilized to ensure crime is prevented before it even happens.<br/><br/>When the founder of this so-called paradise is killed in an unprecedented, theoretically impossible incident, Special Supervisor Hal Scion is tasked with unraveling the mystery threatening to plunge the city into disaster.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clean the Sea!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2232320/Clean_the_Sea/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2232320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a voyage of environmental salvation and collection with <i>Clean the Sea!</i>—a compelling experience now on Steam.<br/><br/>In a world where the oceans are burdened by humanity's neglect, <i>Clean the Sea!</i> challenges you to pilot a lone vessel on a noble quest: cleanse the waters, rescue marine life, and turn the tide on pollution. As you navigate through tranquil yet troubled waters, your mission is not just to collect refuse but to catalyze change—one scoop of trash at a time.<br/><br/>Your quest will take you across the globe to some of the most iconic and afflicted waterways on the planet. Each location offers unique challenges and opportunities, from the icy embrace of the Antarctic to the historic waterways of Amsterdam. As you progress, you'll witness the tangible impact of your efforts, bringing life and color back to places once choked by waste.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2232320/extras/Collect-trash.png?t=1711551087"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2232320/extras/collecttrash.gif?t=1711551087"><br/>Dive into "Clean the Sea!" where your main quest is to pick up trash. Every piece you collect—bottles, bags, you name it—helps clean up the ocean. Sell the trash, get cash, and watch as the sea transforms back to its natural beauty.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2232320/extras/Hire-a-fleet.png?t=1711551087"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2232320/extras/Worker.gif?t=1711551087"><br/>Start with a small skiff and aim high. Upgrades make a big difference: a faster ship speeds up your clean-up missions, and a larger picker increases how much trash you can collect. Upgrade from a skiff to a cruiser, making your clean-up efforts more effective and far-reaching.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2232320/extras/Upgrade-your-ship.png?t=1711551087"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2232320/extras/Upgrade_Vehicles.gif?t=1711551087"><br/>Boost your clean-up game by hiring a fleet of mini-ships. These vessels autonomously collect trash, multiplying your impact without extra effort from you. This fleet represents your commitment to efficiency, helping you tackle more of the ocean's pollution with every trip.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2232320/extras/Save-the-animals.png?t=1711551087"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2232320/extras/Save_Animals.gif?t=1711551087"><br/>As the trash clears, marine life returns to the once-polluted waters. Witness the transformation as dolphins, turtles, and fish reappear, breathing life back into their habitats. This revival of ocean life is a beautiful testament to your hard work and dedication to the cause.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>String Theory</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2883220/String_Theory/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2883220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Draw lines between pegs to create loops. The loops fill in with a different color depending on how many pegs they touch.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Any loop that touches either <strong>three </strong>pegs or <strong>six </strong>pegs turns green.<br/></li><li>Any loop that touches either <strong>four </strong>pegs or <strong>eight </strong>pegs turns purple.<br/></li><li>Any loop that touches either <strong>five</strong> pegs or <strong>seven</strong> pegs turns spotted purple.</li></ul><br/>Replicating the given pattern with as few loops as possible requires strategic placement and overlapping of loops.<br/><br/>With dozens of handcrafted patterns to match, and thousands additional free play patterns, String Theory is a mind-bending game filled to the brim with tricky puzzles to get the gears turning!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLEASE STOP CRYING</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2757840/PLEASE_STOP_CRYING/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a helpless father who has to balance completing a series of house chores and babysitting, before his wife gets home. <br>
<br>
<br>
PLEASE STOP CRYING is a horror game with a design of emulating the stress one may experience when looking out for a baby. Ever considered having kids? Think of this as a demo for what you will have to go through at times. <br>
<br>
FEATURES:<br>
<br>
This is a fast paced FPS lighthearted horror game where your goals are to complete as many chores as you can before being interrupted by the baby. <br/>
<br/>
Complete all the chores as quickly as you can to achieve a record time and the honorable title of "DAD OF THE YEAR".<br/>
<br/>
Enjoy the crispy 90's era graphics for the best experience.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missile Dancer 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2566090/Missile_Dancer_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2566090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Missile Dancer 2 is a new sprite scaler shmup that combines rail shooter and caravan STG.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>New sprite scaler shmup.<br/></li><li>Exhilarating lock-on system.<br/></li><li>Arcade mode and Caravan mode.<br/></li><li>Supports online ranking.<br/></li><li>Equipped with chiptune using FM sound.</li></ul><br/><strong>Arcade mode:</strong><br/>In arcade mode, you will clear 16 stages along the story.<br/>The mission will be completed when you clear all the stages. There are 3 levels of difficulty.<br/><br/><strong>Caravan mode:</strong><br/>In caravan mode, compete for high scores on a dedicated stage for only 3 minutes.<br/><br/>All modes support local ranking and online ranking.<br/><br/><strong>Story</strong><br/>Having developed space exploration technology, humans immigrated to the habitable planet ONEAS. The social order on ONEAS was maintained by the mother computer, and humans were building a civilization on ONEAS as a second Earth. However, the defense system that had maintained peace suddenly went out of control and launched an attack on humanity. The space government determined that the cause was the runaway mother computer and decided to destroy it, and dispatched its latest fighter "Missile Dancer" toward the center of ONEAS, where the mother computer was located.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terra Memoria</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1912750/Terra_Memoria/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1912750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Terra Memoria welcomes you with open arms: six lovable characters, an investigation through all ages, a world with crazy inhabitants, and cozy music… a little RPG with exploration, fighting, construction, and puzzles. <br/><br/>Visit the past and present to discover who controls the crystals, why the ancient machines are attacking, and how everything is linked (nooo, really?😱)<h2 class="bb_tag">Main characteristics </h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1912750/extras/TeM_600px_1.gif?t=1711555688"><br/><br/>Set up your camp with the handyman and the blacksmith while the summoner and the sorcerer cook tonight’s dinner. By the fireside, stories of a shapeshifter and the tunes of a bard resonate. That’s how another day of travel with your new friends ends. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1912750/extras/TeM_600px_2.gif?t=1711555688"><br/><br/>Discover a cute little RPG and its world that combines 3D and pixel art, as well as its authentic music crafted with love. <br/><br/>What’s important is the journey! Take your time, take every path, and befriend eccentric citizens (why are they so weird?). <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1912750/extras/TeM_600px_3.gif?t=1711555688"><br/><br/>Use a unique construction tool to change the world and solve puzzles. Buildings and decorations – craft everything and construct a village! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1912750/extras/TeM_600px_5.gif?t=1711555688"><br/><br/>A local recipe, the mayor’s portrait, or a real false treasure map? Every piece of information is good to add to this participatory publication. <br/><br/>Will you find the clues hidden there?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Castle Constructor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1555310/Castle_Constructor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Choose your Blocks, Build your Castle, Save the Kingdom!</strong></h2>Castle constructor is a new take on the tower defense genre. Design your castle how you want it using a modular system of unique, interlocking, inter-working blocks. Stack them up high or spread them out across the map as you try to build the perfect defense.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555310/extras/Building.gif?t=1711545493"><br/><br/>Landscapes like deserts, mountains, rivers, and hills come with their own advantages and challenges. Fend off waves of enemies who will try to climb over and break through your defenses. From lowly soldiers to powerful siege weapons, you will need to defeat them all as you strive to protect your kingdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555310/extras/Ballista.gif?t=1711545493"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Modes:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Campaign - Play through multiple campaign levels to earn resources which can be used to purchase techs and new tokens that provide blocks, actions, or upgrades that can be played during a level.<br/></li><li>Endless Mode - Fight off endless waves of enemies, earning coins and purchasing new blocks and technology as you try to survive as long as possible.<br/></li><li>Creative Mode - Free play mode. With an infinite number of each card you can build your castle however you want it. Then you can design your own wave of enemies to send against your castle to see how it fares. </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555310/extras/Siege_Tower.gif?t=1711545493"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Modular Castle Building - Build your castle out of multiple different blocks, stacking them up to 5 per tile and taking advantage of both height and adjacency effects. <br/></li><li>3d hex maps - Each map is made out of 3d hex tiles with different features like hills, cliffs, rivers, and more.<br/></li><li>Complex Pathfinding - No fixed paths here. Enemy paths will react as you build up your castle as well as when it is destroyed. Enemies are intent on getting to your keep, going around or even climbing over your walls if it will get them there faster.<br/></li><li>Projectile Physics - Projectiles are physically simulated and can end up hitting a different target or missing entirely.<br/></li><li>Techs - Purchase techs in the campaign or during an endless level to improve your towers. Make enemies climb slower, add more defenders to your walls, and more. </li></ul><br/><a href="steam://openurl_external/https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?url=https://discord.gg/d6UpG2ZVae"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555310/extras/Discord_Header.png?t=1711545493"/></a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blub</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2750190/Blub/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2750190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Guide Blub through levels containing strange enemies. Help him find his way to meet his friends. find keys to advance,<br>
<br>
and enter doors.<br>
<br>
Watch out for rats wearing hard hats<br>
<br>
and spiders, they can catch you pretty quickly<br/>
<br/>
There are phone and post boxes that will chase you when you get too close<br/>
<br/>
use the platforms and jump on tyres to find your way through<br/>
<br/>
Watch out for flying fish<br/>
<br/>
Its a fun game, you decide the pace you like to play at.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billy's Game Show</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2762290/Billys_Game_Show/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2762290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2762290/extras/about.png?t=1711541116"><br/><br/><br/>You're the current contestant in a twisted game environment designed by Billy himself, for his own twisted enjoyment. Billy's Game Show set is made for you to choose your own path, but remember, it's Billy's game, and he sets the rules. He will challenge you with traps, hidden paths, different puzzles, and most importantly, three generators which need you to consistently keep an eye open, otherwise, they will eliminate you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2762290/extras/game_mechanics.png?t=1711541116"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Choose your own path to advance.</li></ul> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Avoid being caught by Billy, or hide when he comes.</li></ul> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Do your tasks quietly and out of sight.</li></ul> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Billy's set is full of traps, so be aware at all times.</li></ul> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Manage your inventory smartly, do not overload it.</li></ul> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> Make sure the three main generators are running smoothly.</li></ul> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2762290/extras/game_billy.gif?t=1711541116"><br/><br/><strong><i>AND MUCH MORE</i></strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst Coach in the World</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2854250/Worst_Coach_in_the_World/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This lighthearted visual novel follows Valentina, a former competitive skater who leaves her skating life behind for an office job far, far away from home. Little is she prepared to end up managing a rundown resort in rural Ukraine, let alone one which has a skating rink at the heart of its shopping mall.<br/><br/>Fate takes an unexpected turn when a freak accident thrusts Valentina and the resort into viral sensations. With the resort's newfound popularity, Valentina must now work tirelessly to transform the derelict and slightly haunted mall into a proper holiday destination.<br/><br/>At the same time, she is reluctantly tasked with managing the once-deserted ice skating rink and keep its skaters under control.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/Characters.png?t=1711538365"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/oksana_steam.png?t=1711538365"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/elena_steam.png?t=1711538365"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/alexei_steam.png?t=1711538365"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/dmytro_steam.png?t=1711538365"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/irina_steam.png?t=1711538365"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/yulia_steam.png?t=1711538365"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/sandro_steam.png?t=1711538365"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/lyudmyla_steam.png?t=1711538365"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/pedro_steam.png?t=1711538365"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/info.png?t=1711538365"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/book.png?t=1711538365"> Linear storyline, 3-hour read.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/skates.png?t=1711538365"> Anatomically correct figure skating positions.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/handicap.png?t=1711538365"> As a severely handicapped sufferer of spinal cord injury (C5-7), my fingers are extremely weak and twitchy, so I sincerely hope you can forgive my use of AI-assisted art in this solo project.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/About_the_author.png?t=1711538365"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854250/extras/mark_steam.png?t=1711538365"><br/><br/>Hi there, my name is Mark Leung. You may know me as the creator of College Saga.<br/><br/>In June 2021, I fell and broke my neck while training my backflip. Immediately, I lost sensation and control below my chest and could hardly move my fingers. Such was spinal cord injury, a cruel and utterly humiliating condition with no cure as of today. To make things worse, I developed a life-threatening bedsore in the ICU in my lower back, which took 2 major surgeries to 'dig out' and fill with surrounding flesh, and months of daily treatments. <br/><br/>After a year of spitting into cough-assist machines and staring at hospital ceilings, I was discharged, having regained nearly no control of my body. I continue to deal with sensitivity to cold, persistent lower back pain, and the daily struggle of dizziness and low blood pressure that takes me up to 2 hours to gradually rise out of bed. Having minimal control with my core, I am always at risk of tipping sideways or forward unless I keep an arm on my wheelchair. With weak fingers, I can't click normal mouses or move around on my wheelchair. I am now 30% of my former self carrying a load of dead weight. I literally can't even steal candy from my own baby.<br/><br/>Being trapped in this body 24/7 has taken a significant toll on my mental health. I have never experienced such an overwhelming and profound sense of shame and loneliness. Knowing about my creative past, my doctor advised me to create once again as a means to prevent myself from spiraling into depression. A form of escapism, if you will. So here is what the doctor ordered: a fun, lighthearted visual novel inspired by 22 years of figure skating.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distant Bloom</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1450250/Distant_Bloom/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to <strong>Distant Bloom</strong>, a <strong>cozy management and exploration game</strong> far away from home!<br/><br/>After a long expedition through space, you and your crew land on an alien planet with the critical mission of establishing a new home for your species. But this place is very different from the vision you saw through your telescope. What happened to the verdant life of this world? <i>And what will happen to you?</i> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/extras/DBGIF1.gif?t=1711545126"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Explore</strong> a desolate world and <strong>restore </strong>its blooming past with the power of plants!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/extras/DistantBloom_newGIF1.gif?t=1711545126"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Nurture new life by learning how to care for an amazingly varied alien flora.</strong> Play around with plant structures and create <strong>a thriving ecosystem!</strong><br/></li><li>Turn your harvest into<strong> recipes, tools, and items</strong> that you can use to build and <strong>improve your homebase.</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/extras/DistantBloom_newGIF2.gif?t=1711545126"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Reunite your scattered crew</strong> into a community where each member has their <strong>own story to tell.</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Explore the wilds to uncover the history of this strange planet.</strong> What <i>–or who–</i> left behind the puzzling ruins scattered across the land?<br/></li><li><strong>Change the world!</strong> Your actions will impact not only nature but also the <strong>future of your crew.</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/extras/DistantBloom_newGIF3.gif?t=1711545126"><br/><br/>Distant Bloom is an <strong>accessible and rewarding game</strong> that offers a <strong>warm, sheltered, and intimate experience.</strong> Explore, create, and bring nature <strong>closer to home!</strong><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FygVMn2Yser" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/extras/discord_banner_DB.png?t=1711545126"/></a> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OG Puzzlers: Synthwave Knights</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2872780/OG_Puzzlers_Synthwave_Knights/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2872780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>OG Puzzlers: Synthwave Knights</strong> is an puzzel game with cool knights in an stunning synthwave style. You have to assemble a single image from random generated indivdual pieces. <br/>Combine all of the smart singel frames into one big image and unlock the next level.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 12 Levels<br/></li><li> puzzle adventure<br/></li><li> auto saving<br/></li><li> simple mouse control<br/></li><li> 100 steam awards</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trust No One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2689610/Trust_No_One/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2689610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You'll need to think outside more than just the box. In "Trust No One,” a point-and-click detective adventure, you play as a journalist who tries to unravel a web of secrets about a mysterious AI-company. Explore the nooks and alleyways of Kyiv to discover the identity of your informant. "Trust No One" beckons you to embrace curiosity. The game's narrative unfolds beyond the ordinary, urging you to think outside conventional boundaries. “Trust No One” is the latest from the Ukrainian game studio Triomatica, following the success of “Boxville,” the winner of DevGamm's Best Mobile Game award in 2022 and GDWC Best Mobile Game award in 2023.<br>
<br>
What you can expect to see in Trust No One:<br>
- Hand-drawn graphics — all backgrounds and objects are carefully drawn by our artist.<br>
- Locations were inspired by real buildings and places in Kyiv, Ukraine.<br>
- Logical puzzles and mini-games are tightly incorporated into the story of the game.<br>
- Atmosphere of mystery, conspiracy and detective adventure.<br>
- Need to be vigilant and attentive to find out what is going on.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wrath of the Goose King</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2787630/The_Wrath_of_the_Goose_King/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787630/extras/Cs01.png?t=1711530486"><br/><br/>The <strong>Wrath of the Goose King</strong> is a turn-based roguelite, where you recruit red pandas, collect powerful spells and gear to fight the evil Goose King and his minions. Create your perfect team and show the geese who is the boss!<h2 class="bb_tag">Fight your way through the Goose Army</h2>Join Hiro, our red panda protagonist, as he tries to break free from the Goose King's grasp. Each of your escape attempts are unique: you will encounter different power-ups, team members, enemies and events. You can even unlock permanent bonuses as you progress through the story.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787630/extras/GIF2.gif?t=1711530486"><h2 class="bb_tag">Join the panda party</h2>Other red pandas have your back! Recruit combat specialists, such as Sir Muffins, the devoted paladin; or Pandalf a traditional spellcaster, to boost the power of your pandaparty. There are 12 classes to choose from. Give all of them a try and master their combat style.<h2 class="bb_tag">Designed for replayability</h2>Enhance the might of your party even further by obtaining additional spells, gear and ice cream bonuses. There are over a 100 spells to try, another 100 gear pieces to equip and 12 ice cream bonuses to taste for additional flavor. Find powerful synergies to become stronger than the Goose King himself!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787630/extras/TrailerGIF.gif?t=1711530486"><h2 class="bb_tag">A journey you will remember</h2>On your quest to save all red pandakind, you will meet dozens of funny characters and enemies to ensure your journey is memorable. Once you have finished the main story, you can unlock 9 secret endings to discover secrets about the main characters, learn more about the world or just to have a good laugh!<br/><br/>Don't be a silly goose: recruit your pandamembers and join the fray!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787630/extras/PromoArt05.png?t=1711530486"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M.O.O.D.S.: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2771200/MOODS_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2771200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">This is a completely free Prologue for our upcoming game. For Coop - assign friends' controllers in the settings OR play via Remote Play Together. If you like the game, feel free to wishlist it and stay updated for the latest features :)</h2><br/><i>▪️ The "Mood Solution" corrupted a civilization of sentient mechs, leading them to form hostile fractions based on singular emotion.<br/>▪️ A small group of not corrupted mechs take up arms to correct the mistakes of the past.<br/>▪️ Engage in combat with a wide variety of firearms and weapon enhancements.<br/>▪️ Can you survive this bullet-hell and restore the once-thriving robot society?</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2771200/extras/Moods_Title_1_ENG.png?t=1711532616"><br/>Each of the <strong>4 Moods</strong> has its own unique <strong>Abilities </strong>and skill trees to explore during the run. <br/>🛡️ <strong>Pride </strong>is covered by a reflection <strong>Shield</strong>, 💘<strong>Love </strong>conquers enemies to <strong>fight on your side</strong>, 🐶<strong>Sorrow </strong>brings the <strong>support mech dog</strong>, and 👿<strong>Anger</strong> just goes <strong>berserk</strong>.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2771200/extras/Moods_Gif_1_ENG.gif?t=1711532616"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2771200/extras/Moods_Title_2_ENG.png?t=1711532616"><br/>Weapons can be heavily altered with <strong>Add-Ins</strong> that enhance certain aspects of your gun or outright <strong>change the way it operates</strong>. Change the bullets' trajectory, add additional effects — you can even freeze time!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2771200/extras/Addin_Dev_Showcase-MOODS.gif?t=1711532616"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2771200/extras/Moods_Title_3_ENG.png?t=1711532616"><br/>Lords of the mech world have gone insane due to the Mood Solution. The only option is to reboot them, but to do so you need to try and defeat them first. Before engaging in battle, choose your dialogue options based on your emotion class. You might not talk them out of the fight, but they could greatly decrease their fighting spirit... or go berserk.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2771200/extras/Boss_Talk_MOODS.gif?t=1711532616"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2771200/extras/Moods_Title_4_ENG.png?t=1711532616"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Base Building</strong><br/>Transform barren robot junkyard into a cozy base. Meet friendly mechs through your journey and invite them to your place.<br/></li><li><strong>Local Multiplayer</strong><br/>This is the game you can play together with your friends! Add controllers or invite your friends via Remote Play Together! <br/></li><li><strong>Procedural Generation</strong><br/>Blast your way through procedural dungeons in classic rogue-lite style! Each biome has unique enemies and environmental hazards. <strong>No run will be the same!</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Fierce Battles</strong><br/>Engage in heated battles! Disassemble or get disassembled - Mercy is not an emotion these mechs have, so be prepared to get riddled with bullets.<br/></li><li><strong>Upgrade Yourself</strong><br/>Learn from your mistakes, upgrade and head back. Unlock more weapons, enhancements and gears, as well as increase your stats.</li></ul><br/><br/><strong>Want to share feedback with us??? Join the <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FdfYQp8AEtv" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Discord</a>!</strong><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1956770/MOODS/" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1956770/MOODS/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar King</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2476640/Dollar_King/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2476640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cute &amp; cool cat politicians battle in this deck-building game!<br>
Play unlimited against players worldwide in this online two-player game!<br>
Win by collecting more votes than your opponent using a variety of cards!<br>
<br>
Start with the same deck and enhance it!<br>
Collect money with Tax, utilize your turn better with Act, remove unnecessary cards with Reorg, obstruct your opponent with Imp, and permanently strengthen yourself with Enh. The strategy is limitless!<br>
Experience the excitement of expanding reproduction!<br/>
A definitive multiplayer board game where you can enjoy different plays every time!<br/>
<br/>
Rate and ranking, friend matches, cross-platform play, and cute emotes are all included!<br/>
<br/>
Users who engage in the following actions may be restricted in part or in all functionalities: Causing trouble or discomfort to others, defamation, acts against public order and morals, deliberately tampering with the game, exchanging personal information.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matsutake Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867250/Matsutake_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2867250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Stick the same mushrooms together to evolve! </h2>Aim for a high score by changing mushrooms to prevent them from overflowing the basket!<br/>If the basket overflows, the game is over.<br/>Aim for a high score by creating large matsutake mushrooms!<h2 class="bb_tag">Mode</h2>There are two modes: "Normal Mode" and "Shiitake Mode" with only Shiitake mushrooms!<h2 class="bb_tag">Ranking</h2>Aim for the top ranking and make matsutake mushrooms!<h2 class="bb_tag">What is the function for streamers? </h2>A function to play in portrait mode for streamers is included.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Streamer Guidelines</strong></h2>・It can be distributed without permission, regardless of whether it is an individual or a corporation.<br/>・We are not responsible for any damage caused by distributing videos of this game.<br/>-The contents of these guidelines may change without notice.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jet Skiing Race</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2879230/Jet_Skiing_Race/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2879230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare to immerse yourself in the ultimate aquatic thrill ride with Jet Skiing Race! <br>
<br>
Command powerful watercraft and plunge into heart-pounding races set amidst dynamic waterways. Pit your skills against seasoned rivals on ever-changing tracks, mastering sharp bends, executing jaw-dropping stunts, and employing cunning tactics to secure victory. <br>
<br>
With your goal set on podium glory, brace yourself to ride the waves and dominate the competition in this adrenaline-charged jet skiing extravaganza.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br/>
- Experience High-Octane Jet Ski Racing<br/>
- Conquer multiple exhilarating levels<br/>
- Embark on special missions, including transporting passengers by ship						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Explorer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2378130/The_Last_Explorer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2378130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Explore an alien planet and its creatures</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2378130/extras/Banner_Exploration.gif?t=1711527136"><br/>Explore an open world full of creatures to learn more about, find all the wreckage from your spaceship and use your camera to learn more about the creatures, the world and how you got there.<br/><br/><strong>Help the alien inhabitants</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2378130/extras/Banner_Gliding.gif?t=1711527136"><br/>Throughout your journey you'll be able to do quests for the aliens or just play minigames with them.<br/><br/><strong>Take beautiful photos</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2378130/extras/Banner_Photos.gif?t=1711527136"><br/>Use your camera to take beautiful photos and analyze your environment. Throughout your journey you'll find new effects to take even better and more unique photos.<br/><br/><strong>A living world</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2378130/extras/Banner_Creatures.gif?t=1711527136"><br/>There are many different creatures you can study, photograph and befriend. Photograph them to learn more and use bait to befriend and ride them.<br/><br/><strong>Discover what happened to the other explorers</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2378130/extras/Banner_Simulation.gif?t=1711527136"><br/>Find out how your ship crashed and what happened to the other astronauts by exploring the island and photographing the wreckage to analyze it and learn more.<br/><br/><strong><u>The Last Explorer features:</u></strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A beautiful open world you can explore any way you want<br/></li><li>Complex creatures to study and befriend<br/></li><li>Small side quests<br/></li><li>A highly customizable camera system<br/></li><li>Many interesting camera effects<br/></li><li>Old spaceship wreckage to learn more about<br/></li><li>A mystery to uncover<br/></li><li>Land, Air and Water creatures<br/></li><li>Xbox controller support</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Box 5: Elements</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2882350/Mystery_Box_5_Elements/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2882350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>A UNFORGETTABLE PUZZLE ADVENTURE </strong><br/>Explore a new series of intricate boxes filled with alluring enigmas and brain-teasing challenges that will leave you a lasting impression<br/><br/><strong>THE ELEMENTS STONE</strong><br/>Unlock all 10 boxes of the game and play this extra challenge in the room of the Elements Stone<br/><br/><strong>EXCEPTIONAL GAME DESIGN</strong><br/>With a straightforward user interface and captivating puzzles, this game promises an engaging experience that expertly balances challenge and entertainment, keeping you engaged for hours.<br/><br/><strong>A CAPTIVATING SOUNDTRACK</strong><br/>Each Box has its music theme, for you to play this adventure in a transcendental way<br/><br/><strong>GOT STUCK?</strong><br/>Click the bulb button in the scene to get a hint that will help you solve the puzzles. <br/>In case you got really stuck on a puzzle, feel free to get in touch with the developer to get some more hints<br/><br/><strong>SHARE YOUR ACHIEVEMENTS</strong><br/>Let your community and friends know what you're playing and how far you've gone in this escape room adventure!<br/><br/>——————————•——————————<br/><br/><strong>XSGames</strong> is an indie game dev from Italy, since 2021, creator of the <strong>Mystery Box</strong> and <strong>The Da Vinci Cryptex</strong> game series						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotional flow</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2714100/Emotional_flow/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2714100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Your friend has been kidnapped by three mysterious figures and you are the only one who can rescue her!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2714100/extras/StoryGif.gif?t=1711525458"><br/><br/>Control a character that only moves left and right and your emotions are your only way to succeed.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2714100/extras/GameplayGif.gif?t=1711525458"><br/><br/>Fight against 3 different bosses each representing a mental illness.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2714100/extras/BossesGif.gif?t=1711525458"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geneforge 2 - Infestation</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2480560/Geneforge_2__Infestation/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Geneforge 2 – Infestation is a truly open-ended fantasy adventure in a unique world of alien fantasy. You are one of the Shapers, wizards with the awesome power to create life. Want a tool, a trap, an army? You summon it into existence. You create mighty beasts, and they totally obey you. Usually.<br>
<br>
But your people have grown lazy and complacent, and a threat has appeared. Your creations are no longer content to serve you. You are lost in a wild, savage mountain range. A rebellion is growing there, and it offers you awesome power if you join. Will you use your powers to destroy the rebels or aid them? Bring peace or lead them to war? The choices are all yours!<br>
<br>
Geneforge 2 – Infestation offers unmatched freedom in how you play. Fight alone with blades, missiles, or magic, or create your own army of custom-made mutant monsters. Alternately, use trickery, diplomacy, and stealth to win the game without ever attacking a foe. There's no 'bad guy'. Choose between a host of rival factions or just destroy everything.<br>
<br>
Geneforge 2 is an epic fantasy adventure with almost ninety zones to explore, 50+ hours of gameplay, and huge replayability. Choose from dozens of spells, weapon skills, abilities, and creations to make to reach a vast array of different endings. The rebellion has begun. Awesome wealth and power is yours for the taking. What will you do?<br>
<br>
Geneforge 2 – Infestation is a total remaster of our 2003 cult-classic Geneforge 2. It contains new areas, quests, characters, and dialogue, a redone interface and systems, and a complete reworking of every single thing to bring it into the modern era of gaming.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Split Personality Doctor: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2858930/Split_Personality_Doctor_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2858930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2858930/extras/story_en.png?t=1711523552"><br/>A doctor in a small town suddenly gained the ability to shrink his body, so he shrunk his body into various patients' bodies and treated diseases by eliminating the virus in the patients' bodies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2858930/extras/features_en.png?t=1711523552"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dominating Summon Combat: Although the Doctor himself has some attack ability, he mainly needs to fight through summons.<br/></li><li>Cooperate with summons to trigger skills.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2858930/extras/g6.gif?t=1711523552"><br/></img></li><li>Each summon has its own special attack mode, which can be upgraded and synthesized to create a more powerful summon.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2858930/extras/composite.png?t=1711523552"><br/></img></li><li>The Doctor can choose a base weapon, and different summons will activate different characteristics of the weapon, such as ejection, explosion, burning, freezing, etc.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2858930/extras/g5.gif?t=1711523552"><br/></img></li><li>Easy to use (only need to control the direction of movement), super refreshing, roguelikes, fast pace (no more than 30 minutes per game).<br/></li><li>Hundreds of items and summons, build different combinations.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2858930/extras/召唤物集合.png?t=1711523552"/></li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>River Town Factory: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2847250/River_Town_Factory_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							River Town Factory: Prologue vs. Official Version Differences<br/>*Special Note: Prologue save data can all be transferred to the official version.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>In the Prologue version, players can increase the favorability of all romanceable NPCs up to 4 hearts.<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, players can increase the favorability of all regular NPCs up to 4 hearts.<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, players can access up to T1 node in the Oracle Temple.<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, 15% of buildings and technologies are available.<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, players can explore the Central Region, including martial arts and relic caves within the region.<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, players can reach a maximum of Level 2 on the SwordWay Sect and River Town Bounty Board (Somewhat Famous).<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, players can participate in the Spring Festival, including the Flower Festival and Qingming Festival.</li></ul><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FwNSHHEB2EJ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/discord.jpg?t=1711550847"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/en1.png?t=1711550847"><br/><br/>Create automated production assembly lines, from wooden planks to circuit boards, design every step of your production line.<br/>Unlock future technologies gradually, from silicon purification to photovoltaic power generation, and build your futuristic workshop.<br/>Use inter-district teleportation stations to receive products at various levels, expanding your factory's territory to the entire continent.<br/>From brewing and oil pressing to manufacturing ovens, even producing watches and antibiotics, astound ancient people with your futuristic goods!<br/>Reinforced concrete, rubber, and large-scale computers, these will be the mass-produced materials you use in the ancient times, a thousand years ago!!!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/steamgif.gif?t=1711550847"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/en2.png?t=1711550847"><br/><br/>There are 12 characters that can be pursued in the game - the royal, the martial arts world, the merchant, etc. Unlock the secrets of each character and pursue the friendships and romances you desire. Choose your partner and discuss marriage, and together move into the workshop where they will provide powerful assistance. Make connections with nearly 30 historical figures, each with their own changing schedules throughout the four seasons. Participate in their lives and use modern knowledge to solve their problems. In the River Town, everything happens naturally, and you have the final say on when to work, explore, and engage in romantic pursuits.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/rwall.gif?t=1711550847"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/rwstory.gif?t=1711550847"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/en3.png?t=1711550847"><br/><br/>A fast-paced combat system that is easy to pick up, combining evasion and offense to defeat your enemies through strategic maneuvers. Whether through formal training or adventures in the martial arts world, master more than 40 martial arts techniques including external skills, internal skills, light skills, and hard skills, allowing you to dominate the martial arts world.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/4zd.gif?t=1711550847"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/en4.png?t=1711550847"><br/><br/>Explore the four major villages on the map, complete village quests, and uncover their secrets.<br/>Explore the mystical realms left behind by ancient predecessors, delve deep into them, and defeat bizarre creatures.<br/>Explore the entire continent, discover treasures, explore bat caves, and punish bandits for the people.<br/>Sign contracts with mine owners throughout the entire map, allowing ancient people to work for you.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/5zddd.gif?t=1711550847"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/en5.png?t=1711550847"><br/><br/>Be a skilled craftsman or a social butterfly? Become the top martial artist or a versatile expert in everyday life? It's all up to you to decide.<br/>Craft spiritual medicines, weapons, and clothing, becoming a master of ancient craftsmanship.<br/>Create over 20 different dishes with various enhancements, such as Five Treasures Stew and Snowy Sunset Soup... Make them in your kitchen!<br/>Fill the Heavenly Workshop with the products you create, allowing ancient people to visit and witness modern technology.<br/>Utilize the power of future technology to repair the time machine and fulfill a mission that only you can accomplish.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/6zd.gif?t=1711550847"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piecing It Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2665630/Piecing_It_Together/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2665630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Piecing It Together brings jigsaw puzzles to a whole new dimension!<br/>Construct 3D puzzles of beautiful dioramas, each brought to life by various artists.<br/><br/>The game provides a calm and meditative environment for you to enjoy.<br/>There are no scores, timers, or meters to worry about. It's just you and your puzzle pieces!<br/>Enjoy a quick puzzling session with just a handful of pieces, or challenge yourself with many!<br/><br/>Piecing It Together is a modern take on a classic pastime that’s fun for the whole family!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Each puzzle has 4 Difficulties, from 20 Pieces up to 200 Pieces<br/></li><li> Meditative gameplay with no timers, meters or scores<br/></li><li> Save and resume your progress at any time<br/></li><li> Relax to our soundtrack inspired by Animal Crossing</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Push, pull, and rotate pieces to complete the puzzle!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2665630/extras/connectGif2.gif?t=1711521616"><h2 class="bb_tag">Play with real 3D puzzle pieces!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2665630/extras/travelGif.gif?t=1711521616"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Be In Love With Girls Group</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2817530/To_Be_In_Love_With_Girls_Group/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"To Be Love With Girls Group" is the world's first real-life interactive video game for nurturing girl groups, produced by "Guanghe Media". Game players will take on the role of a girl group agent from the first perspective in the game to search for and discover girl group trainees, and cultivate them to become formal members of the girl group. Game players can independently choose the story direction with each plot character and master the emotional balance with each plot character. Players will face pressure from senior management in the company, malicious colleagues, and a plethora of candidate trainees, testing whether they can ultimately successfully form a girl group to complete their debut mission and assist the girl group members in breaking through their cocoons. After successfully forming a group, players will be able to continue unlocking the subsequent development content of the Love Girl group through the game. Set off immediately, create your own girl group with your own hands, and ignite your own youth storm!<br/>Game features<br/>·The world's first online and offline game that combines real person development for girl groups. In addition to experiencing a fun process of forming groups and immersing emotional experiences, players can also unlock more new offline content for girl groups through the game.<br/>·The six girls in the plot have very different styles: Hua Ye Xiaoqian, the ancient style department of the folk music department of the Conservatory of Music, Wang Juan, the simple girl from a small town, Ai Li, the cold rock girl, Ma Dongmei, the anime girl from the Northeast, Xu, the stern and caring female boss, and Zhu Yeqing, the eccentric and mysterious female colleague.<br/>·The plot is rich, with multiple branches, multiple endings, and numerous hidden storylines and Easter eggs.<br/>民乐系古风系花叶小倩<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817530/extras/GIF_20240225195157088.GIF?t=1711518360"><br/>东北二次元少女马冬美<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817530/extras/GIF_20240221194638474.GIF?t=1711518360"><br/>甜酷摇滚少女艾丽<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817530/extras/GIF_20240221190115326.GIF?t=1711518360"><br/>公司前台小镇姑娘王娟<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817530/extras/GIF_20240221194300855.GIF?t=1711518360"><br/>色厉内荏女上司徐总<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817530/extras/GIF_20240221190023942.GIF?t=1711518360"><br/>神秘鬼马女同事祝叶青<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817530/extras/GIF_20240221194359467.GIF?t=1711518360"><br/><br/>About Guanghe Media<br/>A group of friends who are always curious about the future, communicate and explore more possibilities for gaming and entertainment with a wide range of players.<br/>Follow the Love Girl Group<br/>Get more information about romantic girl groups<br/>Official Weibo: 恋恋女团<br/>Official Tiktok: 恋恋女团<br/>Official Bilibili: 恋恋女团<br/>Official QQ group: 708723115<br/>Bug feedback QQ group：205466876						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Children of The Woods - Lost Tape</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2752660/The_Children_of_The_Woods__Lost_Tape/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2752660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"The Children of The Woods - Lost Tape" serves as a playable teaser of what can be expected from the upcoming found footage franchise called "The Children of The Woods". Through this first installment, viewers can explore events following the disappearances and the missing 5 individuals from a fresh viewpoint. It offers an immersive experience that delves deeper into the lore and history, providing insights into the origins of the featured footage in the forthcoming installments. It is crucial to remember that the truth is within the woods.<br>
<br>
Game synopsis / story <br>
<br>
You are Private Detective Dale Lincoln, and you are investigating the aftermath of the incident occurred in January of 1999. Use your night vision function on your camcorder  to see details you may have missed with your naked eye. the deeper you go ,the closer you get to the truth . <br>
<br>
Examine items, collect evidence, connect the dots, and beware, something is lurking in the woods.<br/>
<br/>
Playtime 5-15 mins						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outflow</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2818860/Outflow/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2818860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The year 2450, Earth's energy resources were running out. So mankind went to another planet in search of a sustainable source of energy. The discovery of Spica A, a new planet with similar characteristics to Earth, gave people new hope, but it lacked a source of electricity. No other resource on Spica A could replace electricity. Ever since they left Earth, it has been impossible for humans to return. The facelesses have taken control of the world's electricity. <br>
<br>
Connections had to be established with the electric fields and energy had to be transported to Spica A from areas of rugged conditions.  Facelesses built towers resistant to the energy of this region and the Earth's atmosphere. These towers provide resources of their own by transferring energy. Therefore, the enemies started a fierce struggle against humanity to protect the energy towers.<br>
<br>
The main character is tasked with the difficult process of energy transfer and defense against the enemies in order to transfer electricity to Spica A. He landed at the only remaining headquarters on Earth and began his preparations.<br>
<br>
You are Atlas and will keep fighting with the enemies until you reach to the electricity transfer point. Atlas can interact with the objects like cars or checkpoints in this third person action role playing game. He can also perform some sword and bow skills to defeat the enemies. Manually simulated sword mechanic allows you to improve your fighting skill with your experience. You will need to take care of your car's damage and fuel state while you try to keep your journey in track.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hide for Cat - all for the best -</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2607760/Hide_for_Cat__all_for_the_best/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>[A talented cat hides "floors and walls"]</strong><br/><br/>This game is a 2D puzzle action game where you aim to clear the world in a world where the terrain changes exactly as you see it by hiding floors and walls so that they are no longer visible. In order to reach its owner, the cat, the main character, progresses through seemingly impossible stages by hiding and erasing walls and floors.<br/><br/>The appeal of this game is that you can change the terrain and carve your own path to the goal.<br/><br/><strong>[Simple operation method]</strong><br/>In addition to basic movement and jumping, you will use "black boxes" to hide walls and floors to conquer the game. A "black box" appears while you click the mouse, and by hiding the terrain, it is treated as if the terrain does not exist at that location and you can pass through it. You will conquer various stages with this intuitive operation.<br/><br/><strong>[Two different modes]</strong><br/>This game has two modes: a ``puzzle'' mode where you can have fun and have casual fun, and an ``action'' mode where you use gimmicks to reach the goal.Even with the same ``hiding floors and walls'' element, you can have different fun.<br/><br/><strong>【Stage】</strong><br/>There are over 50 stages in total! A variety of stages await you, from easy ones to highly difficult ones to ones with a few quirks!<br/><br/><strong>[Story]</strong><br/>The main character, a cat named ``Hyde,'' goes into an impossible labyrinth in order to find his owner who disappeared one day. She uses her research on ``the power to block out existence and make it impossible to even touch'' to advance through a labyrinth that seems impossible to conquer, with walls and doors buried.<br/><br/><strong>[Distribution guidelines]</strong><br/><br/>Game distribution/live commentary: OK for individuals and corporations<br/>Spoiler: OK<br/>Monetization: OK<br/>Distribution platform: No particular restrictions<br/><br/>・If you would like to broadcast or provide live commentary, we would appreciate it if you could write the following information!<br/>Steam URL						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crystal Guard TD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2846100/Crystal_Guard_TD/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Introducing Crystal Guard TD, a dynamic twist on tower defense!<br/><br/>Make strategic choices in a shop where you're presented with three randomly selected tower options. Spend wisely and combine three identical towers to level them up.<br/><br/>Features <ul class="bb_ul"><li> 20 different towers to try<br/></li><li> 25+ different Power ups<br/></li><li> Pixel graphics<br/></li><li> In-game tutorial slides<br/></li><li> 6 Levels to complete</li></ul><br/>Your mission? Defend your crystal shrine against 20 waves of relentless robots. Can you outwit your enemies and emerge victorious?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELECTROBASIS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2766540/ELECTROBASIS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766540/extras/SteamGif.gif?t=1711490550"><br/><br/><br/>Hundreds, if not <strong>THOUSANDS</strong> of years ago, a Biblical rapture fell upon the Earth, leading for angels to walk beside man, in effort to make humankind more holy living by example. Which, nowadays, isn’t all that sacred of a concept - <strong>angels are everywhere!</strong> THEY’ve integrated human characteristics into their own culture, rather than vice versa.<br/><br/>                              <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766540/extras/SteamPageLore.gif?t=1711490550"><br/><br/>Made up of pure electricity, cherubs take up object heads to anthropomorphize their form. They own businesses, live in casinos, and are free to gamble their heart away. <strong>YOU</strong>, as a fallen angel, crashland <strong>SMACKdab</strong> in the center of a casino in Vegas - LITERALLY crashland. By playing this game you agree to clean-up duty*, fixing up the spark inside! Start with fixing up the casino herself by turning back on the power, and then expand into the happiness of the residents in the rooms upstairs.<br/><br/>                              <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766540/extras/SteamPageGifIntro.gif?t=1711490550"><br/><br/><br/><strong>INCLUDES:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A casino and hotel to explore!<br/></li><li>Five different residents that have something wrong with them!<br/></li><li>Exposition dump in text form for YOUR, yes your, eyeballs to scan over!<br/></li><li>2010s dance party ending!<br/></li><li>At least one rat<br/></li><li>Music from famous musician VEN! You know Ven, don’t you?</li></ul><br/><i>katabasis</i> (n.) <br/>a mytheme or trope in which the hero embarks on a journey to the underworld<br/>any journey downwards or fall						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOG® – The dog takes the hindmost</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2512010/DOG__The_dog_takes_the_hindmost/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The dog takes the hindmost! </strong><br/>Looks like Ludo, but it's DOG®. In this game, you also have to safely bring your four game pieces into your home area. The difference is that they are moved using cards that have a few surprises in store for you. Team spirit is important, because you can only win together.<br/><br/>Highlights:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Different game modes <br/></li><li>For uo to 6 players<br/></li><li>Game boards with different looks</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yatzi</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2512040/Yatzi/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Skillful combination is half the battle!</strong><br/>It's quite tricky to roll a YATZI: Roll five dice with the same number in three tries. This classic dice game thrills players thanks to its simple game rules and exciting gameplay. You can’t be sure who has the most points until the very end.<h2 class="bb_tag">Highlights:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Different game modes <br/></li><li>Game boards with different looks</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
