<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>4D Golf</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2147950/4D_Golf/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2147950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>4D Golf</strong> is a mind-bending golf game unlike any other because it's set entirely in a 4-dimensional space. Complete fun and unique golfing challenges as you gain hands-on experience of the 4th dimension and beyond!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2147950/extras/SteamGIF_1.gif?t=1711121562"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 120 levels and 7 vibrant themed worlds<br/></li><li>Tons of visualization options to master 4D space<br/></li><li>Build your own 4D courses in the level editor<br/></li><li>Race the clock in Marble Platforming Mode<br/></li><li>Navigate hidden paths, moving platforms, shifting gravity, speed boosts, and more!<br/></li><li>Unlock custom accessories by completing challenges</li></ul><br/>Now open your third eye and unleash your full potential!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Forgotten World:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827510/The_Forgotten_WorldPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FVuKggh6WYN" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/dss.png?t=1711106032"/></a><br/><br/><strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 8 in the official version.<br/>Chapters: 2 prologues, 6 official versions</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/111.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>This is about Alice after Wonderland.<br/>Oblivion is the vilest of spells. As an adult, Alice also experiences a less fairytale-like life and stops dreaming, which also means that everything about Wonderland is slowly disappearing. The people of Wonderland have even forgotten why they exist, and before everything dissipates, the Cheshire Cat casts a phantom spell to try to find Alice in the hope that she can save Wonderland once more.<br/>But the Cheshire Cat can't remember the spell either, and the wrong spell sends it traveling to a parallel world, a world where Alice has no idea that Wonderland even exists.<br/>In order to keep Wonderland from being forgotten, the Cheshire Cat brings Alice from each parallel world back to Wonderland, trying to awaken people's memories, and despite failures after failures, the Cheshire Cat still believes that he will find the right Alice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/1y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/1.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Play as different Alice and utilize different abilities and decks to defeat your enemies, each Alice has her own story! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/2y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/2.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Spellbound "monsters" are not real monsters, so defeat them to break the spell and discover their true nature! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/3y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/3.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Playing cards, which seem to be everywhere, will become your biggest fighting force at this moment! Poker soldiers can get different runes to increase combat power! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/4y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/4.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Arrange Poker Pawns of the same number of points or color to get a reinforcement effect, they don't have emotions but are very good at fighting! </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2054970/Dragons_Dogma_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Note: There are other sets that include this item.<br/><br/>Set forth on your grand adventure, Arisen!<br/><br/>Dragon’s Dogma is a single player, narrative driven action-RPG series that challenges the players to choose their own experience – from the appearance of their Arisen, their vocation, their party, how to approach different situations and more. Now, in this long-awaited sequel, the deep, explorable fantasy world of Dragon’s Dogma 2 awaits.<br/><br/>On your journey, you’ll be joined by Pawns, mysterious otherworldly beings, in an adventure so unique you will feel as if accompanied by other players while on your own adventure.<br/><br/>All of these elements are elevated further through physics technology, artificial intelligence (AI) and the latest in graphics, to create a truly immersive fantasy world in Dragon’s Dogma 2.<br/><br/><br/><strong><u>Action that challenges your creativity </u></strong> <br/><br/>Wield swords, bows, and chant magick.<br/>The vocations in Dragon's Dogma 2 give you the ability to approach combat the way you want.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_01.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Company in your single-player experience </u></strong> <br/><br/>Players can customize their own main Pawn, who will always accompany your Arisen, <br/>and enter a covenant with up to 2 additional Pawns from other players through the network. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_02.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Facing the monsters in this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Beyond the town borders, you will encounter diverse monsters that inhabit the lands. <br/>You will need to decide between engaging in battles or finding alternatives; <br/>so be aware of your party’s setup, the terrain around you, and the monsters you face.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_03.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Inhabitants of this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Travelers, merchants, soldiers and other folk go about their daily lives. <br/>Preoccupied by their own objectives and motives, they all exhibit different emotions.<br/>At times, they may lead you to a quest by approaching you and asking for a favor. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_04.gif?t=1711067553"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tchia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1496590/Tchia/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1496590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join Tchia on her tropical open-world adventure as she sets off to rescue her father from the cruel tyrant, Meavora, ruler of the archipelago. Climb, glide, swim, and sail your boat around beautiful islands as you explore a physics-driven sandbox. Face the fabric soldiers created by Meavora in open encounters where your creativity gives you the edge. Take control of any animal or object you can find, make new friends and jam on your fully playable Ukulele.<br/>A poetic coming-of-age story inspired by New Caledonia.<h2 class="bb_tag">SOUL JUMPING</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1496590/extras/Tchia_SteamGif4_600x175_soul.gif?t=1711052991"><br/>Tchia's special gift lets you take control of any animal or object you can find. With over 30 animals and hundreds of objects to choose from, fly around as a bird, explore the ocean as a fish or dig for treasures as a dog! Use your unique soul-jumping abilities to explore solve puzzles, and uncover secrets.<h2 class="bb_tag">EXPLORATION &amp; TRAVERSAL</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1496590/extras/Tchia_SteamGif2_600x175_explore.gif?t=1711052991"><br/>Jump and glide your way across a vast archipelago and use the Tricks system to perform cool stunts and dives. The free climbing mechanic lets you ascend anything in the world without restriction including any physics-driven tree. Take to the ocean waves, and sail your customizable boat across turquoise lagoons and dive around coral reefs and shipwrecks.<h2 class="bb_tag">COMBAT &amp; ENCOUNTERS</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1496590/extras/Tchia_SteamGif6_600x17_combat.gif?t=1711052991"><br/>Face the Maano: mysterious enemies spawned from pieces of wood and fabric. Keep moving, improvise, and use all of Tchia’s abilities to come out on top of those intense encounters. You can also put your skills to the test by tackling mystical challenges in the Totem Shrines.<h2 class="bb_tag">UKULELE</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1496590/extras/Tchia_SteamGif5_600x175_uke.gif?t=1711052991"><br/>Just jamming by yourself or playing alongside other inhabitants of the archipelago, your fully playable ukulele will be a trusty companion throughout the game. Use it at key story moments during rhythm sections, or play unlockable melodies at any point in the open world to trigger special events such as attracting animals, triggering rainfall…<h2 class="bb_tag">STORY &amp; MUSIC</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1496590/extras/Tchia_SteamGif1_600x175_story.gif?t=1711052991"><br/>Take Tchia on a heartfelt adventure and meet a diverse cast of characters inspired by New Caledonian cultures. Fully animated cutscenes voiced in traditional language will punctuate your journey while an original orchestral score infused with local sounds creates a unique and immersive world.<h2 class="bb_tag">CUSTOMIZATION &amp; ITEMS</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1496590/extras/custom_gif_steam.gif?t=1711052991"><br/>Stylize Tchia’s clothing and boat with hundreds of unlockable cosmetic items ranging from a traditional look to the most over the top options. You will also unlock useful and fun tools along the way such as a flashlight, slingshot, compass, camera...<h2 class="bb_tag">NEW CALEDONIA</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1496590/extras/Tchia_SteamGif3_600x175_caledonia.gif?t=1711052991"><br/>The world of Tchia was inspired by New Caledonia, A tiny island in the Pacific Ocean, homeland of Awaceb's co-founders. Inspiration was taken from the rich and varied local landscapes, cultures, music, languages, folklores and traditions and was used to create a fictional world and to tell a universal story for all to understand and enjoy. The characters are voiced by local talent in traditional languages, and subtitled in many languages including English, French, Russian, Chinese, German, and more.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cureocity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2612680/Cureocity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							We are "Bread On Board," a collective of independent game developers spread across four countries, united by our passion and meeting during a GameJam. <br/>Our game demo was born in the "BOOOM CHALLENGE", a GameJam by GCORES. With only 21 days, we created a game based on a given theme. After the competition, we even won the "Most Popular Game" award at an Online Game Trial Event.<br/>The full playthrough of our game will take about an hour. We hope to give you a short, but super heartwarming and loving adventure❤️.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/1.奇幻而治愈（英文）.png?t=1711092805"><br/>A rookie adventurer fresh on the scene and a former mercenary who was transferred into an adventurer due to injury. Two protagonists with contrasting personalities will embark on an adventure of fantasy and healing together. In the mysterious ruins of an underground dungeon that lies in the depth of a jungle, what awaits them will be...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1711092805"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/2.两位冒险者（英文）.png?t=1711092805"><br/>According to the tavern's adventurer logs, the team heading into the dungeon features a rookie adventurer and an ex-mercenary who is now working as a healer. The adventurer looks as charming as a doll, and the enthusiasm never disappears; the healer is cool and a bit traditional, acting as a guiding figure for their adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1711092805"><br/><br/>What stories have unfolded between these two contrasting characters, and what challenges will they face together in this adventure? The continuation of this adventurous story is yours to discover.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/3.注重手法的回合制解谜（英文）.png?t=1711092805"><br/>"People think battles need powerful weapons, but strategy at hand is key." <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_3_en.gif?t=1711092805"><br/><br/>In "Cureocity," the power of your strategy is materialized as the numerical values of your hands in combat. You can swap different weapons or items held in your left and right hands to alter your character's attack and defense stats. You may also change "gestures" to focus attacks or land heavy blows on specific enemies.As you delve deeper into the dungeon, you will take the unique traits of monsters into consideration and discuss strategies with your allies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/4.你的选择决定冒险归途（英文）.png?t=1711092805"><br/>In this adventure, you'll discover not only the secrets hidden within the dungeon, but also the truths about the world and the  characters themselves. When faced with contaminated monsters, you can choose to either fight them or attempt to purify them. Of course, you also have the option to let things take their own course.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_4_en.gif?t=1711092805"><br/><br/>With each decision,the fate of the protagonists may change. The end of this adventure... is yours to decide.<h2 class="bb_tag">About the Publisher</h2>GCORES PUBLISHING is an independent game publishing venture formed by GCORES, committed to bringing you more outstanding indie games from the BOOOM CHALLENGE.<br/>Feel free to follow our <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/44750639" rel="" target="_blank">publisher webpage</a> for future updates.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midnight Ghost Hunt</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/915810/Midnight_Ghost_Hunt/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/915810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>MIDNIGHT GHOST HUNT IS A <i>PETRIFYING</i> PROP HAUNT GAME TO PLAY WITH PALS! </strong><br/><br/>Lying in wait across a series of cursed locations, relentless spirits stalk the halls. Assigned to eliminate them are the Ghost Hunters, armed to the teeth with the ghoul-busting tech to banish them to another realm! Play both Ghost and Hunter in a chaotic 4v4 struggle between the living and the dead.<br/><br/><strong>TONGUE-IN-CHEEK HIDE-AND-SEEK</strong><br/>As a Ghost, conceal yourself inside seemingly harmless pieces of furniture to evade preying Hunters… but when their backs are turned, turn the environment against them with telekinetic bombardment. No chair, lamp, or grandfather clock is innocent in this hijinks-heavy frenzy.<br/><br/><strong>MIDNIGHT MAYHEM</strong><br/>The fun isn’t over yet...when the clock strikes twelve, the witching hour begins, and the Hunters become the Hunted. The tables turn and Ghosts become supercharged, giving Hunters a limited amount of time to survive their vengeful wrath.<br/><br/><strong>MURDEROUS 4v4 MULTIPLAYER</strong><br/>Play together and communicate with your team and ensure a triumphant victory, giving each other pointers on the paths enemies tend to tread. Create synergies with your team's abilities to outthink and outwit your opponents.<br/><br/><strong>HARNESS SUPERNATURAL ABILITIES</strong><br/>The restrictions of reality don’t apply to Ghosts, of course. Claim your supernatural powers, which include turning invisible, causing furniture to float, and conjuring a dangerous Ghostly miasma. Ghosts can even hide in plain sight by masquerading as a Hunter’s doppelgänger!<br/><br/>Ghostly Perks include dramatically increasing your weight, extending your possessing range, the ability to see nearby Hunters through walls, and much more. <br/><br/><strong>ARMED AND READY</strong><br/>Hunters must choose their weapons from a full range of hi-tech gadgets designed to cast out Ghosts from our plane of existence. Detect ghostly presences with the Spectrophone, Radar and Pathfinder, capture them with a Trap, and suck up their spectral remains with the Vacuum – or just blast them to smithereens with the Spectral Cannon, sledgehammers, harpoons, salt-spewing shotguns, and more.<br/><br/>Hunters can also select Perks to give them a special boost. Choose from an extra burst of speed, health-replenishing capabilities and a host of other powers to get ahead of the game.<br/><br/><strong>A BEVY OF BLOOD-CURDLING MAPS </strong><br/>Explore ten unsettling locations, including an abandoned theatre, eerie mansion and cursed carnival. Each map brings with it different tactical considerations and items to throw about… as well as plenty of opportunities to play tricks on the enemy.<br/><br/><strong>FRIGHTENING NEW FEATURES</strong> <br/>As it crept through Steam Early Access, Midnight Ghost Hunt picked up a gaggle of game-changing features, built on the feedback of its community of Ghosts and Hunters.<br/><br/>Dedicated servers and host migration support make setting up matches a breeze, while the Progression Tier and Challenge systems bring added competition to the hunt. Looking for less of the silly and more of the scary? The Experimental Darkness game mode lends a chill to the chaos. Not to mention crossplay, full controller support, and even the GhostMaster minigame to pass the time during the van ride to your next match!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horizon Forbidden West™ Complete Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420110/Horizon_Forbidden_West_Complete_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/extras/horizon_forbidden_west_cinemagraph_610x610.gif?t=1711032993"><br/><br/>Join Aloy as she braves a majestic but dangerous new frontier that holds mysterious new threats. This Complete Edition allows you to enjoy the critically acclaimed Horizon Forbidden West on PC in its entirety with bonus content, including the Burning Shores story expansion that picks up after the main game.<br/><br/>Explore distant lands, fight bigger and more awe-inspiring machines, and encounter astonishing new tribes as you return to the far-future, post-apocalyptic world of Horizon.<br/><br/>The land is dying. Vicious storms and an unstoppable blight ravage the scattered remnants of humanity while fearsome new machines prowl their borders, and life on Earth is hurtling toward another extinction.<br/><br/>It's up to Aloy to uncover the secrets behind these threats and restore order and balance to the world. Along the way, she must reunite with old friends, forge alliances with warring new factions and unravel the legacy of the ancient past.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>See every gameplay detail with Ultrawide 21:9 and Super Ultrawide 32:9 resolutions, as well as 48:9 triple monitor support.*<br/></li><li>Witness the Forbidden West coming to life, with NVIDIA DLSS 3 upscaling and frame generation, image enhancing NVIDIA DLAA and latency reducing NVIDIA Reflex. AMD FSR and Intel XeSS are also supported.**<br/></li><li>Customize graphic settings to your preference, with the potential for unlocked frame rates.**<br/></li><li>Take control with full support for the DualSense™ controller, including haptic feedback and adaptive trigger functionality.*** </li></ul><br/>* Compatible PC and 4K display device required. <br/>** Compatible PC required. <br/>*** Wired connection required to experience the full range of in-game controller features.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age of Water: The First Voyage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2841350/Age_of_Water_The_First_Voyage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The First Voyage is the very beginning of your Age of Water experience. Jump right into the intense naval combat, craft your first boats, explore the waterworld and get a good idea of what Age of Water is about. Don’t forget to wishlist the full game now!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_ship_anim.gif?t=1711025025"><br/><br/>Become a sea captain on a post-apocalyptic Earth completely covered in water and go on an adventure in a huge open world. Sail through storms, fight and trade, capture other people's boats or build your own, extract resources from the bottom of the ocean, reveal the secrets of the Age of Water world.<br/><br/><strong>Water post-apocalypse</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_1.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>The ocean destroyed a once great civilization, but people survived and adapted. They built settlements on the roofs of tall buildings and the tops of other man-made structures. People travel across the ocean in tiny boats and huge combat vessels. The ocean provides everything they need, including extractable resources on the seabed. And yet, the dream of real land is still alive.<br/><br/><strong>True open world</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_2.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Explore the world at your own pace, discover new settlements and meet their inhabitants. Complete tasks, search for and extract valuable resources from the bottom of the ocean, earn money on trade or simply sell the artifacts you have obtained, and when you get the idea of how this world works, build your own base.<br/><br/><strong>Hundreds of unique ships</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_3.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Build boats from scratch or modify existing ones. Players have access to dozens of hulls and hundreds of parts, from which they can assemble anything ranging from a small boat to a hefty vessel 30 meters long, and then install equipment, armor and weapons. It’s important not to forget to gather a team of good crewmembers so that there is someone to stand behind machine guns and cannons or do other work on board.<br/><br/><strong>Fierce naval battles</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_4.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Pirates are always waiting for you at sea, and in some cases more aggressive players even start to chase you, so do not forget to install enough guns on your deck.  You can destroy an enemy vessel, or you can capture it in battle and take it for yourself forever. Adventures might also get you into storming enemy fortresses and defending allied settlements!<br/><br/><strong>Personal naval base</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_5.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>This shelter is reliably protected from enemies, and it allows a player to organize the production of everything that the captain may need on it. Build factories for the production of equipment, weapons, hulls for boats of all sizes, as well as the necessary resources.<br/><br/><strong>Flexible balance between PvE and PvP</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_6.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>At first, you will only meet computer opponents, but later you can challenge other players if you are confident enough in your skills and gear. Always be on the lookout: if your task is to transport illegal goods, then other players may well take the quest to hunt smugglers. In Age of Water, everyone decides for themself who they are today - a peaceful traveler or a bloodthirsty pirate.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slice &amp; Dice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1775490/Slice__Dice/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1775490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Slice &amp; Dice is a tactical dice battle roguelike.<br/><br/>Take control of 5 heroes, each with their own unique dice. Fight your way through 20 levels of monsters and try to take on the final boss. If you lose a single fight you have to start over so be careful/lucky!<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/>- 3D dice physics, choose which dice to reroll<br/>- Simple turn-based combat<br/>- Level up a hero or gain an item after each fight<br/>- Randomly-generated encounters<br/>- Ridiculous combos<br/>- Undo actions as much as you like<br/>- Each turn is like a mini-puzzle<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/>- 128 hero classes (+99999?)<br/>- 73 monsters<br/>- 473 items<br/>- Too many modes<br/>- ∞ curses<br/>- Weird modding<br/>- Online leaderboards<br/><br/><strong>Credits</strong><br/>- Created by tann (it took ~7 years)<br/>- Pixel art by a3um<br/>- Music by Ziggurath, Aleksander Zabłocki, Louigi Verona, Cold Sanctum, Ro'sø, Andrew Goodwin<br/>- Trailer by Everdraed<br/><br/>I plan to not participate in any sales/deals/bundles. No AI was used to make this game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone in the Dark</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1310410/Alone_in_the_Dark/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Alone in the Dark weaves a chilling tapestry of psychological horror and Southern Gothic charm, reimagining the iconic game that set the benchmark for the genre. We invite you to join us on a journey into madness, where each encounter could be your last. With each step you take closer to unravelling Derceto's mystery, the eyes that watch from the darkness grow hungrier. Every bullet means the difference between survival and an unthinkable end. The next door you unlock could lead to a nightmarish realm offering nothing but slashing claws, grasping tentacles, and frayed sanity.  Journey to interbellum Louisiana, where an era of decadence hides a darker tale - of escape from past traumas and an intolerant society, into the waiting grasp of something darker, something that has patiently lurked for impossible eons. This is Alone in the Dark as you've never seen it - a skillfully-woven narrative of Southern Gothic elegance and eldritch madness that pays homage to its legendary origins while taking the next step forward in survival horror storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_VIPIntro_2.gif?t=1710945887"><h2 class="bb_tag">A Haunting Tale of Mystery and Madness</h2>Step inside Derceto Manor, an asylum shrouded in intrigue, guarding a terrible secret. Client Emily Hartwood and private investigator Edward Carnby embark on a harrowing quest for answers; Emily to the mystery of her missing uncle, Edward to the toughest case he will ever face, and both to questions they dare not ask themselves. This re-envisioned classic invites you to explore an unforgettable single player adventure rich with suspense, frights, and revelations that will test the limits of your imagination.<h2 class="bb_tag">Featuring Hollywood Talent</h2>Experience some of the greatest acting survival horror has ever seen through the performances of award-winning actors Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow) in their first videogame roles. Jodie and David’s immaculately captured likenesses breathe life into Emily Hartwood and Edward Carnby, lending a deeply personal aspect to Alone in the Dark’s story that demands it be played twice to get the full experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Tribute to Horror Pioneers</h2>Rediscover the essence of psychological horror in a game that respectfully nods to its 1992 origin, the game that established the survival horror genre. Alone in the Dark is your gateway to an experience steeped in the atmospheric dread of classic horror, with next-generation storytelling and gameplay. A must-play for fans of twisted tales, nerve-wracking exploration, and desperate combat.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Story That Challenges Reality</h2>Envisioned by Mikael Hedberg, acclaimed writer behind modern horror classics “SOMA” and “Amnesia”, Alone in the Dark’s intricate web of mystery delves into themes of trauma, faith, evil, and abandonment. Whether you choose to brave the nightmare as Emily or Edward, you will uncover secrets that defy everything you thought about videogame storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Atrmo_2.gif?t=1710945887"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore Derceto Manor in this reimagination of Alone in the Dark, a love letter to the 90’s cult classic horror game.<br/></li><li>Return to the roots of psychological horror and experience an atmospheric journey worthy of the game that started the genre.<br/></li><li>Dive into a world full of sounds that make your skin crawl with a haunting, yet mesmerizing doom jazz soundtrack.<br/></li><li>Enjoy the thrill of desperate survival in a world where reality starts to crumble, evil lurks in every shadow and ammunition is scarce.<br/></li><li>Experience this nightmare from either Emily Hartwood’s or Edward Carnby’s perspective and unearth the dark secrets of a gothic mansion.<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in a deep psychological story that goes beyond the realms of the imaginable, by Mikael Hedberg, cult horror writer of SOMA and Amnesia.<br/></li><li>See Emily and Edward brought to live by the Hollywood talent of Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow), who lend their voices, their appearance, and their formidable acting skills to the protagonists.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Riddles_2.gif?t=1710945887"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raw Metal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2279600/Raw_Metal/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2279600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Raw Metal is a sci-fi stealth-action dungeon crawler with a focus on smooth, stylish gameplay.<br/><br/>You are a lone scavenger on the distant, barren exoplanet Charybdis. In search of gear and supplies, you infiltrate the depths of Katabase 6, a massive mining facility run by a corrupt megacorporation known as Orpheus Tech. Sneak through the mines undetected, cleverly utilizing various gadgets and equipment to your advantage, but beware; if you're caught, you'll need to rely on your combat skills for a fighting chance to escape.<h2 class="bb_tag">High-Stakes Stealth</h2><br/>Use taser darts, noisemakers, improvised concussion grenades, and more to slip past and isolate guards. The shadows are your domain; manipulate your environment and your enemies well enough and they'll never see you coming.<h2 class="bb_tag">Breakneck Combat</h2><br/>Combat in Raw Metal is fast and punishing. The guards stationed at Katabase 6 are stronger and more heavily armored than you, so fighting them head on will take skill, cunning, and a great degree of risk. However, mastering combos and using your environment will allow you to come out on top, and yield far greater rewards. Depending on whether it is initiated through a clever ambush or a stealth slip-up, combat can range from a calculated risk to a desperate fight for survival.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Blend of top-down stealth and third-person beat 'em up combat<br/></li><li>Freeform combo system that rewards aggression, improvisation, and precise timing and positioning<br/></li><li>50+ unique gear pieces to find and upgrade<br/></li><li>Distinct visuals for each gear piece to customize the look of your character<br/></li><li>Risk vs. reward extraction system that grants you the choice of cashing out your loot, or pushing deeper into the facility<br/></li><li>3 memorable and challenging boss fights, each with their own fighting styles, twists, and story development<br/></li><li>9 hand-crafted levels to infiltrate, with a few variants each to mix up your approach each time<br/></li><li>Environmental hazards and enemy variants to keep you on your toes as the game progresses<br/></li><li>5 deployable gadgets to utilize to your advantage in stealth and combat alike</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pesticide Not Required</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2479320/Pesticide_Not_Required/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pesticide Not Required combines auto-attacking bullet heaven roguelites with farming game mechanics to create an expansive set of strategies and build combinations. Destroy huge hordes of evil insects, grow tons of crops, create your own build path, and unlock unique characters to play with!<h2 class="bb_tag">Create Overpowered Builds</h2> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/extras/CombatChaosFisher.gif?t=1710830410"><br/>You are the bullet hell! Grow an arsenal of ridiculous weapons and craft your own unique build with a combination of 40+ stats. Additionally, each character has their own unique traits that keep runs fresh.<h2 class="bb_tag">Farm, Fish, and Mine</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/extras/FarmFishMineWinterGif.gif?t=1710830410"><br/>Earn vital gold and experience from growing crops, catching fish, and mining. Expand your plot to harvest huge quantities of crops and build carefully to enhance your farming, fishing, and mining capabilities.<h2 class="bb_tag">Automate Your Farm With Pets</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/extras/PetsGifAutumn.gif?t=1710830410"><br/>Recruit friendly pets that will enhance your farm, collect loot, and kill enemies.<br/><br/>Other Features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Quick ~20-minute play sessions<br/></li><li>Customizable home interior and backyard garden area<br/></li><li>Season-themed map variations with 16 difficulty levels<br/></li><li>20+ unlockable characters with special traits<br/></li><li>Persistent skill tree upgrades<br/></li><li>100+ achievements to unlock<br/></li><li>Compendium with unique fish for each season<br/></li><li>Mouse-only gameplay support<br/></li><li>Gamepad and keyboard support<br/></li><li>Go WUMBO!</li></ul><br/>Pesticide Not Required is inspired by awesome games like Brotato, Vampire Survivors, and Atomicrops.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Park Baseball 25</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384620/Out_of_the_Park_Baseball_25/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_banner_1.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/>We are incredibly excited to announce <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong> - the special 25th Anniversary edition of our award-winning baseball strategy series. Can you believe it's been a quarter of a century? Out of the Park Baseball is not just a game - it's a legacy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_henry.png?t=1710574531"><br/><br/>If it happens in real baseball, it happens in Out of the Park Baseball! Discover new talent, draft the next superstar, negotiate with free agents, enter trade talks with other teams, build your dynasty and guide a franchise into an infinite future! As a manager, dive into the more hands-on management and set your team's lineups, pitching staffs, in-game strategy and call the shots from the dugout. You can oversee your league at a high level, or play out each game in the gorgeous 3D game mode, managing play by play or even pitch by pitch. OOTP has it all covered!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_badge.png?t=1710574531"><br/>Here are just a few of the new features coming to <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong>:<br/><br/><strong>A game-changing new Player Development Lab!</strong><br/><br/>Shape the future of your upcoming stars! You can channel your inner Player Development Director like never before. A modern new Player Development Lab is here for every team that allows you to give players individual programs to work on, developing them how you like. Do you want your hitter to work on improving their baserunning? Bunting? Contact? Would you prefer your pitcher to work on building up their stamina? Developing a new pitch? Velocity? It's all up to you - for each of your upcoming future stars!<br/><br/><strong>Massive Player Ratings and AI Upgrade!</strong><br/><br/>It’s the most comprehensive player ratings upgrade in the 25 year history of Out of the Park Baseball! Batting, Pitching, and Fielding ratings have been painstakingly modified to capture the essence of baseball, with modifications to Contact and Power for hitters, Movement and Stuff for pitchers, the addition of Catcher Framing and Stealing Aggressiveness, and much more. BABIP is now front and center for hitters and hurlers, while new internal ratings updates allow for even more flexibility for Commissioners around the world to adjust the game to their detailed delight. Plus, the AI throughout the game has been improved dramatically to deliver the most challenging OOTP experience ever! <br/><br/><strong>Even More Detailed Player Development Control!</strong><br/><br/>Delegate how each and every player on your team will spend their time day in, day out with coaches at practice. Want your power hitter to worry less about avoiding strikeouts and put that time and effort into working on his home run swing instead? Want your aging starter to spend more time practicing his control instead of spending that time worrying about his stuff? By allocating their time and focus to the areas you want, over time you can influence how players develop, maintain their skillset, and fight the aging curve.<br/><br/><strong>2024 Rosters and Rules!</strong><br/><br/>As always, Out of the Park Baseball features up-to-the-minute 2024 MLB rosters that get updated all season long, with every franchise represented from its big league club all the way down to the low minors, and everywhere in between! Plus, OOTP 25 features officially licensed leagues from South Korea (KBO) and Europe.<br/><br/><strong>Improved Historical MLB Modes!</strong><br/><br/>Set up historical MLB games in an all new streamlined way - and benefit from vastly improved historical player ratings! It’s never been faster or easier to experience the entire history of Major League Baseball, now producing even more realistic outcomes thanks to those comprehensive ratings and simulation engine upgrades.<br/><br/><strong>New Retro Visual Immersion!</strong><br/><br/>Watch games with a variety of experiences, including retro-style black and white, ‘50s-era, and ‘70s-era television presentations. Choose from all of these to play games, watch highlights, or just catch a ballgame from a bygone era!<br/><br/><strong>New Licensed Leagues!</strong><br/><br/>For the first time ever, Out of the Park Baseball features an officially licensed Honkbal Hoofdklasse league from The Netherlands and the British Baseball Federation from the United Kingdom! Look for their official clubs, players, competitions, and more!<br/><br/><strong>For the first time ever - an official partnership with the Baseball Hall of Fame!</strong><br/><br/>What happens when you combine the only game that has the entire history of baseball and the the greatest Hall of Fame in sports? An incredible, year-long journey! Join us as we partner with the Baseball Hall of Fame all season - and beyond. Explore Hall of Fame Plaques, with the official, accurate text for each Hall of Famer. Discover incredible Hall of Fame artifacts, curated and released in fun "exhibits" over the course of the season in concert with the Hall - and more surprises too. It's going to be amazing! <br/><br/><strong>Dozens of upgrades big and small!</strong><br/><br/>--&gt; Updated in-game engine base advancement and camera movements<br/>--&gt; A new manager decision history screen gives you a look back on your best and worst trades and transactions<br/>--&gt; Improved trade packages for prospect packages <br/>--&gt; Updated two-way functionality with injured players<br/>And much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/pt_store_text_banner2.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/><br/><strong>Perfect Team is back - bigger than ever!</strong><br/><br/>It’s an all-new Perfect Team! There’s nothing in the world like the incredible online competitions of Perfect Team. Featuring by far the largest player pool ever, and taking advantage of all the player rating and balance upgrades, this year’s Perfect Team is a whole new ballgame.<br/><br/><strong>Brand New Perfect Team Combinator Series Cards!</strong><br/><br/>Pulled non-live cards have a chance to be a special Combinator Series version of the card! Use other cards that share a link (for example being teammates) with the player to get a chance to boost the raw ratings of the Combinator Series card.<br/><br/><strong>A Perfect Team Tournament Roster Builder!</strong><br/><br/>Want to design rosters for the incredible array of Perfect Team Tournaments - all on your own? For the first time ever, Perfect Team will feature a Tournament Sandbox! You can tinker to your heart's content with varying rosters for every type of tournament, with no pressure. This long-requested feature makes its debut in Out of the Park Baseball 25!<br/><br/>In addition to the brand-new Tournament Roster Builder and Combinator Series, Perfect Team 25 also features:<br/><br/><strong>Team Chemistry</strong> - Players who played together in real life will get extra bonuses when on your roster together. Players gain bonuses for seasons they played together, as well as simply being part of the same team or from the same decades<br/><strong>Perfect Team competitions starting on the first day</strong>, including a huge Opening Weekend of Tournaments with big prizes and Perfect Team Championship Series qualifying from Day One! <br/><strong>New content all season long - and beyond!</strong> All new programs, missions, competitions, and excitement await you every day.<br/><br/>Out of the Park Baseball 25 runs on PC/Mac and features the American League and National League logos, the World Series trophy, official logos and jerseys for all 30 MLB teams and 15 KBO teams, over 150 Minor League Baseball league and team logos, and historical MLB logos.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Shire: Room One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517850/Toy_Shire_Room_One/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FkhSxB2MSgD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/Toy_Shire_-_Discord_Banner.png?t=1710352808"/></a><br/><br/><br/>Play through the <strong>three levels in Kevin's Room</strong> and defend your room against your old toys. Face Memphis-X in the final level and put a stop to his assault as he crushes your soldiers in an attempt to get to your base.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyVengeance.png?t=1710352808"><br/>You received new toys from your family. Isn't that lovely? Oh, it's for sure... <br/>Your old toys, though, aren't getting along as well. They are no longer cared for and have been forgotten. So what follows next? They're going to join together against you and assault your brand-new toys, so be prepared. But never worry! You're in luck since your brand-new toys are troops of green soldiers. They still require your aid though! Control, strengthen, and defeat the opposing forces! However, focus with care, the enemies you encounter might not be your old playthings!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/InteractiveTowerDefense.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Tower building alone won't be sufficient to repel incoming attackers. Build up your own troops in the best feasible positions, then unleash attacks into enemy territory. Never abandon your towers, and deploy your troops in accordance with the traits of the enemy. First, the attacking forces will attempt to get past your defenses. Build and improve towers to aid your army. By using unique abilities, you can support your troops and towers as well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/EpicBattles.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Safeguard your base against waves of attackers. You need to pick the right troops if you would like to prevail. Clean the paths and guard any open routes. Upgrade your troops and unlock new ones to take down the waves and claim victory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyRealm.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Enter a world and a narrative built around the toys that enriched your youth, including toy soldiers, dinosaur sets, robots, building blocks, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_3.gif?t=1710352808"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dune: Imperium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1689500/Dune_Imperium/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Header.png?t=1710955211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body0_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Experience the ultimate blend of strategy and intrigue as you navigate the treacherous landscapes of Arrakis in the award-winning board game <i>Dune: Imperium</i>!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle online, locally with AI, or against the formidable House Hagal.<br/></li><li>Earn Achievements that showcase your prowess as a leader.<br/></li><li>Embark on more than a dozen Challenges that will test your wit and cunning.<br/></li><li>Compete for badges in the rotating Skirmish Mode where no two games are the same!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body1_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Arrakis. Dune. Desert Planet. Raise your banner above the vast wasteland before you. As the Great Houses of the Landsraad marshal their forces and their spies, whom will you influence, and whom will you betray? A tyrannical Emperor. The secretive Bene Gesserit. The shrewd Spacing Guild. The ferocious Fremen of the Deep Desert. The power of the Imperium can be yours, but war is not the only way to claim it.<br/><br/><i>Dune: Imperium</i> blends deck-building and worker placement in a deeply thematic new strategy game where the fate of the Empire hangs on your decisions. Will you seek political allies or rely upon military might? Economic strength or subtle intrigues? A council seat… or a sharpened blade? The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body2_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>In <i>Dune: Imperium</i>, you'll step into the role of one of the leaders of the Great Houses of the Imperium in a struggle to control the planet Arrakis and the invaluable Spice it provides.<br/><br/>The game plays out in a series of ten rounds, each of which is defined by a new Conflict on the surface of the planet; some award critical resources, and some provide Victory Points that will propel you to dominance. But choose your battles wisely: spread your forces too thin, and you'll find your enemies growing too strong to oppose.<br/><br/>Each round, you'll draw a hand of five cards from your deck, which will get stronger over the course of the game as you acquire new cards. Each card can be played in one of two ways: To send an Agent out into the Imperium to gather resources, or to Reveal at the end of the round to purchase new powerful cards. You must maintain a careful balance to get the most of the resources available to you. How will you find your path?<br/><br/>As your game progresses, you'll vie for Influence with four factions of the Imperium: The Emperor, the economically powerful Spacing Guild, the mysterious Bene Gesserit, and the ferocious Fremen of the deep deserts. Earning Influence among the various groups helps you to earn the Victory Points you need...but will you compete with your rivals for their favor, or abandon alliances to pursue other opportunities?<br/><br/>Many strategies are at your disposal, and many paths to victory. The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Footer.png?t=1710955211"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contra: Operation Galuga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2235020/Contra_Operation_Galuga/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2235020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A new entry in the legendary Contra series is here! Contra: Operation Galuga is a thorough reimagining of the classic run-'n'-gun action game from the '80s, featuring modern graphics and sound, new stages, new enemies and bosses, new play mechanics, an updated weapons system, and explosive co-op combat for up to two players in Story Mode or four players in Arcade Mode!<br>
<br>
When the Red Falcon terrorist group takes over the Galuga Islands off the coast of New Zealand, elite Contra commandos Bill Rizer and Lance Bean springs into action, initiating an all-out war in which the fate of mankind hangs in the balance!<br>
<br>
Run, jump, and shoot your way through eight levels using a devastating arsenal - including the spread shot, laser, and homing missiles - now with stackable upgrades and awesome Overload abilities! The intense action is customizable with three difficulty settings plus a variety of additional challenge options. The true Contra legacy begins now!<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br/>
•The original run-'n'-gun game is back, reimagined and more action-packed than ever!<br/>
•Attack aggressively across eight explosive stages! Infiltrate the jungle, ascend the waterfall, speed through an enemy base on a hovercycle, and more!<br/>
•Multiple playable characters with distinct abilities!<br/>
•Epic, screen-filling boss battles!<br/>
•New and fan-favorite weapons, now with stackable upgrades and incredible Overload abilities!<br/>
•Multiple difficulty options and a wealth of extra content						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals Zero Hour</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732960/Command__Conquer_Generals_Zero_Hour/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals Zero Hour brings you closer to the enemy than ever before. Engage opposing forces at hot spots around the globe as you match strategies and arsenals against the new masterminds of modern war.<br/><br/><strong>Arsenal.</strong> Unleash the next generation of 3D new units and 20 new upgrades including China's ECM Tank, GLA's BattleBus and the USA's Spectre Gunship.<br/><br/><strong>Missions.</strong> Take on 15 new missions and make tomorrow's headlines. Root out a splinter cell in Cairo, steal deadly toxins from a U.S. lab and more.<br/><br/><strong>Generals.</strong> Match strategies and arsenals against 9 enemy commanders with unpredictable personalities and tactics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Tiberian Sun™ and Firestorm™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229880/Command__Conquer_Tiberian_Sun_and_Firestorm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Second Tiberium War begins in this legendary sequel to the original Command &amp; Conquer. <br/><br/>With his forces stronger than ever, arch villain and leader of The Brotherhood of Nod - Kane - is pitched in an epic battle against the world's war machine - the Global Defense Initiative. Now you must orchestrate the fate of mankind.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on Dynamic Battlefields. Nature itself provides tactical opportunities - destroyable and deformable terrain, forest fires, treacherous ice fields and many more surprises that help or hinder your strategies.<br/></li><li>Exciting New Strategies and Units. Jump Jet Infantry, Hover Tanks, Tunneling APCs, Hunter Seekers, Laser Fences, Mechanized Battle Units and many more.<br/></li><li>The "Veterancy" Factor. Units can become faster and stronger as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>New Kinetic Battlefields. Flying shrapnel, shock waves and crashing debris are just a few of the exciting new technologies developed to enhance the in-game experience.<br/></li><li>The mood and attitude of the battlefield comes alive like never before - covert night missions, searchlights and new defenses intensify the thrill and excitement.</li></ul><br/>Then take the battle further in <strong>Firestorm, the official expansion pack for the game</strong>. Includes all-new campaign missions, cinematics, and units to decide the future of mankind.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Renegade™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229890/Command__Conquer_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer gets up close and personal in this classic First Person Shooter for one of the most iconic franchises.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wreak Havoc</strong> - Experience the Command &amp; Conquer universe on foot as Havoc, wise-cracking GDI Commando.<br/></li><li><strong>Make Your Own Rules</strong>  - Take on the evil Brotherhood of Nod using your own mix of brute force, stealth, and strategy.<br/></li><li><strong>Assault at Ground Level</strong>  - Dish out the damage in either first or third person.<br/></li><li><strong>Total Access</strong>  - Sneak inside and explore full-scale structures, like immense Tiberium Refineries and the ominous Hand of Nod.<br/></li><li><strong>Grind the Gears</strong>  - Beef up your arsenal by commandeering lethal vehicles, such as Nod Buggies, Flame Tanks, and Mammoth Tanks.<br/></li><li><strong>Weapons of Mass Destruction</strong>  - Choose from a multitude of weapons, including the Tiberium Auto Rifle, Chemical Sprayer, and the devasting Personal Ion Cannon.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™, Counterstrike™ and The Aftermath™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229840/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_Counterstrike_and_The_Aftermath/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert</strong> pushed the envelope for the RTS genre in the mid-1990s and became one of the most iconic strategy games of all time. <br/><br/><strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert</strong>  gives you the opportunity to be more devious, cunning, and ruthless than ever before. Red Alert puts the fate of the world in your hands!<br/><br/><strong>Counterstrike</strong>, the exciting expansion pack to Red Alert, is full of clandestine activity, experimental technologies, and disavowed tactics. Includes 16 all-new missions, where you decide the ultimate fate of the struggle between the Allies and Soviets.<br/><br/><strong>In The Aftermath expansion pack</strong>, prepare for guerilla tactics, insidious strategies, and forbidden weapons. Includes 18 all-new missions and multiple units in a showdown that will test your mettle.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ and The Covert Operations™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229830/Command__Conquer_and_The_Covert_Operations/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The legendary RTS game which started it all. Will you side with the humanistic GDI or bring the world to its knees with Kane and the Brotherhood of Nod. Your adversaries are without mercy. And so are you.  <br/><br/>Includes the <strong>The Covert Operations</strong> expansion pack with a range of challenging new missions.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rental</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2796550/Rental/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796550/extras/Gif_Final__2___1_.gif?t=1709834139"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Great Deal!</strong></h2><br/><i>Perfect cabin for a family of four. Close to the beach with great vibes!<br/>For more information about this rental, contact the caretaker!</i><br/><br/>For summer vacation, Umi's family rents a cabin near the beach. However, Umi soon realizes that the offer was not as grand as promised...<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Explore the summer cabin in this short game reminiscent of classic survival horror games.<br/></li><li> Meet and talk to a quirky cast of characters as you try to piece together the secrets of the cabin. <br/></li><li> Find items that will help you advance and find out what is wrong with this place. </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Controls</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Arrows or WASD to move<br/></li><li> Space to interact</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 March Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2845260/100_March_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🌸🌹 WELCOME TO 100 MARCH CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌷🐈</h2><br/>Join the cutest adventure in the Lovely world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of romantic 8 march themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x200.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 March Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁 DLC List for this game 🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Extra.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867620/100_March_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867640/100_March_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x1.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_15" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit Hole</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2831340/Rabbit_Hole/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/smaller.png?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Remember you will live.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Rabbit Hole is a fast paced, tough-as-nails 2D Platformer-RogueLike-Shooter inspired by popular roguelikes, made with a love for the genre. <br/>You are Disc, someone who was suddenly brought to the Rabbit Hole. <br/>Collect guns, fight foes and meet strange new characters on your descent to the bottom, all in an attempt to find your heart again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/1.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“This place is like its own ecosystem. A big living breathing mess.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Every run is different. Enjoy hours of replayable content through randomly generated floor layouts and 50+ weapons to collect and use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/2.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Hey, hey, hey! How's my favorite anxiety-fueled nutjob!”</i></strong><br/><br/>Unlock new characters with diverse playstyles. Each of the 6 unlockable characters keep gameplay fresh and give a unique perspective on the gameplay loop.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/3.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“There was a blank line, almost as if I had erased it”</i></strong><br/><br/>Discover the truth that lies beneath the surface. Collect books and fill out your library to understand its unseen history. In the end, you may even come to understand yourself?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeeperRL</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/329970/KeeperRL/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/Peek-2018-11-28-09-43.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL is an ambitious dungeon simulator with roguelike and RPG elements. Take the role of an evil wizard and study the methods of black magic. Equip your minions and explore the world, murder innocent villagers and burn their homes. Build your dungeon, lay traps and prepare for an assault of angry heroes. <br/><br/>When you control your minions the game changes into a classic roguelike, with turn-based and very tactical combat. You can also play as an adventurer and assault dungeons made by you or other players.<h2 class="bb_tag">Dungeon management </h2>You will dig deep into the mountain and build dozens of rooms, corridors and traps. Your minions will train and produce weapons and armor. Prisoners will be tortured. You will research new technologies like alchemy, beast mutation and sorcery.<h2 class="bb_tag">Z-levels</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341">Develop your base across multiple floors by digging down into the earth or building up. Build fantastic dungeon designs or elaborate castles and towers.<h2 class="bb_tag">Roguelike mechanics </h2>The world is simulated on a very detailed level. Creatures use equipment and consumable items. There are dozens of special items, spells, attributes and special attacks. You can cut off heads and limbs and blind or poison your enemies. If you're not careful with fire, you can burn an entire forest or even your own dungeon.<h2 class="bb_tag">Large, procedurally generated maps </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-animated-gif-maker__2_.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL features a large, procedurally generated world. Explore dozens of locations, from small cottages and shops to major enemies dwelling in castles and dungeons. Uncover secrets, bring back great loot and prisoners back to your base in order to grow in power.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple playable factions</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/gif_keepers-ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>Play as a:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dark wizard researching black magic.<br/></li><li>White knight specialized in horses and angelic beings.<br/></li><li>Necromancer who crafts undead from the body parts of fallen enemies.<br/></li><li>Fragile colony of twelve dwarves.<br/></li><li>Goblin king searching for his lost wives.<br/></li><li>Collective of gnomes with a mechanized army.<br/></li><li>Lone adventurer focused on exploration.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Online map sharing </h2>KeeperRL offers the ability to download dungeons made by other players from Steam Workshop, and places them on your world map as enemies. See how others design their fortresses, fight with their minions, and steal their loot! After winning the game, you'll have the option to share your dungeon online as well.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<br/><br/>※ <i>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</i> is the free-to-play version of <i>Meta-Ghost: The breaking show</i>, to showcase some of the gameplay content.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709870080"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solium Infernum</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1893810/Solium_Infernum/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare yourself for Solium Infernum, the grand strategy game of politics, intrigue and betrayal, set in the ultimate arena of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingDarkSide2.gif?t=1710806769"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_IndulgeYourDarkSide_eng.png?t=1710806769"><br/>Satan's mysteriously vanished and Hell is in an uproar. Play as one of eight all-powerful and menacing Archfiends and indulge your Machiavellian dark side. Command legions, enlist champions, cast sinister rituals, and trick, rob, and insult your rivals to be crowned Hell’s new Dark Majesty.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingStrategy2.gif?t=1710806769"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_StrategyFromHell_eng.png?t=1710806769"><br/>Experience Solium Infernum's legendary devilish political machinations. Requiring nerves of steel and a true heart of darkness, every order you give will have lasting consequences. Get into the minds of your rivals, second-guessing their every move both on the map and on the floor of Hell’s parliament as you sling insults and demands in the only truly political strategy game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Eight playable Archfiends<br/></li><li>Eight single-player Chronicles<br/></li><li>Single-player Skirmish mode<br/></li><li>Revelations Tutorial Scenario<br/></li><li>Sessional and Asynchronous 2-6 player Multiplayer<br/></li><li>Dozens of Infernal Legions, including unique enormous Titans. <br/></li><li>Champion Praetors and dark Artifacts fit for any Archfiend!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingMulitplayer.gif?t=1710806769"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_InfernalMultiplayer_eng.png?t=1710806769"><br/>Play 2-6 player multiplayer games with your soon-to-be ex-friends in a single session of deceit and politics, or put your friendships to the test in quick daily bursts with Solium Infernum’s infamous asynchronous multiplayer for a truly harrowing scheme-in-your-sleep experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/Heading_DarkArt2.gif?t=1710806769"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_DivineMadness_eng.png?t=1710806769"><br/>If you love dark art, you’re in the right place. Brimming with striking visions of Hell unlike anything you’ve seen before, Solium Infernum is an infernal feast for the eyes with multitudes of individual dark paintings to enjoy. Every item of the game is accompanied by mind-blasting artwork, a feat declaring Solium Infernum a winner of the 2022 Game Makers Sketchbook.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingRessurect.gif?t=1710806769"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_CultClassic_eng.png?t=1710806769"><br/>Originally inspired by Milton’s epic poem, Paradise Lost, League of Geeks’ (known for seminal digital board game Armello) sophomore title is a re-imagining and modernisation of Vic Davis’ critically acclaimed cult-classic of the same name, hailed as a masterpiece of strategy game design. <br/><br/>Once again, prepare to lose yourself within ‘the cold glory of a difficult decision’ as we resurrect Solium Infernum from the depths of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/label_praise.png?t=1710806769"><br/>Note: The following quotes refer to the original Solium Infernum (2009) by Vic Davis.<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum is a political wargame set in hell… The game is now finished, and none of the friends survived. By which I mean, we all hate each other now.”</i> <br/>- Rock Paper Shotgun<br/><br/><i>“It’s a game about playing other people, in both senses of the word…. This is game design based on psychology as much as rules.” </i><br/>- Quarter to Three<br/><br/><i>“More than any game I've played in years, Solium Infernum nails the sensation of staring at a screen and losing yourself in the cold glory of a difficult decision.”</i><br/>- Game Developer (formerly Gamasutra)<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum kicked my knees out from under me ... this game took my past experience with strategy games and threw it, like a pro basketball player, into a bin eighty feet away.”</i><br/>- Eurogamer<br/><br/><i>“One of the best games of the year.”</i><br/>— Three Moves Ahead<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_toReign.png?t=1710806769"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milky Way TD SURVIVORS AUTOBATTLER RTS: Earth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2837340/Milky_Way_TD_SURVIVORS_AUTOBATTLER_RTS_Earth/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Milky Way is a mix of Tower Defense, RTS, Auto-Battler and Survivors genres. Visit planets in the Milky Way Galaxy and protect them against hordes of enemies.<br/>Milky Way: Earth is a demo version of the game, where 1 of 4 maps, 9 of 11 towers and 3 of 5 skills are available.<h2 class="bb_tag">BUILD YOUR BASE</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837340/extras/build.gif?t=1711138555"><br/>Develop your economy: gather stone with mines and gold with furnaces.<br/>Strengthen your defenses: use collected resources to build towers to fight off the enemies.<br/>Towers are divided into two types: some of them summon units, while others attack enemies. Some of the summoned units are perfect in order to distract enemies against themselves and protect other towers. Remember that the good placement of the towers is the key to victory.<h2 class="bb_tag">USE SKILLS</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837340/extras/gun.gif?t=1711138555"><br/>Gather mana with pylons and spend it on powerfull skills. You can summon a giant meteor, shoot with orbital gun or unleash a starfall on your enemies. Use everything to win!<h2 class="bb_tag">SURVIVE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837340/extras/orcs.gif?t=1711138555"><br/>There're over 40 types of enemies in the game, some of them have dangerous abilities. Can you survive against all of them?<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Dynamic and engaging gameplay<br/></li><li> A variety of gameplay styles<br/></li><li> 11 towers with their own abilities<br/></li><li> 4 maps with unique atmosphere<br/></li><li> Multitude of upgrades to choose from</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>冒险小子 Adventure boy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2734740/_Adventure_boy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2734740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Adventure Boy is a pixel style 2D board adventure game. The character will automatically move and attack enemies, and skills need to be manually cast. Career transfer provides career weapons and skills, but players can only choose one at a time. Upgrade to obtain random character values and skills, and combine them with different weapons and skills to create your own professional genre. In addition, there are ways to enhance combat effectiveness such as contracts, fruits, and gift boxes.<br/><br/><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Role upgrade</h2></strong><br/><br/>According to the level increase of the character, a random bonus to the character's numerical value and the acquisition of ordinary skills will be provided. Players can choose appropriate values and skills based on the genre they want to create.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2734740/extras/002.png?t=1711137144"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Ordinary skills</h2></strong><br/><br/>Ordinary skills are divided into upgradeable skills and non upgradeable skills. The maximum carrying capacity of non upgradeable skills is 2, and the maximum carrying capacity of upgradeable skills is 5. Upgradable skills can be upgraded up to 5 levels, and after 5 levels, the skills undergo a qualitative change with an additional entry. From low to high, there is a higher chance of achieving higher quality in white, green, and blue.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2734740/extras/001.png?t=1711137144"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Role transfer</h2></strong><br/><br/>Reaching a certain level allows for job transfer, with main professions being Warrior, Sagittarius, and Mage. There are two stages of job transfer, each time providing the professional weapons and skills of the profession. Only one can be selected for each job transfer, and completing the entire profession can be achieved through repeated job transfers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2734740/extras/004.png?t=1711137144"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Other content</h2></strong><br/><br/><strong>Contract: </strong>Players can choose to sign a powerful contract after passing the secret realm level, but the contract also comes with side effects.<br/><br/><br/><br/><strong>Gift Box:</strong> There will be a gift box with a number in the upper right corner of the interface, which represents the probability of successfully opening the gift box. If you think you're lucky, you can try clicking on the gift box at around 30%. Otherwise, it's better to be honest and achieve 100%<br/><br/><br/><br/><strong>Fruit: </strong>When you successfully open the gift box, you can choose the fruit reward, which provides you with character attribute bonuses and can be stacked infinitely. Fruits can also be obtained from completing levels and stored in your backpack before your adventure.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2734740/extras/005.png?t=1711137144"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aurans</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2871030/Aurans/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2871030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>"You have been chosen to shoulder heavy burdens and great powers. You will be granted an exceptional chance, Rowan Alanna Nightingale."</i><br/><br/>When homely nobody Rowan Nightingale gets hit by a car, she doesn't die, but instead is chosen to become an Auran - a being who can make anything happen, on three conditions: she has to be able to imagine it, believe it, and then create it. Taken under her mentor's wing, she travels to other dimensions and learns to harness the power of her imagination, slowly growing more confident in herself. But dark forces are lurking in the shadows, and who better to manipulate than a young, naïve Auran such as her? Soon, Rowan must fight her inner demons - quite literally - in order to save the dimensions from being destroyed. But can you truly believe that you are stronger than the darkest, most evil force in the entire multiverse, when all your life you have believed you weren't worth anything at all?<br/><br/><i>Aurans</i> is a kinetic visual novel, meaning it is linear and with no choices. It is a story about coming of age, learning to believe in yourself, and finding out what really matters to you. Everything is fully hand drawn, and is the first visual novel project of Pixelsplosion Studios.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Story of Mine Company</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2567390/Story_of_Mine_Company/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2567390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Hire miners</h2>You can hire miner for 1 day, or if you have enough lodging space, you can buy his debts.<br/><br/><strong>Hired miners</strong> will work for you for 1 day and then leave. Also, they only get paid at the end of the day unless they have a fatal accident.<br/><strong>Miners-debtors</strong> will work for you forever, so you only have to pay for provisions. You will also receive 2 additional inventory cells since, after work, they return to the base with you.<h2 class="bb_tag">Try to control the chaos of the workflow</h2>In the process of extracting resources, various ridiculous situations arise since the behavior of the miners is unpredictable and sometimes stupid. They can start smoking next to nitrate blocks or start digging a block that has other miners on it. At the same time, blocks under which there is no support or other blocks can collapse with some chance, breaking all buildings under them. The player will have to respond in time to a constantly changing situation.<h2 class="bb_tag">Trade in the market</h2>Prices in the game are volatile. Store resources in storage and sell them at profitable prices.<h2 class="bb_tag">Improve your buildings</h2><strong>Lodging</strong> - increases the max number of miners-debtors.<br/><strong>Storage</strong> - allows you to store items until better days.<br/><strong>Cargo</strong> - allows you to carry more items with you.<br/><strong>Workshop</strong> - allows you to craft items.<h2 class="bb_tag">Control</h2><strong>Player mode</strong> - Action1 set target. Action2 pick up item.<br/><strong>Building mode</strong> - Action1 buid. Action2 destroy. Action3 quick destroy (middle mouse by default).						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TekSkeleton</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2587470/TekSkeleton/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2587470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2587470/extras/DescEng2.jpg?t=1711132088"><br/><br/>TekSkeleton this is a hardcore 2D platformer with 5 hand-crafted levels wrapped in atmospheric retro dungeon-style graphics. This is the debut game of the Tek line games. <br/><br/><strong>Features!</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Spirit of retro games<br/></li><li>Stylish dungeon theme<br/></li><li>Linear progression of levels<br/></li><li>5 difficult handmade levels<br/></li><li>Convenient and sensitive control<br/></li><li>Automatic level restart after loss</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desert Witch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2775880/Desert_Witch/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2775880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							When using a sniper rifle, you eliminate enemies at long distances, although sometimes you have to fight at close range, then you can use a short weapon.<br>
The action takes place in an open world, in a desert area filled with numerous buildings that the player can use to hide or attack.<br>
The game consists of 15 missions in which the player's task is to eliminate a specific person or several depending on the mission.<br>
Completed missions can be repeated in any order.<br>
The target is also a moving car or a building that needs to be blown up.<br>
The notebook contains maps, mission description, information on how to find the target, and a calculator that helps you properly set the telescope, taking into account the distance to the target, wind strength and direction.<br>
In the game, we look from a third-person view from behind. The view changes to first-person FPS when we observe the area through a building window or through a telescope.<br/>
Looking through the telescope, we can turn on the image from the camera tracking the bullet's flight in real time, which is useful at long distances when the bullet's flight lasts several seconds and the target is less visible.<br/>
The bullet's flight is reproduced in accordance with reality, taking into account gravity, side wind and decreasing speed with distance.<br/>
It happens that shots are fired at a distance of over 2 km, the game area is approximately 3x3 km, it is a desert with four built-up districts.<br/>
Generally, our opponent is a group of bandits who want to take control of the newly created city, the player's task is to eliminate them from the occupied area.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gore Doctor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2495990/Gore_Doctor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495990/extras/wishlist_now.gif?t=1711131687"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495990/extras/about7.png?t=1711131687"><br/><br/>Gore Doctor is an immersive horror game set to unleash spine-chilling thrills on PC. You find yourself in the institute of a tormented doctor who, driven by desperation, defies ethical boundaries to save his wife, Scarlett, from a deadly illness. As Scarlett succumbs to her fate, the doctor descends into madness and becomes convinced that death is the only respite. Players must navigate the nightmarish corridors of the doctor’s institute, confronting grotesque horrors, uncovering dark secrets, and striving to escape with their lives intact. <strong>Can you survive the twisted labyrinth and unravel the haunting mysteries within?</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495990/extras/GIF1.gif?t=1711131687"><br/><br/>Your journey begins within the decrepit and foreboding walls of the doctor's institute, a place once dedicated to healing but now consumed by malevolence and despair. <strong>Each step you take into the dimly lit corridors leads you deeper into a world of grotesque horrors, twisted experiments, and unspeakable terror.</strong> The atmosphere is thick with dread, and every creaking floorboard and distant moan only serves to heighten your anxiety.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495990/extras/survive1.png?t=1711131687"><br/><br/>As you navigate the labyrinthine halls, you'll encounter grotesque abominations, born from the doctor's relentless pursuit of knowledge and power. These nightmarish creatures will stop at nothing to protect the doctor's secrets, and you must summon every ounce of courage to survive their relentless pursuit. <strong>The vivid and disturbing visuals will sear into your mind, leaving an indelible mark long after you've escaped the clutches of this nightmare.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495990/extras/GIF2.gif?t=1711131687"><br/><br/>But survival alone is not enough. To truly understand the horrors that have unfolded within these walls, <strong>you must uncover the dark secrets that fester beneath the surface. </strong>Through journal entries, scattered documents, and hidden artifacts, you'll piece together the doctor's descent into madness and the terrible consequences of his actions. <strong>The truth you unearth will challenge your very perception of right and wrong, blurring the line between savior and monster.</strong><br/><br/>Gore Doctor is not for the faint of heart. It is a game that revels in the grotesque, pushing the boundaries of horror and gore to create an experience that will leave you breathless and disturbed. <strong>Brace yourself for a psychological rollercoaster ride, where your every nerve will be tested, and your darkest fears will be unleashed.</strong> Only the strongest will emerge from the doctor's institute with their sanity intact, but be warned, the price of survival may be higher than you can imagine.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495990/extras/GIF3.gif?t=1711131687"><br/><br/><strong>Enter at your own risk, for once you step into the twisted world of Gore Doctor, there may be no escape from its clutches.</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labyrinth of Rage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2492560/Labyrinth_of_Rage/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2492560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">A Souls-Like game like nothing seen before</h2><br/>Trapped inside a <strong>Labyrinth constructed inside a demonic realm</strong>, our hero must face the deepest and darkest depths inside these twisted walls. Imbued with the power of <strong>magic, combat, and archery.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Will you escape the Labyrinth?</h2><br/>Fight your way against hordes of monsters while traversing through the twisted hallways.<h2 class="bb_tag">Various Combat Styles</h2><br/>Use different styles of combat like one-handed sword &amp; shield, bow &amp; arrows, and magic! With many more combat styles on the way.<h2 class="bb_tag">Level up through Gear!</h2><br/>Become stronger by wandering through the labyrinth and acquiring new weapons and armor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Many updates on the way (Early Access)</h2><br/>This game is still in it's infancy and will continue to grow, for the time being it is in Early Access right now.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>gold scrapping simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2709550/gold_scrapping_simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							gold scrapping simulator is a game where you can extract gold from old electronics and smelt it and sell it ,start by working for someone else and then by old item , scrap gold , and sell it or create online store to sell the Valuable items  , or use it in mining<br>
<br>
Some features of the game ;<br>
 Tablet system<br>
 Online stores<br>
 player online store<br>
 Mining system<br/>
 Bills System<br/>
 buy and sell pc parts<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Note : There is so many features will be added in the future and we waiting your suggestions to add it .						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climber Animals: Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2744880/Climber_Animals_Together/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FBw5hVwmqFn" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744880/extras/DISCORD_COME.gif?t=1711127438"/></a><br/><br/><br/>Climber Animals: Together is an exciting and challenging parkour experience for 1 to 8 players. In this game, players try to find their way through a world full of dynamic and challenging obstacles. Each obstacle tests players' strategy, speed and skill. On unique and vividly designed courses, you have the goal of reaching the top by racing shoulder to shoulder with or against your friends.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744880/extras/gif2.gif?t=1711127438"><br/><br/>One of the most important features of the game is that with every fall, your progress is lost and players have to start all over again. While this creates an equal starting point for all players at the beginning of each level, it also increases the difficulty level of the game. This allows for different strategies and paths to be explored each time a level is retried.<br/>Players need to keep their balance and overcome obstacles to reach the top. In this process, it is important for players to use their reflexes, speed and strategic thinking skills. Players can cooperate with or challenge their friends to make their way through this challenging and fun course.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744880/extras/gif1.gif?t=1711127438"><br/><br/>Climber Animals: Together offers a fun and challenging course experience that appeals to all age groups, opening the door to enjoyable moments with your friends. <br/>Every climb is a new adventure and every fall is another opportunity to try something new. Dodge spinning hammers, dodge boxing gloves and keep your balance on spinning poles on this exciting journey!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744880/extras/gif3.gif?t=1711127438"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circus of TimTim - Mascot Horror Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2697070/Circus_of_TimTim__Mascot_Horror_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Circus of TimTim</strong> is a Stealth Horror Survival Game about two siblings trying to sneak inside the most hunted carnival of all time to recover lost items with a metal detector device, however enemies are roaming around and they can hear your every step in the circus. <br/><br/>This is a first person stealth adventure horror game that takes place inside a run-down circus. Play as a sibling tasked to find her brother's missing items after an incident that occurred there, but beware as strange things are happening. Roam around, stealth, hide, run and survive to to uncover the secrets of what happened at the Circus of TimTim - a once fun place turned deadly.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697070/extras/clown.gif?t=1711126873"><br/><br/><strong>Free to explore the run-down circus</strong><br/>Explore the circus and the mysteries that lies ahead. You can freely roam around the carnival to finish your tasks, but beware as something will not allow you to stay there. You have to hide and use stealth in order to evade the enemies.<br/><br/><strong>Equipped with a metal detector, to find items!</strong><br/>You will be equipped with a metal detector to find items lost inside the circus, however while the metal detector can aid you and help you find items quickly, the beeping sound that it will make will attract enemies to your location - so choose wisely!<h2 class="bb_tag">Use tools to lead you to your next objective - but careful as enemies can hear the beep!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697070/extras/toilet.gif?t=1711126873"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the ruins and death of what was once a fun-family circus!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697070/extras/explore.gif?t=1711126873"><h2 class="bb_tag">Make sure not to get lost in it's beauty, because it can be deadly.</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697070/extras/ferry.gif?t=1711126873"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the insides of every corner of the carnival and leave no stone unturned!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697070/extras/bone.gif?t=1711126873"><h2 class="bb_tag">Find items that can help you in the circus.</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697070/extras/teddy.gif?t=1711126873"><h2 class="bb_tag">Filled with threats, that you need to evade by distracting them or using stealth!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697070/extras/dis1.gif?t=1711126873"><h2 class="bb_tag">Lurking at every corner of the circus, so always be aware!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697070/extras/bunny.gif?t=1711126873"><h2 class="bb_tag">Making noise, stepping on rubber ducks and more can attract the enemy!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697070/extras/duck1.gif?t=1711126873"><h2 class="bb_tag">Find tickets and exchange them to open doors by the creepy booth master! </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697070/extras/woman.gif?t=1711126873"><h2 class="bb_tag">If you get discovered, your only option is to find somewhere to hide or die.</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697070/extras/run.gif?t=1711126873"><br/><br/><strong>Circus of TimTim</strong> is a stealth horror game developed and published by 2 developers at Mascot Bro Studio. Any feedback is very much appreciated! Thank you very much.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Legend of Legacy HD Remastered</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2516220/The_Legend_of_Legacy_HD_Remastered/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							RPG fans rejoice as the classic adventure, The Legend of Legacy is remastered in HD and debuting on Steam!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">INTRODUCTION </h2></strong><br/>Many have come, seeking riches, glory, and legendary treasure, but in the end, they all vanish, swallowed up by the darkness. None have seen into the heart of this island, now awakened from its eternal slumber—the mythical land known as Avalon.<br/>Do its depths hide a stairway to paradise or the gates to the abyss?<br/>This is the tale of some yet unknown truth, spun from the legacies of the ancient gods.<br/><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">HD REMASTER'S FEATURES</h2></strong><br/>Beautifully improved graphics and image quality shine in HD! <br/>The new guidebook function makes it easy for newcomers to get started, and the addition of detailed functions allow all players intuitive gameplay options and ease of access.<br/><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">KEY POINTS</h2></strong><br/>Explore a world map bursting with story-book charm. When characters move, the surrounding terrain springs to life like a pop-up picture book.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516220/extras/Legend_of_Legacy_-_Field---Meurs-Running-616x347.jpg?t=1711127520"><br/><br/><br/>Grow your adventure with each step you take and discover more of the map.<br/>As your character moves, the map will be drawn and filled in. This unique feature is called Cartograph.<br/><br/><br/>Legend of Legacy features seven main characters and limitless adventures!<br/>Choose from one of the seven characters to lead your adventure and challenge the legend of Avalon! Legend of Legacy features no set route in the story allowing players the ability to fully and freely control their destinies.<br/><br/><br/>Join forces with the spirits of Avalon to harness the elemental attributes of the battlefield and overcome mighty enemies!<br/>The Fusion World View System by Kyoji Koizumi, creator of multiple innovative battle systems, allows players a unique and exciting combat experience.<br/>In addition there are four types of spirits–water, wind, fire, and darkness. Compete with your foes to claim the elementals’ power and dominate the battlefield.<br/>Players can also utilize spirit arts by making contracts with spirits during battle. When used, the power of a spirit and the associated technique will gain strength allowing you to decimate powerful enemies.<br/>This struggle for power is performed simultaneously with a single command, called a Two-Dimensional Battle.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516220/extras/Legend_of_Legacy_-_Battle---Skill-3-616x347.jpg?t=1711127520"><br/><br/><br/>The sound design of Legend of Legacy shines with a BGM that pursues quality game music with thoughtfully created environmental sounds that spare no attention to detail. Wind, waves, monster cries, changes in footsteps, and echoes within buildings can all be clearly heard in an effort to enhance your experience within the vast expanse of the world! The music was created with the goal of expressing emotions, touching heartstrings, and engraving to memory a one-of-a-kind RPG experience.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516220/extras/LoLHD_PV1_GIF-616x274.gif?t=1711127520"><br/><br/><br/>Legend of Legacy HD Remastered brings classic RPG charm with new and exciting twists to the HD era! With vast gameplay options, thoughtful sound design and beautiful music this RPG adventure is a must add to your wishlist!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True Virus</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1514900/True_Virus/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1514900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1514900/extras/baletnica600x200.png?t=1711126610"><br/><br/>In True Virus, you play the role of a mental hospital patient who has awoken in a world devastated by a deadly pandemic. Your job is to explore the psychiatric hospital and its surroundings in search of clues to find out what really happened.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1514900/extras/stylized_graphics.png?t=1711126610"><br/>Featuring stylized graphics, "True Virus" creates a visually striking and atmospheric environment that enhances the sense of anxiety and trepidation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1514900/extras/tv_gif__2_.gif?t=1711126610"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1514900/extras/mystery.png?t=1711126610"><br/>As you traverse the twisted landscape of the abandoned city, you'll encounter a series of complex puzzles and thought-provoking challenges. Sharpen your problem-solving skills by unlocking hidden passages, deciphering cryptic codes and discovering hidden objects.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1514900/extras/tv_gif_2.gif?t=1711126610"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1514900/extras/puzzle_solving.png?t=1711126610"><br/>Uncover secrets that hide in the darkness, revealing layer after layer of the disturbing story unfolding before you. Delve into the lives of forgotten patients and hospital staff, gradually piecing together their stories and their connection to the mysterious pandemic.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1514900/extras/tv_playerroom_photo.png?t=1711126610"><br/><br/>Will you be able to defeat the abandoned psychiatric hospital and unravel the mystery behind the True Virus?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enigmarble</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2613110/Enigmarble/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2613110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an extraordinary puzzle journey with Enigmarble, the game that brings puzzles to a whole new level! Get ready to immerse yourself in a world of intricately designed challenges and mind-bending fun.<br/><br/>Take control of a marble with your mouse, collect pick-ups and strategically touch interactive blocks while mastering precise movement and dodges to conquer the hazards.<h2 class="bb_tag">Handcrafted Levels</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2613110/extras/Enigmarble-HandcraftedLevels-GIF-optimized.gif?t=1711126288"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in 90 unique level designs meticulously created to test your problem-solving skills. Each level is a work of art, offering challenges that eveolve as you progress. Prepare for an adventure that's as visually stunning as it is intellectually stimulating.<h2 class="bb_tag">Visually Diverse Worlds</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2613110/extras/Enigmarble-VisuallyDiverseWorld-Steam-GIF-optimized.gif?t=1711126288"><br/>Explore the hand-drawn landscapes of Enigmarble, where each level is a visual masterpiece. With six distinct themes, you'll navigate through mysterious dungeons, mechanical steampunk, candy wonderland, lush forests, and futuristic sci-fi. Enigmarble takes you on a visual journey like no other puzzle game.<h2 class="bb_tag">Strategize, Solve, Suceed</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2613110/extras/Enigmarble-DynamicPuzzleElements-GIF-optimized.gif?t=1711126288"><br/>Unleash your inner strategist as you encounter a plethora of interactive puzzle elements in Enigmarble.  Maneuver through switches, doors, pipes, pistons, and a variety of pushable and destructible blocks. Watch out for perilous traps and enemies as you navigate the mazes, making every move a strategic choice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Boss Challenges</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2613110/extras/Enigmarble-BossChallenges-GIF-v2-optimized.gif?t=1711126288"><br/>At the end of each world face the ultimate test in a boss level that will push your puzzle-solving skills to the limit. These challenges are not for the faint of heart. Test your skills and strategic thinking, providing an adrenaline-pumping experience for those seeking the ultimate Enigmarble conquest.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost Love Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2676960/Lost_Love_Island/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FDwA6Sv2D9A" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676960/extras/SaikeyDiscord_new_english.png?t=1711125571"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676960/extras/SteamBannerStory_LLI.png?t=1711125571"><br/><br/>Every party is only as good as its healer. A motto followed by young adventurer Lloyd when he teams up with Meryl, a healer whose talent is only surpassed by her beauty. Everything seems to go fine up until their ship gets sunk by a kraken, leaving them both stranded on a lone island. From now on it's up to Lloyd to survive and take care of Meryl. Clothes, food, tools and weapons, he has to scout the island for resources and crafting materials while hunting animals and chopping wood in a game of survival and exploration.<br/><br/>Eventually, Lloyd and Meryl learn that they're not alone on the island. Other survivors made it out of the ship too, and they even meet a small number of local inhabitants. Some of them join Lloyd and Meryl, united in their will to find a way to set sail back home again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676960/extras/SteamBannerGameplay_LLI.png?t=1711125571"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survival Mechanics:</h2>Lloyd has to manage his stamina as he's exploring the island. If it runs out while he's traveling alone, he won't be able to make it back to Meryl at the camp until the next day. Stamina can be replenished by cooking various meals.<h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting System:</h2>To progress the game and explore the island, Lloyd will need to craft an assortment of tools. Cutting wood, catching fish, hunting wild animals and setting up new pathways with bridges or ropes will be among the most essential tasks in the quest for survival.<h2 class="bb_tag">Changeable Appearance:</h2>Meryl has four different outfits to pick from. Some need to be found before she can wear them. Furthermore, the island's bright sun may have an effect on Meryl's skin, lending her pale complexion a darker, tanned tone. Meryl's appearance can be changed at any time, only depending on game progress.<h2 class="bb_tag">Affection:</h2>Manage an affection system based on character actions. The choice is yours!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676960/extras/SteamBannerCharacters_LLI.png?t=1711125571"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676960/extras/SteamCharaMeryl.png?t=1711125571"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676960/extras/SteamCharaKarina.png?t=1711125571"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676960/extras/SteamCharaSalim.png?t=1711125571"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676960/extras/SteamCharaBob.png?t=1711125571"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676960/extras/SteamCharaLuke.png?t=1711125571"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676960/extras/SteamCharaJeff.png?t=1711125571"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Stack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2868240/Just_Stack/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2868240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Just Stack</strong><br/><br/>Just Stack is a simple and addictive casual game where you stack randomly spawned objects as high as possible.<br/>Challenge your limits to see how high you can stack surreal objects using Unreal Engine 5's beautiful graphics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Into the Dungeon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497910/Into_the_Dungeon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497910/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497910/extras/ACoopDeckbuilder.png?t=1711124883"><br/><strong>Into the Dungeon</strong> is a roguelike deck builder with online coop. Play as one of 4 classes to battle creatures from a grim fantasy world tainted by evil. Build your deck with class unique cards, unlock artifacts that augment the way you play, and team-up with cross class synergies. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497910/extras/4_classes_banner.png?t=1711124883"><br/>Into the Dungeon features 4 unique character classes, each with their own unique perks, cards and playstyles.<h2 class="bb_tag">Classes</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>The Wizard</strong> deals high damage and manipulates the <i>Exhaust</i> card mechanic to his advantage. His unique class artifact the <i>Mana Stone</i> carries mana over through rounds allowing him to deal massive damage with high cost cards.<br/></li><li><strong>The Paladin</strong> can sustain heavy damage with his unique class artifact <i>Plate Armor</i>. He utilizes combos between offensive and defensive cards to deal heavy damage while maintaining his defensive stats. <br/></li><li><strong>The Viking</strong> deals massive damage through single turn combos while granting herself and her allies damage buffs and resistances. Her unique class artifact the <i>Three Leaf Clover</i> enhances her multi-attack playstyle, increasing her damage on every third strike. <br/></li><li><strong>The Bard</strong> is the most complex of the classes with a totally different playstyle from the rest thanks to her unique class artifact the <i>Musicians Trick</i>. Her artifact builds up power every time she plays a card, unleashing the stored energy whenever she plays her unique <i>Song</i> cards. Additionally, She utilizes poisons to her advantage, building up damage over the course of a combat. </li></ul><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497910/extras/Realtime_Combat.png?t=1711124883"><br/>What makes <strong>Into the Dungeon</strong> different from other cooperative card-battlers is that <strong>all players act in real time</strong>. This keeps the pace of the game fast and fun as you simultaneously blast your foes and increase your power. Delve deep into a roguelike deck builder with an easy introduction and a deep challenge to keep you engaged.<h2 class="bb_tag">Hardcore Mode</h2>Upon completing the game in classic mode you will unlock <strong>Hardcore Mode</strong>. This mode is designed to challenge experienced rogue-like deck-builder fans. It includes boosted stats for enemies as well as a round timer for some added pressure. <br/><br/><br/><strong>Join</strong> the <strong>Into the Dungeon Discord</strong>.<br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fp6avBTJruZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/p6avBTJruZ</a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Alchemist's Apprentice in the Maze of Madness</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2597340/The_Alchemists_Apprentice_in_the_Maze_of_Madness/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2597340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Alchemist's Apprentice and you got yourself into some trouble. While sweeping the dorms you somehow managed to get yourself into the final test for your apprenticeship - which would be nice and well and all were it not for the fact that you started your training two weeks ago and know literally nothing about the subject.<br/>And what is that final test, you ask? Well, it is the Maze of Madness, of course. And it deserves that name. Because it is literally designed to drive you mad. So good luck getting out of there without loosing your marbles.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2597340/extras/logo_small.png?t=1711123636"><br/>Dungeon Crawlers are a staple of classic gaming. The first game of the genre was created in 1975 and throughout the 1980s and 1990s the genre enjoyed great success. This game is a loveletter to the genre, with a little twist, of course.<br/>First, there is no combat. Rather, the entire game is about exploration and puzzle solving. Each maze is randomly generated and requries you to mix and match various alchemical elements to complete the labyrinth. Of course these elements must be found first and more often than not traps make that job a lot more difficult. A ticking clock adds pressure to the mix and if time runs out you will end up going insane. Luckily you are provided with a map of each maze and maybe, just maybe, you can find a few upgrades to make navigation easier.<br/><br/><strong><i><u>Features:</u></i></strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedurally generated mazes - No playthrough will ever be the same<br/></li><li>Simple but addictive gameplay - explore, mix and match<br/></li><li>Modern QOL features to help you navigate - maps, upgrades and tooltips<br/></li><li>Completely playable with the mouse - keyboard movement is an option<br/></li><li>Wonderful music to keep you engaged - Composed by Aron Ben Elal</li></ul><br/><i>Enjoy this nice little throwback over and over again. You are the Alchemist's Apprentice and if you survive this test, you maybe can drop that 'Apprentice' from your title.</i> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's Always a Madman: Fight or Flight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2390500/Theres_Always_a_Madman_Fight_or_Flight/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2390500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of the suave secret agent Franklin Benjamin in this single-player spy thriller interactive novel. In this high-octane, two-hour satire of James Bond and Mission: Impossible, you'll drive fast cars, seduce beautiful women, take on false identities, and do whatever is necessary to save the world<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Your Mission</strong></h2>In short, your mission is to save the world, same as always. This time, there's a madman threatening the world with weaponized satellite technology that can strike anywhere at any time, including wiping out other satellites. So it's up to you to ferret out his identity and bring him to justice - or take him out entirely. You're the only one who can stop him, so we're counting on you to accept this mission<br/><br/>Assisting you in this endeavor is the usual team - your experienced partner in the field, Virginia, and our resident tech whiz, Hatcher. But the success or failure of this mission rests on your shoulders and yours alone. This is a single-player game, after all<br/><br/><strong><i>There's Always a Madman: Fight or Flight</i></strong> can be played with just a mouse. Gameplay consists of selecting the action or dialog you wish to take given the situation you’re facing. Although the life of a secret agent is complicated, playing <strong><i>There's Always a Madman: Fight or Flight</i></strong> is simple<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Uncover the Identity of the Madman du jour</strong></h2>Our intel for this mission unfortunately doesn't give us a precise identity for this particular madman, but if he gains control of the airspace above the Earth, then he effectively controls the world. So flush him out and foil his scheme<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Think Before You Shoot</strong></h2>As a secret agent, it's not about who has the fastest trigger finger. Put your mind to good use and make intelligent in-the-moment decisions on how best to handle your current predicament. Only by out-thinking your opponents can you survive to tell the tale<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Save the World in Style</strong></h2>Make use of any and all gadgets in your arsenal to get the job done. And then after you best your foes, rub it in their faces with a well-chosen pun, of course<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Sounds Like a Winner</strong></h2>Although the game is text-based like a novel, an emphasis is placed on visuals and music to set the appropriate mood for each scene, changing based on whether you're in a safe location or you're exposed to danger<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Short and Not-So-Sweet</strong></h2><strong><i>There's Always A Madman: Fight or Flight</i></strong> aims to be about the length of a movie for a single playthrough (roughly two hours). During that time, you may very well have to do some not-so-nice things to succeed. You know, like engaging in shootouts, fistfights, and high speed chases. But that's okay - as they say, nice guys finish last. And we need you to come out on top<br/><br/>For reference, here are some similar games to help you get a further sense for what <strong><i>There's Always A Madman</i></strong> is like: GoldenEye 007 (and other James Bond games like Everything or Nothing), Mission: Impossible, Alpha Protocol, Hitman games, Splinter Cell games, Henchman Story, Agent A: A Puzzle in Disguise, Framed, I Expect You To Die, Batman Telltale Series, The Wolf Among Us, Agent 64: Spies Never Die<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Q: Why make this game text-based? Why not use visuals?</strong></h2>A: James Bond, Jason Bourne, Jack Reacher, and Jack Ryan all started off in text format with novels.  I believe this is the right move for the project - as they say, <strong>the book is always better</strong>, so I think a more book-like experience works here.  The game's text will of course be supplemented with music to set the appropriate mood, such as whether you're in danger or in a safe spot<br/><br/>We're all counting on you to save the day. <strong>After all - if you don't save the world, then there can't be a sequel</strong><br/><br/>This game is the start of a new video game franchise called <strong><i>There's Always A Madman</i></strong>. <strong>Fight or Flight</strong> is the first game in this series - follow the franchise to be notified about this and future games in the series: <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/franchise/TheresAlwaysAMadman" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/franchise/TheresAlwaysAMadman</a><br/><br/>Press kit for journalists and content creators: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdrive.google.com%2Fdrive%2Ffolders%2F1JEw_r99uzERAWqJIU2tOwzl3AKQdPc_O" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1JEw_r99uzERAWqJIU2tOwzl3AKQdPc_O</a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2390500/Theres_Always_a_Madman_Fight_or_Flight" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2390500/Theres_Always_a_Madman_Fight_or_Flight</a><br/><br/>Follow the <strong><i>There's Always a Madman</i></strong> franchise to be notified about this and future games in the series: <br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/franchise/TheresAlwaysAMadman" rel="" target="_blank">The "There's Always a Madman" franchise on Steam</a><br/><br/>And don't forget to check out my previous game, the cozy RPG <strong><i>A Weekend in Puzzleburg</i></strong>. <strong><i>There's Always a Madman</i></strong> is technically a spin-off of <strong><i>A Weekend in Puzzleburg</i></strong> since this new game is based on the Franklin Benjamin character first seen on a channel from the Puzzleburg hotel room TV<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1929760/A_Weekend_in_Puzzleburg" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1929760/A_Weekend_in_Puzzleburg</a><br/><br/>Or check out these other spy video games on Steam from other developers:<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1574480/Agent_64_Spies_Never_Die" rel="" target="_blank">Agent 64: Spies Never Die</a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2318870/Pizza_Spy" rel="" target="_blank">Pizza Spy</a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/801480/Agent_A_A_puzzle_in_disguise" rel="" target="_blank">Agent A: A Puzzle in Disguise</a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/322450/FRAMED_Collection" rel="" target="_blank">Framed Collection</a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1170760/XIII__Classic" rel="" target="_blank">XIII - Classic</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears In Space</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1309620/Bears_In_Space/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FG6w3Zxbp8W" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/Steam_CTAbutton_Discord.png?t=1711123009"/></a><br/>Get ready to unleash your inner bear in Bears in Space, the over-the-top<br/>bullet-hell FPS that's bound to have you ROARING with excitement! Dive headfirst into hordes of oil-thirsty robots as you embody Maxwell Atoms, a Spacetronaut turned extraterrestrial castaway, whose DNA has been merged with Beartana, the She-Bear. <br/>Embark on a zany and humorous out-of-this-world adventure that'll have you blasting your way across exciting and varied locations, from wastelands to space carnivals to ancient hidden temples and more as you quest to find your way back to earth and if there’s time, save your crew.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fast-paced Mayhem</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/BulletHell_acid2.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Bears In Space offers non-stop, high-energy gameplay. Fight your way through waves of fiendish robots using an arsenal of outrageous weaponry and gadgets. Double jump, dash, and dodge enemy attacks in the tradition of the best old-school shooters.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Mighty As A Bear</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/BearMode.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Consume elusive honey pots and unleash your Ursine rage, transforming into a bear!  <br/>Use your unique DNA fusion to your advantage, carving up robot enemies with your mighty bear powers and masterful knowledge of the ancient art of Bear Fu and the fabled Kuma No Ken.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Upgrade Your Arsenal</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/UpgradeRadial.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Complete challenges and break open loot crates to purchase guns, choosing from a diverse range of over 25 weapons!<br/>Most weapons upgrade, with each kill gaining your equipped weapon XP until it evolves into its next evolution tier! So, get out there and let the lasers fly!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Varied Gameplay</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/Varied_Gameplay_BasketCube.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Venture beyond the ordinary FPS experience and discover Substories, secrets and collectibles across every level!<br/>Learn how to bake a cake, investigate a crime scene, battle a Rock God, play a round of Basketcube and even bust some ghosts! All while meeting a colourful cast of characters with their own quirks and stories to tell.<br/>Completing these exciting optional encounters brings with it a hefty loot pay off, making these encounters even more rewarding to search out as you save up for your next weapon!<br/><br/>Choose your difficulty and play the game your way!<br/>Modify your difficulty with independent sliders for incoming and outgoing damage. You can also engage our Platform Helper mode, making all platforming segments of our game significantly easier to conquer! Perfect for kids or gamers new to the FPS genre!<br/><br/><br/>Whether you're a seasoned gamer looking for a blast from the past or a casual player seeking a fun-filled adventure, Bears in Space promises a fun and absurd, action packed time. Get ready to shoot, chuckle, and unleash your inner bear in this one-of-a-kind bullet-hell FPS adventure that’s truly out of this world!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4D Golf</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2147950/4D_Golf/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2147950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>4D Golf</strong> is a mind-bending golf game unlike any other because it's set entirely in a 4-dimensional space. Complete fun and unique golfing challenges as you gain hands-on experience of the 4th dimension and beyond!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2147950/extras/SteamGIF_1.gif?t=1711121562"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 120 levels and 7 vibrant themed worlds<br/></li><li>Tons of visualization options to master 4D space<br/></li><li>Build your own 4D courses in the level editor<br/></li><li>Race the clock in Marble Platforming Mode<br/></li><li>Navigate hidden paths, moving platforms, shifting gravity, speed boosts, and more!<br/></li><li>Unlock custom accessories by completing challenges</li></ul><br/>Now open your third eye and unleash your full potential!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tower Doomer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2864780/Tower_Doomer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2864780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Tower Doomer is a game about physics and demolishing. The main goal is to destroy wooden structures by shooting at them with different projectiles. To complete a level, bring down the golden sphere on the ground, demolish at leat 50% of the structure and do all this with limited strokes. Find the weak spot of each structure to bring it down with less than a few shots. Once a level is finish, you can now play with time and gravity to unleash chaos in an slow motion and free gravity world. Progress through levels to discover new worlds and environments.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Sandbox Mode :</h2>Tower Doomer offers you a sandbox mode where you can create your own structures or use premade one and put them in the demolishing arena. In the sandbox mode, there is no limitation of strokes, gravity and slow motion can be toggle off or on as you wish. This mode is here for letting free your urges of mass destruction and chaos.<br/><br/>Have fun playing with the laws of physics !						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmer's Father: The Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802690/Farmers_Father_The_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Farmer's Father: The Origins</strong> is a free prologue of Farmer's Father. You have 60 minutes to explore, have a glimpse of the story and game mechanics. Fight with hunger, wounds, cold, disease, and enemy cruelty. Defend your family and survive the war! If you like a prologue. Get a full game here:<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1905980/Farmers_Father_Save_the_Innocence/" id="dynamiclink_6" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1905980/Farmers_Father_Save_the_Innocence/</a><br/><br/><i>"The first casualty of war is innocence"</i><br/><br/>War breeds heroes you've never heard of. You are the ordinary person holding a huge burden of protecting what's most precious and innocent. Fight with hunger, wounds, cold, disease, and enemy cruelty. Defend your family and survive the war!<br/><br/>Imagine waking up in the middle of the snowy night to the sounds of a falling sky. Explosions, fire, chaos, the frightened whimper of your child. It’s your turn: now or never, slip away from your enemies before it's too late…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802690/extras/Gif1.gif?t=1711119440"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>FEW OF MAIN FEATURES IN THE GAME</strong></h2><br/>🕊️ Building - animal homestead, baby cradle, trough, and more<br/>🕊️ Crafting - create something useful out of junk<br/>🕊️ Cooking - prepare all kinds of food out of what you can find<br/>🕊️ Sneaking - move quietly then you'll survive<br/>🕊️ Hunting - use guns and provide needed food<br/>🕊️ Exploring - strange sounds, enemies, unknown territories<br/>🕊️ Taking care of family - making family safe, fed, and warm<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>PROTECT YOUR FAMILY</strong></h2>As a father, since the first breath of your child, you’ve always known the responsibility relies on your shoulders… but the stakes were never that high. Do what you must to keep your wife and son alive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802690/extras/Gif2.gif?t=1711119440"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>FARM, HUNT, IMPROVISE</strong></h2>Nothing can be taken for granted now. You will have to earn every meal and bargain for each piece of comfort for you and your family using extreme measures. Hunt for wild animals, make forest recipes, and, as a farmer, use your skills to create a new home during the occupation…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802690/extras/Gif3.gif?t=1711119440"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE</strong></h2>Sneak, wait for your moment, and ATTACK! Every. Second. Counts. Your enemies are cunning and trained. Can you handle that while being "just" a farmer? Your everyday abilities may come in handy so don’t underestimate yourself and keep trying!<br/><br/><strong>After all, you’ve got nothing to lose and everything to gain.</strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hell Inside</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2588390/The_Hell_Inside/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2588390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Hell Inside is an action roguelike taking place in familiar places turned unfamiliar.<br>
<br>
Waking up with nothing but a book as a weapon, you must battle through hordes of monsters that do not seem to have a place here.<br>
<br>
The book is your weapon, and your only one. Your life depends on it.<br>
<br>
The book starts out as as a weak projectile, but with the power of adding pages with upgrades written on them, the book can change and morph into what is needed. Upgrades range drastically with some playing a more supportive role such as a laser sight or a more offensive role, like changing your projectiles into knives.<br/>
<br/>
New pages can also be written by finding ink during runs. These pages can be written before a run starts to have a chance of dropping during the next run.<br/>
<br/>
Escape The Hell Inside						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dodgeman</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2840330/Dodgeman/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2840330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dodgeman is a satisfying physics-platformer, where players traverse procedurally generated courses while dodging various objects in order to reach the end. <br>
<br>
Traverse the endless courses of Dodgeman!<br>
<br>
This product is currently in early access.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloody Ink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2700240/Bloody_Ink/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/logo.png?t=1711115231"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Bloody Ink is a first-person psychological horror game that aims to instill anxiety, distress, and terror.</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/titolo_en_01.png?t=1711115231"><br/><strong>Luca </strong> is a man who has lost his job. He lives day by day trying to survive. When a new job finally promises to change his life, his nightmare begins. Having to take care of a man who is completely burned, Luca moves into the man's house where the terror becomes real.<br/><br/>While exploring the house, you will have the task of taking care of the burned man. Discover what caused the fire in which he lost his wife and how all of this is connected to Luca.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/titolo_en_02.png?t=1711115231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/titolo_en_03.png?t=1711115231"><br/>Collect items and clues that will help you understand the mystery surrounding the fire.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/001.png?t=1711115231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/titolo_en_04.png?t=1711115231"><br/>Darkness is your enemy. Stay in illuminated areas.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/002.png?t=1711115231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/titolo_en_05.png?t=1711115231"><br/>The Time Man is hunting you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/003.png?t=1711115231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/titolo_en_06.png?t=1711115231"><br/>Solve puzzles and guide Luca to the truth.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/004.png?t=1711115231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/titolo_en_07.png?t=1711115231"><br/>In Bloody Ink, the sounds you make influence the game. If you have a microphone, what you say and the sounds you make have an impact on the game.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/005.png?t=1711115231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/titolo_en_08.png?t=1711115231"><br/>Explore the house and the surrounding outer forest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/006.png?t=1711115231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700240/extras/titolo_en_09.png?t=1711115231"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Bloody Ink is designed to terrify and challenge you. Can you find all the hidden easter eggs?</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🔦 Collectible Items.<br/></li><li>🔦 Different game environments.<br/></li><li>🔦 Psychological mechanics: Fear, Voice Interaction, Madness.<br/></li><li>🔦 Set in the universe of Lost Alone Ultimate.<br/></li><li>🔦 Easter Eggs.<br/></li><li>🔦 Movie Quotes.<br/></li><li>🔦 Photorealistic environments.<br/></li><li>🔦 Puzzles.<br/></li><li>🔦 Story-related jumpscares and never randomly thrown in. You shouldn't be scared randomly: you should be in constant fear.<br/></li><li>🔦 The Time Man is coming...</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puzzle Adventure VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2794140/Puzzle_Adventure_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2794140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Immerse yourself in <i>Puzzle Adventure VR</i>.</strong>  (｡♥‿♥｡)</h2>First VR twist on the classic block-matching game! Wield a wand to crush colorful blocks, navigating through increasingly complex puzzles. Perfect for all ages, 'Puzzle Adventure VR' enhances the familiar gameplay with intuitive controls and interactive elements. The game's vibrant graphics and soothing soundtrack create a relaxing atmosphere, making it ideal for both fun and cognitive stimulation. Experience the blend of nostalgia and innovation in this engaging VR puzzle journey. <br/><br/>The game is still in it's early access.<br/>We will appreciate feedback - and rates :) You can make the game grow!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2794140/extras/gameplay_gif_cropped.gif?t=1711115106"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Explore the game and its challenging content</strong>  (╯’□’)╯︵ ┻━┻</h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li><strong>Beat 100 levels!</strong><br/> </li><li><strong>Explore different environments</strong><br/> </li><li><strong>Unlock new wands</strong><br/> </li><li><strong>Overcome engaging challenges</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2794140/extras/store_gif_cropped.gif?t=1711115106"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Join our community and be a part of the development!</strong> (*ゝω・)ﾉThanks!</h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F25VrYpD7" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2794140/extras/discord-button-616px.png?t=1711115106"/></a> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starfall Odyssey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2838520/Starfall_Odyssey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2838520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this action-packed space adventure, you'll take on the role of a brave spacefarer exploring the universe, uncovering secrets, and cleansing space of pirates. Navigate through stunning landscapes, master thrilling challenges, and engage in gripping space battles against hostile ships.<br>
<br>
Starfall Odyssey boasts a compelling storyline that will immerse you as you unravel the mysteries of the cosmos.<br>
<br>
Are you ready to embark on the adventure of a lifetime? Join the Starfall Odyssey and explore the unknown!<br>
<br>
Explore. Fight. Discover. Starfall Odyssey awaits you.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice Bridges</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2838420/Venice_Bridges/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2838420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Venice is under attack by malicious Plague Doctors and you have been chosen to come to its rescue.<br/>Plunge into the world of Venice Bridges, a 3D puzzle adventure game where the beauty of Venice meets hardship and destruction.<br/>Save Venice by luring the Plague Doctors and their squad to their demise, and solve puzzles to restore Venice to its glory.<h2 class="bb_tag">=====</h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore</h2>The many districts of Venice which have been scattered around the waters by the foul creatures - they await your visit to be liberated.<h2 class="bb_tag">Find</h2>The optimal approach to reclaim the scattered church bells and uncover the hidden secrets by solving puzzles embedded in the town districts themselves.<h2 class="bb_tag">Eliminate Or Be Eliminated</h2>Lure the Plague Doctors and their squad into traps and do not challenge them face to face.<h2 class="bb_tag">Strategise Or Let Your Pulse Rush</h2>Play the game strategically by thinking through the steps ahead or just dive into the action and let your pulse rush.<h2 class="bb_tag">Choose &amp; Combine</h2>Play the same district multiple times with different objectives and earn the combined outcome. Each objective requires you to choose a specific approach - play for time, play for score, play for minimal effort, play to find the hidden secret or play to collect and restore.<h2 class="bb_tag">What Is Your Legacy?</h2>There is a final showdown at the end of your adventure featuring the famous Rialto Bridge. Can you reach this far, outsmart the Plague Doctors and finally hoist the oldest of bridges and save Venice?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Holyburn Witches</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2645600/The_Holyburn_Witches/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In the once tranquil village of Holyburn, Maine, a series of horrific incidents left scars that still linger. Unexplained sounds and sightings haunt the desolate forests near this derelict town. Can you survive to unravel the mystery steeped in a history of ritualistic horrors?<br>
<br>
"The Holyburn Witches" is a pure survival-horror experience, featuring meticulously crafted panoramic photographs that capture the fear and solitude of being alone in a haunted forest. The thick atmosphere will crawl under your skin, and every nerve-wracking moment will leave you desperate for escape.<br>
<br>
Collect enough firewood during the day to build a bonfire at night. If it goes out, the witches come. Can you endure enough days and nights to survive the Holyburn Witches?						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike's Garden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2352420/Mikes_Garden/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2352420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Mike is in trouble! </strong>His garden is growing out of control and needs your help. Match species, use tools creatively and chain incredible combos to survive as long as you can!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2352420/extras/streak.gif?t=1711112486"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2352420/extras/tit_greenhouse.png?t=1711112486"><br/>Make your game unique! Earn seeds each game to unlock new species in your own private Greenhouse.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2352420/extras/spacer.png?t=1711112486"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2352420/extras/GIF_GREEN.gif?t=1711112486"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2352420/extras/tit_tools.png?t=1711112486"><br/>Unlock different common, or crazy, garden management tools to keep control of your board.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2352420/extras/spacer.png?t=1711112486"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2352420/extras/GIF_TOOLS.gif?t=1711112486"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2352420/extras/tit_fame.png?t=1711112486"><br/>The only way to win is to become the King of the Garden in the Garden of Fame. Beat your friends by mastering your strategy and never sharing your gardening tips and tricks.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2352420/extras/spacer.png?t=1711112486"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2352420/extras/GIF_FAME.gif?t=1711112486"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2352420/extras/tit_quests.png?t=1711112486"><br/>Learn by doing. Complete all micro-quests that teach you the mechanics and systems to unlock a unique plant.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2352420/extras/spacer.png?t=1711112486"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2352420/extras/GIF_QUESTS.gif?t=1711112486"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barold: Inferno</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2213430/Barold_Inferno/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2213430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><h2 class="bb_tag">ABOUT BAROLD: INFERNO</h2></strong><br/> <strong> - A Roguelike adventure.</strong><br/><i><br/>As Barold, wake up in hell and face off against formidable foes like Slimes, Dragons, Cerberus, Balrogs, Hydras and more. <br/>Progress through the circles of Inferno by upgrading your abilities, from passive auto shooters to intense sword fights - becoming a more formidable opponent with each circle.<br/><br/>But be cautious, as the demons and gods of hell will stop at nothing to entrap you in Inferno forever. Along the way, collect powerful elements that can combine into various items, each offering unique abilities, upgrades and attributes.<br/>Meet a diverse cast of characters, each with their own stories.</i><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>GAMEPLAY</strong></h2><strong>I </strong> Wake up in Inferno after your death in the mortal world.<br/><br/><strong>II </strong>Find Elements and combine them into powerful weapons, abilities and summons.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2213430/extras/description1.png?t=1711112404"><br/><br/><strong>III </strong>Explore the dungeons and find bosses.<br/><br/><strong>IV</strong> Defeat the bosses and collect their Elements and Coins.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2213430/extras/description2.png?t=1711112404"><br/><br/><strong>V</strong> Use the same Elements to upgrade your already existing abilities.<br/><br/><strong>VI </strong>Try to get to the Ninth Circle of Inferno.<br/><br/><strong>VII </strong>Use the Coins from the previous run to upgrade your next attempt!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2213430/extras/description3.png?t=1711112404"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>DISCORD SERVER</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2213430/extras/Discord.png?t=1711112404"><br/>Join our Discord Server to leave feedback and see the Behind the Scenes - <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FEePdZ2Mu9v" rel="noopener" target="_blank">discord.gg/EePdZ2Mu9v</a> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paws in the Maze</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/963950/Paws_in_the_Maze/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/963950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to "Paws in the Maze," a thrilling adventure where you take on the role of a big-hearted pitbull on a mission to rescue two lost puppies trapped in a vast, dark labyrinth. As the brave protagonist, you must rely on your keen senses and powerful bark to locate the wayward pups and guide them to safety.<br>
<br>
Embark on an epic journey through a maze unlike any other, stretching far and wide beyond the bounds of imagination. With twists and turns at every corner, this sprawling maze promises hours of exploration and excitement as you navigate its intricate passages.<br>
<br>
But fear not, for you're not alone in this quest! "Paws in the Maze" offers the option for split-screen gameplay, allowing you to team up with a friend, partner, or fellow dog lover for an even more enjoyable experience. Together, you'll tackle the challenges of the maze, share in the triumphs of discovery, and revel in the joy of rescuing the adorable puppies.<br>
<br>
Get ready to unleash your inner hero, embark on an unforgettable adventure, and experience the thrill of "Paws in the Maze" like never before!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy: The Soldier</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2870470/Troy_The_Soldier/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2870470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Game Description: </strong><br/><br/><i>Play as the young enlisted Michael as he goes through odd location to odd location looking for why he's stuck in a 40 year time loop. Meet odd fellows, weird looking Oddities, people doing their low entry jobs, and talking piles of ash as you embark on your very odd quest. </i><br/><br/><u>Purchase skills and give them to the RIGHT party members</u><br/><br/><u>Enjoy the 75+ theme soundtrack with new songs for each room (<i>almost</i>)</u><br/><br/><u>Purchase items to upgrade health and other stats</u><br/><br/><u>Look through the stylistic monochromatic game based around limited color pallet handheld games</u><br/><br/><u>Equip different types of gear to each of your party members (anyone can equip any armor, except a few)</u><br/><br/><u>Go through seven different areas (<i>or eight if you can find it</i>) all with their own different colors, unique enemies, unique bosses, and tracks</u><br/><br/><u>And be sure to be sparing of your items, you never know when you might need them.</u><br/><br/>The game's around four hours or more, give or take with the main file size coming from all the music (<u>All of which are open to listen to in the files, so be weary of spoilers.</u>)<br/><br/>RPG MAKER VX ACE's Run Time Package (RTP) is needed to play this game.<br/><br/>(Thank you Galv Scripts for creating the scripts used for this game, and thank you to yanfly as well.)						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miss Neko: Pirates</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2695270/Miss_Neko_Pirates/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2695270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In "Miss Neko: Pirates," players take on the role of the captain of the "Lucky Coin," overseeing the protagonist's adventures on a pirate-infested island from a top-down perspective. Strengthen your character to survive in this hostile world.<br/><br/>Thrown into the sea by a mutinous crew, the captain of the "Lucky Coin" was left for dead.Yet, some mysterious force allows you to survive from death, surviving the depths as the crew believes they've killed their captain. Stripped of everything, can you seek revenge with formidable combat skills, reclaim your pirate ship, seize the island's treasures, and punish the mutineering crew?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2695270/extras/jadeshop-min.gif?t=1711106345"><br/><br/>Game Features:<br/><br/>Pirate-themed storyline and adventure<br/>Diverse and characterful beast-girl crew members<br/>Explore rich RPG maps<br/>Engage in challenging top-down battles and equipment growth<br/>Own your pirate ship, collect crew members to accompany you on board						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. What &amp; Detective Son</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2855580/Dr_What__Detective_Son/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an epic adventure with Dr. What and Detective Son in this captivating logic game available on Steam! Dive into a world where each level presents a unique challenge, requiring you to flex your mental muscles and employ cunning strategies to unravel mysteries and solve puzzles.<br>
<br>
With a whopping 100 mind-bending puzzles awaiting your expertise, the journey promises hours of immersive gameplay. Join forces with the ingenious Dr. What and his intrepid sidekick Detective Son as you navigate through a labyrinth of enigmas and conundrums. From deciphering cryptic codes to unraveling perplexing riddles, each puzzle offers a fresh test of your deductive reasoning and problem-solving prowess.<br>
<br>
This game is a standalone adaptation of an online browser-based game called "Mysterious Pron," where you had to guess the URL of the next level. Hints were hidden in various places—sometimes beyond the game itself. In this game, you have to do exactly the same: solve the case using various hints and type the solution to proceed to the next case. You will have to type in your guess to find out if you solved the case or maybe if you have found hint(s).<br>
If you struggle too much, feel free to seek hints in the dedicated Discord channel ;)						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
