<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Nightingale - Digital Art Book</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2834900/Nightingale__Digital_Art_Book/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2834900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Step into the magical universe of Nightingale with the "Art of Nightingale" digital book, a captivating exploration of the game's stunning worlds. This beautifully illustrated volume offers fans and art enthusiasts alike a behind-the-scenes look at the creation of Nightingale's enchanting environments, mysterious creatures, and intricate designs.<br>
<br>
Through pages filled with exquisite artwork and insightful commentary from the creators, readers will discover the inspiration behind the game's unique Victorian gaslamp fantasy aesthetic. The Nightingale digital art book delves deep into the creative process, from initial sketches to final renditions, showcasing the dedication and artistry that bring the Fae Realms to life. Experience the wonder, danger, and beauty of Nightingale in a whole new way.<br>
<br>
English language.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2379780/Balatro/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Balatro is a poker-inspired roguelike deck builder all about creating powerful synergies and winning big.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Endless_Possibility.gif?t=1708448566"><br/><br/>Combine valid poker hands with unique Joker cards in order to create varied synergies and builds. Earn enough chips to beat devious blinds, all while uncovering hidden bonus hands and decks as you progress. You’re going to need every edge you can get in order to reach the boss blind, beat the final ante and secure victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Jokers_Clean_Thin.gif?t=1708448566"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The definitive poker roguelike experience.<br/></li><li>Endless possibilities - every pick-up, discard and joker can dramatically alter the course of your run.<br/></li><li>In-depth campaign mode complete with 8 difficulties, as well as challenge, daily and seeded runs. </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Break_The_Game.gif?t=1708448566"><br/><br/>Deftly deploy an array of potent tools: different Decks, Jokers, Tarot cards, Planet cards, Spectral cards, and Vouchers. Use these versatile instruments to ignite a combo frenzy and turbocharge your poker hands, crafting electrifying, adrenaline-fueled synergies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro_5_Aces_GIF__HQ_.gif?t=1708448566"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 Jokers, each with their own unique abilities<br/></li><li>15 Decks with distinct modifiers to choose from for each run<br/></li><li>5 potential variants of each Joker which add further abilities<br/></li><li>22 Tarot cards variants that can enhance your regular playing cards<br/></li><li>11 Planet cards that help level up your possible poker hands<br/></li><li>32 Voucher cards to help provide permanent buffs for your current run</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Find_Your_Flow.gif?t=1708448566"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in Balatro’s distinctive psychedelic world. Let the synthwave soundtrack wash over you -  wind down, escape the daily grind and prepare to enter the ultimate roguelike flow state.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improve your collection and discover new cards and secrets with every single run.<br/></li><li>Make use of the in-depth stats screen to study your best hands, most used Jokers, and more!<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the CRT fuzz and enjoy detailed, hand-crafted pixel art.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Spectral_Pack.gif?t=1708448566"><br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F5mH3dNhjx2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro-join_the_discord.png?t=1708448566"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fossilfuel 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2299660/Fossilfuel_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2299660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2299660/extras/wishlist_now.gif?t=1708443832"><br/><strong>Dinosaur-themed survival horror set in a flooded underground base. </strong><br/><br/><strong>Wishlist today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>In this thrilling first-person horror shooter, you will play Jack Allen, as he investigates the mysterious Alaskan Sierra Research Facility, now flooded with water, which has been overrun by deadly dinosaurs. You will have to put your skills to the test as you embark on a heart-pumping, 12-hour journey through flooded tunnels, puzzle-filled bunkers, and dark corners filled with jump scares. The base has a dynamic sandbox layout where players can revisit areas, get upgrades to their weapons, and clear sections to create safe zones by draining water in the flooded sections. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2299660/extras/RaptorHeadShot.gif?t=1708443832"><br/><br/>Use a massive arsenal of deadly weapons to bring the pain! Blast dinos apart in glorious gory detail all powered by Unreal Engine 5. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2299660/extras/AnglerFish.gif?t=1708443832"><br/><br/>Much of the game takes place in flooded hallways and rooms. You will have to put on scuba gear and face off against monsters of the deep. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2299660/extras/lock.gif?t=1708443832"><br/><br/><i>Fossilfuel 2</i> is filled with many puzzles to keep you on your feet. Explore the vast nonlinear base of the flooded Sierra Research Facility and face off against not only Dinosaurs but the environment as well.<h2 class="bb_tag">Overview</h2><br/><i>Fossilfuel 2</i> is the highly-anticipated sequel to the indie game <i>Fossilfuel</i>, and it promises to deliver an experience like no other. With improved Unreal Engine 5 graphics, advanced AI, and a range of new weapons, you will have to use all your ingenuity and skill to survive in this Dino-infested facility.<h2 class="bb_tag">Rich Lore</h2>The Sierra Research Facility in Alaska was once a beacon of cutting-edge research and development, but the dinosaurs in the base escaped, and the base has been cut off from the mainland. Much of the base has been flooded with seawater. Jack Allen is part of an expedition sent out to investigate the Sierra disaster. But when their boat gets attacked by a Megalodon, the crew becomes shipwrecked on the shores of Sierra and must find a way to escape. <br/><br/>As a member of this team, you will delve into the dark secrets of the facility and uncover the truth behind the Dino outbreak. With a gripping narrative and heart-pumping action, <i>Fossilfuel 2</i> will keep you on the edge of your seat from start to finish. The game has a heavy focus on underwater horror and has a massive cast of dinosaurs including Utahraptor and Spinosaurus.<h2 class="bb_tag">Nonlinear Replay Value:</h2>With a wide range of weapons and challenging AI, each encounter with the Dinosaurs will be unique. In <i>Fossilfuel 2</i>, no two playthroughs are the same. The game features <strong>multiple endings</strong> and <strong>player choices</strong> that change the course of the game. And with 12 hours of intense horror action, you will want to come back and play again and again to experience all the thrills this game has to offer. Get ready for a pulse-pounding adventure and uncover the truth at the Sierra Research Facility.<h2 class="bb_tag">Sandbox Mode:</h2>A Garrys mod-like sandbox can be unlocked for players to brandish their creativity. Spawn NPCs and watch them fight, or make a house with the block spawner, the possibilities are endless.<br/><br/><strong>ADD TO YOUR WISHLIST TODAY AND DON'T MISS OUT!</strong><br/><br/>You are encouraged to join the discord or leave comments in the community forum. Your feedback will be taken into consideration!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Stars: The Ur-Quan Masters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2645580/Free_Stars_The_UrQuan_Masters/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">You are the captain</h2><i>Free Stars: The Ur-Quan Masters</i>® is a classic space game that captures the charm of retro science-fiction, space combat, and high adventure. Your story begins as the captain of the last human starship, with Earth trapped under a hostile forcefield. You are the last hope for humanity in a fight for control of the galaxy, as you explore thousands of unknown worlds and get dozens of quirky aliens to help.<h2 class="bb_tag">Meet fascinating alien characters</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_alien_dialog_optimized-loop-count.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>​The galaxy is thriving with alien species, each with unique mysteries and motives. Meet an eclectic cast of characters, brought to life with full English voiceover. Ask sharp questions, make new friends, and exchange colorful insults.<h2 class="bb_tag">Adventure through HyperSpace</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_explore_hyperspace.gif_scaled-loop-count.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>Discover a vibrant galaxy filled with wonder, terror, and absurdity. Explore thousands of uncharted worlds across hundreds of stars, and gather important resources and technology.<h2 class="bb_tag">Battle your rivals in starship combat</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_super_melee_scaled-loop-count.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>Build your fleet and battle enemy starships, facing off against friends or the computer-controlled AI. Play action-packed Super Melee as its own mode, or as part of the single-player adventure – or choose automated combat to stay focused on the story.<h2 class="bb_tag">Experience a sci-fi classic – for free!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_precursors_intro.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>As a celebrated piece of gaming history, <i>Free Stars: The Ur-Quan Masters</i>® has also received wide acclaim for its story, characters, and setting. It was created as a love letter to classic science fiction like Douglas Adams, David Brin, and Jack Vance. In turn, its setting inspired a new wave of game creators, including the visionaries behind <i>Mass Effect</i>, <i>No Man’s Sky</i>, <i>Subnautica</i>, <i>Starfield</i>, <i>Fallout</i>, and <i>Stellaris</i> – to name just a few.<br/><br/>In 2002, the game was released under an open source license thanks to the generosity of Paul Reiche and Fred Ford. It continues to be available to play as a free download, for game historians and fans to enjoy.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Experience an open-world adventure, venturing through space to defeat the invading Ur-Quan and its hierarchy of battle thralls.<br/></li><li>Travel through extra-dimensional HyperSpace and discover nearly 500 unknown star systems filled with alien worlds.<br/></li><li>Fight enemies in fast-paced space battles with 25 different starships, each with its own unique attacks and powers.<br/></li><li>Befriend, threaten, or fight a diverse cast of aliens with unique personalities, from scary, to funny, to just plain weird.<br/></li><li>Explore thousands of planets, collecting resources and technology to upgrade your flagship and grow your fleet.<br/></li><li>Play standalone Super Melee to practice space combat against AI opponents or to duel against a friend.<br/></li><li>Mod and tinker with freely available, open-source code and content.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIDUS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2372170/NIDUS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2372170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>NIDUS is a CHALLENGING Split-Stick Arcade Experience</strong></h2>Designed for those who enjoy mastery of stimulating and highly demanding gameplay. Control a Symbiotic Flower and Wasp in Unison, as you struggle to survive a surreal and threatening ecosystem. Immerse yourself in full throttle simulation with <strong>Single Player</strong>, or try to survive together with a friend in hectic <strong>Local Co-Op</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2372170/extras/gigantControl.gif?t=1708455854"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2372170/extras/coOp.gif?t=1708455854"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>KEY FEATURES</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Single Player or Co-Op</li><li>No-Hit score multiplier</li><li>Evolve flower for defense, wasp for attack</li><li>Worlds upgrade as you choose your path </li><li>Nightmarish bosses with exalted forms</li><li>Unlockable difficulties</li><li>20 - 30 minute runs</li><li>Competitive leaderboard</li><li>Surreal hand animated visuals</li><li>Gamepad or Mouse/Keyboard supported</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2372170/extras/playmode_v2.png?t=1708455854"><br/><br/><strong>PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING: NIDUS CONTAINS INTENSE HAND ANIMATED VISUALS THAT FEATURE EXPLOSIVE MOVEMENTS, CRAWLING PATTERNS, AND FLASHING COLORS</strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please, Touch The Artwork 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2600140/Please_Touch_The_Artwork_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Disclaimer:</strong><i> This is a short game made in</i> <strong>6 months</strong><i>. It's</i> <strong>100% FREE</strong><i>(no ads, no dlc's), made by a </i><strong>solo dev</strong><i> in honour of James Ensor’s 75 year remembrance.</i> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/extras/Steam3DRoomGIF_Wide.gif?t=1708440801"><br/><br/>Touch the artwork and help a lost skeleton artist find its way home in a surreal, hand-painted universe. <br/><br/>Collect hidden objects for its quirky inhabitants, solve casual puzzles, and restore cracks in the fabric of the paintings. <br/><br/>This slow paced relaxing adventure was carefully crafted from works by James Ensor, a Belgian pioneer in the world of Modern Art.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Hidden object adventure<br/></li><li>5 unique worlds<br/></li><li>Hints when stuck<br/></li><li>Casual point &amp; click gameplay<br/></li><li>Zoom-in for extra details<br/></li><li>Real hand-painted art<br/></li><li>Atmospheric relaxing sound<br/></li><li>Silly and quirky<br/></li><li>Slow-paced &amp; relaxing<br/></li><li>Fit for ages 12-99</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Small Mazes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2570630/20_Small_Mazes/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2570630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a puzzle game with twenty small mazes. If you solve the mazes, you beat the game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>It's about 1-2 hours long, maybe.<br/></li><li>You need a keyboard and mouse to play it. One person played through the whole game on the Steam Deck, but I tried it and think it's better on PC.<br/></li><li> A few puzzles require knowledge of English. No puzzle requires sound or audio to solve it. No puzzle requires being able to recognize different colors.</li></ul> <br/>I hope you enjoy it. <br/> 						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caribbean Legend</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2230980/Caribbean_Legend/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i><strong>Based on Sea Dogs series and inspired by Sid Meier's Pirates!</strong></i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/История_EN.gif?t=1708341012"><br/><br/>Welcome to the Caribbean in 1654 AD, a place teeming with opportunities and mysteries. Assume the role of Charles de Maure, a young French noble who embarked on a journey to the New World to assist his brother. What initially appeared to be a simple family matter quickly evolves into a lifelong adventure.<br/>Immerse yourself in the tale of a noble brat who rises to become the most influential figure in the Caribbean. <strong>Riches, titles, power, and romance – the ultimate booty awaits, and it's up to you to seize it all.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/steamchar.jpg?t=1708341012"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Embark on a 200-hour-long journey.<br/></li><li>Undertake hundreds of quests.<br/></li><li>Freeplay, rush through the story, or combine both - you're the Captain, and your ship will sail where you command.<br/></li><li>Experience a historical narrative with a touch of mystique.<br/></li><li>Explore romantic interests and companions.<br/></li><li>Choose from various career options, from general-governor to pirate baron.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/Мир_EN.gif?t=1708341012"><br/><br/>The Caribbean Sea – a realm of dozens of islands and cities, a grand archipelago shrouded in mystery and secrets. From the summits of Indian pyramids to the ocean depths, unique rewards, quests, and curiosities await. <strong>This open world is your sandbox, you are free to explore it and shape your legend as you see fit. </strong>Your decisions determine where to go, what to do, and who to take with you. Subdue the New World or it will destroy you!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Discover dozens of islands and settlements.<br/></li><li>Build your very own colony.<br/></li><li>Explore caves, pyramids, jungles, Indian tribes, and lost cities.<br/></li><li>Visit taverns, brothels, shipyards, churches, forts, and many other points of interest.<br/></li><li>Engage in treasure hunting and gambling.<br/></li><li>Experience dynamic weather and the serene turquoise sea.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/Море_EN.gif?t=1708341012"><br/><br/><strong>Owning a warship is a privilege, a symbol of status and luxury. </strong>You are among the very few who can afford such grandeur. Begin your journey with a simple sloop and work your way up to commanding a ship of the line or even a fleet of these formidable vessels, ready to plunder cities at your whim. No one will stand in your way. Tired from leading massive armadas and the responsibility? Take command of a fast Frigate or Corvette and just free roam the Caribbean. In moments of tranquility at sea, relish the stunning views, embrace the sense of exploration, or navigate in the heart of a storm.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/valciria3_копия.png?t=1708341012"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Command dozens of ships representing the glory of the Age of Sail.<br/></li><li>Customize, paint, upgrade, and repair your vessel.<br/></li><li>Engage in unforgiving yet enjoyable naval combat.<br/></li><li>Experience intense boarding action, from the upper deck to the captain's cabin.<br/></li><li>Collect unique vessels to rule the seas.<br/></li><li>Manage booty distribution, morale, and the threat of mutinies.<br/></li><li>Assemble a formidable team of officers.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/боевка_EN.gif?t=1708341012"><br/><br/>Captains are most vulnerable when they set foot on land. Surviving naval combat can be challenging, but at least you won't die alone – your crew will stand with you till the very end. Land battles are different: dishonest, ruthless and risky for you and those who you hold dear. <strong>Bring your companions with you, poison your weapons, study the terrain, craft deadly items, and confront thugs, soldiers, pirates, and rivals head-on.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/face_201_копия.png?t=1708341012"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tailor your character's build – become a heavy swordsman, a nimble rogue, a master sharpshooter, or a silver-tongued diplomat.<br/></li><li>Equip yourself and your companions with a wide array of swords, axes, rapiers, armor, muskets, and pistols.<br/></li><li>Craft amulets, ammo, potions, and always be prepared for battle.<br/></li><li>Seek out challenges – the more you fight, the stronger both you and your character become.<br/></li><li>Command military operations from raiding to sieges.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708005696"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708005696"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smalland: Survive the Wilds</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/768200/Smalland_Survive_the_Wilds/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>"Before the time of the giants, we lived freely under the Sun and Moon. Centuries have passed, but those stories of the surface world have been passed down through the generations. Now the giants are gone, and you, Vanguard, must venture out into the wilds once more, on an urgent mission. Be brave, and do not falter…"</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/TreeLookingup.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the vast “Land of the Small" </h2>Traverse lake sized puddles, scale skyscraper sized trees, scramble through cavernous cracks in roads, as you experience a huge open world from a new perspective. Explore dense forests, hazardous swamps and strange ruins left over from the time before. Uncover lore and knowledge from hidden NPCs scattered throughout the world and learn to survive in this vast wilderness. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Land_of_Small.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Tame and ride creatures</h2>Uncover recipes that will let you tame and ride an array of critters. Leap huge distances on the back of a Grasshopper, zoom around on a Damselfly, scurry from place-to-place on a Spider. This world and its inhabitants are yours to conquer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Mounts.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive together</h2>Play alongside friends with support for up to 10 players in multiplayer. Explore together, fight together, build together and survive the wilds as a team.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Together.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build encampments on the ground or amongst the trees</h2>Scavenge or refine resources to build your encampment with multiple material tiers, from leaves and twigs to sturdy stone. Pick your favourite spot in the world and build, or scale vast trees and claim your own settlement at the top.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Housing.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Craft powerful armour sets</h2>Collect powerful armours that provide you with resistances and abilities and mix them up to personalise your appearance. Glide through the skies in winged armour, swing from tree to tree with the grappling hook and many more. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Armors.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive the Wilds</h2>Most of the creatures you encounter will see you as lower on the food chain – Ants, Cockroaches, Beetles, Wasps, and Spiders all view you as a potential meal. Weather conditions and seasons are in constant flux so if you want to survive for another day, preparation is key.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Survive_the_Wilds.gif?t=1708077077"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider I-III Remastered Starring Lara Croft</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2478970/Tomb_Raider_IIII_Remastered_Starring_Lara_Croft/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2478970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover Lara Croft’s Original Adventures, Lovingly Restored</h2> <br/>Play the Original Three Tomb Raider Adventures: For the first time ever, play the complete experience with all expansions and secret levels on modern platforms in this definitive collection.<h2 class="bb_tag">Included Game Titles</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tomb Raider I + Unfinished Business<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider II + Golden Mask<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider III + The Lost Artifact</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><strong>Solve Ancient Mysteries</strong>: Uncover treasures of the ancient world by solving puzzles and unraveling mysteries lost to the ravages of time.<br/><br/><strong>Globe-trotting Adventure</strong>: Follow Lara Croft around the world and face off against deadly foes and dangerous myths.<br/><br/><strong>Lovingly Restored</strong>: Experience the classics boasting upgraded graphics, with the option to switch to the original polygon look at any time.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islands of Insight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2071500/Islands_of_Insight/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Islands of Insight: a sublime shared-world puzzle game set in a fantasy realm of ancient wonders and natural beauty. Brimming with mysterious puzzles to solve, secrets to uncover, and vibrant landscapes to explore, this peaceful world of floating islands is the perfect place to unwind. Embark on a puzzle adventure of your choice, all at your own pace.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_1-Title-Journey_EN.png?t=1708109878">‎‎‏‏‎<br/>Play as a Seeker on a peaceful journey rich in exploration and puzzle-solving. Embark on the Path of Discovery and let your curiosity guide you through a breathtaking open world where the answer is always in sight.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_Gifs_Journey_HD.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_2-Title-Puzzles_EN.png?t=1708109878"><br/>Seek out and solve an unparalleled collection of over 10,000 puzzles divided across 24 puzzle types. Every corner of the world holds a new eureka moment for you to discover. From enigmas of perspective to logic problems, environmental challenges and more, the puzzles you’ll encounter vary in difficulty and have been crafted by some of the best minds in puzzle design to create an engaging experience for both newcomers and seasoned puzzle fans.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_Gifs_Puzzles_HD.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_3-Title-Exploration_EN.png?t=1708109878"><br/>Freely explore the main island’s expansive open world where most of the puzzles and secrets are found. Wander the vibrant landscapes and architecture of its 5 distinct biomes or spread your wings to glide above them. Navigate the environment’s verticality and take your game to new heights. Unlock puzzle types and new areas in the campaign by completing 20+ Enclaves housing curated puzzle challenges. Go where you want. Solve what you want. The only path here is the one you make.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/3.IOI_Steam_Gif_Exploration___Discovery_2.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_5-Title-Experience_EN.png?t=1708109878"><br/>Customize your character. Increase your puzzle masteries to level them up while earning sparks to unlock new abilities. Complete daily quests. Seamlessly interact with other players in our shared world to gain or offer a bit of guidance, or choose to figure things out entirely on your own. With puzzles that refresh over time, a new discovery awaits with every visit to the islands.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/4.IOI_Steam_Gif_An_Evergreen_Experience_2.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/>Age restrictions may apply to access this game.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2436570/DRAGON_QUEST_BUILDERS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/Toybox_Announce_Build.gif?t=1707862917"><br/>The first title in the BUILDERS series, DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS, is bringing its handy crafting features to Steam!<br/>Gather, craft and build to defeat defeat the evil Dragonlord and restore Alefgard to it's former glory!<br/>In a world made out of blocks, everything that you see can be materials used to create! Farm ingredients, craft various items and build your base to unite the people roaming the ruins. From buildings to entire towns, you have the freedom to make your village your very own.<h2 class="bb_tag">■ Story</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/Toybox_Announce_Lightning.gif?t=1707862917"><br/>BUILDERS is set in the realm of Alefgard, the setting for the first ever DRAGON QUEST game.<br/>The world of Alefgard has been plunged into darkness, its light stolen by the evil Dragonlord, and this story begins with the appearance of a young hero with a mysterious ability to build things... And so the stage is set for an epic tale in which the dark world of Alefgard is returned to life with the power of creation!<h2 class="bb_tag">■ The first DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS title, helpful crafting features include:</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/intextbanner_3.png?t=1707862917"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Place blocks remotely, or destroy blocks with ease, with just a single click of the mouse!<br/></li><li> Now Includes a helpful Undo feature, which allows you to put things back to how they were before!<br/></li><li> Now Featuring Big Bash, a useful feature introduced in DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS 2 that allows you to break all objects in a particular area in one go!<br/></li><li> Terra Incognita, BUILDERS’ free build stage, the stackable block height is doubled!<br/></li><li> Includes fun side content, like collecting figurines of NPCs and monsters, or gathering pixels and exchanging them for a variety of handy items!<br/></li><li> Use Build Cards to share buildings with other players and bring their buildings to life on your island!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">■ Includes all DLC from previous versions of DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/intextbanner_4.png?t=1707862917"><br/>The Steam version of DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS includes all of the DLC from past versions including the free build mode, Terra Incognita: Magic Carpet, Boss Monster Model Set, Astronomy Set and Pixel Ring.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/Toybox_Announce_Stack.gif?t=1707862917"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Will:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802530/Space_WillPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 10 in the prologue, 59 in the official version<br/>Galaxy: 2 in the prologue, 6 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><strong>Sixty basic cores, hundreds of base station equipment, and thousands of chips, you can freely cooperate and shoot through the dual-angle joystick operation in a survival Roguelike game! Explore the sci-fi space and build your strongest battleship!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Step 1: Choose a "core" as your basic role<br/>Step 2: Choose a "crew" as your initial weapon<br/>Step 3: Select a galaxy for exploration</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game will continuously collect new "units" or "chips" during the exploration process<br/>Using "crew" can expand weapons and enhance combat effectiveness for your warship<br/>Using "chips" can enhance various abilities of your warship</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Each "core" or "unit" has a maximum of 4 interfaces. When the interfaces are used up, you cannot equip more parts, but you can also infinitely increase the number of your interfaces!<br/>Each "crew" can use the right mouse button to rotate and adjust the optimal angle for combat</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game features dual joystick shooting, with the keyboard moving and the mouse aiming at the enemy. Of course, there are many weapons that can automatically attack or be placed in the scene as traps for use~</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_TITLE_FULLSCREEN.gif?t=1708080818"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_1.png?t=1708080818"><br/> <br/>In New Eden, 1695, communities of settlers are plagued by a dreadful curse. As Banishers, step into their lives, investigate the source of evil, unravel chilling mysteries, explore diverse landscapes, and interact with unforgettable characters whose fate lies in your hands.<br/><br/>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden is an all-new title crafted by renowned studio DON'T NOD, known for their acclaimed titles such as Life is Strange and Vampyr. Immerse yourself in an intimate narrative Action-RPG, taking you on an exhilarating journey between life, death, love and sacrifices.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_2.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_FANTASY.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Play as a couple of Banishers, Red and Antea, experienced spirit hunters entrusted with the daunting task of dispelling a malevolent curse through powerful rituals. Protect the living from the threat of lingering ghosts and specters, and become a beacon of hope in a world consumed by darkness.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_3.png?t=1708080818"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_NARATION_LOVE.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Experience a heart-wrenching love story between Antea Duarte and Red mac Raith. When Antea is killed and turned into a spirit, you find yourself facing a choice. Will you uphold your oath and ascend her soul, or will you sacrifice the living in the hope of bringing her back? Your decisions will shape the fate of New Eden’s inhabitants - may they be living or dead, and determine the end of your journey.<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>BLAME</strong> the living and sacrifice their lives, holding them responsible for their actions<br/></li><li><strong>BANISH</strong> souls of the departed, condemning them to eternal suffering<br/></li><li><strong>ASCEND</strong> souls, liberating them from eternal sorrow and granting them serenity</li></ul><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_4.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_COMBAT.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Banishers are specialized in combat against undead creatures, such as specters or ghosts. Combine Red's physical arsenal with Antea's supernatural powers in a dynamic combat system. Find your own style by mixing weapon attacks and spiritual abilities. Powerful synergies will lead you to defeat New Eden’s most dangerous enemies and bosses.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_6.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_SKILL.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Unleash the full power of the Banishers by unlocking new gear and supernatural abilities. By exploring New Eden, you will find ancient artifacts, trinkets and valuable resources to enhance your equipment in preparation of future fights. In addition to your arsenal, progress in Antea’s skill trees to upgrade her devastating spectral powers and unseal new combos.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_5.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_EXPLORATION.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Investigate haunting cases in a mystical world full of dark secrets. Discover New Eden, a North America settlement marked by terrible stories and secrets of its tormented inhabitants. Understanding each resident’s motivations will be essential to guide your decisions throughout the game.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_7.png?t=1708080818"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Ninja Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_9" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🥋🐾 WELCOME TO 100 NINJA CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🗡️</h2>🗡️Join the cutest adventure in the Ninja world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of ninja themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game.<br/>😊Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x200.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Ninja Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Extra.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816000/100_Ninja_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815980/100_Ninja_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Artbook.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x1.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_10" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_11" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III - BlackCell (Season 2)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731840/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III__BlackCell_Season_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Get Call of Duty® Points* and in-game content for Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III and Call of Duty®: Warzone™.<br>
<br>
Offering includes:<br>
<br/>
- Battle Pass for Season 2<br/>
- 20 Battle Token Tier Skips<br/>
<br/>
Exclusive BlackCell Sector on the Battle Map:<br/>
<br/>
- 1100 Call of Duty® Points<br/>
- BlackCell Operator<br/>
- Assault Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Battle Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Finishing Move<br/>
<br/>
- BlackCell Bonus Topper with 11 additional reactive Operator skin alternatives and 6 Weapon Blueprints with Tracers.<br/>
<br/>
Activision may update, replace, or remove this in-game content at any time.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1708019001"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal Richards (formerly of Echos)</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1708019001"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about the future of Sheepy, limited edition merch and more.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXIT KUN</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781370/EXIT_KUN/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a game of finding differences and observing. Our game challenges players to carefully observe and spot the distinctions that lead them to the elusive "Exit KUN."<br>
<br>
Game Overview:<br>
<br>
You find yourself trapped in an enigmatic underground labyrinth, and your only goal is to reach "Exit KUN." The journey demands keen observation of your surroundings. Every detail matters, and anomalies could be your key to progress.<br>
<br>
How to Play:<br>
<br/>
Observe Carefully: Scrutinize your surroundings to uncover anomalies that may guide your way or pose a threat.<br/>
Turn Back if Needed: If anomalies are detected, swift decision-making is crucial. Turn back immediately to avoid unforeseen consequences.<br/>
Forward Momentum: Should your observation reveal no anomalies, press forward. <br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Developer Notes:<br/>
This game is inspired by Exit 8. You are free to create, upload, and monetize videos and any other content featuring Game on platforms such as YouTube, Twitch, and other video-sharing websites. The characters, places, and elements involved in the game are fictitious. Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, or events is purely coincidental.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/315210/Suicide_Squad_Kill_the_Justice_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Rocksteady Studios, the creators of the Batman: Arkham series, Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is a genre-defying third-person action shooter where the ultimate band of misfits must do the impossible to save the world: Kill the Justice League.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/SSKTJL_Intro.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Join the newly “recruited” members of Amanda Waller’s infamous Task Force X (aka the Suicide Squad), Harley Quinn, Deadshot, Captain Boomerang and King Shark, as they set out on an impossible mission to Kill the Justice League. Drop into an expansive and dynamic open-world Metropolis ravaged by Brainiac’s invasion and terrorized by the heroes who once protected it. <br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/Traversal_2.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Each Squad member brings their own traversal mechanics to help them navigate a sprawling and battle-torn Metropolis, combining free-roaming exploration and combat verticality for an unforgettable experience. Players are free to experiment with a variety of different play styles to unleash maximum damage on their enemies. Whether in single player or online with up to three of your friends, players can take on this suicide mission their own way.<br/><br/>Post-launch, players can expect a continuously evolving Metropolis with free new playable villains, environments, weapons, in-game events, and more, all included with purchase of the base game.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788630/Nothing_Together/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play together. Maybe.<br/><br/>Just do Nothing as the timer goes up and climb the leaderboards. If you do Something, you lose.<br/><br/>Play in <strong>Together </strong>mode, where up to 20 players unite to do Nothing, or compete with other players in <strong>Battle Royale</strong> to find out who's the best at doing Nothing!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161700/Persona_3_Reload/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a transfer student thrust into an unexpected fate when entering the hour "hidden" between one day and the next. Awaken an incredible power and chase the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fight for your friends, and leave a mark on their memories forever. <br/><br/>Persona 3 Reload is a captivating reimagining of the genre-defining RPG, reborn for the modern era.<br/><br/>Key Features: <br/>- Experience the pivotal game of the Persona series faithfully remade with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, and signature stylish UI. <br/><br/>-Fully immerse yourself in an emotional, gripping journey with new scenes, character interactions, and additional voiceover.<br/><br/>- Choose how to meaningfully spend each day through various activities, from exploring the Port Island to forging genuine bonds with beloved characters.<br/><br/>- Build and command your optimal team to take down otherworldly Shadows and climb closer to the truth.<br/><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Deluxe Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook: Filled with 64 pages of character art, concept art, backgrounds and other illustrations from the game!<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack: Listen to newly arranged tracks from the original Persona 3 plus all-new tracks from Persona 3 Reload, presented by the Atlus sound team for a total of 60 new songs.</li></ul><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Premium Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack<br/></li><li>Persona 3 Reload DLC Pack:  P5R Phantom Thieves Costume Set, P5R Shujin Academy Costume Set, P5R Persona Set 1, P5R Persona Set 2 , P5R BGM Set, P4G Yasogami High Costume Set, P4G Persona Set</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1131620/Dominion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Expand a small kingdom to a mighty Dominion!  <br/><br/>Play the Spiel des Jahres winning boardgame beloved by millions around the world. This is the officially licensed implementation.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Reigning.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Discover the game that defined a genre, Dominion was first to popularize deck-building and remains a staple of tabletop. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/GrowYourKingdom.png?t=1707010484">Collect as many Victory Points as you can by building a powerful deck. Your deck starts out a small sad set of Estates and Coppers, but you hope that by the end of the game it will be brimming with Gold, Provinces, and the inhabitants and structures of your kingdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/BuildEngine.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Choose wisely among the 10 cards available in the tableau to create the strongest combos to dominate your opponent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CollectAllExpansions.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Make your games more exciting with additional cards and rules from up to 15 expansions including the recent Plunder expansion! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/NearInfiniteVariety.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Over one hundred thirty-two septillion possible Kingdom combinations, 500+ cards, 15 and counting expansions, and ongoing promo packs make Dominion one of the most extensive and replayable boardgames in the hobby. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CompeteComputer.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Sharpen your skills with solitaire style solo play against a robust AI, with four levels of difficulty. Our innovative AI learns through self-play. Earn Achievements and win in Recommended Sets against each AI level. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/PlayWithFriends.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Join up to 6 players online through your device or pass and play among your friends. Play ranked or unranked matchmaking, with realtime and asynchronous modes. Set up a private table for a family game, challenge a stranger in the lobby, or invite a friend!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Daily.png?t=1707010484"><br/>A daily ritual to relax with over a cup of coffee. Try the Daily Dominion, a free puzzle level available to players around the world. Practice your strategy to keep up a winning streak and climb the leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CrossPlatform.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Play from any supported device, whenever you want, after verifying your email in-game. Join games with opponents on platforms other than your own to enjoy the largest possible multiplayer pool and speedy matchmaking. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/JoinCommunity.png?t=1707010484"><br/>With an active Discord and online community, make new friends or challenge new people to a game. Export and share kingdoms and game summaries to compare strategies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/FreeToPlay.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Download the game that started it all for free! The base set of Dominion is available at no charge. Try the rotation of expansion cards in the Daily at no cost once per day. Jump into a lobby game with expansions enabled to try before you buy. Only the host needs to own the expansions.    <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Intro.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Learn the ropes in this easy to pick-up, hard to master title. Play one of the most highly regarded strategy tabletop games of all time through our simple tutorial.  The core loop is easy to follow, but offers a wealth of strategy to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>1-6 player</strong> support<br/></li><li><strong>500 </strong> plus <strong>cards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Solo play</strong> against four AI difficulties<br/></li><li><strong>Async </strong>&amp; <strong>real-time</strong> multiplayer<br/></li><li><strong>Ranked</strong> &amp; <strong>unranked</strong> matchmaking<br/></li><li><strong>Lobby</strong> &amp; <strong>Private game</strong> tables<br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform multiplayer</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform purchases</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Daily challenge</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Challenging AI</strong> that learns through self-play<br/></li><li><strong>Recommended Sets</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Customize</strong>, save &amp; share <strong>Kingdoms</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Achievements</strong>, <strong>Stats </strong>&amp; <strong>Leaderboards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Pass &amp; Play</strong> mode<br/></li><li>Automated <strong>score-keeping</strong> &amp; hints<br/></li><li><strong>Smart-play</strong> options to streamline gameplay<br/></li><li><strong>Jumbo mode</strong> for readability on phones<br/></li><li><strong>Turbo mode</strong> to zoom through games quickly<br/></li><li><strong>Tutorial</strong> &amp; <strong>Rules</strong><br/></li><li><strong>4 languages</strong>: English, Japanese, German, French<br/></li><li><strong>15 expansions</strong> plus three promo packs </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Awards for the Boardgame</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Awards.png?t=1707010484"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/881020/Granblue_Fantasy_Relink/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/881020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Story<br/>
Granblue Fantasy takes place in the Sky Realm, a world where myriad islands float in a great blue expanse. Take your role as captain of a skyfaring crew, joined by a scrappy little dragon named Vyrn and a young girl with mysterious powers named Lyria. Together you sail with a colorful cast of crewmates, including kings and misfits alike, for Estalucia, a fabled island beyond the end of the skies.<br/>
<br/>
In the Zegagrande Skydom, islands are guarded by powerful creatures known as primal beasts and winds carry tales of a secretive organization known as the Church of Avia. Unveil a web of intrigue reaching far beyond the borders of Zegagrande and engage in a battle for the fate of the Sky Realm itself.<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay<br/>
Engage in real-time combat with a party of four in this character action RPG—choose from a diverse roster of skyfarers, each with their own unique weapons, skills, and combat styles. Teamwork makes the dream work with party-based mechanics such as Link Attacks and Chain Bursts to help you crush foes in spectacular fashion. Tackle quests solo or with the help of others for up to 4-player co-op and take down treacherous foes to score rare loot to further enhance your gear. Every enemy and party formation has its own strengths and weaknesses—the key to victory lies in working out how these pieces fit together.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced combat not your thing? Assist modes can provide accessibility for gamers of all skill levels. Toggle on Full Assist to have all actions performed automatically during battle!<br/>
<br/>
The Sky Realm is rich in lore and history. Browse Lyria's journal at any point during the game to access a trove of writings on the world's peoples, places, and more. In addition to the wealth of side quests available, Fate Episodes allow you to delve into the backstories of each member of your crew!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2772560/Supermarket_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This Prologue is a limited version of the full game to stop waiting and jump into running your supermarket already. Don't forget to wishlist the full game to continue your most fun supermarket experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Design your store, optimizing for efficiency and aesthetics. Determine where products are displayed, manage your aisles, and ensure a smooth shopping experience for your customers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Order stock using an in-game computer and anticipate the arrival of your next delivery. Unpack goods, organize them in your storage room and display them on shelves, fridges, and freezers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Read product barcodes, handle cash and credit card transactions, and ensure customers leave satisfied with their shopping and checkout experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier_Raw.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Navigate the complexities of a real-time market. Buy products when prices dip and determine the best-selling prices to balance customer satisfaction with profit margins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><br/>Wishlist the full game "Supermarket Simulator" where every decision matters. Will you rise to the occasion, transforming a modest establishment into a retail powerhouse, all while balancing customer satisfaction, finances, and mafia expectations?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Lily - Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2220360/Paper_Lily__Chapter_1/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Something terrible has happened. You can’t bear to think about it - but you can’t live like this anymore. You stopped attending school, you haven’t left your house in months, you have no reason to get out of bed anymore. There are no choices left.<br/><br/>No choice except... that strange golden letter.<br/><br/>It’s time to get your life back together. <br/><br/>One last try.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/divider.png?t=1706724298"><br/><br/>Paper Lily is a story-driven, psychological horror RPG where each puzzle has multiple solutions and outcomes. <strong>There is always another way.</strong><br/>Follow Lacie's story as you explore a dangerous hidden world, solve puzzles in multiple different ways, and face strange enemies. The game is playable in about 4 hours and contains multiple endings depending on your actions.<br/><br/>Paper Lily - Chapter 1 is the continuation to the prologue, <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1698960" rel="" target="_blank">Project Kat</a>, but it can also  be enjoyed without having played it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/lacie_sai_walk.gif?t=1706724298"><h2 class="bb_tag">Out of Context Features</h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple ways of solving puzzles!<br/></li><li>Touch grass, and trees<br/></li><li>Minigames where you press buttons and push boxes around<br/></li><li>Call your mother<br/></li><li>Harmless Snack™<br/></li><li>Various things made of paper<br/></li><li>Bunnies (or whatever those things are)<br/></li><li>Demons<br/></li><li>Fast demons<br/></li><li>Social anxiety simulation<br/></li><li>Table salt<br/></li><li>...Is that Kat? Nah, probably not<br/></li><li>Bathroom etiquette<br/></li><li>Death</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2072450/Like_a_Dragon_Infinite_Wealth/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/Accolades_616.png?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>EPIC EMOTIONAL DRAMA</strong><br/>Two larger-than-life heroes brought together by the hand of fate, or perhaps something more sinister…<br/><br/>Ichiban Kasuga, an unstoppable underdog who’s no stranger to crawling up from rock bottom, and Kazuma Kiryu, a broken man facing down his last days.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/2_Epic_Emotional_Drama.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>BEST-IN-CLASS RPG ACTION</strong><br/>Experience one-of-a-kind combat with dynamic, fast-paced RPG battles where the battlefield becomes your weapon, and anything goes. Adapt your party’s skills to the situation with outlandish jobs and customizations to strategically subdue enemies with over-the-top moves. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/3_Best_In_Class_RPG_Action.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>INFINITE ADVENTURE</strong><br/>Live it up in Japan and explore all that Hawaii has to offer in an adventure so big it spans the Pacific. Unforgettable moments await at every step of the journey with a unique mix of quests and activities to enjoy at your leisure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/4_Infinite_Adventure.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Deluxe Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Ultimate Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/>- Assorted Outfit Bundle: Customize your party's look with outfits &amp; swimwear<br/>- Sujimon &amp; Resort Bundle: Get legendary Sujimon, resort guests and special boosters<br/>- Yakuza CD Collection Set: Increase your in-game playlist with classic karaoke tracks						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summon Masters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2100140/Summon_Masters/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2100140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a card and board game with the following features:<br>
<br>
Deck Building: Players can build their own decks to battle with. Depending on different strategies and opponents, players can choose different cards to counter.<br>
<br>
Tactical Gameplay: The game uses a 3x10 chessboard, and players can freely place cards to fight. Players need to develop tactics and arrange card positions and usage order within limited space.<br>
<br>
Different Professions: Players can choose freely from four professions - swordsman, mage, monk, and archer. Each profession has different characteristics and skills, and players can choose according to their preferences and tactical needs.<br/>
<br/>
Competitive Battles: Players can battle with other players after building their decks, and it is fun to fight with other people. Through battles with other players, players can improve their strength and tactical skills.<br/>
<br/>
Team Dungeons: In addition to fighting against other players, players can also team up with others to challenge high-difficulty dungeons. Players need to defeat powerful bosses through cooperation and strategy to get more rewards and cards.<br/>
<br/>
Special Challenges: Players can participate in special rules challenges and use their intelligence to defeat other players. These special rules make the game more interesting and challenging, and players need to constantly think and try new strategies.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced: Each game is fast-paced (within 5 minutes), and can be played in short fragments of time. The fast pace of the game allows players to enjoy the game in a short time, while also being able to play at any time and anywhere.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2248950/TransSiberian_Railway_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take the helm of a classic Russian locomotive, discover the raw beauty and wildness of Siberia and try to survive on the longest railway line in the world. This is the Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator. A game for real adventurers!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/drinking1.gif?t=1707824452"><br/><br/>Complete the tutorial and the first kilometers of the route for free.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/explosion_gif.gif?t=1707824452"><br/><br/>The Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator offers amazing rail and survival challenges on real Russian dangerous routes. Feel what it is like to put your hands at the helm of a powerful freight locomotive and explore the untouched natural landscape that is sure to delight you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/shooting_gif.gif?t=1707824452"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Prologue features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Detailed simulation of driving a VL10 locomotive - the locomotive control is slightly simplified.<br/></li><li> Locomotive repair system - Manage and replace locomotive parts that are constantly wearing out.<br/></li><li> Train traffic simulation - Follow rail signs and signals to avoid derailment or damage to a part of the locomotive.<br/></li><li> Work system - Earn by completing transport orders. <br/></li><li> Game modes (Survival) and (Simulator). It is recommended to play in the (Survival) mode. This is the leading game mode that is constantly being developed. <br/>For players who are not interested in survival mechanics, a simple Simulator mode is available. <br/></li><li> Mafia system - Complete missions for the mafia to earn extra money.<br/></li><li> Survival system with statistics of hunger, thirst, alcohol, hangover, disease and hypothermia - Eat and drink to avoid death. <br/>Keep the right temperature so you don't freeze.<br/></li><li> Shooting system - Use your weapons for hunting and self-defense.<br/></li><li> Purchase and sales system - Buy various items, food, tools, weapons and ammunition.<br/></li><li> Locomotive inspection mode - Inspect the condition of locomotive parts and replace them in time to avoid damage.<br/></li><li> Dynamic weather system with day and night cycle - Survive extreme weather conditions.<br/></li><li> Route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Novosibirsk-Main) - scale 1:1. Buy the full version with the route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Krasnoyarsk).<br/></li><li> Police system - A corrupt militia watches over your movements.<br/></li><li> Much more to discover.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intravenous 2: Mercenarism</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2651330/Intravenous_2_Mercenarism/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Wishlist_Game.png?t=1705699394"><br/><br/>Step into the shoes of Gideon, a ruthless mercenary who cares about nothing but his wealth. Set two months before the events of Intravenous 2, you will take on seemingly simple jobs, the effects of which will ripple out and affect the main game's protagonist. But why should Gideon care? He's just in it for the money.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Stealth_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Stealth or Firepower:</strong> the choice is yours. Sneak through shadows, turn off the lights, pick doors, or unleash a hail of bullets. The game will adapt to your play style.<br/></li><li> <strong>Customize Your Skills:</strong> develop your skills the way you want to, whether it's mastering the art of stealth or becoming a gunslinging virtuoso.<br/></li><li> <strong>Bullet Time:</strong> Gideon is no stranger to stimulants that enhance his cognitive abilities - bending time to give him the edge in tense situations.<br/></li><li> <strong>Vast Arsenal:</strong> choose from firearms, gadgets, and a variety of ammo types to creatively tackle the challenge<br/></li><li> <strong>Weapon Modification:</strong> personalize each firearm with suppressors, laser sights, and more, tailoring your arsenal to the task at hand.<br/></li><li> <strong>Responsive AI:</strong> engage in intense combat with enemies that react to your actions, take cover, use tactics and call for backup.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Action_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2744170/Artifact_SeekerPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/DS.png?t=1706492908"/></a><br/>The difference between the prologue version and the official version<br/>There is a special artifact in the prologue<br/>Characters: 2 in the prologue, at least 5 in the official version<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 3 in the final version.<br/>Systems: Tavern, Marketplace, and Endless Mode will be added to the game.<br/>Artifacts: More artifacts will be added to the game.<br/>Skills: More skills will be added in the official version.<br/>Affixes: More Affixes will be added in the official version.<br/>Events: There will be more interesting Events in the official version.<br/>Progress: No need to worry, all progress will be carry into the official version.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/11y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1z.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/2y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/gif1.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong>[/b]<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><strong><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </img></img></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Gravity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1205130/Dark_Gravity/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1205130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FjQnsk3AhJ7" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1205130/extras/banner_discord_GamePlanet.png?t=1708458030"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1205130/extras/DG_Title_01.gif?t=1708458030"><br/>Shoot, destroy, collect, craft and destroy even more! "Dark Gravity" is a fast-paced, low poly vertical shoot'em up game that features non-linear campaign mode with lots of enemies and bosses. Craft new weapons, upgrade your fighter and build an ultimate aerial war machine!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1205130/extras/DG_Title_02.gif?t=1708458030"><br/>After the fifth world war, there was peace in the world. For over a decade, the Grand Alliance has been leading humanity towards a better tomorrow by stifling all dangers in the bud. For some time, however, there is suspicion of a new threat that cannot be ignored. <br/><br/>As a member of SAF forces, your mission is to take over the Shielton base, captured by unknown rebels. No one knows who they are and what they want. What's worse, even IMC forces couldn't drive them away from the base because of their advanced weaponry. Weaponry out of this world. But... are those rebels the main threat? Isn't there anything bigger behind all this? No time for questions! You must stop them at all costs!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1205130/extras/DG_Title_03.gif?t=1708458030"><br/>Gameplay mechanics are very simple - destroy all enemies and try to avoid every bullet... well, at least those which can be avoided. Your special maneuver allows you to dodge normal projectiles. Even if you get hit, you will only lose one extra weapon! However, watch out for powerful bosses! They can thorn you into pieces with their ultimate unavoidable attacks!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1205130/extras/DG_Title_04.gif?t=1708458030"><br/>The story mode can be completed in a few various ways. Military operations are carried out on several fronts simultaneously. It's up to you which path you will choose. From battles high in the sky, through military bases, underground factories, collapsed mines and abandoned laboratories, to secret Arctic research facilities and the interiors of unknown civilization artifacts - you must go through all of this several times to accomplish all missions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1205130/extras/DG_Title_05.gif?t=1708458030"><br/>Every difficulty level is different. Improving your skills and fighter will help you out at facing hard and insane mode bosses, as they don't appear at easier levels. Enemy's layouts will change as well as their shooting patterns. At higher difficulties, you will also meet enemies that you have not met before.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1205130/extras/DG_Title_06.gif?t=1708458030"><br/>Collecting drop parts and blueprints throughout the missions will allow you to unlock and craft new fighters, weapons, and upgrades. However, remember that only playing at the highest levels of difficulty will allow you to achieve a pinnacle of technology. Uncover the crafting tree and develop unique power-ups!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invisible Fear</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2666570/Invisible_Fear/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2666570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>This is my first game as a solo developer, of course you may encounter some bugs that I will be fixing! Since my childhood it was my dream to create my own game and here it is. I put a lot of time and effort into this game, I hope you enjoy it!</strong><br/><br/>Evelynn, an ordinary teacher in a private school, who had to endure tragic events, after that the school was closed and she was hospitalized with a serious injury. Now the previous nightmare follows her, haunts her dreams and calls her to go back, so Evelynn decides to return to the school to find out what happened on that terrible day. She wants to end her painful memories. There she encounters something supernatural...<h2 class="bb_tag">Abandoned School</h2>- Go through the nightmare in an abandoned school and find out what happened on the tragic day that changed everything here.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2666570/extras/School01.gif?t=1708455647"><h2 class="bb_tag">Camera is the key to survive</h2>- Use your camera or security cameras to protect yourself from creatures that comes out at night. The cameras can show you some invisible things.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2666570/extras/School04.gif?t=1708455647"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive the night</h2>- In order to survive the night you need to find a certain number of artifacts. Each night will become more difficult and the creatures more dangerous.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2666570/extras/School02.gif?t=1708455647"><h2 class="bb_tag">Replayability</h2>- The items spawn is set randomly, as is the creatures on the location. You'll never be sure what awaits you in the next room: artifact or a trap?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2666570/extras/School03B.gif?t=1708455647"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idle Fields</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1807570/Idle_Fields/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1807570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1807570/extras/FunGif.gif?t=1708451929"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">What is Idle Fields?</h2></strong>Idle Fields is a relaxing Idle game where you grow crops, fish, cook, decorate your house, take care of animals, and complete everything possible by leveling up skills and unlocking rewards. Level up Farming, Husbandry, Fishing, Cooking, Woodcutting, and Constrution.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1807570/extras/IntroGif.gif?t=1708451929"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1807570/extras/Bunnies.gif?t=1708451929"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">This game offers you:</h2></strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>50 levels in 6 different skills<br/></li><li>Workers to automate skills<br/></li><li>Many achievements with more to come<br/></li><li>A relaxing atmosphere<br/></li><li>Beautiful outfits for all your workers</li></ul><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Is This Game For You?</h2></strong><br/>If you like a simple short-experienced game you won't have to focus on often, yes! If you want something super engaging, maybe not.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Join our Discord</h2></strong><br/>Player impact is a huge factor of this game. Every suggestion has a chance to make it into the game!<br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FbVBjrtJByx" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1807570/extras/Discord.png?t=1708451929"/></a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World War: An Age of Industry &amp; Magic</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2388410/World_War_An_Age_of_Industry__Magic/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2388410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							World War: An Age of Industry &amp; Magic is a fast-paced, collectible card game. Choose destructive cards of the Military, healing and mystical cards of the Church, or specialized cards of the State and the Academy to crush all enemies who challenge your rule.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2388410/extras/Building.png?t=1708451590"><h2 class="bb_tag">World War: An Age of Industry and Magic </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Challenging single player campaign<br/></li><li>11 unique playable levels<br/></li><li>Battle 11 rival enemies with distinct play styles and with their own decks<br/></li><li>Immersive world building and detailed maps<br/></li><li>Robust deck builder allows users to create a library of decks<br/></li><li>Game changing “Hero” cards with unique abilities<br/></li><li>52 cards ensure dynamic gameplay<br/></li><li>Player profile customization<br/></li><li>No pay to play<br/></li><li>Online matches</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ooka Ooka Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816760/Ooka_Ooka_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2816760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ooka Ooka Adventure is an adorable 2 player co-op puzzle platformer! Join the Ookas, Ooka Bing and Ooka Ping, on their journey as they gather the Great Bananas! With the two together they can assist each other into getting to places they normally couldn't, or together solve a puzzle!<br/><br/><strong>Local Co-op</strong> : Join Ooka Bing and Ooka Ping as together they solve puzzles! A person controls either Ooka Bing or Ooka Ping and work together to complete the level!<br/><br/><strong>Flexible Controls</strong> : Take control of Ooka Ping or Ooka Bing, either using gamepads, or with the mouse and keyboard! Gamepads are recommended but the game works perfectly fine with only 1 mouse and keyboard! A combination of gamepad and keyboard is possible!<br/><br/><strong>Casual Fun</strong> : The Ookas's Adventure, though an important one, is a fun one! The game is a puzzle platformer, but time limits are not in play! Take your time to learn the levels and then execute once you're ready!<br/><br/><strong>Remote Play</strong> : If using remote play it is recommended for the connecting player to use keyboard controls to avoid general input lag. If gamepads are drifting more than usual or not working correctly, try disabling steam input.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exiled Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2694210/Exiled_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the relentless thrill of Exiled Survivors!<br/>Engage in fast-paced action, shape your destiny with strategic choices, and confront formidable monsters and bosses.<br/>Unlock up to 30 characters as you embark on an epic journey through this adrenaline-fueled adventure.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features :</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fast-Paced Action:</strong> Jump into the action immediately for an adrenaline-pumping gaming experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694210/extras/Projectiles.png?t=1708448551"><br/></img></li><li><strong>Player-Driven Variety:</strong> Your choices shape the gameplay, even amidst the randomness of each session.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694210/extras/Fireball_Evolutions.png?t=1708448551"><br/></img></li><li><strong>Bite-Sized Gaming:</strong> Enjoy engaging sessions lasting 15-20 minutes, perfect for casual and intense play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694210/extras/Monsters.png?t=1708448551"><br/></img></li><li><strong>Monstrous Challenges:</strong> Confront interesting monsters and formidable bosses.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694210/extras/Characters.png?t=1708448551"><br/></img></li><li><strong>Continuous Progression:</strong> Unlock levels and characters at your own pace, turning every session into a step forward in your gaming journey.</li></ul><br/>Note: Some in-game images were originally generated by an artificial intelligence and subsequently modified for artistic enhancement. The fusion of AI creativity and human touch results in unique visual elements that contribute to the immersive experience of Exiled Survivors.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky Settlers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2494870/Sky_Settlers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494870/extras/AboutGif2.gif?t=1708448456"><br/>Sky Settlers is a minimalist city builder game, where you have different cards that you use to build your sky colony. Each tile has connections to other tiles, that give the player either more or less points depending on what tiles are around that tile. When you have enough points, you can buy new islands to build on. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494870/extras/GameplayGif2.gif?t=1708448456"><br/><br/>After buying an island you will be presented with two quests, one of which you can choose. These quests are given to you as cards and are placed as any other tile. By completing quests you can get points and unlock new cards into your rotation. Those are the basics, although there are a lot more things you will have to discover yourself!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494870/extras/FeaturesGif3.gif?t=1708448456"><h2 class="bb_tag">What the game offers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A relaxing atmosphere (until you stumble upon a disaster that is)<br/></li><li>A lot of different handcrafted islands<br/></li><li>Many unlockable cards with different effects and tiles<br/></li><li>Quests<br/></li><li>Rare events<br/></li><li>Disasters<br/></li><li>Infinite gameplay (until you lose of course)</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">The game does not feature</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Resource &amp; Population management<br/></li><li>Technology tree<br/></li><li>And other major city building mechanics</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stories from the Outbreak</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1968630/Stories_from_the_Outbreak/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1968630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The year is 2020. A new virus – the New Death – has begun turning people into violent zombies. The government has collapsed, and a brutal paramilitary group has taken control over most of Latvia. The streets are not safe, and the police or army will not protect you.<br/>You turn the radio on. The military is announcing that one last ferry will be heading out to Iceland from the western shore. Escape will be granted to those with enough fuel for the entry fee, and enough courage to attempt the journey across zombie-infested Latvia.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1968630/extras/fight_600x.gif?t=1708448416"><br/><br/>Stories from the Outbreak is a turn-based roguelike zombie RPG. The combat is heavily strategic, allowing customisation in team composition and character progression, and the game features dozens of trinkets that provide passive bonuses following the best roguelike design practices. Between combats, you must make decisions about traversing the landscape, and written events force you to navigate the moral complexities of surviving in a hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Planned</strong> Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Form a team of survivors, each with unique abilities and personalities. Decide the fates of your team members as you go<br/></li><li> A wide selection of trinkets and abilities allows creative approaches to strategy, and the random element of roguelikes keeps the game fresh through many playthroughs<br/></li><li> Over 25 enemy types combine into hundreds of different encounters that will push your tactical thinking to its limits<br/></li><li> Search for supplies and face moral dilemmas in an event system where your choices matter<br/></li><li> Over 80 000 words of written content explore the lore of the Outbreak and the backstories of the various characters, and hidden surprises await even as you keep replaying the game<br/></li><li> Late-game replayability is reinforced by unlocking new trinkets (permanent progression) and various challenge modes</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1968630/extras/map_600x.gif?t=1708448416"><br/><br/>In this brutal world, not all of the people are going to survive. Not every team is going to make it. This is how it is intended to be.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save Twiks</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811080/Save_Twiks/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>“This is the horrific and dramatic story of 2024.”</strong><br/><br/><i>The game is based on true story, however all names and events are fictional and any similarities with real life are coincidental.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811080/extras/ГИФКА1__1_.gif?t=1708448104"><br/><br/>The man was traveling by train. He had a kitten named Twiks, which he was carrying to Twiks future home. Twiks had a collar and a special “pet” train ticket.<br/>On January eleventh, Twiks got out of its traveling cage and went exploring. <br/>The conductor noticed the kitten when train made a stop in Kirov. Her story was that she thought it was a stray kitten as she couldn’t find its owner. She threw away the kitten outside the train, not even thinking that it was about 30 degrees below zero. About three hundred people were looking for Twiks.<br/>He was found dead covered with snow not too far from train tracks around Kirov on January 20th.The volunteers that found Twiks said he was chewed to death by dogs.<br/><br/>I was touched by this tragic event and I decided to to create the game <i>which is going to cover very difficult topics, such as:</i> <br/> - Loss of loved ones; <br/> - Irreversibility of traumatic events;<br/> - Careless people;<br/> - Emptiness and fear of loneliness<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811080/extras/ГИФКА2.gif?t=1708448104"><br/><br/>You will be consumed by cold and dark world of the game “Save Twiks” and seek for answers. <br/> - Did you have a chance to save poor kitten Twiks or his fate was already decided?<br/> - What was this? Was it tragical accident or willful evil?<br/> - What should you do if you come face to face with these events?<br/><br/><strong><i>You will meet the harsh Russian reality. The small town is covered with snow. The train is stuck on the tracks at the edge of time. Someone’s destiny awaits among countless train cars.</i></strong><br/><br/>You are walking around and exploring gloomy train cars. You are meeting and talking with few passengers and live with them through their personal tragedies and horrors. <br/>Will you be able to push through this unimaginable horror, to change the the events of this tragic story?<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:/b]<br/> - Welcome to the cold train, with enormous train cars count;<br/> - Every train car is separate world with its’ own story;<br/> - Intense horror is neatly woven into dramatic narrative; <br/> - The dashing 90’s atmosphere;<h2 class="bb_tag">DESCRIPTION OF CONTENT FOR ADULTS</h2>The developers describe the content as follows:<br/>The game contains images of violent scenes that may have a negative impact on the psyche. Some content may not be suitable for certain age groups. A reasonable limit on the game's audience is recommended.<br/><br/><strong>The average time to complete the game is 50 minutes.</strong></strong> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lost Legends of Redwall: Feasts &amp; Friends</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2632490/The_Lost_Legends_of_Redwall_Feasts__Friends/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Feasts___Friends_Steam_Description_Header_1.png?t=1708453647"><br/><br/>Come savor the peaceful town of Lilygrove in this cute and cozy cooking game based on the beloved book series <i>Redwall</i> by Brian Jacques. Join Scout-Chef Rootsworth in the kitchen as you challenge hand-crafted recipes, meet a charming cast of characters, forage fresh ingredients, and enjoy a beautiful small-town story. Get ready to prepare a feast for your woodland friends!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Feasts___Friends_Steam_Description_Header_Overview.png?t=1708453647"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Features_Text.png?t=1708453647"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Feasts___Friends_Steam_Description_Header_Woodlander_Characters.png?t=1708453647"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Rootsworth.png?t=1708453647"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Belladora.png?t=1708453647"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Glimber.png?t=1708453647"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Albert.png?t=1708453647"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Capt_Barker.png?t=1708453647"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Foxglove.png?t=1708453647"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Feasts___Friends_Steam_Description_Header_Small_Town_Story.png?t=1708453647"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Foxglove.gif?t=1708453647"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Feasts___Friends_Steam_Description_Header_Simple_As_2.png?t=1708453647"><h2 class="bb_tag">Turning on the heat and adding the ingredients</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Add_Ingredient.gif?t=1708453647"><h2 class="bb_tag">Following the recipe card and performing the right actions on time</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Stir.gif?t=1708453647"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Feasts___Friends_Steam_Description_Header_Prep_Minigames.png?t=1708453647"><h2 class="bb_tag">Slice</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Slice.gif?t=1708453647"><h2 class="bb_tag">Dice</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Dice.gif?t=1708453647"><h2 class="bb_tag">Chop</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Chop.gif?t=1708453647"><h2 class="bb_tag">Spicing up each meal up with the right spices to hit the Flavor Targets and get a perfect score</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Feasts___Friends_Steam_Description_Header_Roadmap.png?t=1708453647"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Roadmap_Text.png?t=1708453647"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632490/extras/Feasts___Friends_Steam_Description_Header_Divider_1.png?t=1708453647"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lost Legends of Redwall™: The Scout Anthology</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2169570/The_Lost_Legends_of_Redwall_The_Scout_Anthology/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2169570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2169570/extras/Steam_Description_Section_Header_lOGO.png?t=1708447508"><br/><br/>Step into the epic, story-rich world of Mossflower in the first official Redwall story since 2011. "The Scout" is a linear action-adventure game told in three acts. Play as Liam or Sophia, the newest member of the Lilygrove Scout Corps, as the young mice find themselves on the journey of a lifetime to save their home from ruthless pirates. Will they reach Redwall and save their friends before all is lost?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2169570/extras/Steam_Description_Section_Header_1.png?t=1708447508"><h2 class="bb_tag">The Scout Act 1</h2>After months of training, betrothed mice Liam and Sophia are ready to graduate into fully-fledged Scouts: a group of woodland rangers tasked with the protection of the land and trained in the ancient ways of woodcraft. Their initiate ceremonies are cut short when sea rats attack their beloved home. As the senior Scouts rally for battle, it's up to the Scout Corps' newest recruit to outwit the enemy, light the beacon, and summon aid from the surrounding woodlands - before there is nothing left to save.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2169570/extras/Steam_Description_Section_Header_2.png?t=1708447508"><h2 class="bb_tag">The Scout Act 2</h2>The beacon is lit, troops rally to fend off the invading searats, and Liam reunites with his dear Sophia beneath the Lilygrove Lighthouse, but not all is well. Scumsnout's vengeful cries can be heard in the distance and it is revealed that our Scout's betrothed has been poisoned by the wereat's venomous bite. With no time to spare, the couple race to the Winsome Wraith, where a mysterious and dangerous stoat may have the antidote they seek. As if things weren't bad enough, the sea rats are moving inland and the shadow of a large predatory bird lurks just at the edge of the woods.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2169570/extras/Steam_Description_Section_Header_3.png?t=1708447508"><h2 class="bb_tag">The Scout: Act 3</h2>After being mortally poisoned by Scumsnout's vicious maw, our young Scouts have made it to the Winsome Wraith in one piece, if just barely. While the mysterious stoat's treatment has bought some precious time, Liam and Sophia must now travel the rest of the way to Redwall Abbey for a more permanent cure. This is the dramatic conclusion of their journey through the murk of Portman's Slough, the miraculously-functioning puzzles of Grating Gulley, and the ancient ruins of the Otters' Den.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2169570/extras/Steam_Description_Section_Header_Features_2.png?t=1708447508"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2> <ul class="bb_ul"><li>A brand new original story set the winter before the events of the first book.<br/></li><li>A stunning woodland world inhabited by charming critters and villainous vermin. <br/></li><li>Two characters with divergent dialog for replayability.<br/></li><li> Unique real-time scent mechanic fitting for woodlanders who experience the world primarily through their noses.<br/></li><li>An assortment of achievements and collectables for the completionist spirit. <br/></li><li>Original soundtrack created especially for fans of Redwall.<br/></li><li>Fully voice acted by a talented cast of new and established actors.<br/></li><li>Engaging puzzles and side stories for those who delight in world building.<br/></li><li>Full controller support with multiple schemes to choose from.<br/></li><li>Anthology Includes all 3 Acts in one, with revamped lighting and controls.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2169570/extras/Steam_Description_Section_Header_Mechanics_2.png?t=1708447508"><h2 class="bb_tag">Mechanics</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>"The Scout" debuts a dynamic scent system unlike any game before it. Rather than stagnant, pre-designed paths that imitate scent, particles read the wind and the environment to simulate realistic currents and pools. Scents themselves consist of parts and patterns designed around real scent theory.<br/></li><li>When traversing the world of Mossflower, you make use of your mouse agility to explore the world in a unique and wondrous way. Shimmy along ledges, scramble sheer cliffs, and even squeeze through impossibly small spaces. With courage, faith, and friends by your side, Mossflower's fate rests in your paws!<br/></li><li>Rely on stealth, wit, and agility to evade your enemies. Manipulate dull-witted vermin with scent and scent to avoid getting caught in their grubby paws. <br/></li><li>Use your trusty way glass to scope the area and identify danger. Rely on your home-made slingshot to solve puzzles, break pots, and activate traps.<br/></li><li>Decide if you will prioritize the mission and leave the others to save themselves or take the time to lend a helping paw. Some may praise philanthropy, still others would praise pragmatism.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2169570/extras/Untitled_Artwork.png?t=1708447508"><br/><br/>"The Lost Legends of Redwall™" is inspired by the wildly popular characters and world created by Brian Jacques in the Redwall™ best-selling book series, published by and on behalf of Penguin Random House and now announced for a major movie and TV series by Netflix.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2169570/extras/LicenseLogos.png?t=1708447508"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2169570/extras/SomaLogos.png?t=1708447508"><br/><br/>"The Lost Legends of Redwall™" is a series of games and a proud collaboration between Redwall Abbey Company Ltd, Penguin Random House UK, and Soma Games. Together we have nurtured a product that we believe captures the original heart of Brian Jacques’ masterpiece. Lovingly crafted at every turn, The Lost Legends of Redwall™ hopes to earn its place among the influential games of the new millennium.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2169570/extras/Untitled_Artwork.png?t=1708447508"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEASTWATCH: Meat &amp; Mayhem</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2596480/BEASTWATCH_Meat__Mayhem/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2596480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2596480/extras/Beastwatch_Logo.png?t=1708445150"><br/><i>Beastwatch is a retro-style horror shooter in which you play a security guard working his first night in a slaughterhouse.</i><br/><br/>Plunge into an unimaginable macabre nightmare in Beastwatch, a terrifying first-person shooter that immerses you in the heart of darkness. On your first shift as a security guard at a shadowy slaughterhouse, you expected a quiet night, but blood spills, and hidden horrors emerge as the animals take a sinister turn.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2596480/extras/Beastwatch_Divider.png?t=1708445150"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2596480/extras/Beastwatch_Gif.gif?t=1708445150"><h2 class="bb_tag">KEY FEATURES</h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Immersive Retro Atmosphere:</strong> Explore a world of terror thoughtfully designed with retro graphics that transport you to the golden age of horror gaming.<br/><br/></li><li> <strong>Intense First-Person Action:</strong> Confront grotesque mutations in thrilling first-person combat as you fight for survival in a slaughterhouse overrun by chaos.<br/><br/></li><li> <strong>Unthinkable Horrors:</strong> Face unimaginable abominations that will challenge your sanity and tactical skills around every corner.<br/><br/></li><li> <strong>Tense Exploration:</strong> Traverse dark hallways, chilling storerooms, and secret passages as you unravel the story behind the nightmare lurking in the slaughterhouse.<br/><br/></li><li> <strong>Mysteries to Uncover:</strong> Discover clues, solve puzzles, and unravel the darkest secrets of the slaughterhouse as you struggle to survive.<br/><br/></li><li> <strong>Claustrophobic Atmosphere:</strong> Immerse yourself in an intensely claustrophobic atmosphere where every corner hides a new terror waiting to shred you apart.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2596480/extras/Beastwatch_Divider.png?t=1708445150"><br/><br/>Prepare for a visceral horror experience that will test your nerves and wit. <br/><br/>Are you ready to face your first night in the slaughterhouse?<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2596480/BEASTWATCH_Meat__Mayhem/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2596480/BEASTWATCH_Meat__Mayhem/</a> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schmaragon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2057690/Schmaragon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2057690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Schmaragon is an exciting third-person indie MOBA with shared experience, created using assets from Paragon.<h2 class="bb_tag">Schmaragon also boasts a set of interesting features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Variable-powered heroes</strong>: Some heroes are significantly more powerful than others. For example, Level 3 heroes are 4-5 times more powerful than Level 1 heroes.</li><li><strong>Hero companions</strong>: A mutt or a beast that you can control, providing you with combat and tactical advantages.</li><li>Schmaragon players can choose which abilities they want their heroes to have, and they can even change their heroes after the match has already started.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">The team-based leveling system and its consequences:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Schmaragon employs a team-based leveling system, where all team members share the same XP level and acquire abilities and items simultaneously.<br/></li><li>Because all team members always maintain the same XP level, players can leave the match at any time, knowing that they will be promptly replaced by another player of the same XP level.<br/></li><li>Therefore, we've introduced some interesting measures. A 1-minute AFK (Away From Keyboard) period will result in removal from the match, while 2 minutes of no contribution (e.g., no damage dealt to enemies) will lead to a ban from the match.<br/></li><li>Team members can also vote to ban other team members from the match (requiring 4 out of 6 votes).<br/></li><li>Because heroes have varying power levels (three Level 1, two Level 2, and one Level 3 hero on each team), they don't equally impact the match's outcome. Level 3 heroes have the most significant impact. The idea is that less experienced players would opt for Level 1 heroes, which have a lesser impact on the match's outcome.<br/></li><li>Players have an incentive to stay until the end of the match due to the permadeath mechanic, as they receive bonus hero lives for doing so.<br/></li><li>Additionally, there's a concept of adjusting bounties. Dying frequently reduces the XP fed to the opposing team, while accumulating many kills increases your bounty.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Permadeath mechanic explained:</h2><br/>In this unique MOBA setup, heroes start with a limited number of lives. They lose lives when defeated but can regain them by vanquishing creeps, defeating enemy heroes, or participating in the game until the end of the match. <strong>This is important: lives are permanently stored on a central server, guaranteeing that the number of lives persists and carries over between matches.</strong> If a hero runs out of lives, the player can no longer play as that hero.<br/><br/><strong>The gameplay and psychological impacts of permadeath:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dying only affects you; the impact of death on your team is minor. That means less toxicity between teammates and a friendlier environment for new players.<br/></li><li>Although not a requirement, there is a strong incentive for every player to finish the match because big rewards in terms of hero lives are granted at the end.<br/></li><li>The concept draws inspiration from Eve Online, where players command spaceships susceptible to destruction in diverse ways. Once your ship is destroyed, it is permanently lost. While you can acquire another, the one you originally had is irretrievably gone.<br/></li><li>Permadeath can add a heightened sense of risk and reward to the gaming experience. Knowing that failure carries consequences can make success more satisfying.<br/></li><li>Permadeath can lead to stronger emotional connections between players and their characters or assets. The fear of loss can make victories more meaningful.<br/></li><li>The potential for permanent consequences encourages players to learn from their mistakes, adapt their strategies, and become more skilled over time.</li></ul><br/><strong>Questions and answers:</strong><br/><br/><i><strong>Q:</strong> Is the only effect of permadeath going to be that people play much more defensively and care less about their teammates?</i><br/><strong>A:</strong> This is a valid point, but we have some countermechanics:<br/>If the hero life loss becomes too overwhelming, players have the option to fall back to a default hero (Kwang, Serath, or Crunch), which is not affected by the permadeath system. This is because Schmaragon allows changing the hero in the middle of the match. If the hero life loss is still too overwhelming, players have the option to leave the match. This is because, as explained earlier, Schmaragon doesn't penalize quitting in the middle of the match.<br/><br/><i><strong>Q:</strong> Encouraging quitting during the match? That doesn't seem like the best idea.</i><br/><strong>A:</strong> There is a strong incentive for every player to finish the match because big rewards in terms of hero lives are granted at the end. However, if you have to leave for any reason, we will not penalize you. <br/><br/><i><strong>Q:</strong> Doesn't it sound like a system that only exists to charge players money when they run out of lives?</i><br/><strong>A:</strong> We promise not to use any shady methods to make money. Currently, our studio doesn't have a monetization plan.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle Evil: The Priest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2074260/Middle_Evil_The_Priest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2074260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dark Middle-Ages. A young priest is coming in a small village where the local church became full of  evil. Your need to help villagers and do seven night prayers which will defeat the evil.<br/><br/>It will be not easy. Skeletons, ghosts, vampires and other devils spawns will try to stop and kill you! But you have in your inventory all you need to take the victory: saint cross, sharp sword, censer with herbs and the holy book! Learn and compose the words to make the miracles! Any word - is your way to win! Villagers will help you to by selling different potions and items!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2074260/extras/me_gif2.gif?t=1708441326"><br/><br/>Death - is just beginning. If the  evil will kill you - dont worry! The Underworld will glad to open the doors for your hero! Here you can upgrade the health or stamina and return to life to try win the creatures of the darkness!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2074260/extras/me_gif1.gif?t=1708441326"><br/><br/>Особенности игры:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>2d cartoon graphics and animation</li><li>dynamic gameplay</li><li>mirracles from words</li><li>middle ages atmosphere</li><li>cozy village and gloomy underworld</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lazaret</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2088280/Lazaret/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2088280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A rescue team is called out to investigate a distress signal coming from a ship identified as the MTS Endurance - a ship known to have disappeared 4 years ago on a voyage across the Atlantic. The rescue operation goes awry, and you are left stranded and alone on the derelict ship. Searching below deck you find no sign of life. The crew appears to have just vanished; replaced with eerie stone statues, but perhaps you're not as alone as you first thought. Explore the derelict ship to uncover what happened 4 years ago and what fate befell the crew.<br>
<br>
Lazaret is a first-person horror game with light puzzle elements and an emphasis on atmosphere. You play as a lone member of a rescue crew who must complete puzzles and explore the derelict ship while trying to avoid meeting the same fate as the missing crew. Danger lurks around every corner - you must run or hide to stay alive as you learn more about the ship and what caused its mysterious disappearance 4 years ago.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ascent of the Dragon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815110/Ascent_of_the_Dragon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2815110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Ascent of the Dragon" is an endless side-scrolling runner! It has leaderboard support, so when you are playing this during office hours, meetings or calls, you can still get some progression in your life. Trust me, your boss won’t give you that satisfaction. <br/><br/>Here are many of the reasons to play this game:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Pretending to Work: It's the perfect cover for when your boss is talking about something that's supposed to be easy but ends up being very complicated as always.<br/></li><li>Nightingale, Palworld, or Helldivers 2 will take some time to download. It's better to play this than to just stare at your screen.<br/></li><li>Procrastination Aid: Have important tasks to do and you are looking for an escape rope? This game is the perfect tool for procrastination. <br/></li><li>Screensaver: When you leave the game running, it makes for a great and unique screensaver. The ultimate disguise to continue the charade.<br/></li><li>Thanks to the leaderboards, you can play during office hours, meetings or calls to still enjoy some progression in your life as your boss will never give you that satisfaction.<br/></li><li>Dragons: Everybody loves dragons, so why miss out? Note: If you haven’t bought the game at this point in the description, I will send my pet dragon to burn you to a crisp.<br/></li><li>Healthy life choice: It's cheaper than a beer or any type of junk food, which makes it healthier.<br/></li><li>Strive to be the best: This probably won’t be hard, this game will probably sell worse than the deal I made with the devil.<br/></li><li>Introvert: When you're not in the mood to interact with other humans, this game provides the perfect excuse. "Sorry, can't talk. I'm busy guiding a dragon to its next collision”.</li></ul><br/><br/>If you are still reading the description at this point, then there’s no other option than to accept the inevitable. Buy this game. Come on! DO IT.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2379780/Balatro/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Balatro is a poker-inspired roguelike deck builder all about creating powerful synergies and winning big.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Endless_Possibility.gif?t=1708448566"><br/><br/>Combine valid poker hands with unique Joker cards in order to create varied synergies and builds. Earn enough chips to beat devious blinds, all while uncovering hidden bonus hands and decks as you progress. You’re going to need every edge you can get in order to reach the boss blind, beat the final ante and secure victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Jokers_Clean_Thin.gif?t=1708448566"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The definitive poker roguelike experience.<br/></li><li>Endless possibilities - every pick-up, discard and joker can dramatically alter the course of your run.<br/></li><li>In-depth campaign mode complete with 8 difficulties, as well as challenge, daily and seeded runs. </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Break_The_Game.gif?t=1708448566"><br/><br/>Deftly deploy an array of potent tools: different Decks, Jokers, Tarot cards, Planet cards, Spectral cards, and Vouchers. Use these versatile instruments to ignite a combo frenzy and turbocharge your poker hands, crafting electrifying, adrenaline-fueled synergies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro_5_Aces_GIF__HQ_.gif?t=1708448566"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 Jokers, each with their own unique abilities<br/></li><li>15 Decks with distinct modifiers to choose from for each run<br/></li><li>5 potential variants of each Joker which add further abilities<br/></li><li>22 Tarot cards variants that can enhance your regular playing cards<br/></li><li>11 Planet cards that help level up your possible poker hands<br/></li><li>32 Voucher cards to help provide permanent buffs for your current run</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Find_Your_Flow.gif?t=1708448566"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in Balatro’s distinctive psychedelic world. Let the synthwave soundtrack wash over you -  wind down, escape the daily grind and prepare to enter the ultimate roguelike flow state.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improve your collection and discover new cards and secrets with every single run.<br/></li><li>Make use of the in-depth stats screen to study your best hands, most used Jokers, and more!<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the CRT fuzz and enjoy detailed, hand-crafted pixel art.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Spectral_Pack.gif?t=1708448566"><br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F5mH3dNhjx2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro-join_the_discord.png?t=1708448566"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diets &amp; Deities</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2084880/Diets__Deities/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2084880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Welcome to the Epicentre of the Universe </h2>Meet Diets and Deities, where cooking and music go together like salt and pepper!<strong> You play as Nephele, the first (and potentially last) deity created in a millennia and it's up to you to dance and dodge your way through forgotten cultures, move to the beat, and eat your weight in long-lost dishes. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2084880/extras/gif-predemo-levels-demo.gif?t=1708439425"><br/><br/>- <strong>Diverse areas and characters</strong> inspired our team's background: Australia (with First Nations creatives), Bali, Brazil, and China<br/>- <strong>Locally composed and produced music</strong> with authentic cultural instruments and sounds<br/>- <strong>Wholesome and non-competitive rhythm gameplay</strong> that focuses on an audio-visual experience and satisfaction over perfection<br/>- <strong>16 real recipes</strong> inspired by each culture for players to unlock and cook at home<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2084880/extras/gif-predemo-bazaar-showcase.gif?t=1708439425"><br/><br/>Set at the epicentre of a multicultural universe - food and music are the essences of life...at least that's how things used to be. You fight against the Colonel, KFZ, whose amalgamation of cheesy and greasy fast food has taken over the universe. Nephele must reawaken each corrupted Deity using music and cooking to give life back into their lands and cook delicious dishes along the way! <strong>Can you handle the heat and become a culinary champion?</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2084880/extras/gif-predemo-tutorialtransition.gif?t=1708439425"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YonDelver</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1787550/YonDelver/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1787550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>There's a lot of bullets in between you and the bottom...</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1787550/extras/Alot_of_Bullets.gif?t=1708438278"><br/>Arena battles and ambushes can get hectic quickly. Collecting consumables and gear to help you survive is highly recommended.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>You will need more than skill to survive.</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1787550/extras/600x100_Mad_Kindler.gif?t=1708438278"><br/>Many weapons, items, and consumables have multiple uses. Experiment with them all to find the best combinations with your builds!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Complete Combat Control</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1787550/extras/600x100_CCC_Full_Gif_Attempt.gif?t=1708438278"><br/>In short, it is possible for a player to beat the entire game with starter gear.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spoils of a Starfighter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803090/Spoils_of_a_Starfighter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							_______________________________<br>
<br>
Fight for spoils<br>
<br>
Gain experience<br>
<br>
Upgrade your ship<br/>
<br/>
Modify your weapons.<br/>
<br/>
Reach the top of the survival leaderboard<br/>
<br/>
________________________________<br/>
<br/>
Movement is WASD or a gamepad controller<br/>
<br/>
Rotation is either mouse left click or you can choose to auto aim in the options<br/>
<br/>
_______________________________						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>qomp2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2243510/qomp2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2243510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Control a Pong ball aching to break free of its life stuck between two paddles. Explore a dangerous, minimalist world, armed with simple two button controls: tap a button to change direction diagonally by 45 degrees, and hold down a button to unleash a cathartic dash forward. That’s all you need to solve environmental puzzles and labyrinthine levels. Around each corner is a new challenge that will test your two-button and problem-solving skills. A variety of difficult enemies and bosses help you mark your time as you navigate through 30 levels spread across four worlds.<br/><br/>qomp2 effectively captures the essence of the original 1972 Pong and its spiritual successor, the 2021 experimental indie title qomp.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Cerebral Puzzling:</strong> The simple, two button controls belie complex and compelling gameplay. Use your reflexes and think ahead to avoid hazards, flip switches, and bounce your way through 30 tricky levels. Hidden collectibles push you to explore every inch of the minimalist maps.<br/></li><li><strong>A Surprise around Every Corner:</strong> qomp2 constantly delights as new features, mechanics, enemies, traps and hazards are introduced as you progress deeper into the game. Don’t get complacent: As soon as you’ve mastered one aspect of gameplay, another is ready to challenge you.<br/></li><li><strong>Bosses:</strong> Four challenging bosses block your path at the end of each world. You will need to use all your newfound skills to master their attacks and defenses. Don’t worry. Death isn’t the end in an arcade-inspired world.  Quick respawn makes sure you’re back in the action in seconds.<br/></li><li><strong>A Serene Soundscape:</strong> A soundtrack of ambient jams gets you in the groove, and helps you keep your cool, as you work your way through the minimalist maze.<br/></li><li><strong>An Emotional Journey:</strong> An enigmatic story of doubt, fear, and self-acceptance, told wordlessly through simple effects and gameplay.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANGEL SPIRIT</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2812040/ANGEL_SPIRIT/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2812040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2812040/extras/ANGEL_SPIRIT_TITLE_1_SMALLER.png?t=1708428797"><br/><br/>ANGEL SPIRIT is a first-person retro-inspired 3D platforming/adventure game, taking place in a fantasy world comprised of 10 unique levels.<br/><br/>Experience the world through the eyes of an angel, summoned to embark on a quest for magical abilities.<br/><br/>This game offer a uniquely tranquil experience for those who appreciate exploring interactive realms.<br/><br/>The gameplay is very simple. You walk/run through each level, with the main content being the atmospheric immersion that each environment provides.<br/><br/>There is a non-trivial amount of first-person 3D platforming to enhance the gaming experience, along with an auditorily polished, highly satisfying UI/UX.<br/><br/>The priority audience are those who enjoy games that focus on immersing the player into atmospheric landscapes and environments.<br/><br/>Short in duration, the game hopes that the player enjoys their time by soaking in the atmosphere of each level, appreciating the innermost complexes of the mind that are stimulated with the simplistic visual and auditory input.<br/><br/>For those with advice or suggestion on how to improve both this and future games, please leave your advice and input in the community forums.<br/><br/><strong><i>- OP37K</i></strong> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robzawar</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815960/Robzawar/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2815960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Robzawar is an addictive game that plunges players into the heart of an exciting struggle for survival in an alien world. As the main character, you find yourself in the role of a tough robot whose spaceship has crashed on a treacherous dinosaur planet.<br>
Your main goal is to survive in a hostile environment while fending off the merciless attacks of the local dinosaur population. With your wits, reflexes and limited arsenal, you must navigate landscapes full of dangers.<br>
Use the keyboard to move and the computer mouse to shoot. The goal of the game is to destroy as many dinosaurs as possible and set a record in the online table.<br>
The fate of your robot protagonist is in your hands as you embark on an unforgettable journey through the dinosaur planet.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Everywhere</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2249850/Cats_Everywhere/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2249850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A relaxing hidden object game for cat's lovers.<br/><br/>Find all the cats by clicking on them, in a hand-drawn background.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>200+ Cats to find<br/></li><li>4 Locations<br/></li><li>Hint System<br/></li><li>Steam achievements</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samurai`s Way</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2694730/Samurais_Way/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an electrifying odyssey through ancient world in "Samurai`s Way", the inaugural title from TinC Studio that merges the relentless thrill of a 2D runner with the strategic depth of a clicker arcade. Drawing inspiration from the storied philosophy of the samurai way, this game invites players to step into the sandals of a novice warrior, forged in the spirit of Bushido, on an epic quest for honor and enlightenment.<br>
<br>
As the dawn mist settles over the emerald hills of ancient world, our hero, a young samurai named Kenji, finds himself on a path filled with perils and revelations. Disillusioned by the tyranny corrupting his homeland, Kenji embarks on a relentless journey, seeking wisdom and the strength to bring peace to his people. His travels are not just a test of skill but a spiritual trial to uphold the virtues of Rectitude, Courage, Benevolence, Respect, Honesty, Honor, and Loyalty, which are the pillars of his warrior soul.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blast Them All</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2722490/Blast_Them_All/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>SURVIVE ENDLESS WAVES.</strong> The growing waves of zombies challenge you and your dexterity. Keep your cool and put on a good show in the face of ever-increasing difficulty.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722490/extras/BTA_01.gif?t=1708420833"><br/><br/><strong>ADAPT TO CHANGING ARENAS.</strong> At the end of each wave, the arena you survived fades away to make way for your next challenge. Take advantage of the new layout, weapons and traps at your disposal and try to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722490/extras/BTA_02.gif?t=1708420833"><br/><br/><strong>GO WILD AND SCORE MAXIMUM POINTS.</strong> Chain together elimination and ignite your gauge. Annihilate the zombies in your path and boost your multiplier before blasting your score. Push on and die proudly, with your name at the top of the leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722490/extras/BTA_03.gif?t=1708420833"><br/><br/><strong>STRENGTHEN YOURSELF DURING AND BETWEEN WAVES.</strong> Collect upgrades and take advantage of their contents to perform during the round. After each special wave, choose upgrades from the store and make good use of your reroll tokens to adapt your upgrades and push your survival further.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722490/extras/BTA_04.gif?t=1708420833"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny House</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2826220/Tiny_House/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2826220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							There are 14 rooms, each concealing riddles and collectible objects, waiting to be unraveled by you. Whether you're new to escape games or a seasoned adventurer, the diverse puzzles will captivate you.<br>
<br>
All packed into a cute 3D isometric style, Tiny House is completely free to play, no In-app purchases are needed to complete the rooms. You can still remove Ads and support the development with an IAP of your choice.<br>
<br>
Experience the captivating 3D graphics that set Tiny House apart, blending classic point-and-click adventure with modern room escape mechanics<br>
<br>
Tiny House is available in English, French, Italian, German, Spanish, Russian, Japanese, Korean, and Portuguese. The game language automatically changes based on your OS language settings.<br>
<br/>
Don't forget to let your friends know how far you've gone on the game, they may want to compete with you in this exciting escape room experience!<br/>
<br/>
- What's an escape room game? <br/>
In an escape game, you aim to break free from a trapped location by employing skill, patience, and logical thinking. By examining and interacting with objects, you gather clues and items essential for solving puzzles and ultimately escaping the room.<br/>
<br/>
------------------------------------------------<br/>
<br/>
XSGames is an independent solo startup from Italy						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Purrfectly Hidden Cats - Kittenrock</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2786450/Purrfectly_Hidden_Cats__Kittenrock/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2786450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Purrfectly Hidden Cats - Kittenrock" welcomes you to a richly interactive 2D world set in a picturesque mountain resort. The hand-drawn scene in Kittenrock is a labor of love, brimming with intricate details, natural beauty, and humorous Easter eggs, inviting thorough exploration and discovery.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2786450/extras/PHC_KittenRock_Cats_1_.png?t=1708417299"><br/><br/>The gameplay blends classic hidden object mechanics with a unique twist—interactive people and cats around the map, enhancing the engagement and depth of the experience. Your primary goal is to spot the skillfully hidden cats that merge seamlessly into the scenic resort surroundings, often revealed through playful interactions with the environment and its inhabitants.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2786450/extras/Kittenrock-Gif.gif?t=1708417299"><br/><br/>Beyond the joy of discovering cats, the game unfolds engaging mini-stories that add layers of depth and charm. These stories are woven into the fabric of Kittenrock, creating a narrative that celebrates exploration and curiosity.<br/><br/>In 'Purrfectly Hidden Cats - Kittenrock,' the game's zoom feature enhances your experience: zoom in to uncover intricate details and interact with characters, or zoom out to admire the whole scenic beauty of the resort. Whether you prefer a close-up exploration or a broader perspective, the game offers a uniquely engaging and visually stunning journey, encouraging you to discover hidden cats and enjoy the diverse landscape of Kittenrock.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2786450/extras/PHC_KittenRock_Features_1_.png?t=1708417299"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Engaging hidden object gameplay with an emphasis on observation and interaction.<br/></li><li> Interactive characters that add dynamic layers to the gameplay.<br/></li><li> Mini-stories linked to each discovered cat, enriching the game's narrative.<br/></li><li> A vast, interactive mountain resort environment filled with delightful Easter eggs.<br/></li><li> Distinctive line-art graphic style enhancing the game’s visual appeal.<br/></li><li> Soothing and immersive background music, perfectly matching the game's rhythm.<br/></li><li> A variety of achievements to encourage exploration and reward your discoveries.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead Shells</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2823920/Dead_Shells/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2823920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Armed with only a makeshift melee weapon (a wrench fused with a metal pipe) and the newfound ability to manipulate time and slow it down for fleeting moments to gain an edge, this game revolve around solving puzzles and unraveling the secrets to escape the chilling land of the dead shells.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2823920/extras/StoreGif2.gif?t=1708416127"><br/><br/>Your goal is to be precise, quick, and responsive to defend yourself and survive long enough to solve the puzzle to escape the land-A graveyard. You will have the opportunity to gain an edge with a new found ability of slowing down time for a brief moment and finding adrenaline pills will help you activate and maintain it.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic City Detective: Wrath of the Ocean Collector's Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2795850/Magic_City_Detective_Wrath_of_the_Ocean_Collectors_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A gripping detective series filled with mystery and riddles awaits you! Shocking news: supernatural beings are living among us! Sometimes, however, they don't hide well enough. Ribeira Lima, the ocean siren, has become the public's favorite in Rio, but the audience never imagined that her role in their lives is much bigger. After all, she is the only one who knows how to soothe the ocean with her magical singing! But now the daughter of the ocean is gone, and there is no one to sing the Song of the Ocean. Meanwhile, an overwhelming tsunami is coming to Rio, ready to sweep away everything in its path. So, you're the only one who can find Ribeira and save the city! Thankfully, you have all the skills you need to do it! Challenge your investigator skills in this spectacular  new Hidden-Object Puzzle Adventure!<br>
<br>
This Collector's Edition includes:<br>
<br>
🏰	Your own choices!<br>
You have the ability to choose the characters' phrases for one action or another and influence the plot of the mystery story. Don't forget that only your choice determines the course of these complex investigations and can affect the lives of the characters! <br>
<br>
🏰	A variety of achievements!<br/>
Conduct your own investigation by solving intricate puzzles, solving complex riddles and playing various mini-games. You need to solve the most important mystery by searching various places, collecting things and interviewing passers-by. Unlock all the achievements to highlight your success!<br/>
<br/>
🏰	Bonus materials!<br/>
Collect all the clues and save the residents, successfully solve the mystery to gain access to bonus locations, where you'll discover some interesting details about the characters. You might think that some mysteries are not meant to be solved, but you can do it, can't you?<br/>
<br/>
🏰	Collectible items!<br/>
This exciting new edition of the mystery story is filled with various clues and mysterious items that you need to find in order to advance your investigation! Find the collectibles at each crime scene and find the hidden objects. You'll have to be a very careful detective to collect the entire collection!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plantabi: Little Garden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2764070/Plantabi_Little_Garden/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764070/extras/description-title.png?t=1708412454"><h2 class="bb_tag">WHAT IS PLANTABI?</h2>Plantabi is a chill sandbox game where you take care of adorable plants and design the cozy little garden of your dreams!<h2 class="bb_tag">YOUR LITTLE GARDEN</h2>Feel the laid-back vibes as you take care of your leafy buddies in your own little garden. And the fun doesn't stop there – you can unlock and collect more items to spruce up your cozy space, adding that extra touch of charm. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764070/extras/description-bar1.png?t=1708412454"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE TASK</h2>Expand your collection by helping the shop owner complete orders and unlock a wider array of plants to care for in Plantabi!<h2 class="bb_tag">A DIFFERENT PLANT</h2>Form a unique bond with a fellow plant collecting buddy who came from a different planet and, together, unlock a different variety of plants not seen in the shop!<h2 class="bb_tag">ENHANCE!</h2>Experiment with different pot designs and colors to create the perfect aesthetic for your green companions. Additionally, enhance your plants' growth by equipping a variety of orbs, each imbued with unique properties.<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Adorable 2D pixel art for a cute visual experience.<br/></li><li> A wholesome and chill atmosphere that sets a relaxing tone.<br/></li><li> A diverse collection of over 90 plants to nurture and cultivate in your virtual garden.<br/></li><li> A wide array of items to personalize and decorate your cozy garden.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Object Chronicles: Poisoned Truth Collector's Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2756720/Hidden_Object_Chronicles_Poisoned_Truth_Collectors_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2756720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Mark Mendelson was expecting a pleasant family get-together, but all he got was a lethal dose of champagne. You've been asked to find the killer. And you cannot fail! You'll be deep into family relations and learn all the secrets of the wealthy Mendelson clan. Who will inherit the fortune? Who did the head of the family quarrel with just a few hours before his abrupt death? Answer these questions and send the criminal to jail! Can you solve the perplexing case and ensure the guilty party faces the consequences? The challenge awaits in this spectacular new Hidden-Object Puzzle Adventure!<br>
<br>
This Collector's Edition includes:<br>
<br>
🔎	Family secrets!<br>
Delve into intricate relationships, and decipher motives behind the murder. Will you identify the heir to the Mendelson fortune? Or reveal the untold rifts among family members that led to the fatal confrontation?<br>
<br/>
🔎	Reveal the truth!<br/>
Engage your mind with challenging yet captivating puzzles that promise rewards in the form of crucial clues and motives. Your mission: find the culprit and ensure justice prevails!<br/>
<br/>
🔎	Bonus chapter!<br/>
Play the exclusive bonus chapter that peels back the layers of yet another captivating mystery within the family, unraveling more thrilling secrets! Focus solely on the pursuit of truth and justice without any hindrances!<br/>
<br/>
🔎	Detective process!<br/>
Enjoy the detective experience without the usual bureaucratic distractions, immersing yourself fully in the thrill of solving the case. Your keen eye and sharp mind are indispensable in cracking this captivating mystery!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waifu Club - Azumi</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2500780/Waifu_Club__Azumi/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2500780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2500780/extras/460x215.png?t=1708410358"><br/><br/>Waifu Club is a <strong>very addicting puzzle game</strong> in which you must solve puzzles of the lovey <strong>Azumi</strong>.<br/>Every awesome puzzle has 40 tiles.<br/><br/>The game has an <strong>amazing soundtrack</strong>, 8 levels of the beautiful Azumi in <strong>HD Quality</strong>.<br/>This said the game is a <strong>perfect way to relax </strong> from a hard day at work.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>8 levels of our beautiful girl Azumi<br/></li><li>Relaxing music and gameplay<br/></li><li>all images in high HD quality <br/></li><li>makes you forgot all your sorrows</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Modes</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Puzzle Mode<br/></li><li>Gallery Mode</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empyrean Swarm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2639910/Empyrean_Swarm/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embrace the power of your adaptable fighter, the lone survivor of your once-mighty fleet. In the midst of a relentless pursuit by a shadowy adversary, you'll feed off the energy of vanquished enemy vessels, desperately fighting to escape the ominous clutches of an enigmatic nemesis who hungers for dominion over not just your technology but your very flesh. <br/><br/>Conquer formidable boss battles while you surf the cosmic tides created by the wreckage of your alien foes. Evolve and strategize your path to supremacy by leveling up and making pivotal choices as you navigate a riveting narrative.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639910/extras/Empyrean_Swarm_Gameplay_Text.png?t=1708408533"><br/>Fight waves of enemies as you try to escape your doom. Gain experience to upgrade your ships weapons and powers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639910/extras/Adaption.gif?t=1708408533"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639910/extras/Empyrean_Swarm_Kill_Bosses_Text.png?t=1708408533"><br/>Kill tons of bosses and gain new powers and ship systems to help you survive and escape the alien threat!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639910/extras/Gain-Abilities_Tall.gif?t=1708408533"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639910/extras/Empyrean_Swarm_Void_Text.png?t=1708408533"><br/>Once you complete the campaign, step up to the global stage in an endless Rogue-like game type with tons of new enemies and abilities--rack up points and compete arcade-style against the world! Will you be the one to rise to the top?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639910/extras/The-Void_Tall.gif?t=1708408533"><br/><br/>Join the community and follow the game development in our discord!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIMMY'S AGONY</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2591130/JIMMYS_AGONY/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>JIMMY'S AGONY</strong> is a 2d beet em up game where you'll play as <strong>Tommy  JR</strong> in time between 1940's to 1960's, You'll play levels that help <strong>Tommy JR </strong>find something he want, it's against what he believe in, so will he do it, or not.<br/><br/>Enter through environments, from dark alleys and gang-infested streets to underground bunker. Engage in pulse-pounding battles against ruthless thugs, crime lords, and powerful bosses who will stop at nothing to stop <strong>Tommy </strong>From Reaching he's purpose.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591130/extras/TOMMY_SIT_CIGAR.png?t=1708422332"><h2 class="bb_tag">GAMEPLAY</h2><br/>With help of a companion show of your punching, crushing skills to <strong>Tommy's </strong>enemies with hand, leg, and air attacks, and even grab and throw them to show them who is the boss.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystic Guardians Slide</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2832820/Mystic_Guardians_Slide/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2832820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Instructions:</strong><br/><br/>Mystic Guardian Slide is a game in slide puzzle style. Solve Puzzles with enchanted creatures!<br/>Uncover the magic puzzles.<br/>Join enchanted animals, each dressed in a unique and magical way!<br/><br/><br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/><br/>Different dressed style animals<br/>Puzzles<br/>Gallery<br/>HD quality pictures<br/>Nice relaxing music						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
