<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Spell Disk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2292060/Spell_Disk/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Spell Disk is a rogue-lite action game with a unique synergy building mechanic so that your runs can never be the same. Strategize and create your own spell combo synergies to blast through enemies on your way! Each run is unique, so you must plan out how to build your power.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/extras/combo_paper.gif?t=1709316039"><br/>Discover combos and synergies that no one’s seen before! Maximize your power to better your chance of escaping the dungeon of Spell Disk.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/extras/Items_Updated.gif?t=1709316039"><br/>Craft spells, disks, and artifacts during your run that synergies with each other in their own ways.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/extras/Lobby_Updated.gif?t=1709316039"><br/>Unlock new weapons and powers to hack and slash through the enemies blocking your way.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vivaland: Dream House</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2606170/Vivaland_Dream_House/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2606170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1976830" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1976830</a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2606170/extras/ezgif-3-474fd0310c.gif?t=1709314012"><h2 class="bb_tag">Introducing the Vivaland Prologue: Dream House</h2><strong>Build Mode: Craft Your Dreams</strong><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in one of the core game modes of Vivaland: the Build Mode. It's a sandbox where you have control over architectural and design elements, enabling you to construct and decorate a house from the ground up!<br/><br/><strong>Get to Know the First Town of Vivaland</strong><br/><br/>The town of Vivaland offers 8 residential lots, each awaiting your personal touch. Claim your slice of the town, visit your friends' properties, and collaborate on grand projects that will redefine the neighborhood.<br/><br/><strong>Seamless Single and Co-op Experience</strong><br/><br/>Begin your Vivaland adventure either as a lone explorer or with your friends by your side – the choice is yours. You can build together with up to 8 players<br/><strong>Content</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Walls Toolkit:</strong> Build with single wall, curved wall and the room tool!<br/></li><li><strong>Doors &amp; Windows:</strong> Choose entrances and views that reflect your taste.<br/></li><li><strong>Foundations, Multiple Floors, and Stairs: </strong>Build structures that rise to new heights.<br/></li><li><strong>Furniture:</strong> Design with a vast selection of interior items.<br/></li><li><strong>Roofing:</strong> Choose from 10 distinct styles and an array of roof patterns.<br/></li><li><strong>Different styles of items:</strong>  Bohemian, Retro, Victorian, Antique, Cottagecore, Gothic, Modern, Minimalist, Industrial.</li></ul><br/><strong>Functional Freedom</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Resizable Objects:</strong> Adjusting the size of decorative objects.<br/></li><li><strong>Recolorable Furniture and Decor: </strong> Fine-tune your interior design with your color palettes. Save favorite shades and match your items.<br/></li><li><strong>Room Dimension Flexibility: </strong>Tweak the height and width of your rooms.<br/></li><li><strong>Grid Function: </strong>Precise item placement is a breeze with toggleable grid support.<br/></li><li><strong>Intuitive Controls and Snapping: </strong>Seamlessly move and arrange objects.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUARDS!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2514460/GUARDS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/4playerchaos.png?t=1709330868"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/chaosgif.gif?t=1709330868"><h2 class="bb_tag">1-4 PLAYER CO-OP</h2>Work together as a team and fight your way through the wretched streets of New Alestead. You will need to rely on your teammates if you are going to make out of the city alive.<h2 class="bb_tag">LIGHTNING FAST ACTION</h2>New Alestead has a disease... and you are the cure! Dispense justice quickly and thoroughly because these criminals wont wait to attack you one at a time.<h2 class="bb_tag">EVERYTHING IS A WEAPON</h2>Sometimes you need to improvise! Use crates, barrels, planks, bits of door, arms, a variety of City Watch approved civility moderation tools or even your foot to bring criminals in dead or alive.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/scoutplanexecute.png?t=1709330868"><h2 class="bb_tag">MISSION DISPATCH</h2>It's not all City sanctioned murder and wanton property destruction, sometimes you actually need to arrest some people, secure contraband or escort important VIP's out of the city.<h2 class="bb_tag">ON STAKEOUT</h2>When you find the criminals hideout, you will be outnumbered and outgunned. Wait and watch from the shadows to observe enemy patrol patterns, gang composition and any environmental objects that you might be able to use to your advantage.<h2 class="bb_tag">NO PLAN SURVIVES FIRST CONTACT</h2>When it all kicks off you're going to have to think on your feet and coordinate with your partners. Just try to make sure you take out more bad guys than other officers in the process!<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/takebackcity.png?t=1709330868"><h2 class="bb_tag">A CITY RULED BY GANGS</h2>Three rival factions control the city. The Fogtoof Boyz, an Orc gang with a reputation for violence and destruction. The Commision, a band of rogue merchants whose lust for power put them on the wrong side of the law, and The Corpse Cult - an religious organization infecting the city by turning its followers into mindless zombies.<h2 class="bb_tag">FIND THE KINGPINS</h2>Each gang has a kingpin. Take out the kingpin, you take out the gang. You will have to work your way up the food chain in order to find the kingpins location and assault their hideout.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Brew Barons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1636710/The_Brew_Barons/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1636710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A tranquil world becomes ever more corrupt by the day, spoiled by a strong-armed pirate organization that forcefully impose their brewing monopoly over the lands. Armed with your own brewery and seaplane, it's up to you to explore, forage, craft, sell and deliver your handcrafted brews with aid from fellow pilots who've joined your cause to overthrow the corrupt pirate organization and restore peace.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1636710/extras/steamgif1a.gif?t=1709308740"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Assemble your plane from a variety of parts, each with their own traits.<br/></li><li>Chose your pilot and copilot of whom have strengths and weaknesses.<br/></li><li>Explore the world in search of ingredients to bring back to your brewery. </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1636710/extras/steamgif2.gif?t=1709308740"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Pick and choose which foraged ingredients to blend. <br/></li><li>Distill and/or Ferment, each producing a different outcome. <br/></li><li>Design and name your bottle to your liking.<br/></li><li>Design your very own bar to sell your brews and bring fame to your establishment!<br/></li><li>With fame comes special delivery orders from other bars to stock your brew </li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeeperRL</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/329970/KeeperRL/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/Peek-2018-11-28-09-43.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL is an ambitious dungeon simulator with roguelike and RPG elements. Take the role of an evil wizard and study the methods of black magic. Equip your minions and explore the world, murder innocent villagers and burn their homes. Build your dungeon, lay traps and prepare for an assault of angry heroes. <br/><br/>When you control your minions the game changes into a classic roguelike, with turn-based and very tactical combat. You can also play as an adventurer and assault dungeons made by you or other players.<h2 class="bb_tag">Dungeon management </h2>You will dig deep into the mountain and build dozens of rooms, corridors and traps. Your minions will train and produce weapons and armor. Prisoners will be tortured. You will research new technologies like alchemy, beast mutation and sorcery.<h2 class="bb_tag">Z-levels</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341">Develop your base across multiple floors by digging down into the earth or building up. Build fantastic dungeon designs or elaborate castles and towers.<h2 class="bb_tag">Roguelike mechanics </h2>The world is simulated on a very detailed level. Creatures use equipment and consumable items. There are dozens of special items, spells, attributes and special attacks. You can cut off heads and limbs and blind or poison your enemies. If you're not careful with fire, you can burn an entire forest or even your own dungeon.<h2 class="bb_tag">Large, procedurally generated maps </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-animated-gif-maker__2_.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL features a large, procedurally generated world. Explore dozens of locations, from small cottages and shops to major enemies dwelling in castles and dungeons. Uncover secrets, bring back great loot and prisoners back to your base in order to grow in power.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple playable factions</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/gif_keepers-ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>Play as a:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dark wizard researching black magic.<br/></li><li>White knight specialized in horses and angelic beings.<br/></li><li>Necromancer who crafts undead from the body parts of fallen enemies.<br/></li><li>Fragile colony of twelve dwarves.<br/></li><li>Goblin king searching for his lost wives.<br/></li><li>Collective of gnomes with a mechanized army.<br/></li><li>Lone adventurer focused on exploration.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Online map sharing </h2>KeeperRL offers the ability to download dungeons made by other players from Steam Workshop, and places them on your world map as enemies. See how others design their fortresses, fight with their minions, and steal their loot! After winning the game, you'll have the option to share your dungeon online as well.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Grindea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/269770/Secrets_of_Grindea/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/269770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Secrets of Grindea</i> is an old-school Action RPG with co-op support for up to 4 players. It is a tribute to and sometimes a parody of the old SNES games so many of us grew up with and loved! Journey through fantastical lands, and battle tons of different enemies and bosses in your quest for truth, friendship and, above all, finding the world's rarest treasures!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A rich world filled with 300+ unique, colorful characters and an engaging story to drive your journey forward.<br/></li><li>Co-op support for up to four players! Enjoy the entire storyline with your friends or call someone in to help with the more difficult challenges.<br/></li><li>Customization, customization, customization - design a character that represents you, then mix and match any of the 31 spells and skills across 9 different categories.<br/></li><li>30+ epic boss fights! Overgrown slimes, giant robots, mimics - we have it all!<br/></li><li>Side content - design your own home, fish, craft items, tame pets, partake in mini-games, grow plants - there’s plenty to keep you entertained when you want a break from the main story.</li></ul><br/>And last but not least:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Arcade Mode - Separate from Story Mode, the game includes a <strong>full roguelite</strong> version where you need to battle your way to the top on a single life, building a town of your own as you progress.  How far can you get?</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON BALL FighterZ</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/678950/DRAGON_BALL_FighterZ/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/extras/GIF_DBFZ_STEAM.png?t=1709230702"><br/><br/>DRAGON BALL FighterZ is born from what makes the DRAGON BALL series so loved and famous: endless spectacular fights with its all-powerful fighters.<br/><br/>Partnering with Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ maximizes high end Anime graphics and brings easy to learn but difficult to master fighting gameplay.<br/><br/>High-end Anime Graphics<br/>Using the power of the Unreal engine and the talented team at Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ is a visual tour-de-force.<br/><br/>3vs3 Tag/Support<br/>Build your dream team and sharpen your skills to master high-speed tag combinations.<br/><br/>Thrilling Online Features<br/>Ranked matches, interactive lobby, crazy 6-player Party Match... There is something for every taste!<br/><br/>Exclusive Story Mode<br/>Discover a never-seen-before scenario featuring Android 21, a brand new character whose creation was supervised by Akira Toriyama himself.<br/><br/>Spectacular Fights<br/>Experience aerial combos, destructible stages and famous scenes from the DRAGON BALL anime in 60FPS and 1080p resolution!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Godrop:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802550/GodropPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Prologue and the official version of the difference between<br/>Levels: one in the prologue, four in the official version<br/>Follow-up Program:<br/>The game will continue to update content after release, which includes:<br/>More bosses: different fighting styles and types of boss fights.<br/>More tech: weird and wacky tech combinations.<br/>More weapons: more basic weapons and weapon variants.<br/>More game modes: In addition to the basic level mode there will also be a survivor mode and parkour mode. </strong><br/><br/><strong>A special roguelike game that focuses entirely on ramming, piercing, and spraying as the core gameplay. You will play as Gotrop, a powerful unknown alien invasion weapon, facing the layers of barriers set up by the arrogant and ignorant humans in the solar system, using good movement and killing to steal the energy of human warships, driving our strong interaction force outer armor for invincible transformation, and destroying all the enemies in our way with incredible maneuverability and invulnerable ramming ability! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/y1.png?t=1709446521"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/1.gif?t=1709446521"><br/><strong>A combat system focused on energy. Just by being in motion you can generate a constant stream of energy, and mysterious alien technology also allows Gotrop to steal energy directly from his enemies. There is energy can be transformed into an invincible droplet state, invulnerable and unbreakable, our enemies can not cause any damage to us, but we can directly puncture the inside of their battleships havoc! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/y2.png?t=1709446521"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/2.gif?t=1709446521"><br/><strong>A large number of tech components have been beamed into the solar system, and Gotrop can access tech for morphing upgrades simply by cleaning up the battlefield! Whether it's a drill that can drill into enemy ships faster, outer armor that can reflect all attacks, or a spout that spews bullets, they can be acquired after sweeping through the enemy! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/y3.png?t=1709446521"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/3.gif?t=1709446521"><br/><strong>The solar system has been fortified by humans and is in crisis. Gotrop will break through layers of asteroids, energy stands and turret arrays until he completely destroys the human space fleet and takes over Earth! </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1709288144"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1709288144"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709288144"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1709288144"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1709288144"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1709288144"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1709288144"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1709288144"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1709288144"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709288144"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1709288144"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiritfall</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1835240/Spiritfall/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/PlatformFighterRoguelike.png?t=1709235442"><br/><strong>Spiritfall</strong> combines tight Platform Fighter combat, smooth movement, and Roguelite mechanics into one! Trek across dangerous lands, string together deadly combos to fend off swarms of enemies, and harness an ever-changing set of powers through a randomly generated map. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/SynergiesAwait.png?t=1709235442"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/GIFDivineSynergiesQuality.gif?t=1709235442"><br/>The divine spirits offer powerful blessings that enhance your abilities in combat. Discover your favorite abilities, and experiment with different builds. With over 150+ blessings to choose from, these gifts allow for a range of tactical approaches that encourage you to find synergies that fit your playstyle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/StrongerFromDefeat.png?t=1709235442"><br/>Death is but a temporary setback. Reawaken stronger than before at the Sanctum and continue your adventure. Use the resources you gathered to upgrade your skills, unlock unique powers, and awaken mighty weapons with unique movesets.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/Community.png?t=1709235442"><br/>A heartfelt thank you to our Early Access community! Your feedback has been invaluable during Spiritfall's development, helping make the game what it is today. We invite you to keep shaping our world together. Connect with fellow players on Discord and get the latest news by joining our newsletter.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minami Lane</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678990/Minami_Lane/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Minami Lane is a small, wholesome management game set on a Japanese-inspired street. Create and manage your own street, make sure everyone is happy, and watch the villagers live their lives! Enjoy 2 to 4 hours of playtime, cute tanukis and lots of cats!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/Gameplay.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/><i><strong>Build your street</strong></i><br/>Build homes to add villagers to your street, then improve their happiness by beautifying every inch and building a variety of shops &amp; attractions! These include ramen shops, boba cafes, bookstores and more, each with unique inventories and effects.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Building.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/><i><strong>Manage your shops</strong></i><br/>Attract customers with everything from floral bouquets to karaoke! Shops you create will need your careful guidance to offer the right products at the right prices. Lead them to success and make your neighborhood thrive.<br/><br/><i><strong>Watch your villagers live their lives</strong></i><br/>Once you start the day, you'll get to see each villager react to your street and offer helpful feedback on how to improve! Memorize their preferences and refine your street the following day.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Review.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/><i><strong>Reach your objectives</strong></i><br/>Complete missions to unlock new levels with more buildings, villager types, and other surprises.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/Features.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>What Minami Lane offers:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>2-4 hours of play time<br/></li><li>Create and customize your own adorable street<br/></li><li>Manage shops by adjusting their inventory, recipes, and prices<br/></li><li>Play strategically to complete each level's mission objectives<br/></li><li>Keep the streets clean by picking up trash<br/></li><li>Tanukis and cats!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Ramen.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>What Minami Lane does not offer:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hardcore strategy<br/></li><li>Multiplayer<br/></li><li>Tons of missions<br/></li><li>New levels after release</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/GameModes.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>In Minami Lane's missions, you'll need to strategically plan each day and use random events to your advantage to complete multiple objectives. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Bike.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>The sandbox mode focuses on creativity and relaxation, allowing you to immerse yourself in the peaceful, cozy world without the stress of objectives.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/DevTeam.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>Minami Lane is the collaborative effort of Dorian (Doot), Doriane (Blibloop) and Antoine (Zakku). Doot, a former data scientist turned game developer, brings light strategy and management gameplay, while Blibloop breathes life into the isometric world with her Studio Ghibli-inspired, hand-drawn designs. Zakku adds the finishing touches with joyful, wholesome music compositions and soundscape. We really hope you will enjoy this tiny game we made with love 💕<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678990/Minami_Lane/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678990/Minami_Lane/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR WARS™: Dark Forces Remaster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2292260/STAR_WARS_Dark_Forces_Remaster/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_8.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/><i>Star Wars</i>™: Dark Forces Remaster has been brought to life by the team at <strong>Nightdive Studios</strong>, fully remastered through its proprietary KEX engine, allowing the game to run on modern gaming devices at up to 4K resolution at 120FPS. New and returning players will enjoy <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces Remaster’s upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<br/><br/>The original 1995 <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces raised the bar for FPS games, offering players a significant degree of movement and interactivity, a large selection of items and power-ups, and engaging environments. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_10.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/>In the first <i>Star Wars</i> FPS video game, players assume the role of Kyle Katarn, a defector of the Galactic Empire turned mercenary for hire. Katarn joins the Rebel Alliance’s covert operations division tasked with infiltrating the Galactic Empire, where he discovers the secret Dark Trooper Project. The development of this powerful new series of Imperial battle droids and power-armored stormtroopers stands to strengthen the Empire’s grip on the galaxy unless Katarn and the Rebel Alliance intervene.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>All fourteen original levels, featuring <i>Star Wars</i>™ worlds and capital ships<br/></li><li>Use your ability to jump, duck, and crawl to solve puzzles and defeat enemies<br/></li><li>Your Personal Digital Assistant provides you with in game information such including map, inventory, and mission briefing<br/></li><li>Engaging first-person ground combat featuring ten weapons and twenty types of enemies<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS visuals<br/></li><li>Advanced 3D rendering enables updated lighting and atmospheric effects<br/></li><li>Modern gamepad support adds a new weapon wheel, and rumble<br/></li><li>Controller Support - vibration and gyro controls <br/></li><li>A variety of power-ups are made available to the player, including health, shields, weapons and ammunition<br/></li><li>For combat, the player may use fists, explosive landmines and thermal detonators, as well as blasters and other ranged weapons<br/></li><li>Includes immersive environmental puzzles and mazes </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_1.gif?t=1709278523"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shashingo: Learn Japanese with Photography</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1632490/Shashingo_Learn_Japanese_with_Photography/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Explore bright, fictional Japanese streets filled with details and interesting objects to capture with your camera. Each photograph you take will translate the name of the content into Japanese and English so you can learn with your surroundings.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/extras/Shashingo_Take_Photo.gif?t=1709246737"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A stylised, approachable 3D environment<br/></li><li>In-game photography system<br/></li><li>Japanese audio<br/></li><li>Photo album to store your flash cards<br/></li><li>A game mode that tests your memory<br/></li><li>Beginner phrases and grammar lessons<br/></li><li>Day/Night and weather cycle<br/></li><li>Display romaji, kana, furigana <i>(recommended)</i> or kanji</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/extras/Shashingo_Flash_Cards.png?t=1709246737"><h2 class="bb_tag">Create Stunning Photography Based Flashcards</h2>Every photo flash-card you take will be unique to you. The idea behind this is to strengthen the relationship between a word and how you see its physical appearance. In the real world, you can then see such objects and make connections to the Japanese words you've already learned while playing Shashingo.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/extras/Shashingo_Photo_Album.png?t=1709246737"><h2 class="bb_tag">Track Your Progress in the Photo Album</h2>Your photo album is where you keep your collection of Photo Flash-Cards. If you remember them well in Find Mode, they'll be separated into the 'mastered' tab and shown with a gold star sticker. However, if you're struggling to remember a word in Find Mode, they'll be marked with a purple exclamation mark sticker, so you know which words you need to practice more.<br/>You can also mark your favourite words &amp; images with a cute little heart sticker to add them to your favourites page.<br/><br/>At the back of your in-game photo album, there are numerous pages of Japanese lessons designed for beginners that will teach you how to speak Japanese and use the vocabulary that you learn in Shashingo. Also included are some key words and important phrases that can help you in your future conversations.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dicefolk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1996430/Dicefolk/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FtN3yxBv4tq" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Join_Our_Discord_600x224.png?t=1709379465"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Dicefolk is a tactical roguelite game based on customizable dice and monster-catching mechanics. On your adventure as a Chimera Summoner, you'll meet dozens of unique and powerful creatures that you can recruit to create the perfect team.<br/><br/>Play as Alea, a young Dicefolk hero who discovers her ability to befriend Chimera and fight back against evil forces threatening humanity’s extinction.</strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Battle_Start.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H2.png?t=1709379465"><br/>Embark on a thrilling quest to save humanity from the grasp of an evil sorcerer. Build a team from over 100 unique, hand-drawn Chimera to suit your playstyle. Unlock all the talismans to uncover the mystical secrets behind the Chimeras’ existence.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Map.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H3.png?t=1709379465"><br/>With a large variety of Chimeras to befriend and command, you'll need to strategize and adapt your playstyle to suit each battle. From tough tanks to speedy attackers, each Chimera brings a unique set of abilities to the table. Your tactical choices will determine your success in battle!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Recruiting.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H4.png?t=1709379465"><br/>It’s all up to you! Customize your dice for maximum influence over your Chimeras’ attacks and abilities. Control the order in which battles play out and choose when parties take action. Dicefolk defies RNG and gives you unprecedented influence on the roll of the dice! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Battle.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H5.png?t=1709379465"><br/>Each playthrough offers its own rewards, and the Chimeras you encounter in one run can be entirely different than those you find in another. With different Chimeras comes different strategies to assemble your team for the perfect run!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Anim_H5.gif?t=1709379465"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Dino Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_12" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🦖🐾 WELCOME TO 100 DINO CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🦕🐈</h2>🦎 Join the cutest adventure in the Dino park with Cats and Dinos! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of dinosaurs location and dino-cats as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/600x200.png?t=1709146681"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Dino Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815640/100_Dino_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=DinoCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Extra.png?t=1709146681"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816050/100_Dino_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=DinoCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709146681"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815630/100_Dino_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=DinoCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709146681"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/600x1.png?t=1709146681"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709146681"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803010/100_Robo_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803010/100_Robo_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815640/100_Dino_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815640/100_Dino_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709485776"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709485776"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709485776"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709485776"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709485776"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solium Infernum</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1893810/Solium_Infernum/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare yourself for Solium Infernum, the grand strategy game of politics, intrigue and betrayal, set in the ultimate arena of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingDarkSide2.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_IndulgeYourDarkSide_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Satan's mysteriously vanished and Hell is in an uproar. Play as one of eight all-powerful and menacing Archfiends and indulge your Machiavellian dark side. Command legions, enlist champions, cast sinister rituals, and trick, rob, and insult your rivals to be crowned Hell’s new Dark Majesty.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingStrategy2.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_StrategyFromHell_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Experience Solium Infernum's legendary devilish political machinations. Requiring nerves of steel and a true heart of darkness, every order you give will have lasting consequences. Get into the minds of your rivals, second-guessing their every move both on the map and on the floor of Hell’s parliament as you sling insults and demands in the only truly political strategy game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Eight playable Archfiends<br/></li><li>Eight single-player Chronicles<br/></li><li>Single-player Skirmish mode<br/></li><li>Revelations Tutorial Scenario<br/></li><li>Sessional and Asynchronous 2-6 player Multiplayer<br/></li><li>Dozens of Infernal Legions, including unique enormous Titans. <br/></li><li>Champion Praetors and dark Artifacts fit for any Archfiend!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingMulitplayer.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_InfernalMultiplayer_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Play 2-6 player multiplayer games with your soon-to-be ex-friends in a single session of deceit and politics, or put your friendships to the test in quick daily bursts with Solium Infernum’s infamous asynchronous multiplayer for a truly harrowing scheme-in-your-sleep experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/Heading_DarkArt2.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_DivineMadness_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>If you love dark art, you’re in the right place. Brimming with striking visions of Hell unlike anything you’ve seen before, Solium Infernum is an infernal feast for the eyes with multitudes of individual dark paintings to enjoy. Every item of the game is accompanied by mind-blasting artwork, a feat declaring Solium Infernum a winner of the 2022 Game Makers Sketchbook.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingRessurect.gif?t=1708670283"><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_CultClassic_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Originally inspired by Milton’s epic poem, Paradise Lost, League of Geeks’ (known for seminal digital board game Armello) sophomore title is a re-imagining and modernisation of Vic Davis’ critically acclaimed cult-classic of the same name, hailed as a masterpiece of strategy game design. <br/><br/>Once again, prepare to lose yourself within ‘the cold glory of a difficult decision’ as we resurrect Solium Infernum from the depths of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/label_praise.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Note: The following quotes refer to the original Solium Infernum (2009) by Vic Davis.<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum is a political wargame set in hell… The game is now finished, and none of the friends survived. By which I mean, we all hate each other now.”</i> <br/>- Rock Paper Shotgun<br/><br/><i>“It’s a game about playing other people, in both senses of the word…. This is game design based on psychology as much as rules.” </i><br/>- Quarter to Three<br/><br/><i>“More than any game I've played in years, Solium Infernum nails the sensation of staring at a screen and losing yourself in the cold glory of a difficult decision.”</i><br/>- Game Developer (formerly Gamasutra)<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum kicked my knees out from under me ... this game took my past experience with strategy games and threw it, like a pro basketball player, into a bin eighty feet away.”</i><br/>- Eurogamer<br/><br/><i>“One of the best games of the year.”</i><br/>— Three Moves Ahead<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_toReign.png?t=1708670283"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruindog:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802430/RuindogPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 4 are available in the official version.<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 4 in the official version<br/>Weapons: 3 in the prologue, 26 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/11z.jpg?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>A long, long time ago, in a solar system not so far away, alien bugs invaded Earth, but they were soon beaten back home, and by the way, their home planet was blown up. After centuries of being invincible, it became popular for humans to watch live alien hunting shows, participate in alien hunts, save up money, equipment, and use the various loot they found to keep going to new maps and defeating more powerful enemies. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1y.png?t=1708706298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1z.gif?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>Enemies will come at you from all sides on every level, proceed with caution or you'll be torn to pieces in an instant</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3y.png?t=1708706298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3z.gif?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>Each character has a different growth path and active skills, utilize these skills and choose the most appropriate item for the current hero to achieve the mission objective</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5y.png?t=1708706298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5z.gif?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>Earn more resources and achieve various mission objectives to unlock different maps/difficulties and even new map mechanics!<br/>Each map has very different mission objectives and combat mechanics, so choose the one that better suits the current mechanic to win the game</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kneedle Knight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2491720/Kneedle_Knight/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Kneedle Knight</i> is a third-person, puzzle platformer game developed by students at SMU Guildhall Cohort 32. In <i>Kneedle Knight</i>, the player controls a mouse knight that uses his magical needle to sew fabric which he can merge into, moving back and forth between 3D and 2D. <br/><br/>Sir Lukoss the Small was a noble knight sent on a quest to defeat the evil Witch of Fabric. The Witch, using her enchanted fabric, imprisoned and transformed many citizens and knights into malicious fabrications. Sir Lukoss climbed up through her fortress to put an end to her tyranny, only to be hexed by her magic and transformed into a mouse. In the dark dungeon of the Witch’s lair, the mouse finds a magic needle, granting him special powers to sew fabric of his own and merge in and out of the enchanted threadwork. <br/><br/>Now Sir Lukoss must use his newfound weapon to sew his path forward and up through the evil stronghold. The mouse knight can use his needle to solve puzzles, overcome challenging obstacles, and defeat the animated candle minions of the Witch. All with the hopes of returning to face the Witch of Fabric yet again to finish his noble quest.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Single-player, puzzle platformer game<br/></li><li>Playtime (main story): 1-2 hours<br/></li><li>Playtime (100% achievements): 2 hours<br/></li><li>Steam leaderboard support for level speed running<br/></li><li>Made in Unreal Engine 5<br/></li><li>Original soundtrack</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myth of Empires</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1371580/Myth_of_Empires/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Embark Upon a Thrilling Journey</h2>Explore a land with diverse landscapes, ecologies, and weather, as well as a realistic day/night cycle. The v1.0 release of Myth of Empires also features a new map – Dongzhou Island, offering new adventures and challenges.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/11111探索之旅，发现新世界的惊险旅程.gif?t=1709470230"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Own Empire From the Ground Up</h2>Myth of Empires features sandbox gameplay with a high degree of freedom; the game has 1300+ different crafting recipe, allowing you to build your own empire. The v1.0 release adds new recipes, including mechanical tools and base defenses, as well as a new planting system. The possibilities are endless.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/2【替换Gif】自由创造，打造你的帝国.gif?t=1709470230"><h2 class="bb_tag">Recruit NPCs, Tame Wildlife</h2>In-depth taming and training systems allow players to recruit or subdue additional forces to aid them in combat and production. The v1.0 release adds new boss NPCs and powerful beasts. In addition, smaller types of animals can be used to help power your base’s defenses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/333333驯服万物，NPC、马匹与野生动物.gif?t=1709470230"><h2 class="bb_tag">Wage Epic Wars on Ancient Battlefields</h2> Myth of Empires features hundreds of different weapons, armor, and large-scale engineering equipment. Pick the weapons that best suit your playstyle, or utilize your strategic capabilities to build an army. The v1.0 release introduces powerful mechanical base defenses, wooden oxen, and other new combat equipment to further enrich the game’s deep war experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/4【替换Gif】史诗战争体验，挑战百变的古代战场.gif?t=1709470230"><h2 class="bb_tag">Engage in Cross-server Battles </h2>Establish administrative regions, fight for the position of county magistrate, and compete to expand your territory through Fortress Battles. Craft the perfect guild and utilize your diplomatic prowess to ensure its long-term stability.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/555555跨服征战，共同创造历史.gif?t=1709470230"><h2 class="bb_tag">Write Your Own Legend </h2>With 25 different development paths, a 16-level title system, and more than 100 achievements, you have complete freedom in growing your character. Become a legendary military commander, or content yourself with the life of a simple farmer – the choice is yours.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/6【替换Gif】传奇生涯，定制独特的人生.gif?t=1709470230"><h2 class="bb_tag">Play Multiple Gameplay Modes Offering Endless Possibilities </h2>Myth of Empires supports official servers, custom servers, as well as solo and hosted modes. Creative players are also able to use the game’s robust mod editor to tailor the game to their dream experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/no7多样玩法.gif?t=1709470230"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Epoch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/899770/Last_Epoch/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Epoch combines time travel, exciting dungeon crawling, engrossing character customization and endless replayability to create an Action RPG for veterans and newcomers alike. Travel through the world of Eterra’s past and face dark empires, wrathful gods and untouched wilds – to find a way to save time itself from The Void.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Gameplay.gif?t=1709060046"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>15 Mastery Classes</strong><br/>Embark on your adventure as one of five powerful classes and, through your journey, ascend into a unique Mastery Class that unlocks more specialized abilities and build-options. <br/></li><li><strong>120+ Skill Trees</strong><br/>Every skill has its own augment tree that will allow you to control, alter, and empower your playstyle. Transform your skeletons into archers, your lightning blast into chain lightning, or make your serpent strike summon snakes to fight alongside you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Nodes.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Hunt Rare &amp; Powerful Loot</strong><br/>Fill your arsenal with magic items that you may craft to perfection, change the rules of your build with powerful unique and set items, and always have that next upgrade just on the horizon with Last Epoch's deep and randomized loot system.<br/></li><li><strong>Rewarding Crafting System</strong><br/>The items you wield are yours to forge! Last Epoch’s community-revered crafting system allows you to control your character's power progression, featuring robust and deterministic upgrade mechanics.<br/></li><li><strong>Uncover the Past, Reforge the Future</strong><br/>Travel to different moments of time where you will discover the many factions and secrets that exist within the world of Eterra and fight to set the timeline onto a new path.<br/></li><li><strong>Endless replayability</strong><br/>With a wealth of classes and skills to customize, deep game systems, randomized loot, and continuing development, Last Epoch is a game that will keep you coming back for years to come.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Monolith.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Easy to Learn, Hard to Master</strong><br/>We’re committed to making gameplay approachable for new and veteran players alike by allowing you to jump into the fray quickly and providing many in-game resources. Though don’t be fooled, Eterra has many dangers waiting for you that require a mastery of combat and build-crafting.<br/></li><li><strong>Zero Pay-To-Win</strong><br/>Last Epoch will never offer gameplay advantages by being able to spend real money. We believe in creating a fair environment for all players. </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminator: Dark Fate - Defiance</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1839950/Terminator_Dark_Fate__Defiance/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif1.gif?t=1709216510"><br/><strong>Terminator: Dark Fate – Defiance</strong> is a <strong>real-time strategy game</strong> based on the Terminator: Dark Fate universe that follows the war between humanity and Legion's synthetic intelligent machine network.<br/><br/>In the<strong> single-player campaign</strong>, you take the role of a commander in the Founders, a force made up of the remnants of the US military and guide your army in an attempt to foil Legion's plan to exterminate the last remnants of humanity. In skirmish and multiplayer modes, play as three very diverse factions: Founders, Movement and Legion.<br/><br/>Take control of an army carried over from mission to mission on a series of large strategic maps. Make decisions about unit placement, battle tactics and abilities so that you don’t just survive but can become the leader of the resistance against the machines. Hone your skills and military expertise by replaying and achieving the best possible outcomes.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic battlefields: realistic tactics and consequences</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif2.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>Engage in complex, realistic battles where your <strong>tactical decisions</strong> are vital to your survival and ultimate victory. Use a variety of military equipment, vehicles and ammunition types in your battles against the enemy. Recruit and train new units, assign new skills and acquire new weapons and equipment to continue the resistance.<br/><br/>Encounter tense battles. Your battlefield tactics and choices have deep consequences that will impact through the campaign, with other factions and characters either joining you or fighting against you, and with certain missions being available or not depending on your actions. <br/><br/><strong>Your resources are limited</strong> and you must protect your army. Weapons of war receive damage through a modular component damage system where armour characteristics, component malfunctions and hull structure all affect if your troops survive.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Lead the survival of mankind</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif3.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>Recruit others to your cause and <strong>grow your army</strong>. Mix and match the composition of your troops to fit your preferred battle tactics. Use infantry units, heavy armoured military vehicles, plasma cannon technology, drones and other flying units and even human skirmishers to achieve victory.<br/><br/>Use the battlefield to your advantage! <strong>Physics-based building demolition</strong> lets you generate a realistic set of tactical consequences, especially in urban areas.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer Mayhem: Skirmish and Online Battles</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif4.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>The excitement amplifies in <strong>skirmish and multiplayer modes</strong>, where <strong>you can play as three distinct factions</strong>: Founders, Movement, and Legion. <br/><br/>Engage in epic battles across vast strategic landscapes, testing your skills and military expertise. Every decision matters, impacting alliances, missions, and the overall survival of mankind.<br/><br/>Challenge your skills in skirmish and online multiplayer matches, facing off against AI or real-life human opponents in intense 1v1 and 2v2 battles.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2379780/Balatro/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Balatro is a poker-inspired roguelike deck builder all about creating powerful synergies and winning big.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Endless_Possibility.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/>Combine valid poker hands with unique Joker cards in order to create varied synergies and builds. Earn enough chips to beat devious blinds, all while uncovering hidden bonus hands and decks as you progress. You’re going to need every edge you can get in order to reach the boss blind, beat the final ante and secure victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Jokers_Clean_Thin.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The definitive poker roguelike experience.<br/></li><li>Endless possibilities - every pick-up, discard and joker can dramatically alter the course of your run.<br/></li><li>In-depth campaign mode complete with 8 difficulties, as well as challenge, daily and seeded runs. </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Break_The_Game.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/>Deftly deploy an array of potent tools: different Decks, Jokers, Tarot cards, Planet cards, Spectral cards, and Vouchers. Use these versatile instruments to ignite a combo frenzy and turbocharge your poker hands, crafting electrifying, adrenaline-fueled synergies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro_5_Aces_GIF__HQ_.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 Jokers, each with their own unique abilities<br/></li><li>15 Decks with distinct modifiers to choose from for each run<br/></li><li>5 potential variants of each Joker which add further abilities<br/></li><li>22 Tarot cards variants that can enhance your regular playing cards<br/></li><li>11 Planet cards that help level up your possible poker hands<br/></li><li>32 Voucher cards to help provide permanent buffs for your current run</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Find_Your_Flow.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in Balatro’s distinctive psychedelic world. Let the synthwave soundtrack wash over you -  wind down, escape the daily grind and prepare to enter the ultimate roguelike flow state.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improve your collection and discover new cards and secrets with every single run.<br/></li><li>Make use of the in-depth stats screen to study your best hands, most used Jokers, and more!<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the CRT fuzz and enjoy detailed, hand-crafted pixel art.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Spectral_Pack.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F5mH3dNhjx2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro-join_the_discord.png?t=1709312324"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please, Touch The Artwork 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2600140/Please_Touch_The_Artwork_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Disclaimer:</strong><i> This is a short game made in</i> <strong>6 months</strong><i>. It's</i> <strong>100% FREE</strong><i>(no ads, no dlc's), made by a </i><strong>solo dev</strong><i> in honour of James Ensor’s 75 year remembrance.</i> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/extras/Steam3DRoomGIF_Wide.gif?t=1708975190"><br/><br/>Touch the artwork and help a lost skeleton artist find its way home in a surreal, hand-painted universe. <br/><br/>Collect hidden objects for its quirky inhabitants, solve casual puzzles, and restore cracks in the fabric of the paintings. <br/><br/>This slow paced relaxing adventure was carefully crafted from works by James Ensor, a Belgian pioneer in the world of Modern Art.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Hidden object adventure<br/></li><li>5 unique worlds<br/></li><li>Hints when stuck<br/></li><li>Casual point &amp; click gameplay<br/></li><li>Zoom-in for extra details<br/></li><li>Real hand-painted art<br/></li><li>Atmospheric relaxing sound<br/></li><li>Silly and quirky<br/></li><li>Slow-paced &amp; relaxing<br/></li><li>Fit for ages 12-99</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Small Mazes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2570630/20_Small_Mazes/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2570630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a puzzle game with twenty small mazes. If you solve the mazes, you beat the game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>It's about 1-2 hours long, maybe.<br/></li><li>You need a keyboard and mouse to play it. One person played through the whole game on the Steam Deck, but I tried it and think it's better on PC.<br/></li><li> A few puzzles require knowledge of English. No puzzle requires sound or audio to solve it. No puzzle requires being able to recognize different colors.</li></ul> <br/>I hope you enjoy it. <br/> 						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonder</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692570/Sonder/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Local Co-op requires a gamepad controller for both players. Online Co-op supports mouse and keyboard. </i><h2 class="bb_tag">Psychological narrative </h2>- After a mass-scale destruction of all artificial intelligence, a scrapped robot and soul form an unexpected friendship. After a mysterious train knocks them out, they wake up in a world shaped by their own thoughts. Will they be able to cooperate and escape this dark reality?<h2 class="bb_tag">Immersive atmosphere </h2>- Immerse yourself in an atmospheric world crafted with a stylish, minimalistic approach that captivates your attention and enhances the shared adventure. Unleash the power of collaboration, confront existential mysteries, and embark on a gaming journey like no other.<h2 class="bb_tag">Collaboration </h2>- Work together - succeed together. Each character has unique abilities that allow them to manipulate the world in their own way, meaning they can only proceed if they cooperate. In combat, maximum efficiency can be achieved by combining the player’s powers, allowing them to neutralize the most dangerous of foes.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708702172"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708702172"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider I-III Remastered Starring Lara Croft</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2478970/Tomb_Raider_IIII_Remastered_Starring_Lara_Croft/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2478970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover Lara Croft’s Original Adventures, Lovingly Restored</h2> <br/>Play the Original Three Tomb Raider Adventures: For the first time ever, play the complete experience with all expansions and secret levels on modern platforms in this definitive collection.<h2 class="bb_tag">Included Game Titles</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tomb Raider I + Unfinished Business<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider II + Golden Mask<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider III + The Lost Artifact</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><strong>Solve Ancient Mysteries</strong>: Uncover treasures of the ancient world by solving puzzles and unraveling mysteries lost to the ravages of time.<br/><br/><strong>Globe-trotting Adventure</strong>: Follow Lara Croft around the world and face off against deadly foes and dangerous myths.<br/><br/><strong>Lovingly Restored</strong>: Experience the classics boasting upgraded graphics, with the option to switch to the original polygon look at any time.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1708019001"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal Richards (formerly of Echos)</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1708019001"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about the future of Sheepy, limited edition merch and more.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruction</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2774240/Instruction/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2774240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2774240/extras/Aboutdevelopment.png?t=1706909482"><br/><br/>Instruction is a story based clicker game where you, an employee of a power plant, are tasked with generating power for your city. The powerplant's built in intelligence mentor program, or I.M.P. for short, will help you generate the necessary amount of voltage to fulfill your quota. I.M.P may have developed a little too much of a personality for the powerplant's liking, but don't worry! It's still more than capable of keeping you on track. <br/><br/>In this game you'll be tasked with using different systems to generate power. Each system works differently and can be upgraded to increase your efficiency. Discover each of the power plant's mechanisms, and uncover the story behind your less than friendly companion. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2774240/extras/Gamefeatures.png?t=1706909482"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 300 unique lines of dialogue<br/></li><li>5 different systems to generate power<br/></li><li>Secrets and hidden interactions</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2774240/extras/Aboutdevelopment.png?t=1706909482"><br/><br/>This game was developed as a student project at DigiPen Institute of Technology and was created for educational purposes only. Please check out our publisher page for more information.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788630/Nothing_Together/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play together. Maybe.<br/><br/>Just do Nothing as the timer goes up and climb the leaderboards. If you do Something, you lose.<br/><br/>Play in <strong>Together </strong>mode, where up to 20 players unite to do Nothing, or compete with other players in <strong>Battle Royale</strong> to find out who's the best at doing Nothing!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typing of the Undead</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/897900/Typing_of_the_Undead/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/897900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In a world filled with Zombies, the last survivor of a Spec Ops squad tries to survive,<br/>and make his way through Hordes of Zombies to reach his final destination.<h2 class="bb_tag">OVERVIEW</h2><br/>Typing of the Undead is a Typing Zombie Survival Zombie Experience game.<br/>Play in Handcrafted game levels utilizing stylized graphics. <br/>Type as fast as you can and try to keep yourself alive for as much as possible.<br/>Be fast and accurate with your typing to keep your combos high and increase the points that you earn.<br/>Use the points that you earned to buy upgrades to die less and unlock new weapons.<h2 class="bb_tag">CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</h2><br/>Choose between 52 different heads and 30 different skins to customize your character.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/897900/extras/character_customization.gif?t=1709545378"><h2 class="bb_tag">UPGRADES</h2><br/>Upgrade your character by purchasing upgrades with the points that you earned during playing. Purchase Body armor to die harder and different weapons with unique upgrades of their own.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/897900/extras/upgrades.gif?t=1709545378"><h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>5 different difficulty levels to play with, a harder difficulty level awards more points.<br/></li><li>A lot of Different Zombies to keep the game interesting.<br/></li><li>10 Unique hand-crafted maps to play with utilizing stylized graphics.<br/></li><li>Unique Bosses to make your life harder.<br/></li><li>Statistics and Typing Statistics (Kills, Waves Survived, Combos, Time Survived, Wpm (Words Per Minute), Words Typed, Letters Typed, Total Errors, and more..)<br/></li><li>Multiple Language Support for the UI (English, French, Italian, German, Spanish, Russian, Chinese, Greek)<br/></li><li>Steam integrated - Keep your Score and Stats safe with your Steam profile.<br/></li><li>Steam Achievements<br/></li><li>Custom Dictionary<br/></li><li>Color Blindness support <br/></li><li>Hand Placement guide.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silent Cause</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776800/Silent_Cause/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<u>Short, story and exploration based, single-player horror</u> where you are trying to find out what happened to family. While police found no cause from outside or from within family. While case has been closed it started drawing all sorts of people from ghost hunters to private investigators, you are one of them. Find what actually happened behind disappearance and sudden appearance of family by finding notes and clues that people left and try to uncover the mystery behind the murder while someone watching is coming closer and closer. Armed only with flashlight try to light up dark rooms that are long abandoned. It is up to you to end the story with knowing what actually happened or let questions stay unanswered.<br/><br/><br/><strong><i>STORY RICH</i></strong><br/><br/>Uncover the story behind sudden disappearance of family and find clues that people left behind and make puzzling questions answered. Police found nothing so people like you go and try to find anything that could help with the case but they also found nothing, you will come here as any other but for you there is dark secret to uncover. Are you ready to handle truth? <br/><br/><strong><i>ENVIROMENT RICH</i></strong><br/><br/>Explore while you go after tracks of lost people while exploring rooms which are leading you their own way meanwhile you try to make way through them which is not always as straightfoward as it seems.<br/><br/><br/><strong><i><u>FIND CLUES</u></i></strong><br/><strong><i><u>MAKE YOUR WAY THROUGH LOCKED ROOMS</u></i></strong><br/><strong><i><u>UNCOVER MYSTERY</u></i></strong><br/><strong><i><u>EXPLORE DIFFERENT SETS OF ROOMS AND STYLES</u></i></strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afterworld</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2839720/Afterworld/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2839720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join the realm of Afterworld.<br>
<br>
Help the spirits of the Afterworld, and get rewards for completing quests.<br>
<br>
Combat other inflicted spirits that are causing destruction and mayhem all over Afterworld.<br>
<br>
Save hidden animals and let them join your team, each with with their own unique skills and mystics.<br/>
<br/>
Equip different weapons which each change the fighting style of your character.<br/>
<br/>
The game was made on RPG maker and uses it's combat system, but with some differences from your average "Take-Turn" combat.<br/>
<br/>
Play this short game to find animals, protects others, save the Afterworld, but most importantly, have fun.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With in the Obscurity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2817190/With_in_the_Obscurity/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>A first-person perspective mystery puzzle-solving game.</strong><br/><br/>In the 1990s, a young Chinese individual established a website called Abnormal1999 in the United States, which collected a large amount of abnormal cases and events. Meanwhile, in China, a police officer named "Liu Qingchun" also founded the 403 Intelligence Division, which similarly gathered abnormal intelligence. Over the course of more than a decade, these two organizations gradually grew in size and began to oppose each other, employing numerous intelligence personnel to gather information and leads.<br/><br/>This game is the first installment of this series, with plans to release 2 episodes each month, totaling 6 episodes for a season. Each episode is both independent and interconnected. In this installment, a highly bizarre case is featured: <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817190/extras/Video3.gif?t=1709539262"><h2 class="bb_tag">Season 1, Episode 1《With in the Obscurity》</h2>the police discovered 7 bodies in a desolate forest, each belonging to a member of a local spiritual group participating in a "spiritual practice." According to forensic analysis, all 7 individuals had no external injuries or signs of poisoning. At the time, there were a total of 8 participants in the spiritual practice, with one person missing. Interestingly, all the relatives of the deceased chose not to pursue the killer, leaving the case unsolved.<br/><br/>Players take on the role of one of the 8 individuals involved, gradually uncovering the truth of the events as an eyewitness to the "spiritual practice" incident.<br/><br/>Players must solve various puzzles and deduce the truth based on the "clues" obtained in the game.<br/><br/>You need to carefully read the clues you receive and play the game according to the clues provided.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Will</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2639400/Space_Will/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Sixty basic cores, hundreds of base station equipment, and thousands of chips, you can freely cooperate and shoot through the dual-angle joystick operation in a survival Roguelike game! Explore the sci-fi space and build your strongest battleship!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639400/extras/1y.png?t=1709539737"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639400/extras/1y.gif?t=1709539737"><br/><strong>Step 1: Choose a "core" as your basic role<br/>Step 2: Choose a "crew" as your initial weapon<br/>Step 3: Select a galaxy for exploration</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639400/extras/2y.png?t=1709539737"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639400/extras/2y.gif?t=1709539737"><br/><strong>The game will continuously collect new "units" or "chips" during the exploration process<br/>Using "crew" can expand weapons and enhance combat effectiveness for your warship<br/>Using "chips" can enhance various abilities of your warship</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639400/extras/3y.png?t=1709539737"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639400/extras/3y.gif?t=1709539737"><br/><strong>Each "core" or "unit" has a maximum of 4 interfaces. When the interfaces are used up, you cannot equip more parts, but you can also infinitely increase the number of your interfaces!<br/>Each "crew" can use the right mouse button to rotate and adjust the optimal angle for combat</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639400/extras/4y.png?t=1709539737"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639400/extras/4y.gif?t=1709539737"><br/><strong>The game features dual joystick shooting, with the keyboard moving and the mouse aiming at the enemy. Of course, there are many weapons that can automatically attack or be placed in the scene as traps for use~</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stellar Ghosts Settlers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2578790/Stellar_Ghosts_Settlers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2578790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Currently in Closed Beta. If you want to be part of it, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fsgs-game.com%2Fcontact-us%2F" rel="noopener" target="_blank">use our online contact form</a> to let us know. Places are limited.</strong><br/><br/><br/><strong>Stellar Ghosts Settlers</strong> is a Sci Fi Fantasy 3rd person action shooter game that sticks to the basics and immerse you in a world full of original and powerful wild life.<br/><br/>You're part of a group of settlers who decided to go away from the corrupt galactic Government's yoke. The settlers decided to set their first colony on the recently discovered and uninhabited planet Prosopopia B-21, planet full of resources so that the colonists can thrive. Despite the hostile wild life the settlers managed to set multiple bases across the planet. Unfortunately it wasn't that long until the galactic Government found out about that treason and decided to invade the planet in order to get their hands on all those new resources.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 6 Playable characters<br/></li><li> Lots of weapons<br/></li><li> use characters' specific abilities (regeneration, mega blast, force shield, invincility, sidekick orb shooter and incineration)<br/></li><li> Enjoy hours of gameplay with Campaign Mode's missions<br/></li><li> Fight hordes of hostile wildlife pests<br/></li><li> Epic fights against powerful bosses<br/></li><li> Drive mechs and use higher firepower to fight through the levels<br/></li><li> Complete the missions and unlock new arenas in Arena Mode<br/></li><li> Upgrade your favorite characters' stats with the credits you receive after completing each mission<br/></li><li> Showcase your skills in the arena and see if you can make it to the leader board</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Query</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2835970/Space_Query/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2835970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Explore the Cosmos with Space Query!<br>
<br>
Embark on an astronomical adventure with Space Query, the ultimate solar system simulator! Whether you're a budding astronomer, a space enthusiast, or just curious about the universe, Space Query is your gateway to the stars. This simulation software brings the solar system to your fingertips, allowing you to explore the orbits of planets and witness the fascinating effects of introducing new cosmic objects like asteroids, extra suns, or even a black hole.<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br>
<br>
Realistic Solar System Simulation: Dive into a detailed and dynamic model of our solar system. See the planets orbit in real-time or speed up time to watch years unfold in minutes! The software uses accurate positioning data updated live from NASA info, for a realistic simulation.<br/>
Interactivity at Its Best: Add celestial bodies to the system and observe the gravitational dance. Witness the impact of these additions on the delicate balance of our cosmic neighborhood.<br/>
Detailed Planetary Exploration: Zoom in on each planet to discover rich, full-color images based on authentic NASA photography. Uncover secrets and learn fascinating facts about each celestial body.<br/>
Customizable Viewpoints: Position yourself anywhere in the solar system. Want to see the orbits from Mars? You can! Experience the universe from new and unique perspectives.<br/>
User-Friendly for All Ages: Designed for space enthusiasts aged 7 to 77, Space Query is intuitive, engaging, and educational. A perfect blend of fun and learning for the whole family!<br/>
Prepare to be captivated by the beauty and complexity of our universe. Space Query is not just a software; it's a journey through space and time, offering endless exploration and discovery. Are you ready to unlock the mysteries of the cosmos?<br/>
<br/>
Download Space Query now and start your celestial adventure!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Contact</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2784970/The_Contact/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2784970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Synopsis</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2784970/extras/スクリーンショット__1257_.png?t=1709507156"><br/><br/>One day, a cryptic message was posted on an online bulletin board.<br/>Opening the mysterious URL revealed location coordinates. Despite sensing a dangerous atmosphere, you decide to venture to the location, thinking it might alleviate boredom.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>This game is a walking simulator set in a dimly lit, quiet building. Guided by the phone number and location information from the post, the protagonist pursues the enigmatic "it." With a realistic atmosphere and a subtle sense of dread, players experience the terror of everyday encounters in this horror game.<h2 class="bb_tag">Streaming Guidelines</h2>Streaming and content creation of this game are permitted, regardless of monetization status.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wandering Demon Blade</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2809290/The_Wandering_Demon_Blade/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2809290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Wandering Demon Blade is a melancholy, action platformer, with a focus on fast paced Sword Combat with quick reaction times and decision making.<br/><br/><strong>Fast Combat </strong>: Fights are difficult and a degree of mastery will go a long way. Death will come quickly and naturally to everyone involved. How quickly a battle starts and ends may impact the next. Every fighter can hold their own but only you will survive.<br/><br/><strong>Mysterious Purpose </strong>: Waking up in a shadowed world with no knowledge of how, learn about the Demon Blade's past, present, and future through an enigmatic story told by 3rd person accounts. Piece together the clues to figure out the meaning behind the Demon Blade.<br/><br/><strong>Silenced Game </strong>: The world is a quiet place; only filled with sounds often overlooked. These sounds help portray the story and the purpose of the Demon Blade.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elevator Experience</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2790340/Elevator_Experience/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2790340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a one-of-a-kind journey of exploration in "Elevator Experience". Step into the elevator and prepare to be transported to a world of mysteries, where every floor holds a new adventure waiting to be unlocked. With its dynamic gameplay and immersive environments, get ready for an experience like no other.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><h2 class="bb_tag">Randomized Rooms</h2><li>Discover a myriad of themed rooms, each with its own set of mechanics and challenges to conquer. From futuristic laboratories to enchanted forests, every room offers a fresh experience and countless opportunities for adventure.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2790340/extras/laserroom.gif?t=1709490280"><h2 class="bb_tag">Immersive Atmosphere</h2></img></li><li>Immerse yourself in the captivating atmosphere of the rooms, brought to life through stunning visuals and atmospheric sound design.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2790340/extras/snowroom.gif?t=1709490280"><h2 class="bb_tag">Challenging Mechanics</h2></img></li><li>Put your skills to the test with a variety of mechanics and challenges unique to each room. Whether you're deciphering ancient runes or navigating treacherous traps, "Elevator Experience" offers gameplay that is both engaging and rewarding.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2790340/extras/cardroom.gif?t=1709490280"/></li></ul><br/>Prepare to embark on an extraordinary adventure filled with mystery, suspense, and endless surprises in "Elevator Experience". Are you ready to unlock the secrets of the elevator? Step into the elevator and begin your journey into the unknown.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen's Garden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2639600/Queens_Garden/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Discover Queen's Garden, a colorful match 3 adventure! The King is planning on surprising his Queen by growing the biggest garden ever seen. He's counting on you to complete this prestigious task. Collect all the tools and flowers you need by completing wonderful match 3 levels. Are you up for this challenge? <br>
<br>
In a barren kingdom set atop a hill<br>
There lived a king and queen, who likely live there still<br>
The king was a caring man who loved to please his queen<br>
His plan was to grow a garden bigger than there had ever been<br>
You will cultivate a sea of bloom; fill the air with the breath of roses<br/>
From barren land to blossom—a sweet bouquet to royal noses<br/>
A perennial job for a seasoned grower—a garden for royalty<br/>
Apply within to serve the queen and be ever rewarded for your loyalty!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leap In The Right Direction</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2838910/Leap_In_The_Right_Direction/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2838910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an exhilarating journey with 'Leap In The Right Direction,' a 2D platformer featuring the friendliest of frogs! Test your skills through the challenging level filled with tricky jumps and cunning obstacles. Navigate the vibrant world, overcome frustrations, and leap your way to victory. With precision and determination, this game offers a visually captivating experience, challenging both your reflexes and patience. Are you ready to take the leap?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aurorae</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2795710/Aurorae/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Aurorae is a fighting card collection game, which adopts the art form of anime drawing and cartoon characters. The game adopts a horizontal combat mode, combined with a very rich and diverse character skill design, hoping to bring players a different gaming experience.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Weekend - Search and Relax Collector's Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2839670/Amazing_Weekend__Search_and_Relax_Collectors_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2839670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Amazing Weekend: Search and Relax offers a variety of unique and compelling mini-games, hidden-object puzzles, and more! Complete games to unlock new levels and explore interesting new locations where you’ll go hiking, horseback riding, boating, and relaxing through a weekend of recreation! Take a break from the daily hustle and bustle with this incredible new way to relax and get inspired!<br>
<br>
This is a special Collector's Edition release full of exclusive extras you won’t find in the standard version.<br>
<br>
The Collector’s Edition includes:<br>
* Explore twelve additional levels bursting with hidden objects and mini-games!<br>
* Download beautiful wallpapers to stay inspired every day of the week!<br/>
* Bring the adventure home with the exclusive music player!<br/>
* Visit the shop to view trophies and souvenirs from your weekend!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2806940/B1/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2806940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You find yourself lost in a mysterious space in the underground shopping area of a certain building while trying to have lunch. Clear the game presented by someone and aim to escape from the eerie underground shopping area.<br>
<br>
B1 is a simple horror walking simulator with a rule to turn back when feeling something strange and to go around the underground passage if nothing seems to happen.<br>
<br>
Clear this game the specified number of times and take the elevator to B1 to escape.<br>
<br>
Among the occurring changes, some can be checked and collected.<br/>
There are also achievements that can be obtained by collecting everything, so please give it a try.<br/>
<br/>
You can change settings such as field of view and mouse sensitivity.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirate Pop Quest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2842460/Pirate_Pop_Quest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Pirate Pop Quest" sets sail on a thrilling arcade adventure that tests you with reflexes! Burst bubbles of vibrant colors as you navigate through challenging levels. Strategically match pairs to unleash cascading combos and unlock treasures hidden beneath the waves!<br>
<br>
With easy-to-use controls, your mouse becomes your trusty compass, guiding you through the high seas of bubble-bursting excitement. Join the pirate crew and embark on an epic quest filled with plundered prizes and endless fun!<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
<br>
- Colorful Bubble Bursting: Pop bubbles of various hues to reveal new Colorful Bubbles<br/>
- Strategic Matching: Strategically match pairs of bubbles to trigger cascading combos<br/>
- Challenging Levels: Navigate through increasingly challenging levels, each with its unique obstacles and surprises.<br/>
- Epic Soundtrack: Dive into an epic soundtrack that evolves as you progress, enhancing the excitement and immersion of your pirate quest.<br/>
- Atmospheric Ambiance: Delight in the ambient sounds of the pirate world, from creaking ship timbers to seagull cries, creating a rich and immersive gaming environment.<br/>
- Crisp Pops: Enjoy satisfying bubble-popping sounds with each successful match, adding a delightful auditory dimension to your gameplay.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Witch Veils: The Mansion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2830010/The_Witch_Veils_The_Mansion/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2830010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<u><strong>ATTENTION: PHOTOSSENSITIVITY WARNING</strong></u><br/><br/>This game contains visual effects that may trigger seizures in individuals susceptible to photosensitive epilepsy. If you, or someone in your family, has a history of epilepsy, consult a doctor before playing.<br/><br/><strong>Description: </strong><br/>When two witches and an apprentice are kidnapped in a mansion, only Star, the apprentice, can save them and uncover what is happening.<br/><br/>The veil that separates order and chaos is weakened. Days ago, the witches' council detected the misuse of chaotic energy, determined to maintain the world's order, they send two of their best witches and an apprentice to investigate what may be happening.<br/><br/>Gameplay:<br/>Explore the mansion in search of your friends. The main character, Star, has no eyes but can see through sound. Use this mechanic to uncover secrets, keys. But beware, because you are not alone. There is something else trying to break the veil that separates the realms to cross over to our side. Don't let him catch you, hide, because he roams through the mansion.<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover what is happening through files:</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2830010/extras/TRAILERSTEAM-ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter_1_.gif?t=1709395398"><h2 class="bb_tag">Solve Puzzles:</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2830010/extras/TRAILERSTEAM-ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter.gif?t=1709395398"><h2 class="bb_tag">And Save Your Friends:</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2830010/extras/intro-ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter_1_.gif?t=1709395398"><h2 class="bb_tag">Welcome to the World of Witch Veil.</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2830010/extras/fantasma_da_cartola.gif?t=1709395398"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simploe Tasks</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2831610/Simploe_Tasks/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Game Description:<br>
3D horizontal board shooting fixed viewing angle.<br>
<br>
How it works:<br>
Fire: Left mouse button<br>
Move: A/D<br>
Jump: W<br/>
<br/>
Clearance Conditions:<br/>
1. Destroy all monsters that try to get close to plants.<br/>
2. Destroy monster lair.<br/>
<br/>
End Conditions:<br/>
1. Excessive blood loss.<br/>
2. Monsters infect plants.<br/>
2. Close the game.<br/>
<br/>
PS: There are only 2 levels, so you can't save your progress! Sticking to the second level will be very easy and refreshing.<br/>
<br/>
Keep firing, prioritize killing flying monsters, it's acceptable to take damage to a certain extent, and you can try more jumping and turning skills to maintain the continuity of the attack.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desktop MagicBox</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2416140/Desktop_MagicBox/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2416140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"> <h2 class="bb_tag"> <strong> Vivid desktop widget </strong> </h2> </h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>This is a small box for mounting 3D models on the desktop, with four sides to display different models. It supports VMD format animations, let your model dance when dragged into the box<br/></li><li></li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"> <h2 class="bb_tag"> <strong>Features </strong> </h2> </h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Directly load PMX and PMD format model files</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Support VMD format animations[[/list]<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Provide two rendering styles: realistic and toon[[/list]<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Automatic addition of physics effects</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Support for the Workshop</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Models can be popped out of the box for individual control</li></ul></li></ul></li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microcosmum 2 - Soundtrack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2843840/Microcosmum_2__Soundtrack/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2843840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Excellent meditative soundtracks, created by a talented composer specifically for Microcosmum 2.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microcosmum 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1486140/Microcosmum_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1486140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1486140/extras/Logo.png?t=1709384449"><br/><br/><br/><br/>You are a collective microorganic alien intelligence.<br/>You used to be the dominant species of a whole planet, but you had to leave your home since then.<br/>Having spent many long years in space, you've finally landed on a habitable planet. You are to revive your "empire" and become small, yet great, once again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1486140/extras/1all_2.gif?t=1709384449"><br/><br/>A relaxing strategy game featuring unconventional gameplay. Your objectives include development, evolution, border expansion and protection of your hive.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1486140/extras/en-ORGANISMS-CONSTRUCTOR.png?t=1709384449"><br/>Organism constructor:<br/>Receive new details from defeated enemies and construct your own organisms. Every detail has a set of particular features, sometimes bestowing the organism with special abilities, such as slime bomb, spikes and much more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1486140/extras/2all_1.gif?t=1709384449"><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1486140/extras/en-GAME-WORLD.png?t=1709384449"><br/>World map:<br/>The game takes place on a world map, split into locations. Everything is fully real-time. Opponents capture more land area, compete with each other, extract resources and develop said areas.<br/><br/>Environment:<br/>All locations have particular environmental conditions. Organisms may freeze or overheat. They may mutate due to radiation and receive bonuses.<br/>Acclimatize your organisms to certain environmental conditions in the incubator.<br/>You are able to terraform your lands, creating extreme environments - beneficial to your organisms, yet deadly to your opponents. <br/><br/>Extract resources, erect "buildings", capture and defend land areas on the global map.<br/><br/>You can also feed your organisms, much like fish:)<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1486140/extras/en-UNIQUENESS.png?t=1709384449"><br/>Uniqueness and Project Concept:<br/>Microcosmum 2 was conceived as a unique game, unlike any other strategy game, capable of surprising with new ideas. The emphasis is on creating a deep atmosphere, meditative gameplay, and a pleasant visual style. The goal is for the player to immerse themselves in the atmosphere and relax during the game.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1486140/extras/en-AUTHORS.png?t=1709384449"><br/>Microcosmum 2 was created by a team of two people. For five years, we spared no effort, time, or resources in creating the game. For us, Microcosmum is not just a game; it's a unique world created by us with its own character and atmosphere.<br/><br/>Microcosmum: Survival of Cells was our first successful game. It became beloved by a large number of players and continues to be popular to this day. Therefore, in Microcosmum 2, we invested all our strength and accumulated experience to make it much better and bring joy to everyone who has been eagerly awaiting the second part, as well as to be a discovery for those who are just getting acquainted with Microcosmum.<br/><br/>Enjoy the game! :)						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARCH ALL - SNAKES</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2840230/SEARCH_ALL__SNAKES/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2840230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">SEARCH ALL - SNAKES</h2> - This is a game in the “search for objects” genre, in which you need to find all the snakes in a large location. Snakes will be located in a variety of places, from the most visible to barely noticeable places. The entire game location looks animated due to the animation elements. Find all the snakes! Don't let them go unnoticed :)<br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/>  - Animation elements on the location;<br/>  - 100 snakes to find;<br/>  - Pleasant soundtrack;<br/>  - The gameplay can be interrupted at any time, and the game will automatically save the result;<br/>  - Hints implemented! If you have trouble finding an item, use the hint!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rust Rails</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2591880/Rust_Rails/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">RESOURCE COLLECTION AND CRAFT</h2>On your journey, you will encounter various resources from which you can create weapons, armor, various items, or exchange them with a merchant.<br/>Be careful, the space in your backpack is not endless, you will have to choose what to take with you and what to leave.<h2 class="bb_tag">EVERY ADVENTURE WILL BE UNIQUE</h2>The Roguelike system will make each race unique, a procedurally generated map, dungeons, train stations, loot will not let you get bored!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591880/extras/mapGif.png?t=1709377149"><h2 class="bb_tag">BATTLE SYSTEM</h2>The weapons have unique mechanics - homing missiles, an energy ball, ballistic projectiles, and maybe ninja frogs...? Moreover, each projectile has its own type of damage - Normal, Energy, Frost, Fire, Poison. Weapons with different damage types pair well or poorly with active artifacts!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591880/extras/SkillGig.png?t=1709377149"><h2 class="bb_tag">WORLD EXPLORATION</h2>Random encounters with peaceful characters, secret rooms, riddles, dialogues will help you learn the history of this world.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunt Hide Run</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375710/Hunt_Hide_Run/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							There are two teams: Hunters and Runners. <br/>Hunters have to find and kill all Runners before time runs out.<br/><br/><strong>HUNT!</strong><br/>Hunters use blades that are very dangerous for Runners.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375710/extras/HUNT.gif?t=1709376833"><br/><br/><strong>HIDE!</strong><br/>Runners can hide in different spots… even among fake bots!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375710/extras/HIDE.gif?t=1709376833"><br/><br/><strong>RUN!</strong><br/>Run away from Hunters if they find you! <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375710/extras/RUN.gif?t=1709376833"><br/><br/><strong>Match Settings</strong><br/>Host can change some match settings: characters’ velocity, round time, jump height, etc.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ace Pilot Pacific</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2246530/Ace_Pilot_Pacific/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2246530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Ace Pilot Pacific</h2> is my 3rd game and I have been working on it for around a year and a half. The action takes place during World War 2 in the Pacific.<br/><br/>You will fly one of the six different aircraft available against the Japanese.<br/>You will be dog fighting against Zeros, Ki43, Ki49, G4M, G4M2, Hk8K2, Nakajima Kikka, J8M Shusui, and Shinden.<br/><br/>Choose between 5 missions:<br/>- Atoll<br/>- Pearl Harbor<br/>- Wake Island<br/>- Japan Run<br/>- Ha Long Bay<br/><br/>You can play them in the order you want without restriction. The goal is to obtain the highest score in every mission. When you or one of your Allies destroys a plane, you gain a flag. When you have 3 flags, you gain an Ace level. The mission ends at Ace 100, if you are still alive. When you destroy an enemy, you get a Power UP, at Ace 100 you get an Upgrade.<br/><br/>All missions start with you and a wingman against 3 Japanese and when you gain an Ace Level, the number of enemies increase as well as the number of Allies, but the numbers are random, sometimes you get more Allies, sometimes it's the opposite.<br/><br/>Backgrounds are very detailed all in 4K HD. Atoll is a small map, Wake Island is a giant one 32768x30720 pixels. The effect is stunning and if you're like me, you will want to go swimming on that beach.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2246530/extras/F4U_x1_1.gif?t=1709465313"><br/>All the objects are 3D, even the sea. <br/>I recommend you use a game controller. It's like flying a small RC aircraft on your screen. But it also works with a keyboard.<br/><br/>I am planning to add more missions if the reviews are good. If you like it, give it a thumbs up.<br/>Hubert						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrono Recorder</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2843090/Chrono_Recorder/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2843090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The player is trapped in an unknown space. <br>
In the player's hands is a clock that controls time and a camera that controls the state of objects. <br>
Clocks can stop or slow down time. <br>
The camera can turn back time or change the gravity of an object.<br>
The player must use these two objects to clear the stage.<br>
<br>
<br/>
This game was created by 4 developers.<br/>
There are not many stages in the game, so please enjoy it lightly.<br/>
<br/>
(Maps may be added in the future. Good responses encourage developers.)						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bam Boom Blade 竹個擊破</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2709800/Bam_Boom_Blade/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709800/extras/banner.png?t=1709531788"><br/><br/><strong>Bam Boom Blade</strong> is a physics-based 2D joust game for 2 players. Players will act as a wuxia riding on a bamboo, and try to defeat your rival using only 2 joysticks on your gamepad.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SIMPLE AND INTUITIVE</strong></h2>Use left joystick to <strong>Bend</strong> bamboo, and use right joystick to <strong>Wave</strong> sword. It's just that easy. You and your friends can learn as soon as you hold your gamepad.<br/><br/>The control and mechanics are simple, but winning is not. Take full control of your body, sword, and manage the bamboo.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>The Bamboo</strong></h2><strong>Left Joystick</strong> is for Body and Bamboo. Push your joystick alongside the bamboo to climb up/down, or push towards other angles to bend the bamboo.<br/><br/>Build your momentum to one-hit kill. Climb down to the bottom and have a close combat. Intentionally get injured and free your leg to move wildly. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709800/extras/Bamboo.gif?t=1709531788"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>The Blade</strong></h2><strong>Right Joystick</strong> is for Blade. When you hit, it makes a difference to hit different body part. Your Blade can parry rival's blade. <br/><br/>Parry rival's sword and do a counter attack. Attack your rival's flailing limbs with a precise slash! Or simply wait your rival to dash into your sword.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709800/extras/Blade.gif?t=1709531788"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Akari and the Abyss</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2275710/Akari_and_the_Abyss/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2275710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2275710/extras/11.png?t=1709348457"><br/>This game is a JRPG featuring a girl exploring the demon-infested Hell Palace. <br/>During her journey, the demon-slaying girl, Akari, encounters incidents where people's souls have been stolen. <br/>In order to save everyone, Akari challenges the Hell Palace and the story begins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2275710/extras/33.png?t=1709348457"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Female protagonist<br/></li><li>Turn-based battles<br/></li><li>Selectable difficulty levels<br/></li><li>Auto-function available</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tank Tyranny</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781730/Tank_Tyranny/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Gear up for an epic tank showdown in this dynamic local multiplayer game! Outwit friends in intense PvP battles or team up to defend against ruthless enemies in PvE!<br/><br/>You can count on each stage being different with procedurally generated levels, random item drops, and an arsenal of wacky powerups to give you an advantage in the competition!<br/><br/>Unlock tons of different decorations and hats to customize your character!<br/><br/>Grab up to 6 friends to play with - or against - to determine who is the ultimate champion!<br/><br/>Credit for trailer music: Fuzzeke<br/><br/><u>Features</u><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Up to 6 player local multiplayer<br/></li><li>VS game mode, for playing against your friends (2-6 players)<br/></li><li>Survival game mode, for fighting off waves of enemies with your friends (1-6 players)<br/></li><li>Arsenal of 7 different powerups to turn the tides of competition<br/></li><li>20 different unlockable decorations for the lobby<br/></li><li>8 different unlockable hats</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let Them Breathe: Hello Mother</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2787890/Let_Them_Breathe_Hello_Mother/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Mrs. Chen, the mother of Jesse Chen, is asked to pick up some documents; these documents reside at the University of Tokyo where she used to work. Upon her picking up these documents, she engages with audio recordings and diary entries that tells her what exactly took place in the experimentation room.<br>
<br>
Follow Mrs. Chen and discover more about the world of Let Them Breathe. In this walking simulation and collectable game, you will explore a small abandoned laboratory. Within the different compartments of the library, you will find items in which you will be able to engage with such as recordings, and documents in which you have to collect so as to win the game. <br>
<br>
In this casual short game with a spice of thriller, the atmosphere allows for the player to walk the environment to discover what took place within various locations of the game. The player will find out more about the location, and the two individuals who once occupied the space prior to the player's arrival. <br>
<br>
Let Them Breathe: Hello Mother is a video game that takes place within the Let Them Breathe franchise. It tells the story of Mrs. Chen who is the mother of one of the characters in the indie web series and even the indie movie, Let Them Breathe: City on the Ocean.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suborbital</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2528640/Suborbital/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2528640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Many many years into the future, humanity has created and used warp drives. However, due to the recency of the technology, it still has many flaws. You are equipped with experimental engines and a warp drive, and you are tasked with finding the wreck of the EV Triumph, a large exploratory ship which lost contact on its journey through deep space. The reason was unknown, but you suffer the same fate.<br>
<br>
Brace for a journey into the unknown. Explore a massive wreck and salvage materials to get out of your time-limited survival situation as quickly as possible. Every decision you make could mean the difference between life and death: Resourcefulness and strategy will be tested as you scavenge for supplies, and your ever decreasing oxygen levels keep you on your toes.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit Hole</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2831340/Rabbit_Hole/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/smaller.png?t=1709337648"><br/><strong><i>“Remember you will live.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Rabbit Hole is a fast paced, tough-as-nails 2D Platformer-RogueLike-Shooter inspired by popular roguelikes, made with a love for the genre. <br/>You are Disc, someone who was suddenly brought to the Rabbit Hole. <br/>Collect guns, fight foes and meet strange new characters on your descent to the bottom, all in an attempt to find your heart again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/1.gif?t=1709337648"><br/><strong><i>“This place is like its own ecosystem. A big living breathing mess.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Every run is different. Enjoy hours of replayable content through randomly generated floor layouts and 50+ weapons to collect and use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/2.gif?t=1709337648"><br/><strong><i>“Hey, hey, hey! How's my favorite anxiety-fueled nutjob!”</i></strong><br/><br/>Unlock new characters with diverse playstyles. Each of the 6 unlockable characters keep gameplay fresh and give a unique perspective on the gameplay loop.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/3.gif?t=1709337648"><br/><strong><i>“There was a blank line, almost as if I had erased it”</i></strong><br/><br/>Discover the truth that lies beneath the surface. Collect books and fill out your library to understand its unseen history. In the end, you may even come to understand yourself?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speed NFL</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816550/Speed_NFL/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2816550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Play a football (American) game in 25 minutes. Select your team before using the NFL rankings to decide on your offensive tactics.<br>
<br>
Key Features<br>
<br>
NFL ranking<br>
Betting odds<br>
Play options - rush, Screen, Shotgun, bomb, side-line, end-zone, hail Mary, FG and punt<br/>
Time-outs<br/>
Flags<br/>
Scoreboard<br/>
Stats<br/>
Quarter by Quarter<br/>
OT<br/>
Team colours<br/>
Player names<br/>
Plaver v Player or Player v Computer<br/>
<br/>
Game uses the ZX Spectrum interface.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Secret of Varonis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2174900/The_Secret_of_Varonis/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2174900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Come join us on Discord! <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FRKjYSATbTe" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/RKjYSATbTe</a><h2 class="bb_tag">An indie Gameboy-style RPG!</h2>The Secret of Varonis features old-school combat mechanics and visuals faithful to the gaming heyday of 1989. If you're nostalgic for retro games, or just looking for a good, challenging RPG, look no further.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Choose a party of humans, espers, robots, and monsters, each with a unique leveling scheme<br/></li><li>Employ over 500 combat items and abilities, either learned, looted, bought, or crafted<br/></li><li>Explore five unique worlds, each with their own story and characters, plus the sealed city of Varonis which unites them all...<br/></li><li>Enjoy the best of oldschool mechanics without the pain points: no required grinding, optional field encounter mode, and other newschool ideas</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">What lies beyond the gate?</h2>The city of Varonis once housed a wondrous portal. Wisemen and scientists emerged, bearing new technology and powerful artifacts. But when dangerous monsters also spilled out, the portal was sealed and the city abandoned. Jonas and Janine, two warrior twins, set out to discover what has become of the secret city, but when they fail to return, it is up to four village youths (and their trusty robot) to rescue them... and uncover the truth behind the gate of Varonis.<h2 class="bb_tag">The four races</h2>To challenge Varonis and the many trials beyond, you'll need to build your own party:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Humans - Sturdy generalists who buy potions to advance in stats. They carry swords, saws, shotguns, spellbooks... Versatility is key!<br/></li><li>Espers - Natural-born fighters that learn from combat, granting stats, abilities, and powerful multitarget magic.<br/></li><li>Robots - Customizable companions that can be built in many different ways. A tankbot made of armor? A ninjabot made of swords?<br/></li><li>Monsters - Scrappy shapeshifters whose role in combat can change in a flash. Most monster abilities can be found nowhere else.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In a Detective's Mind</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2814270/In_a_Detectives_Mind/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2814270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In a Detective's Mind is a short game made by two people, where you will play as Andrew, a detective who is learning to deal with the problems of his past. You will have to solve two cases, where you will receive very few details about what happened. The objective is for you to be able to put together in your head what happened in the place, with as little detail as possible, so it will be important that you explore and make deductions, so that you can solve the cases and puzzles in the game.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build your destiny</h2>Being a detective is not an easy task. With each new case you decide to investigate, new people have their fates sealed in your hands. One word, one wrong accusation can mean the end of an innocent life.<br/><br/>In a Detective's Mind proposes an experience where your decisions matter, changing not only the destiny of the people around you, but yours as well. Having <u>3 different endings</u>, In a Detective's Mind takes you on a journey of no return.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MegaBlasters!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2071420/MegaBlasters/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071420/extras/AmazingGifNew.gif?t=1709539839"><br/><br/>Get ready to laugh and blast through 100 physics-based maps in this comedic multiplayer FPS game. With wacky weapons and fast-paced action, it's a hilarious and explosive experience for you and your friends.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071420/extras/Features_Banner.png?t=1709539839"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play with 3 other blasters, either friends or random (all wrigglin' around)<br/></li><li>Chaotic physics based guns <br/></li><li>100+ Chaotic physics maps (with destructive maps for destructive people)<br/></li><li>Quick in-game chat (distract n' kill lol)<br/></li><li>Who doesn't like blackholes and stuff?<br/></li><li>Make someone go boom (sus bomb)<br/></li><li>Noodle limbs (cuz why not)<br/></li><li>Punch with your noodle hands</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
