<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1702808053"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1702808053"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1702808053"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1702808053"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1702808053"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1702808053"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1702808053"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trinity Fusion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1911360/Trinity_Fusion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take control of your parallel selves on a mission to save the dying multiverse. Explore dark, sci-fi worlds and engage in fast-paced, smooth and precise combat.<h2 class="bb_tag">A rogue-lite journey through the multiverse</h2>The various branches of the multiverse are always changing. Fight through a combination of procedurally-generated levels as well as hand-crafted challenges and arenas that will put your skills to the test. Levels with 3D graphics are seamlessly constructed out of hundreds of custom-made rooms.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/extras/Ranger_Factory.gif?t=1702635042"><h2 class="bb_tag">High-intensity combat</h2>With weapons and attack systems that leverage our previous experience working on fighting games. You’ll slide, dash and dodge between enemy attacks and strike back with an arsenal of satisfying special weapons and abilities.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/extras/Ranger_City_Walls_GIF_Cleanup.gif?t=1702635042"><h2 class="bb_tag">Three characters, three universes to explore</h2>Each of your parallel selves has their own world with multiple biomes to explore, as well as their own sets of unique abilities and weapons. Travel through a universe of desolate wastes and caverns roamed by mutant creatures, escape the endless forges and labs of a world ruled by machines, and survive the dangerous sky cities of a post-human society.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/extras/Player_Running_Cleanup.gif?t=1702635042"><h2 class="bb_tag">Constant Progression</h2>Unlock permanent upgrades in the Hub and discover new starting points for your run as you reclaim major locations in each universe. Finding yourself getting stuck in one area? Start your next run in a different one! No matter where you die, or which starting point you pick, you're making progress somewhere.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1911360/Trinity_Fusion/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1911360/Trinity_Fusion/</a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1702674942"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WITCH ON THE HOLY NIGHT</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2052410/WITCH_ON_THE_HOLY_NIGHT/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2052410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2052410/extras/WITCH_ON_THE_HOLY_NIGHT_About_this_game.gif?t=1702631006"><br/><strong>Product Description</strong><br/>TYPE-MOON, known for the wildly popular mobile game "Fate/Grand Order" and the epic visual novel "Tsukihime," is releasing a remaster of the 2012 hit "Witch on the Holy Night. Experience a coming of age story set in the vibrant, bustling 1980s, which follows an innocent young man and two young "witches." Updates added since the original release include long-awaited fully voiced characters as well as visuals remastered in full HD, bringing the experience to life with unparalleled quality and fidelity. Masterful manipulation of visual elements imbues combat scenes with nail-biting tension, but also breathes life into the characters' everyday activities. Animated graphical elements bring an entirely new level of depth to the reading experience as well!<br/><br/><strong>STORY</strong><br/>In the mansion on the hill, there lived two witches...<br/><br/>It is the late 1980s—the twilight of an era of beauty and vigor.<br/>A boy moves to the city, barely missing two witches living in modern times.<br/><br/>The boy leads a completely ordinary life.<br/>She carries herself with gallant pride.<br/>The girl lives a sleepy, hidden life.<br/><br/>Each walks a starlit path.<br/>One would never expect their paths to cross.<br/>The story of how these three disparate people came together is soon to be told.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons of Sundaria</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/587520/Dungeons_of_Sundaria/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/587520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">The Dungeons:</h2> <br/>* 8 Huge Dungeons filled with hundreds of fiendish monsters and dozens of diabolical bosses.<br/>* Three Levels of Difficulty: Normal, Hard, and Nightmare.  <br/>* Online single player or co-op up to 4-players.<br/>* Local Split-screen multiplayer co-op up to 4-players (only requires a single game copy).<h2 class="bb_tag">Make your Hero:</h2> <br/>* 7 Races: Human, Dwarf, Elf, Halfling, Orc, Goblin and Drog'al (lizard).<br/>* 5 Classes: Champion, Ranger, Cleric, Wizard, and Rogue. <br/>* Customize the appearance of your Hero.<h2 class="bb_tag">Become a Legend:</h2> <br/>* Collect a huge variety of Weapons, Armor, and Accessories to customize your Hero and grow in power.<br/>* Craft powerful equipment and become a force of reckoning.  Multiple tiers of armor and weapons.<br/>* Embrace the Heroism system, allowing you to continually increase the power of your Hero.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1702562956"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1702562956"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1702000678"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1702000678"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood West</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_steam_text_header.png?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>Weird West legends meet eldritch horror in <strong>BLOOD WEST</strong>, an immersive stealth FPS. Become the Undead Gunslinger, doomed to roam the barren lands until he finds the means to purge their curse and free his soul. No, this isn’t your typical Wild West desperado redemption arc. This is a damnation arc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_episodes_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The Canyons, the Swamp, and the Mountains. Each swarming with abominable monsters and unholy demons, these are open-ended worlds for you to explore freely at your own pace. It will take the player over 20 hours on average to complete all three scenarios, and over 35 if they want to see everything the barren lands have to offer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_stealth_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/><strong>Blood West</strong> is a stealth FPS inspired by the genre classics such as the Thief series (whose fans will be happy to hear the voice of Stephen Russell, the actor voicing the master-thief Garrett, returning here as the protagonist), S.T.A.L.K.E.R. games, or - from the contemporary catalog - Hunt: Showdown. The gameplay rewards the careful approach: scouting the area, stalking your enemies, and striking from the shadows. Can you figure out a way to clear a fort full of ghouls and monsters without raising an alarm?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_horror_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The Barren Lands present the player with a nightmarish, twisted vision of the Wild West legends. The curse that has befallen the realm has corrupted every living thing, defiled the land itself, while summoning restless spirits and dark entities. In this mixture of gunslinger pulp and Lovecraftian horror, dark occult magick presents just as much of a threat as sudden lead poisoning.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_characters_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>In <strong>Blood West</strong> you will meet many colorful, yet strangely twisted, fully-voiced NPCs. Just as much prisoners of the Barren Lands as you are, they will sometimes share their unusual stories and send you on various missions. Play nice and they might reward you or become your allies. Cross them and risk their wrath.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_secrets_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The game won’t hold your hand. You’ll have to explore the land for yourself (buying a map from a vendor might prove useful!), and figure out your own way to approach quests. As you poke around the three expansive maps, keep an eye out for hidden places and secret stashes. There’s gold in the mountains! Fair warning - it’s probably cursed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_brutal_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>If sneaking around isn’t exactly your thing, or you feel that you have a power advantage over your enemies, you can always take the head-on approach and meet your enemies guns blazing. <strong>Blood West</strong> comes from the creators of the fan-favorite boomer shooter <strong>POSTAL: Brain Damaged</strong>, so much gratuitous fantasy violence and pixelated blood splatter is to be expected!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_inventory_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>One man’s hell might be another hoarder’s paradise! From simple one-use items like bandages, through medical tinctures, explosives and incendiaries, straight to arcane artifacts that - once slotted - can change the way you play the game, the Barren Lands are just filled with STUFF. There are tons of useful items to discover, and there’s a special player’s stash crate for all those super-rare potions that you’ll hoard and never use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_weapons_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>A gunslinger without a gun would be just a regular slinger. Where’s the fun in that? <strong>Blood West</strong> makes sure you’ll have plenty of weapons to choose from. Revolvers, rifles, shotguns, carabines - a great variety of firearms, from standard army-issue to those infused with powerful magic, or straight-up possessed. And if you prefer not to cause a ruckus, there’s a wide selection of hand-to-hand combat weapons and archery weapons to pick your favorites from.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_skills_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The RPG-like perk-based progression system in <strong>Blood West</strong> will allow you to highly customize the gameplay experience to your liking. Become a stealthy hunter, a revolver-fanning gunman or a relentless berserker. You will gain experience and progress through the skill tree, while discovering new artifacts in each of the scenarios that will bestow on you additional abilities. Combining skills and load-out creates more possible playstyles than you’d normally be able to explore in one playthrough.<h2 class="bb_tag">Are you ready to take back the frontier from the dark forces of demonic corruption and earn the right to move on to a better world? The Barren Lands call you, Gunslinger!</h2><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1702394215"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1702394215"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1702394215"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1702620270"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1702620270"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinball M</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2337640/Pinball_M/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-1.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-2.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free<br/>- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage<br/>- Thrilling competition<br/>- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation<h2 class="bb_tag">Sink your teeth into these tables as purchasable DLC: </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">- Chucky's Killer Pinball:</h2> Step into a twisted realm where the innocent becomes sinister, and the playful turns menacing. Navigate through an eerie playfield where Chucky lurks in the shadows, ready to pounce.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Dead by Daylight™️ Pinball:</h2> Become the hunter or even the hunted in a thrilling fusion of classic pinball and the excitement of one of the most popular horror games ever created.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Duke Nukem's Big Shot Pinball:</h2> Enjoy the biggest, grooviest, most BADASS pinball table ever made packed with guns and babes. Push start and play with balls of steel!<h2 class="bb_tag">- The Thing Pinball: </h2>Use your pinball skills and battle against the shape-shifting alien through the arctic chill of U.S. Outpost #31. Can you trust anyone, even yourself?<br/>- Even more coming...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-4.png?t=1701703297"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn back immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Option</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.<br/>If you are easily intoxicated, changing the following settings may help.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera shake】</strong><br/>The camera shakes when you walk or run, but if you set the value to 0.0, the camera will not shake.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Acceleration】</strong><br/>If you set the maximum value to 30.0, the camera will move without delay.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Sensitivity】</strong><br/>If the sensitivity is high, the camera will move significantly when the mouse is moved. <br/>Adjust the value if you find it difficult to operate the camera with the default value of 1.<br/><br/><strong>【Motion Blur】</strong><br/>Afterimages will appear when the camera is moved. Recommended to disable at 30FPS<br/><br/><strong>【Preset】</strong><br/>Set the overall graphic settings.<br/>If you do not have sufficient specs, it is better to set it to "Low" to avoid sickness.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1702747783"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658820/Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							10 possible fruits and one goal, reach the Watermelon.<br/>Your job is to combine matching fruits to evolve them to the next one and eventually reach the coveted Watermelon.<br/>To help you, you have 3 different abilities at your disposal. But watch out, using these will cost you some of your points. Be smart about when you use them to get the highest score!<h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLAYER</h2>Measure your fruit skills against another player.<h2 class="bb_tag">GET THE WATERMELON</h2>How many Watermelons can you combine before your basket overflows?<h2 class="bb_tag">USE YOUR ABILITIES</h2>Power, level up and destroy — These abilities will help you reach the Watermelon, using any of those will also allow you to angle your aim.<h2 class="bb_tag">GOLDEN FRUIT</h2>If luck is on your side, you might even see the mysterious Golden Fruit. Find it and witness its effect firsthand.<h2 class="bb_tag">STATISTICS</h2>Track your progress with in-depth statistics. Visit the menu to see the number of fruits you've combined, your ability usage, and much more.<h2 class="bb_tag"></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.codecks.io%2Fwatermelon-game" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/extras/Roadmap_Banner.png?t=1702238677"/></a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heart-S-Truck</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2671740/HeartSTruck/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671740/extras/About_this_game.png?t=1702849379"><br/>In "Heart-S-Truck," brace yourself for a platforming odyssey set in a whimsical universe where the fate of humanity rests on the wheels of brave delivery trucks. As a valiant truck with a vital mission, you'll navigate treacherous paths demanding precision, velocity, and unwavering focus.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671740/extras/gameplay_features.png?t=1702849379"><h2 class="bb_tag">Forge Bonds with Quirky Characters </h2>Dive into deep interactions with the world’s vibrant residents. Listen to their stories, share in their dreams, and knit the threads of a scattered community together by fulfilling critical deliveries in their time of need.<h2 class="bb_tag">Conquer the Physics of Platforming</h2>Face the thrilling challenge of a physics-based driving platformer. Mastery over momentum and the art of balance is key as you turn each delivery into a heart-pounding trial.<h2 class="bb_tag">Revel in a Vivid, Hand-Painted World</h2>Journey through an enchantingly painted world that invites you to explore a spectrum of stunning and diverse environments, each alive with color and motion.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671740/extras/About_developmen.png?t=1702849379"><br/>Heart-S-Truck is an intermediate game project at the University of Southern California by Rosemary Wu and Yufei Xiao, in collaboration with students from Berklee College of Music. For more information, please visit our publisher page. To learn more about the USC Games program, the #1 game program in the world, check out the USC Games website, linked to the right.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Null Gravity Labyrinth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2701170/Null_Gravity_Labyrinth/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find and touch the golden cube to exit this abstract labyrinth. <br>
When touching a spinning cube all elements with the same color as the cube will disappear and new paths will form. <br>
When you touch a portal it will teleport you to the connected portal of the same color. <br>
Currently only level 1 and 2 are playable.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nudel Tag</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1149280/Nudel_Tag/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1149280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In <strong>Nudel Tag</strong>, challenge your friends to get the most tips, in a crazy ramen restaurant !<br/>Find up to 4 controllers, to have the most fun, and see who is the best waiter in the house !<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1149280/extras/Gif_01.gif?t=1702832317"><br/><br/>You need to bring plates, from the chef, to the customers, easy, right ?<br/>Well, unless the other waiters steal your plates and cash in your precious tips !<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1149280/extras/Gif_02.gif?t=1702832317"><br/><br/>How can you get more chances to get some tips ? <br/>Well, you can always spend what you got so far in bonuses <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1149280/extras/Gif_03.gif?t=1702832317"><br/><br/>Have fun with this party game !						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Castle Kingdom Wars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2284390/Castle_Kingdom_Wars/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2284390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Defend your castle and crush your opponent's castle.<br>
<br>
Unlock new heroes and improve them to defeat your enemies. Upgrade your castle and unlock more features.<br>
<br>
Make your own strategy to beat your enemies. Characters have different skills so you can defeat your enemy with different tactics. Knight, swordsman, archer, skeleton, mage, catapult and much more hero are ready to fight for you.<br>
<br>
There are 2 game modes in this game:<br>
<br/>
1- You can play singleplayer and play agains ai. there are lots of different levels in singleplayer mode.<br/>
<br/>
2- There is also a battle simulator sandbox mode. Spawn warriors in the battle arena and see how they fight against each other at the battlefield. You can spawn any hero and watch hero wars. There is no character limit at this mode so you can play with lots of heroes at battle simulator.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neon Geometry Dash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2704460/Neon_Geometry_Dash/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You have different levels, where you will have to travel down space, moving left and right avoiding collisions.<br>
<br>
Each level is a new adventure with new mechanics and soundtracks.<br>
<br>
Neon: Geometry Dash has the following features:<br>
<br>
• Rhythm-based Action game.<br/>
• Many levels with unique soundtracks!<br/>
• Vertical action game with simple look but addictive mechanics.<br/>
• Practice mode.<br/>
• Very easy but challenging game.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1702808053"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1702808053"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1702808053"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1702808053"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1702808053"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1702808053"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1702808053"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mocap Fusion [ VR ]</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540000/Mocap_Fusion__VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Motion Capture Fusion [VR]</strong> is an immersive roomscale mocap sandbox for artists and animators who wish to create and export motion capture animations<i>, or create live content</i>, using conventional VR hardware. With as little as a single VR HMD and two controllers users may create mocap on their own avatars. Advanced users may create more detailed motion capture including full body tracking and can be combined with other sensors (eg. Apple IPhone <i>Truedepth sensor</i> and Oculus Quest 2 <i>optical finger tracking</i>) to connect avatars to simultaneous inputs. This fusion of multiple sensor can combine many layers of motion capture in a single take; including: full body tracking, face capture, lipsync, gaze tracking, optical finger tracking. <br/><br/><strong>Highlights</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Record motion capture using custom avatars, scenes and props.<br/></li><li>Add custom shaders, textures, emotes expressions, dynamicbone physics and more.<br/></li><li>Vive pro eye, Vive lip tracking and Iphone ARkit facecap support.<br/></li><li>HTC Vive, Valve Index, Oculus Rift, Oculus Quest2, some WMR headsets.<br/></li><li>Can be used without VR, trackers only, or with only IPhone head tracking.<br/></li><li>Add multiple avatars into a scene, build storyboards, react to other prerecorded avatars.<br/></li><li>Camera motion capture and zoom, player acts as the cinematographer in VR.<br/></li><li>VTOL and Fixed Wing flight simulation vehicle platforms for aerial photography shots.</li></ul><br/><strong>Supported Output Formats</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Exports to <strong>SFM</strong> <i>(.dmx)</i>.<br/></li><li>Exports to <strong>Blender</strong> <i>(.blend)</i>.<br/></li><li>Exports to <strong>Unity</strong> <i>(.anim)</i>.</li></ul><br/><strong>Live-Link (live production) and Live-Recording plugins</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Live Link plugin available for <strong>Unreal Engine</strong> <i>(live avatar sync, live recording)</i>.<br/></li><li>Live Link plugin available for <strong>Blender</strong> <i>(live avatar sync, live recording)</i>.<br/></li><li>Live Link plugin available for <strong>Unity</strong> <i>(live avatar sync)</i>.</li></ul><br/><br/>Include custom avatars and use the avatar throughout the production workflow. This eliminates the need for retargeting and ensures the mocap data always fits 1:1 without causing any offsets in the final results.<br/><br/>One of the unique features of <strong>Mocap Fusion</strong> is that it has the ability to export motion capture data and reconstruct the scene in Blender, making it available for final rendering in minutes.<br/><br/><strong>Compatible Headsets (VR HMDs)</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Valve Index<br/></li><li>HTC Vive <i>(and Vive Pro Eye)</i>.<br/></li><li>Oculus Quest <i>(1 and 2)</i>.</li></ul><br/><strong>Optional Tracking Hardware</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>SteamVR Vive trackers.<br/></li><li>IPhone Truedepth sensor <i>(facecap and eye tracking)</i>.<br/></li><li>Oculus Quest 2 <i>(full optical finger tracking)</i>.</li></ul><br/><strong>Capabilities </strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Export mocap and create scenes in Blender™ instantly.<br/></li><li>HTC™ Vive Trackers (Up to 11 optional points) full body tracking.<br/></li><li>Ability to record, playback, pause, slomo, scrub mocap in VR.<br/></li><li>Customizable IK profiles and avatar parameters.<br/></li><li>SteamVR Knuckles support for individual finger articulation.<br/></li><li>Quest 2 optical finger tracking app for individual finger articulation and finger separation.<br/></li><li>Vive Pro Eye blink and gaze tracking support.<br/></li><li>Sidekick IOS Face capture app (Truedepth markerless AR facial tracking).<br/></li><li>User customizable Worlds, Avatar and Props may be built for mocap using the APS_SDK.<br/></li><li>Compatible with existing Unity3D™ avatars and environments.<br/></li><li>Supports custom shaders on mocap avatars.<br/></li><li>DynamicBone support for adding hair, clothing and body physics simulation to avatars.<br/></li><li>Breathing simulation for added chest animation.<br/></li><li>Add/Record/Export VR Cameras for realistic camera mocap (eg. VR Cameraman effect).<br/></li><li>Optimization for exporting mocap (.bvh) data to Daz 3D.<br/></li><li>Placement of "streaming" cameras for livestreaming avatars to OBS or as desktop overlays.<br/></li><li>Microphone audio recording with lip-sync visemes and recordable jaw bone rotation.<br/></li><li>Storyboard mode, save mocap experiences as pages for replaying or editing later.<br/></li><li>Animatic video player, display stories and scripts, choreograph movement.<br/></li><li>Dual-handed weapon IK solvers for natural handling of carbines.<br/></li><li>Recordable VTOL platform for animating helicopter flight simulation (eg. news choppers).<br/></li><li>VR Camcorders and VR selfie cams may be rigidly linked to trackers.<br/></li><li>VR props and firearms may be rigidly linked to trackers.<br/></li><li>Ghost curves for visualizing the future locations of multiple avatars in a scene.</li></ul><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/>The experience depends on the user's PC and the tracking hardware used. The recommended <i>SteamVR</i> headsets are the Valve Index or the HTC Vive. A Quest HMD may also produce reasonable results. <i>It is also possible to use the software without an HMD (eg. when livestreaming).</i> Full body tracking is only available when using feet and hip trackers (and optional elbows, knees, chest). Users may achieve more realistic tracking results when using body trackers. Body trackers are optional and standing mocap is supported. Further realism my be achieved on compatible avatars by also enabling face capture or using a Vive Pro Eye for gaze and blink tracking.<br/><br/><strong>History</strong><br/>Originally this was designed as an intuitive way for users to create virtual training videos and presentation in an immersive VR environment for added realism and then export their animation for rendering. The project was made available to a community for beta testing and since has received feedback and many feature requests which has helped add to the utility of the software for a verity of different creators.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Puzzle 4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2703400/Christmas_Puzzle_4/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Elf is back! Play matching levels and complete his quests to restore beautiful town in Winterland. <br/><br/>Build a cozy little cottage on the hill and a cookie factory, fire up the oven and get baking! Think you could whip up a nice batch of muffins? Build an ornament factory, ski workshop and complete dozens of other quests to prepare a fantastic holiday party. Winter has tons of fun in stock for you.<br/>Use incredible powerups to blast through the puzzles and have a fantastic Christmas Puzzle holiday again!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>	225 match-3 levels to play <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703400/extras/gameplay.gif?t=1702801633"><br/><br/></img></li><li>	Complete dozens of quests<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703400/extras/left_building.gif?t=1702801633"><br/><br/></img></li><li>	Follow the Christmas story<br/></li><li>	Build the Elf town<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703400/extras/scene_scroll.gif?t=1702801633"/></li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Game Of Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2600070/The_Game_Of_Death/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a bone-rattling adventure in 'The Game Of Death!' In this unique game, you'll play as Death, the iconic skeleton character, who's just one day away from retirement when a sinister thief robs him of his hard-earned life savings. With your golden years hanging in the balance, it's up to you to reclaim what's rightfully yours and finally set off on that dream vacation.<br>
<br>
Immerse yourself in a vibrant, otherworldly realm teeming with challenging platforming levels, fiendish puzzles, and an array of quirky characters. The clock is ticking as you venture through enchanting landscapes, eerie graveyards, and bizarre dimensions, each with its own distinct challenges and hidden secrets.<br>
<br>
- Key Features:<br>
<br>
- Play as Death, the lovable skeleton character, in a quest to reclaim your life savings.<br/>
- Unearth hidden secrets, solve puzzles, and take on cunning enemies.<br/>
-Slice your enemies with your iconic scythe as you navigate treacherous terrain.<br/>
- Find and capture the alive collectables<br/>
- Complete 60 levels in 12 unique worlds<br/>
- Beat the clock and improve your time<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Join Death on his retirement adventure as he turns the tables on fate itself. Will you help him recover his hard-earned savings and finally enjoy that dream vacation? Get ready for a unique, fun-filled platforming experience in 'The Game Of Death,' where the afterlife has never been so entertaining!"						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Caveman</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2719270/Last_Caveman/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2719270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							What do parachutes, augers and bazookas have in common?<br>
They help the "Cavemen", a troop of irresistible fellows with loincloths and three-day beards, to complete their search for a cozy home with as little loss as possible.<br>
The extremely active cavemen undertake all kinds of breakneck adventures to realize their plan.<br>
You have to make sure that as many of them as possible reach their destination safe and sound. <br>
Assign them various tools and functions so that they can dig, build bridges or jump from great heights. <br>
You have several tutorial levels at your disposal in which you can easily learn how to use all the functions. <br>
Show the Cavemen the right way over hill and dale through desert and ice landscapes, dark primeval forests and mysterious, futuristic areas and get as many of them as possible to their destination unscathed!<br/>
<br/>
Features<br/>
- Different game worlds<br/>
- Tutorial levels to learn the functions<br/>
- Two difficulty levels<br/>
- Hours of challenging entertainment						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Red Beret</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2532720/The_Red_Beret/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2532720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Nazis secretly conducted human experiments on Jews and prisoners of war, and plunged mutants into war. The UK sent a paratrooper team to secretly infiltrate the experimental island to eliminate the super mutants there. Unexpectedly, the plane was shot down by the enemy's Anti-aircraft gun. As the only survivor, Damon is about to complete this seemingly impossible task<br>
The first thing to do is to survive and resist the attacks of the mutants scattered on the island in the first few days<br>
Building bases and weapons with materials obtained through felling trees, mining stones, and collecting resources<br>
Collecting fruits or planting crops to supplement nutrition for the body by capturing prey<br>
There are many types of resources on the island, but you still need to be patient in collecting them						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>小钢炮大冒险 Hot Hatch Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1549630/_Hot_Hatch_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1549630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2>This is a story about a rally racing car crossing into a different world and experiencing various thrilling adventures.<br/>Here, you'll utilize your exceptional driving skills to solve various problems for the inhabitants of this different world. Help goblins with speedy deliveries, assist goblins in finding lost goats, rescue dwarves amidst volcanic eruptions, and more.<h2 class="bb_tag">How to play?</h2>Keyboard controls<br/>W : acceleration<br/>S : braking<br/>A : left turn<br/>D : right turn<br/>Spacebar : handbrake<h2 class="bb_tag">Quick tip:</h2>Engage the handbrake while taking sharp turns, counter-steer, and you'll pull off some impressive drifts.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Within The Depths</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1712460/Within_The_Depths/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1712460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Have you ever had the feeling that you're being watched?</i><br/><br/>Within the Depths is a realistic-fiction horror game with both Singleplayer PvE and Multiplayer PvP action-packed gamemodes!<br/><br/><strong><u>Singleplayer:</u></strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Story Mode</strong>: Navigate carefully avoiding dangerous creatures in an attempt to discover the secrets of this mysterious island and escape. Perhaps there is more going on here than meets the eye...<br/></li><li><strong>Arcade Mode</strong>: Sharpen your skills as you control either a human or the creatures in different scenarios facing off against AI opponents!</li></ul><br/><strong><u>Multiplayer:</u></strong><br/><i>Note from Developer: Multiplayer is not quite ready to release in it's current state, but I will be working on it and releasing it in a future update, hopefully within just a week or two. I'll be posting updates on the discord </i>:)						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PortalSnake</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2614480/PortalSnake/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Puzzle game.<br>
<br>
Bend each level by moving around portals and walls, then press play and watch the snake complete the level.<br>
<br>
Portals can be used to scale, rotate and duplicate snakes.<br>
<br>
50+ levels.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DON'T SHOOT US</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674870/DONT_SHOOT_US/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674870/extras/777.gif?t=1702832698"><br/><br/>⭐ DON’T SHOOT US is a tactical shooter and survival game where players will have to try to survive as long as possible against hordes of infected of all kinds. DON’T SHOOT US offers innovative game mechanics, a unique shooting system, highly developed artificial intelligence. The scenario of DON’T SHOOT US can be compared to a documentary or a report on the daily work of police or military.⭐<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674870/extras/002.gif?t=1702832698"><br/><br/>DONT SHOOT US brings players cutting-edge gameplay, with all-new weapon handling, advanced AI system, photorealistic NANITE technology assets, new armory and other gameplay innovations that elevate this game to total immersion.<br/><br/>Between thugs, infected and allies, don’t shoot too fast ! Who knows ?...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674870/extras/999.gif?t=1702832698"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedgehot - Battle Strike</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1824570/Hedgehot__Battle_Strike/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1824570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Hedgehot - Battle Strike :</strong>  Cards in which reside magical creatures are used to challenge other users and pave a way to the top.<br/><br/><br/>Hedgehot - Battle Strike is a 1 versus 1 Card Game similar to the likes of Heartstone or Runeterra, where using your cards, brain and stamina, you try to defeat your opponent and bring their life points to 0.<br/><br/><strong>Features : </strong> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Friendly Battle - Invite your friends in a lobby to challenge them to prove your skills.<br/></li><li> Online MatchMaking - Find or create a lobby for random players around the world to challenge you. Best place to refine your skills.<br/></li><li> Deck Builder - Choose your favorite cards to challenge others with.<br/></li><li> Shop - Purchase cards to upgrade your deck and create the best possible Meta.</li></ul><br/><br/><strong>Community : </strong><br/>You may join the Hedgehot - Battle Strike official discord to find other battlers and a place to share your experience! <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqvAB8tuCDc" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/qvAB8tuCDc</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metal Rampage Uprising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713890/Metal_Rampage_Uprising/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Metal Rampage: Uprising - plunge into the exciting world of the future, where humanity is in danger from an army of destructive robots. You, in the role of a highly effective combat robot, have become humanity's last hope for salvation.<br>
<br>
Embark on an epic adventure through the abandoned remains of cities, where danger lurks at every turn. Your main goal is to destroy the ruthless army of evil robots and fix the triggers.<br>
<br>
The game is a 2D platformer with puzzle elements. You need to destroy the enemies of the location, collecting special parts from them that will allow you to further progress through the plot.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br/>
- Nice pixel graphics<br/>
- Various enemies and locations<br/>
- Good soundtrack						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metania</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2432190/Metania/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2432190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The story follows Jack, a young man struggling with Mental Illness<br>
 who is tormented by visions, voices, and an inability to remember the past.<br>
 He is determined to uncover the mysterious circumstances of his family's disappearance.<br>
 With only his own unsettled thoughts as his guide.<br>
 Jack embarks on a journey through all distinct Levels in order to unravel this mystery.<br>
 Each stage is filled with locked doors, puzzles,<br>
 and cryptic notes that must be solved to progress, as each step brings him closer to the truth.<br>
 Along the way, John must come to terms with his reality,<br>
 and accept his role in his family's disappearance, revealing a tragedy much more devastating than he could have ever imagined.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OFFROAD VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2715420/OFFROAD_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Offroad VR is an exhilarating virtual reality experience, offering a challenging physics-based offroad driving game. In this game, players must navigate difficult terrains, using gears effectively to overcome obstacles and demonstrating timely reflexes to progress. With different tracks, changing weather conditions, and various vehicle options, this game brings the realistic offroad experience into the virtual world.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
<br>
Physics-Based Challenges: In a game where players encounter real offroad challenges, mastering vehicle control is essential to navigate through challenging terrains.<br>
<br>
Diverse Vehicles: Offroad VR provides a variety of vehicle options, allowing players to explore different experiences—from ATVs to offroad vehicles, delve into various classes of vehicles to conquer the tracks.<br/>
<br/>
Different Tracks and Weather Conditions: The game offers an exciting offroad experience with varying track difficulties and different weather conditions. Conquer challenges in snow, rain, mud, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Explore Offroad VR:<br/>
<br/>
Offroad VR combines adrenaline-pumping offroad adventures with virtual reality, providing gamers with a realistic driving experience. Explore different tracks with various vehicles and push the limits of your offroad passion.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowman Story</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635930/Snowman_Story/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is the story of a snowman named Chris. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635930/extras/steam_banner01.png?t=1702716912"><br/>Brought to life one cold winter's day by a lonely boy in need of a playmate, Chris is content with his simple existence. But when a cackling crow reveals to him one night that he'll melt away as soon as the weather warms, Chris must embark on a long journey to a paradise far to the north, where it's said that snowmen can survive even the coming of spring.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635930/extras/steam_banner.png?t=1702716912"><br/>Along the way, he'll encounter a host of friendly woodland critters who'll guide him on his trek, and help him tackle tricky ice puzzles whenever things get slippery. (Note that these puzzles are fully skippable for players who just want to enjoy the story!)<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635930/extras/steam_banner02.png?t=1702716912"><br/>He'll also come across other snowmen who tried but failed to make the very same pilgrimage, and gain the ability to read the memories embedded in their melted remains. Hopefully, by learning how they met their tragic ends, Chris can avoid the same fate.<br/><br/>After all—what meaning can there possibly be in a life that lasts but a single winter?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635930/extras/steam_banner03.jpg?t=1702716912"><br/>A wintertime tale of warmth and friendship that'll surely melt your heart, Snowman Story is the perfect game to curl up with by the fire this (or any) holiday season.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Substance 3D Painter 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2718190/Substance_3D_Painter_2024/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2718190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
<strong>Adobe Substance 3D Painter</strong> is the reference texturing app for 3D professionals and enthusiasts. From AAA Game Developers to Indies, from Feature Animation to Visual Effects studios, the industry uses Painter to bring their creations to life thanks to its unparalleled speed, flexibility and visual quality.<br/><br/><strong>You will get free updates on Steam up to the end of 2024</strong><br/><br/><strong>Substance 3D Painter adapts to you, no matter your skill level</strong><br/>Use Smart materials and have textures wrap onto your objects automatically, throw particles to easily add weathering effects with the help of the integrated physics engine or paint precise micro-details across complex asset spanning over dozens of textures sets or UDIMs.<br/><br/><strong>Texture assets for any target renderer or game engine</strong><br/>Substance 3D Painter is compatible with Unity, Unreal, Amazon Lumberyard, VRay, Arnold, Renderman... No matter what your final platform is, Painter can convert your textures into the right format and give you results as close as can be from what you see in the viewport.<br/><br/><strong>Welcome to the community</strong><br/>The Substance 3D community is made of some of the most helpful and talented artists in the world! Have a question or need some guidance? Join us on Discord or on our official forums, there is always someone ready to help. <br/>Want a specific material or effect but don't have the skill or patience to create it yourself? Join the more than 100 000 users on the Substance 3D Community Assets website (previously Substance Share) and download some of the hundreds of free assets available to help you in your artistic journey.<br/><br/><strong>This license does not include access to the Substance 3D Assets platform (previously Substance Source).</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hazordhu</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1509810/Hazordhu/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1509810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Delve into the low-fantasy medieval lands of Hazordhu, where you will explore a vast open world full of dangers and wonders where every building and every item is player-made, and the online world changes based on your actions. Play locally or online, and join the official community on the website and/or discord.<br/><br/>Begin as a humble nobody, and develop your skills to become whatever you wish to be!<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Play offline and explore the world in peaceful solitude, or host your own Community Server for anyone to join!<br/></li><li> Explore a massive, open world full of unique creatures and dangerous enemies<br/></li><li> Survive against the growing threats of the wilderness and other players<br/></li><li> Thrive and grow your base into a flourishing settlement</li></ul><br/>Live your fantasy life with tools and skills specifically tailored to an immersive roleplay experience<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Hundreds of unique items and buildings to craft<br/></li><li> Hunt, gather, build and grow your way from surviving to thriving<br/></li><li> 9 Distinct skills to develop and grow<br/></li><li> Community driven development, including the original soundtrack and artwork</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Huddled Together 挤在一起的猫猫们</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2675630/Cats_Huddled_Together/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2675630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to "Cats Huddled Together"<br>
This is a cat-themed jigsaw puzzle game where each piece features an adorable cat. It requires your patience and dexterity to bring the cats together. Come and take up the challenge!<br>
<br>
-----Game Controls------<br>
<br>
- Drag the puzzle pieces with the left mouse button.<br>
- Rotate the puzzle pieces with the right mouse button.<br>
- Press the Q key to hide or show the game UI.<br/>
- You can toggle the cat sound effects on or off in the settings.<br/>
<br/>
-----Game Features------<br/>
<br/>
- 1,000 adorable hand-drawn cats.<br/>
- 24 levels with varying numbers of pieces.<br/>
- An immersive puzzle experience.<br/>
- Cute cat sound effects.<br/>
- Relaxing background music.<br/>
<br/>
------------------------						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Black Guards of Odom - Desert Town Prison</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687990/The_Black_Guards_of_Odom__Desert_Town_Prison/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687990/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1702749724"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687990/extras/Black_Guard_Description_1_EN.png?t=1702749724"><br/>You just joined the guards in Odom, a border town full of merchants, travelers, and shady individuals. However, it doesn't take long for the skilled and talented to rise above the rest. A bit of elbow grease will allow you to quickly climb the ranks and unlock the many perks that come with promotions.<br/><br/>Your initial main task as a foot soldier will be to patrol the districts, where you'll scan the alleyways for suspicious individuals and search them for illicit goods. Like many guards in many towns, even the sentinels of Odom are corrupt... Will you choose to fine the criminals and pocket some of the money, or arrest them to advance your career? Both options will help you in one way or the other.<br/><br/>The more promotions you earn, the more perks you'll unlock. Soon you'll get to patrol richer districts, and even command your own rank-and-file soldiers to do your work for you. As a commanding officer, your subordinates' achievements also become your own! Some of the higher ranks will require buttering up your superiors, but your increased pay and a bit of saving will make short work of that, too.<br/><br/>Boundless opportunities await a ruthless and corrupt guard, and your only limit is your imagination. How far will your ambitions take you?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687990/extras/Black_Guard_Description_2_EN.png?t=1702749724"><br/>Learn the layout of the town as you patrol the four districts. Criminals tend to stick to certain corners that you'll soon identify, making every sortie quick and profitable. Search and interrogate suspicious individuals and choose whether to arrest or fine them depending on your current goals.<br/><br/>Earn promotions that will both make your patrol work easier, as well as grant you access to certain privileges!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687990/extras/Black_Guard_Description_4_EN.png?t=1702749724"><br/><strong>Promotions and perks</strong><br/>You'll have to work hard to climb the ranks, but with every promotion you get, you'll unlock specific perks that will make your job easier or increase your array of possibilities. You'll earn little more than a pay increase at first, but soon you'll gain access to the underground prison and even get subordinates of your own. What kind of power will you wield once you climb to the very top?<br/><br/><strong>Powered by Live2D</strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Moor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2700010/Last_Moor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About this game</strong><br/><br/>Last Moor is a horror game in which a man wakes up and escapes from a secret laboratory on the moon.<br/><br/>He infiltrated the lab to treat his terminally ill daughter, but after losing consciousness, everyone in the lab disappeared.<br/><br/>Will he be able to solve various puzzles and escape by exploring this laboratory with only monsters?<br/><br/><strong>Characteristics</strong><br/><br/>Last Moor is a horror game in which you solve several puzzles, get a key and password, and escape. There are monsters in some areas and you have to hide or run away from them. Of course you could fight if you had a weapon!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Voice from the Well: The Velessar Saga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2293860/The_Voice_from_the_Well_The_Velessar_Saga/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2293860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Stranded in a foreign world, Jay must fight to reclaim his stolen memories as mysterious forces conspire!</strong><br/>The Voice from the Well: The Velessar Saga is an adaption of the improved first arc of the Velessar Saga. Set in a fantasy realm inspired by historical dark ages Scandinavia and filled with mystery. <br/><br/>The game follows soon-to-be seventh grader Jay, as he finds himself stranded in a dark forest. Mysterious forces are at play as he wakes up the next day only able to remember the events of the day before. Jay sets out to reclaim his lost memories!<h2 class="bb_tag">Player choice</h2>Choices made throughout the game will lead to alternate endings and new scenes. Each ending is a glimpse into what could have been and several are hints at future developments later in the Velessar Saga.<h2 class="bb_tag">Fully voiced cast</h2>The diverse cast of characters from The Voice from the Well has been brought to life with voice acting for each character! With an immersive soundtrack and sound effects, headphones are highly recommended!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jisatsu | 自撮</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2716110/Jisatsu/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Jisatsu | 自撮</strong> is a Japanese found footage mockumentary horror game.<br/><br/><i>Removed VHS filter and Headbob for a better experience.</i><br/><i>Supporter content can be turned on and off on the title screen.</i><br/><br/>Key Features:<br/><br/>Immersive experience: An atmospheric, believable environment intensifies the horror experience.<br/><br/>Psychological horror: The game will drive you insane.<br/><br/>Japanese Theme: Environment art inspired by Japanese horror films.<br/><br/>AutoSave: Autosaves every chapter.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Born Again</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2332210/Born_Again/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2332210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Fight, Die, and Repeat in the realms of Born Again! A thrilling permadeath, rogue-like, MMORPG where every life is full of challenges and rewards at every turn. Embark on a fateful journey to defeat the enemies bringing disorder to the Outer Realms. Face off against kings, rulers, and deities all fighting for their reign in this pixel-art world filled with charm and excitement.<br>
<br>
Born Again offers fast-paced, action-packed combat with its hack-n-slash gameplay mechanics that will keep you on your toes. Engage in exhilarating battles with hordes of enemies using a variety of weapons and unleash unique abilities to turn the tide of battle in your favor. As you progress, you'll have the opportunity to customize your play-style by choosing from a wide selection of items and blessings to equip, tailoring your character's abilities and powers to suit your play-style.<br>
<br>
But beware, Born Again is not for the faint of heart. Death is inevitable and not the end, but rather a chance to be Born Again to anew with fresh opportunities and challenges. Take on the rulers of the realm, challenging boss battles that will test your skills to the limit, and prove yourself as a true hero of the realm.<br>
<br>
With its charming pixel-art graphics, Born Again offers a unique visual style that is both nostalgic and captivating. Explore a vast world filled with secrets, treasures, and mysteries waiting to be uncovered. Dive into the chaotic world and unravel the mysteries of the world as you progress through the game.<br/>
<br/>
Born Again is not just about the battles, but also about the loot. Discover and equip a wide range of items, weapons, and armor as you explore the world and defeat enemies. Each item has its own niche and properties, allowing you to strategically plan your loadout and adapt to various situations.<br/>
<br/>
Are you ready to be Born Again and embark on an epic adventure filled with hack-n-slash action, rogue-like challenges, and thrilling boss battles? Join the fray in Born Again and experience an MMORPG like no other!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bwudaling: Da Fight for da Bwudahood</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2681660/Bwudaling_Da_Fight_for_da_Bwudahood/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2681660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The game nobody wanted but everyone needed. The evil Twent has attacked, bringing his minions with him, as well as hundreds of saws to block your path. Dodge, duck, dip, dive, and dodge to prove your love for Bwuda, the almighty, as you track Twent down to his evil lair, and finish him once and for all.<br/><br/>Bwudaling is the next great bullet hell, where you'll use the unique abilities of one of 4 classes to bring yourself and your friends past the waves of saws sent to stop you, tracking down the bosses found at the ends of all 3 map packs. With the truly immaculate character customization you'll find, featuring almost 20 entire (mostly distinct) unlockable <i>AND WEARABLE</i> t-shirts, you won't want to miss out on the future 2053 GOTY						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloompunk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2456330/Bloompunk/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2456330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2456330/extras/About-game-final.png?t=1702678919"><br/><br/>Bloompunk is a rogue-like FPS hybrid set in a vibrant world of animated plants. By combining biological and mechanical technology, harness the power of nature, grow your living arsenal of weapons and abilities, and fight back against biomechanical forces intent on disrupting the world's natural balance in this action-packed, non-stop frenzy of bullets, light, and thorns.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2456330/extras/gameplay-final.png?t=1702678919"><h2 class="bb_tag">Restore a Dying World</h2>Embark on a journey of redemption as you emerge into a world on the verge of environmental collapse. Become nature's vengeance as you, an adaptive bioengineer, must destroy your own biomechanical creations threatening to consume all plant-life throughout the forest. Battle through verdant foliage and destroy the invading technological corruption on your path to restore balance.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2456330/extras/Environment_Banner_Gif.gif?t=1702678919"><h2 class="bb_tag">Grow Your Living Arsenal</h2>Unlock powerful abilities that augment your playstyle and unleash deadly attacks! From summoning solar lasers to blasting through the air, the choice is yours. However, use your unlocked abilities wisely to survive waves of enemies intent on thwarting you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2456330/extras/Upgrade_Gif.gif?t=1702678919"><h2 class="bb_tag">Relentless Action</h2>Bloompunk features fast-paced first-person shooter combat. Experience a polished movement system that allows you to run, slide, and glide through the air as you evade enemies, traverse the world, and dish out destruction from any vantage in the forest. How long can you endure?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2456330/extras/Bloompunk_Gameplay_2_Resize.gif?t=1702678919"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2456330/extras/About-Dev-final.png?t=1702678919"><br/><br/>Bloompunk was created as part of the University of Southern California’s Advanced Game Project (AGP) in collaboration with Cal State Fullerton and Otis College of Art and Design. For more information, please visit our publishing page. To learn more about the USC Games program, the #1 game program in the world, please visit the website listed on the right side of the store page.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2456330/extras/USC_Games_edited.png?t=1702678919"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeju's fantasy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2223530/Jejus_fantasy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2223530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A dark spell has been casted over most of the creature to gain control over them. Venture into an atmospheric world as you become the hero of this story and try to restore normality. <br/><br/><strong>Craft unique weapons</strong><br/>Collect items as you advance in your adventure and use them as materials. Some rare items can become very powerful weapons.<br/><br/><strong>Choose your companion</strong><br/>Don't explore this beautiful world alone! Make new friends and uncover pets to travel with you and complement your fighting abilities.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Dialogue</strong><br/>Choose your answers as you progress through the story and receive different outcomes.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reign of the Renegade</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2306530/Reign_of_the_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2306530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Reign of the Renegade is a challenging roguelite deckbuilder. Learn Actions, Collect Artifacts, and level up your Character to make powerful synergies.<br/><br/><strong>3 Unique Characters</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2306530/extras/Characters.gif?t=1702672024"><br/>Overwhelm enemies with your strength as the Warrior, dive into the shadows and strike as the Rogue, or center yourself and unleash channeled blasts as the Monk. Each character has their own style, as well as advantages and disadvantages.<br/><br/><strong>12 Different Classes</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2306530/extras/12_Classes.gif?t=1702672024"><br/>Hone each Character's playstyle further by picking from one of their classes. Will you be a fist-flinging Berserker, or a calculated Executioner?<br/><br/><strong>300 Actions to Master</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2306530/extras/Actions.gif?t=1702672024"><br/><br/><strong>100+ Artifacts to Collect</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2306530/extras/Artifacts.gif?t=1702672024"><br/><br/><strong>100+ Enemies to Vanquish</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2306530/extras/Enemies.gif?t=1702672024"><br/><br/>Can you beat the odds, and will that be enough to end the Reign of the Renegade?						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Academy's Special Place</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2002010/My_Academys_Special_Place/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2002010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2><br/>At the academy that our hero attends, his homeroom teacher also happens to be his older sister, Yaeka.<br/><br/>As an instructor, she is distinguished and very popular among the students. <br/>Her only real flaws are that she's always drunk and kind of a slob when she's at home.<br/><br/>One of the hero's classmates is Maika, an exchange student and big Akiba nerd. Once classes are over, she's always inviting him to wandering about Akihabara with her. <br/><br/>At this point, the hero is used to seeing her buying up doujinshi and doujin games, a skewer of grilled squid in one hand.<br/><br/>He thought that these days would continue on forever.<br/><br/>But a sudden request for Maika to return to her home country changes everything.<br/><br/>Alongside Yaeka, who is also Maika's homeroom teacher, he tries to help Maika out, but...<br/><br/>With the "Academy's Special Place" as the stage, two love stories are about to begin.<br/><br/>This is the third and final game in the series!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Art by Ryohka<br/></li><li>Fully-voiced (except the MC)<br/></li><li>Text available in Japanese, English, and Simplified Chinese<br/></li><li>CG Gallery Mode available</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zeitghast</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2593070/Zeitghast/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2593070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2593070/extras/Zeitghast_Store_Header.png?t=1702671399"><br/><br/>Zeitghast is a fast-paced, action-packed <strong>sidescrolling Platformer-Shooter</strong> in which you navigate a technologically enhanced prehistoric world. Take on the role of a <strong>Zeitghast</strong>--A magical time spirit tasked with protecting the timeline, and <strong>stop the evil Dr. Antag O’Neste</strong> as he travels back in time to take credit for every invention that ever existed.<h2 class="bb_tag">Race Through a Variety of Unique Stages!</h2>Traverse a multitude of challenging levels by jumping, dashing, shooting, and slashing! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2593070/extras/Zeitghast_Gif_5.gif?t=1702671399"><h2 class="bb_tag">Over a Dozen Unique Weapons!</h2>An ice cannon, a rocket launcher, and even a fire-breathing lizard?! There are a wide variety of weapons to pick from, so grab your favorite and start shootin’ and slashin’.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2593070/extras/Zeitghast_Gif_4.gif?t=1702671399"><h2 class="bb_tag">Time is Money!</h2>Time is the common currency and lifeforce for our Zeitghast protagonist. You can earn more time by collecting time tokens in the level, or by defeating enemies! However, be careful not to run out of time.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2593070/extras/Zeitghast_Gif_6.gif?t=1702671399"><h2 class="bb_tag">Discover Secrets In Every Stage!</h2>Be on the lookout for time-saving secrets, hidden weapons, and of course, collectibles in every stage!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2593070/extras/Zeitghast_Gif_2.gif?t=1702671399"><h2 class="bb_tag">Fight Dangerous Enemies!</h2>Fight powerful enemies originating both from the rift between space-time and Dr. Antag’s army of cyborg dinosaurs!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2593070/extras/Zeitghast_Gif_7.gif?t=1702671399"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orcish Skies</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2510680/Orcish_Skies/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Fly to the aid of the Fifty Clans in this Tactical Roguelike Deckbuilder set high in the skies above the Terrestrial Plane.  Customize your airship with new cards, equipment, techniques, powers and passives to take on the worst that the Korblian Empire can throw at you.<br>
<br>
While Chieftain Rugana is no stranger to combat, she brings in some outside help and some unlikely allies to help her people show the Empire the door.  From the wild and volatile elven mage Llari, to the Cutthroat Rakshasa Arms Dealer, Smoke.  Choose one of five characters, each with 120 unique cards and 130+ unique upgrades.  Every character has dozens of unique strategies and playstyles, there's endless room to experiment, discover your favorites, or even brew up something all your own.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Split Polarity: The Science Puzzle Arcade Game!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2655020/Split_Polarity_The_Science_Puzzle_Arcade_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2655020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong><u>Find a friend and prepare for divisive immateriality and opposing gravity in <i>Split Polarity!</i> </u></strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2655020/extras/Screenshot_5_small.png?t=1702668749"><br/><br/>The atoms have become unstable, so its your job to guide the highly volatile particles into the black holes. Play against friends in local multiplayer in Versus Mode, or attempt a high score in the Labyrinth.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong><u>Versus</u></strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2655020/extras/Screenshot_1_small_.png?t=1702668749"><br/><br/>Compete against friends in a competitive puzzle which will turn your head upside down! Try to guide your atoms into the black holes, use the numerous random power ups, and try to not collide with your opponents...unless you want an atomic collision that is!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong><u>Labyrinth</u></strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2655020/extras/Screenshot_4_small.png?t=1702668749"><br/><br/>Want to test your atomic skills? Try to get the highest score possible in Labyrinth mode! The task is a very simple one - dodge the radioactive wormholes, and collect quarks to make your atom stable once again. However, science is never that simple!<br/><br/>Remember, this isn't rocket science. Just <strong>Quantum Physics!</strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
