<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>9 Days</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2075720/9_Days/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>GET READY FOR THE FIGHT, TIME IS TICKING!</strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075720/extras/GIF_02_24_02.gif?t=1709917242"><br/><br/>You have 9 Days to explore the vast world to find the best skills and items for the final fight. Choose carefully where you go and how you spend your time. Remember, you only have 9 days!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CRAFT YOUR FIGHTNING STYLE</strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075720/extras/GIF_01_24_02.gif?t=1709917242"><br/><br/>Craft your own style of fighting by mixing different Ki Attacks, Dodges and Melee Strikes together.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>YOU HAVE 9 DAYS</strong></h2>During the 9th day, the time for exploration is over. You will be confronted by Afran to determine the fate of the world.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchors Blockade Zone:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2819850/Anchors_Blockade_ZonePrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FPZHEvJTz65" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/dss.png?t=1709912394"/></a><br/><br/><strong>Difference between Prologue and Official Edition<br/>Prologue opens up a map</strong><br/><strong>Anchor: Blockade Zone game, is a collection of gun modification, exploring the map, death drop equipment of the Cthulhu theme 2D pixel style shooter. The game puts you in the role of an agent who enters a blockade zone to investigate with the aim of finding out the cause of the strange events in the blockade zone. Your character is trapped in the blockade and has to search for food, water and other supplies in order to survive, as well as completing quests to gather information and find the truth. In the process, don't be too surprised to encounter anything unnatural, whether it's going back in time or to the future. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/1y.png?t=1709912394"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/战斗.gif?t=1709912394"><br/><strong>Experience exhilarating shooting, fight sworn battles with hostile agents, Kraken monsters, and more, and beat the truth out of the world with the weapons in your hands! Poor for tactical penetration, rich for fire coverage, it's all up to you! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/2y.png?t=1709912394"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/改枪.gif?t=1709912394"><br/><strong>We strive to make you feel the thrill of 2d shooting, so that you can feel the real shooting experience.<br/>Up to hundreds of gun accessories, allowing you to freely remodel your exclusive weapon! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/3y.png?t=1709912394"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/仓库.gif?t=1709912394"><br/><strong>Recruit agents for your exploration operations and train them to grow into excellent agents to help you complete various missions and search various maps.<br/>Each exploration map is a repeated horizontal jump across the edge of life and death for agents, with different maps having different chances of resulting in an agent's outright death. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/4y.png?t=1709912394"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/搜索.gif?t=1709912394"><br/>Explore the map carefully and make sure your agent gets back to base safe and sound every time.<br/><strong>If an agent is unlucky enough to die or return to the city with serious injuries, the items he is carrying and searching for will be dropped with him. Only items placed in the safe will be retained. </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMERHOUSE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2533960/SUMMERHOUSE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2533960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2533960/extras/summerhouse_new_store_page.gif?t=1709984408"><br/><br/>SUMMERHOUSE is a small-scale building game and a love letter to the feeling of long lost summer afternoons.<br/><br/>Craft a neighbourhood of tiny, beautiful lived-in homes in a variety of settings: the sea, the city, or the mountains. While there are some little secrets to uncover, there are no rules, and you can’t win or lose. Just chill out, build to your heart’s content and soak up the atmosphere.<br/><br/>If relaxation and creation are your thing, this is a game for you :)<br/><br/><i>Please keep in mind that this is a small game with no goals or challenges, created by a single person🙂</i> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORE BLASTERS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/BORE_BLASTERS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/BLAST.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_blast_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Blast your way through rocks and dirt with your machinegun drill. Carve through the ground to uncover precious ores and defeat menacing foes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/LOOT.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_loot_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Uncover ancient relics and artefacts hidden in the deep. Amass a fortune in rare gems &amp; ores.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/UPGRADE.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_mortar_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Invest in powerful upgrades and unlock new abilities, turning your humble gyrocopter into a fearsome force to be reckoned with.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/DISCOVER.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_discover_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Explore a diverse range of biomes, from treacherous volcanic caverns to lush overgrown underground forests, each with its own unique challenges and rewards.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/FEATURES.png?t=1709907021"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Intense mining action with fast-paced blasting<br/></li><li> Constant progress - even failed runs aren't punishing<br/></li><li> Diverse biomes to explore<br/></li><li> Purchase upgrades to overpower your gyrocopter<br/></li><li> Navigate the overworld to unlock new mine shafts<br/></li><li> Collect and loot rare gems, ores, and artefacts to upgrade your gear and abilities<br/></li><li> Endless replayability with procedurally generated levels</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_drones_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/><br/>Drawing inspiration from mining games like Motherload and Galactic Mining Corp, Bore Blasters takes the genre to the next level with high octane action and fast paced gameplay. Fans of digging and collecting will find plenty to love, while the addition of deadly enemies and mysterious artefacts will keep even the most seasoned miners on their toes.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/WL_arrow.gif?t=1709907021"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_missiles_frame.gif?t=1709907021"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Realm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1330000/Stolen_Realm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/GreenDragon.gif?t=1709885067"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TURN-BASED STRATEGY MEETS ACTION RPG IN THIS DUNGEON CRAWLING LOOTER</strong></h2><br/><br/>Stolen Realm is a <strong>simultaneous turn-based tactical dungeon crawling looter with action RPG elements</strong> where you control up to <strong>6 heroes, solo or through online co-op</strong>, venturing forth in adventures set in a high-fantasy, low-poly world. <br/><br/>Stolen Realm features an <strong>innovative turn-based combat system</strong> where <strong>simultaneous turns</strong> allow every team to take their actions at once, creating quick combat encounters that blend the tactical depth of titles like Divinity: Original Sin with the thrill of a fast-paced action RPG. Every battle scales based on the number of players involved, so you can easily jump in and out of the game even in the same playthrough!<br/> <br/>With a <strong>highly customisable class system</strong>, Stolen Realm allows you to create traditional RPG classes or break the mold to forge a unique champion of your own as you draw from a pool of hundreds of possible skills. Make a spell-slinging assassin, a priest born of frost, or a shadow-infused knight. Further customize your build by earning and reforging <strong>loot that truly changes the way you play</strong>: wield Abbadon the Soul Crusher, a mythic mace that raises slain enemies as skeletal warriors to fight for you, or unsheath the Bloodletter, a cursed sword that grants additional power at the cost of your lifeblood. D&amp;D-like events where attribute-based rolls will have permanent effects on your character add yet another layer to building a character that is truly your own. Anything is possible in this title that keeps compelling choices at the forefront of your experience.  <br/><br/>Keeping the core appeal of RPGs at its forefront, Stolen Realm ensures you spend all your time, fighting, building your characters and making compelling choices that determine your immediate path or effect your character, rather than getting bogged down in side quests and other RPG-bloat.   After each battle, pick your path between story events, resource gathering, shops and treasure rooms, until you get to the final boss of each <strong>procedurally generated adventure.</strong> If you’re up to a challenge, crank the difficulty up with <strong>6 different difficulty levels</strong> – or pick <strong>Hardcore Mode with permadeath</strong>, where every battle can be the last!<br/><br/>Also features <strong>Roguelike Mode</strong>, a fast paced version of the game where you can mix and match builds that are simply not possible in the traditional campaign!<br/><br/>Carve a place in history with your sword and magic. Rise to honor and glory in the battlefield. <strong>Recover the Stolen Realm.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/CycloneKick.gif?t=1709885067"><h2 class="bb_tag">PRAISE FOR STOLEN REALM</h2><br/>“The tactical depth of Divinity: Original Sin” - GamesRadar+<br/><br/>“we’re losing our evenings to… Stolen Realm” - TheXboxHub<br/><br/>“A gorgeous looking game” - PC Gamer<br/><br/>“You can be a fire warrior. You can be a healing necromancer. You can do all sorts of weird s**t.” - <strong>Sacriel</strong><br/><br/>“What I like about this game is it’s straight to the point. You just go in, you’re building your character, you’re getting items…and you just fight. There’s no bulls**t.” - <strong>Shroud</strong><br/><br/>“It’s rad” - <strong>Sequisha</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/Dwarven_Warmachine.gif?t=1709885067"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>KEY FEATURES</strong></h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play solo or with friends in up to 6 player online co-op, allowing you and your friends to wreak havoc amongst your foes<br/></li><li>Experience thrilling and fast-paced turn-based battles thanks to a simultaneous team turn system<br/></li><li>Full story campaign, roguelike mode and streamer mode<br/></li><li>Use over 300 skills in 10 distinct skill trees allowing for complete and flexible character customization<br/></li><li>Navigate hex-based battlefields where positioning is key due to battle shrines with special effects, exploding barrels and movable crates<br/></li><li>Find and loot over 700 unique items, fully customizable with modifiers, as you explore a wonderful world full of magic, secrets and unexpected dangers<br/></li><li>Co-op focused design keeps gameplay fast paced and strategic for up to 6 players <br/></li><li>Easy drop-in, drop-out design and automatic scaling that allows you to join or drop out mid-quest <br/></li><li>D&amp;D-like attribute-based rolls in special events that have permanent character effects<br/></li><li>Fight against over 200 types of enemies in battles that will be different every time: thanks to the Enemy Modifications feature, every creature you face on the battlefield will be unique<br/></li><li>A world that changes on each expedition, from frosty peaks guarded by the elusive Blue Dragon to overgrown jungles where the rock giants roam. <br/></li><li>Pick your path between battles, choosing where to go between story events, resource gathering, shops, fights, and treasure rooms until you get to the final boss of each adventure<br/></li><li>6 different difficulty levels<br/></li><li>Choose between Normal Mode and Hardcore Mode with permadeath if you want a real challenge!</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE 2K24</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2315690/WWE_2K24/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2315690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							FORTY YEARS OF WRESTLEMANIA<br>
<br>
WrestleMania is the biggest event in sports entertainment, where Superstars become WWE Legends. Experience a gripping retelling of WrestleMania’s greatest moments in 2K Showcase of the Immortals, where you can relive a collection of some of the most unforgettable, career-defining matches.<br>
<br>
AN ICONIC ROSTER<br>
<br>
WWE 2K24 boasts a star-studded roster featuring WWE Legends like “Stone Cold” Steve Austin, Undertaker, and Andre the Giant, alongside current WWE Superstars like “The American Nightmare” Cody Rhodes, John Cena, Rhea Ripley, and Roman Reigns, whose larger-than-life entrances and signature moves are heightened by ultra-realistic graphics.<br>
<br>
NEW MATCH TYPES<br>
<br>
From Guest Referee to Casket, Gauntlet, and Ambulance matches, there are a bevy of new match types to experience in WWE 2K24, including support for multiple Superstars in Backstage Brawl.<br>
<br>
PROVE YOURSELF IN MyRISE<br>
<br>
Unleash your raw talent and become the undisputed champ in MyRISE, featuring two thrilling career arcs and original storylines chronicling your ascent to WWE stardom from the men's and women’s divisions.<br>
<br>
BUILD YOUR FACTION<br>
<br>
Assemble your favorite WWE Superstars and Legends in MyFACTION. Acquire cards, build a dominant faction, compete in online multiplayer and the all-new ranked quickplay. Plus, earn exciting promotional and final rank rewards as you climb the new seasonal leaderboard!<br>
<br>
CONTROL THE WWE UNIVERSE<br>
<br>
Develop feuds, weekly shows, and more in Universe mode, WWE 2K24’s ultimate sandbox, with expanded rivalry actions, all-new cutscenes, and support for double-title matches!<br>
<br>
CALL THE SHOTS IN MyGM<br>
<br>
Oversee the biggest brands and Superstars in sports entertainment as you challenge rival general managers for the top spot in MyGM. Explore more match types, more brands, and new general managers. Trade Superstars between brands, make executive decisions on contracts, and amp up the drama.<br/>
<br/>
**Online play including MyFACTION requires an internet connection and 2K Account. Terms apply.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duelists of Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1664200/Duelists_of_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/DoE_EVO_Trailer_-_steam_gif_short_30fps.gif?t=1709925308"><br/>Duelists of Eden is a card-grid-fighting game set after the events of One Step From Eden. Build your custom deck and battle online in real-time action! There are over 14 unique characters with strengths and weaknesses to encourage creative spell combinations and synergies. Will you combo slashes, fire, or even use bombs to eliminate your competition?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/SaffronWitch_steam_header-features.gif?t=1709925308"><h2 class="bb_tag">Deckbuilding</h2>Fight in a mix of strategy and real-time action! Create your own unique combination of spells to take down the competition. <br/>Save and edit an unlimited amount of decks in the editor!<h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic cardtridge and combo system</h2>Create combos on the fly, adapting the scenario and what spells you and your opponent have.<h2 class="bb_tag">Tutorial and training mode</h2>Learn the ropes in the tutorial mode and deep dive into the mechanics via training mode. <br/>Training mode includes hitboxes, character states, quick deck edits, speed modifiers, and more!<h2 class="bb_tag">Custom rollback netcode</h2>The game was completely rebuilt to support custom rollback netcode, for the smoothest experience possible.<h2 class="bb_tag">Replay mode</h2>Review your matches in replay mode!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/Selicy_OSFE_gif_steam.gif?t=1709925308"><br/><br/>Local multiplayer may require a controller.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Keeper Gold™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1996630/Dungeon_Keeper_Gold/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Being the Dungeon Keeper and all, this is your home, too. And it’s your business to take these loathsome creatures of darkness and hone them into screaming, frothing, clawing forces of destruction. Lure them in with food and the promise of dank and fetid places to sleep. Keep them in line with the back of your hand and the threat of dire consequences. Pit their scaly hides against the best that the Forces of Good can muster, and they’ll die for you as they rip steaming entrails out of the hapless heroes.<br/><br/>It’s a degenerate and nasty job…and you love it. Yes, home is where your heart is. In a box. Packed in salt. That's right — Dungeon Keeper, Bullfrog's classic dungeon management strategy, gives you no extra credit for having any morals. After all, the underworld isn't black and white!<br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Revolutionary game packed with tons of dark humor, an impressive variety of hellish creatures, and highly addictive gameplay<br/></li><li>Build your dungeon &amp; protect it with a labyrinth of dark corridors, a web of deadly traps, an arsenal of powerful spells, and an army of bloodthirsty demons<br/></li><li>A refreshing title for someone tired of rescuing princesses, saving worlds, and all that love, happiness, and political correctness junk. Just this once, be the bad guy!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals Zero Hour</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732960/Command__Conquer_Generals_Zero_Hour/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals Zero Hour brings you closer to the enemy than ever before. Engage opposing forces at hot spots around the globe as you match strategies and arsenals against the new masterminds of modern war.<br/><br/><strong>Arsenal.</strong> Unleash the next generation of 3D new units and 20 new upgrades including China's ECM Tank, GLA's BattleBus and the USA's Spectre Gunship.<br/><br/><strong>Missions.</strong> Take on 15 new missions and make tomorrow's headlines. Root out a splinter cell in Cairo, steal deadly toxins from a U.S. lab and more.<br/><br/><strong>Generals.</strong> Match strategies and arsenals against 9 enemy commanders with unpredictable personalities and tactics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Tiberian Sun™ and Firestorm™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229880/Command__Conquer_Tiberian_Sun_and_Firestorm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Second Tiberium War begins in this legendary sequel to the original Command &amp; Conquer. <br/><br/>With his forces stronger than ever, arch villain and leader of The Brotherhood of Nod - Kane - is pitched in an epic battle against the world's war machine - the Global Defense Initiative. Now you must orchestrate the fate of mankind.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on Dynamic Battlefields. Nature itself provides tactical opportunities - destroyable and deformable terrain, forest fires, treacherous ice fields and many more surprises that help or hinder your strategies.<br/></li><li>Exciting New Strategies and Units. Jump Jet Infantry, Hover Tanks, Tunneling APCs, Hunter Seekers, Laser Fences, Mechanized Battle Units and many more.<br/></li><li>The "Veterancy" Factor. Units can become faster and stronger as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>New Kinetic Battlefields. Flying shrapnel, shock waves and crashing debris are just a few of the exciting new technologies developed to enhance the in-game experience.<br/></li><li>The mood and attitude of the battlefield comes alive like never before - covert night missions, searchlights and new defenses intensify the thrill and excitement.</li></ul><br/>Then take the battle further in <strong>Firestorm, the official expansion pack for the game</strong>. Includes all-new campaign missions, cinematics, and units to decide the future of mankind.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Renegade™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229890/Command__Conquer_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer gets up close and personal in this classic First Person Shooter for one of the most iconic franchises.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wreak Havoc</strong> - Experience the Command &amp; Conquer universe on foot as Havoc, wise-cracking GDI Commando.<br/></li><li><strong>Make Your Own Rules</strong>  - Take on the evil Brotherhood of Nod using your own mix of brute force, stealth, and strategy.<br/></li><li><strong>Assault at Ground Level</strong>  - Dish out the damage in either first or third person.<br/></li><li><strong>Total Access</strong>  - Sneak inside and explore full-scale structures, like immense Tiberium Refineries and the ominous Hand of Nod.<br/></li><li><strong>Grind the Gears</strong>  - Beef up your arsenal by commandeering lethal vehicles, such as Nod Buggies, Flame Tanks, and Mammoth Tanks.<br/></li><li><strong>Weapons of Mass Destruction</strong>  - Choose from a multitude of weapons, including the Tiberium Auto Rifle, Chemical Sprayer, and the devasting Personal Ion Cannon.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Keeper™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2616460/Dungeon_Keeper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2616460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Discover your dark side as you build an evil underground kingdom and defend it against the forces of good. Carve out a living, breathing world and attract a host of devilish creatures to swell the ranks of your dark hordes. Form an alliance with the Horned Reaper to expand your empire and invade the realms above. In this dungeon-building, treasure-defending, hero-destroying adventure, it feels good to be bad — and the badder, the better! <br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Get your hands on even more evil tools.</strong> Use everything at your disposal — torture devices included — to create the deadliest dungeon imaginable. Set traps, send dastardly demons to do your bidding, and unleash the powers of the underworld with a brand-new magic system. <br/></li><li><strong>Rule your way.</strong> Keep your minions well-supplied with bustling infrastructure and good pay, or scare them into miserable servitude. There’s no extra credit for good behavior. <br/></li><li><strong>Bring your friends to their knees.</strong> Play with up to 4 frenemies, and prove who’s the most ruthless dungeon keeper in all land.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™, Counterstrike™ and The Aftermath™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229840/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_Counterstrike_and_The_Aftermath/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert</strong> pushed the envelope for the RTS genre in the mid-1990s and became one of the most iconic strategy games of all time. <br/><br/><strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert</strong>  gives you the opportunity to be more devious, cunning, and ruthless than ever before. Red Alert puts the fate of the world in your hands!<br/><br/><strong>Counterstrike</strong>, the exciting expansion pack to Red Alert, is full of clandestine activity, experimental technologies, and disavowed tactics. Includes 16 all-new missions, where you decide the ultimate fate of the struggle between the Allies and Soviets.<br/><br/><strong>In The Aftermath expansion pack</strong>, prepare for guerilla tactics, insidious strategies, and forbidden weapons. Includes 18 all-new missions and multiple units in a showdown that will test your mettle.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sim City 3000™ Unlimited</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2741560/Sim_City_3000_Unlimited/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2741560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Create and control your urban empire with more power than ever before. With SimCity 3000 Unlimited, you get all the great features of the original SimCity 3000 plus much more. Expand your SimCities with 2 new building sets from Asia and Europe. Take on 13 challenging scenarios, or create your own. Unleash 4 new disasters, including an unforgiving whirlpool and plummeting space junk. This is truly SimCity without limits!<br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Re-create cities from around the globe with hundreds of new buildings.<br/></li><li>Reunify East and West Berlin in one of 13 scenarios.<br/></li><li>Spruce up your city with over 95 world landmarks.<br/></li><li>Protect your citizens from 4 new disasters.<br/></li><li>Select hundreds of buildings from SimCity 3000 and all-new Asian and European buildings.<br/></li><li>Create unique masterpieces for your metropolis with the Building Architect Plus tool.<br/></li><li>Inflict 9 disasters, including toxic clouds, plague of locusts, space junk, and a whirlpool.<br/></li><li>Play 13 challenging scenarios, or make your own with the SimCity Scenario Creator.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sid Meier's Alpha Centauri™ Planetary Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2204130/Sid_Meiers_Alpha_Centauri_Planetary_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2204130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Mankind begins its most monumental task: the colonization of space. A crew of internationally renowned scientists and security strategists, with wide-ranging convictions and diverse ethics, embarks on a mission that will change the world. One Planet. Seven unique factions. Which will you lead? Each faction has its own agenda, each leader a final goal. You must play to each strength and exploit each hidden weakness in your quest to rule the future.<br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Great spin-off of the legendary Civilization series, in a refreshing sci-fi setting<br/></li><li>Design your own units. Balance their speed, power, and toughness to suit your current tactical needs<br/></li><li>Seven factions to chose from, each with its own artificial intelligence model that creates a very suggestive feeling that you’re up against real people</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoria: Age of Shattering</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1159090/Zoria_Age_of_Shattering/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1159090/Zoria_Age_of_Shattering/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1159090/Zoria_Age_of_Shattering/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/Steam_Mouse_Button.gif?t=1709858682"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/YOU_ARE_THE_COMMADER.gif?t=1709858682"><br/><br/>You will lead a diverse team through the various lands of an Uram continent and against challenges <strong>countless groups of monsters and bosses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/WORLD.gif?t=1709858682"><br/><br/>Zoria has now fallen prey to the sheer brutality of the hellspawn that roams its land. Its<strong> lush forests, mysterious caves, and majestic buildings</strong> have transformed into haunting and dreadful locations. Take your time and explore unknown areas, as each holds a mystery. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/Combat.gif?t=1709858682"><br/><br/>Combat is bread and butter, and <strong>you will engage in it easily.</strong> Use the <strong>unique skills </strong>of all of your party members: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attack from close range or distance with different attack patterns and directions,<br/></li><li>Heal or shield allies with various spells and commands,<br/></li><li>Inflict status aliments like damage over time, stun, immobilize, and other elemental effects,<br/></li><li>Leverage your environment to gain the upper hand or create new scenarios to distance yourself from the enemy.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/CRAFT.gif?t=1709858682"><br/><br/>Keep a keen eye on your <strong>equipment and vitality</strong> as they both deteriorate over time. A <strong>bonfire in Zoria's provides a safe spot</strong> to restock your resources and prepare for the next battle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/success.gif?t=1709858682"><br/><br/>Take care of each of your warriors' <strong>skill development</strong>, and it will repay you on the battlefield. Remember that having an individual with the right skills can <strong>get you into previously inaccessible places and quests</strong>. It may turn out that interacting with a specific character with various objects in the world of Zoria may lead you to discover hidden treasures or make your travel easier.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/base.gif?t=1709858682"><br/><br/>You have to be wise in and out of the battle. You cannot win the game without making progress - this also counts toward your outpost. You may regularly <strong>update the base by unlocking new wings to the buildings</strong>, and by doing so, you will be rewarded with either resources, quests, or items. <strong>Different buildings will have different numbers of available upgrades.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/followers.gif?t=1709858682"><br/><br/>In your outpost, you can<strong> plan and assign tasks to your companions</strong>. Send selected party members on an autonomic mission, in which you won't participate but will receive what they find along the way. You will also get some of the experience they gain. <strong>Never forget that their lives are in your hands!</strong><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1159090/Zoria_Age_of_Shattering/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1159090/Zoria_Age_of_Shattering/</a></img></img></img></img></img></img></strong> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potions: A Curious Tale</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/378690/Potions_A_Curious_Tale/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Add Potions: A Curious Tale to your wishlist!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/Wishlist_616.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/LunaCombatGif.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Use your wits to strategize conflict resolution that goes beyond pure combat-- you’ll have to think on your feet and act quickly to sidestep danger and trick, charm, and scare your opponents into dropping valuable resources. <br/><br/>As powerful as your potions are, you’ll find yourself up against monsters that can shrug off your most powerful attacks. Manage your resources carefully and use the environment and even other monsters to defeat your enemies, or you may find yourself with an empty satchel when you need your elixirs the most.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/SteamCraftingVideoFullPotTitleNX.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>On her path to potions mastery, Luna must gather rare ingredients even before she brews her first potion. While her grandmother and friends teach her basic skills and recipes, Luna must fill her vials through experimentation and discovery. <br/><br/>Explore the deep crafting system as you discover new ingredients across 7 biomes to craft over 100 unique potions with different element combinations. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/PuzzleGifTitle.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Solve devious puzzles and mysteries with your wits and your arsenal of mystical potions. With a little help from your grandmother (a powerful witch in her own right) and Helios, your cat familiar, you’ll overcome the challenges of these enchanted lands.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/StoryTitle.png?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Growing up is hard, and it’s even harder when you’re a witch! Encounter fairy tale and folklore characters as you guide Luna on her quest to become a potions master. With her sharp-tongued familiar at her side, Luna learns important coming-of-age lessons: Respect is earned, advice can be deceiving, and adults aren't always right.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FQS2SN55CC4" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/SteamHeaderDiscord616.png?t=1709876407"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/PetCatHeart.gif?t=1709876407"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Saboteur™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/24880/The_Saboteur/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/24880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Not all wars are fought on the open battlefield. Download The Saboteur to visit 1940s Nazi-occupied Paris, as you play tough Irish racecar mechanic Sean Devlin. Working with the French Resistance, Sean is out for revenge against ruthless Nazi Colonel Kurt Dierker, who executed Sean’s best friend.<br/><br/>This open-world action thriller takes you through the seedy streets of Paris as you seek to undermine the German authority and lead a rebellion. Fight across rooftops and through dangerous alleys, and operate a wide variety of vehicles as you navigate your terrain. You can even climb the Eiffel Tower or Notre Dame Cathedral for a sniping mission.<br/><br/>Use stealth and disguise to strike at the heart of the Nazi war machine by disabling trains, destroying bridges, and blowing up enemy facilities. As you work to remove the oppressive forces from parts of the city, the drab black-and-white palette gives way to bright colors, signifying that you’ve inspired the townspeople. The more you incite the people, the more they’ll aid you by intervening in fights or providing a quick getaway from pursuing Germans. The Saboteur presents a fresh take on World War II and features dramatic cinematic elements. The action and intrigue is yours to experience via download on the PC now.<br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>First Ever Open-World Paris</strong> — Climb the Eiffel Tour, snipe from Notre Dame Cathedral, and brawl on the Champs d’Elysee as you sabotage your enemies. Fight, climb, and prowl through the dark alleys, rooftops, burlesque houses, and seedy streets of the City of Lights — the ultimate playground for the Saboteur.<br/></li><li><strong>The Art of Sabotage</strong> — Being the Saboteur is all about attacking while staying unnoticed. Get your mission intel at underground clubs and cabarets. Eliminate your adversaries with stealth attacks, disguise, distractions, and explosives. Master a variety of weapons, automobiles, and skills to sabotage enemy operations. <br/></li><li><strong>The Will to Fight</strong> — An action-packed experience and thrilling storyline are made even more engaging by an innovative visual style, characters, and the new “Will to Fight” technology. Experience how the city reacts and changes around you as you free it from Nazi oppression. Only you can restore hope and grandeur to Paris.<br/></li><li><strong>French Resistance Strikes</strong> — Call for support from The Underground in the form of getaway cars, weapon deliveries, distractions, and much more.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearts of Iron IV: Trial of Allegiance</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2695150/Hearts_of_Iron_IV_Trial_of_Allegiance/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2695150/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2695150/extras/gif-open-front.gif?t=1709827274"><br/>Write new alternate histories of the globe’s most dramatic conflict in <i>Trial of Allegiance</i>, a new content pack for<i> Hearts of Iron IV</i>. Explore and dominate a world where the strife of the Second World War threatens the safety and security of South American nations. Build a regional superpower to counter the rising global powers, or join the war early, taking your chances with one of the major ideological blocs. South America is rich in resources and manpower - can you lead Argentina, Brazil or Chile to a glorious alternate future?<br/><br/><i>Hearts of Iron IV: Trial of Allegiance</i> includes:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">National Focus Tree for Brazil: </h2></strong>Challenged by a decade of internal strife and constitutional crises, Brazil can follow the historical path as a late but valuable member of the Allied cause. Alternately, seek continental hegemony under a new government with new priorities.<br/></li><li><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">National Focus Tree for Argentina:</h2></strong> Rife with corruption, revolts and worker unrest, Argentina presents a difficult political challenge. Once you’ve settled the problems at home, you can contribute more on the world stage and help this nation reach its full potential.<br/></li><li><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">National Focus Tree for Chile:</h2> </strong>Chile is a vigorous republic with a radical tradition that must face domestic fascist parties, the embers of ethnic unrest and the imposing influence of the United States. Chart a course of equality and renewal, rallying under the banner of continental unity.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2695150/extras/toa-gif-focus-trees.gif?t=1709827274"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Paraguay and Uruguay:</h2></strong> Minor content as well as several new releasable nations.<br/></li><li><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">New Art: </h2></strong>New 3D unit sprites for the Brazilian army, as well as new unique 2D art for National Focus trees and units<br/></li><li><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">New Music:</h2></strong> Six new songs, with two each for the major nations in the pack.<br/></li><li><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">New Voiceovers:</h2> </strong>Voiceovers in Brazilian Portuguese, Argentinian Spanish and Chilean Spanish.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2695150/extras/toa-gif-planes.gif?t=1709827274"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snufkin: Melody of Moominvalley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1808680/Snufkin_Melody_of_Moominvalley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/extras/Snufkin_Steam_1_opt_c.gif?t=1709917468"><br/><br/>Snufkin: Melody of Moominvalley is a story-rich musical adventure game about Snufkin restoring the valley and helping the quirky and memorable characters and critters who call it home. A series of hideous parks have cropped up in Moominvalley, disrupting the landscape and its harmonious nature. As Snufkin you will distract police officers, pull out signs, and knock over misplaced statues as you vigorously try to restore nature and the inhabitants’ home while putting an end to the industrious Park Keeper’s plans…<br/><br/>Experience a beautifully crafted and quintessentially Nordic game, brought to life with stories, emotions, and a melancholic atmosphere set in Tove Jansson’s vivid and beloved world of Moomin. You are invited to a wholesome experience for every age that combines open-world mechanics with puzzles, stealth, and melodic elements!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/extras/Snufkin_Steam_2_opt_c.gif?t=1709917468"><h2 class="bb_tag">GORGEOUS STORYBOOK STYLE BRINGING A WORLD TO LIFE</h2><br/>Immerse yourself in a beautiful and imaginative world that captures the very essence of the Moomin stories; an extensive tapestry of graphical books and cartoons brought to life in a never-before-seen way. <br/><br/>Experience the harmonious symphony with every footfall, elevated by music and melodies from the Icelandic post-rock band Sigur Rós. Befriend Moominvalley inhabitants as Snufkin with a few tunes from his harmonica. Wander Moominvalley with your heart open and your steps light. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/extras/Snufkin_Steam_3_opt_c.png?t=1709917468"><h2 class="bb_tag">A CAST OF WONDERFULLY WHIMSICAL CHARACTERS</h2><br/>Get to know a diverse cast of characters with strong yet whimsical personalities, depth, and complexity. Embark on a journey to not only find the cause of the hideous parks but to also discover and interact with the charming Moominvalley inhabitants.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/extras/Snufkin_Steam_4_opt_c.gif?t=1709917468"><h2 class="bb_tag">A MUSICAL ADVENTURE</h2><br/>Explore a host of locations where the sun dips below the horizon, casting a warm amber glow across the meadows; where the scent of wildflowers mingles with the crisp breeze, carrying promises of untold stories and hidden wonders; and where you as Snufkin - with your hat pulled low and harmonica in hand - head out. Gain inspiration by exploring Moominvalley and by solving puzzles.<br/><br/>Main features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Set out on a cozy, story-rich adventure game in a gorgeous storybook art style <br/></li><li> Get the strict Park Keeper and his horrible parks out of Moominvalley with the help of your trusty harmonica, a bit of stealth, and the friends you’ll meet along the way<br/></li><li> Meet over 50 charming characters and creatures calling Moominvalley their home<br/></li><li> Experience narrative gameplay and a myriad of charming stories and quests involving the beloved characters inspired by Tove Jansson’s work<br/></li><li> Explore Moominvalley’s open world and solve musical and environmental puzzles along the way to uncover the happenings in the valley<br/></li><li> Immerse yourself in the beautiful soundscape of music and melodies composed in collaboration with Sigur Rós</li></ul><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.snufkin.game%2Fdiscord" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/extras/Snufkin_Steam_Discord_c.png?t=1709917468"/></a><br/><br/>© Snufkin: Melody of Moominvalley. Developed by Hyper Games. Published by Raw Fury AB. © Moomin Characters ™						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berserk Boy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1561340/Berserk_Boy/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1561340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1561340/extras/BerserkBoy_SteamGIF04.gif?t=1709810066"><br/><br/>In the distant future, a mad scientist and his army of darkness seek to enslave the people of Earth. Hope for all humanity rests with The Resistance, but are they enough? Enter Kei, a rookie hero who is transformed by mysterious Orb energy into BERSERK BOY!<br/><br/>With high-speed action and the power to defeat evil, BERSERK BOY must face off against the diabolical Dr. Genos and his army of Dark Energy minions. Can he save the world before it's too late? It's time to GO BERSERK!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1561340/extras/BerserkBoy_SteamGIF02.gif?t=1709810066"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong> Unleash your ultimate form:</strong> with the power of the Berserk Orbs - Lightning, Fire, Earth, Air, and Ice - and become a force to be reckoned with!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1561340/extras/BerserkBoy_SteamGIF01.gif?t=1709810066"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Go Berserk!</strong> Become a master of speed and skill as you chain together combos to fill your Berserk Meter and unleash devastating special attacks! Upgrade your abilities and become an unstoppable force!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1561340/extras/BerserkBoy_SteamGIF03.gif?t=1709810066"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong> Explore the sprawling world of New Hope City!</strong> and beyond, unlock hidden missions along the way. Jump, dash, slam, and slide through multiple stages with Metroidvania elements as you discover alternate paths and hidden collectibles! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1561340/extras/BerserkBoy_SteamGIF05.gif?t=1709810066"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>BERSERK BOY brings retro gaming:</strong> into the modern age with slick and stylish platforming action. Inspired by the genre greats, you'll be able to play for big scores and fast times in this modern adventure with a retro feel.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1561340/extras/BerserkBoy_SteamGIF06.gif?t=1709810066"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Music by Sonic Mania composer Tee Lopes:</strong> Soundtrack by the master behind other amazing works such as the TMNT soundtrack, Streets of Rage 4, Metal Slug Tactics, and more! Enjoy the high-energy beats as you Go Berserk and save the world!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 March Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2845260/100_March_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🌸🌹 WELCOME TO 100 MARCH CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌷🐈</h2><br/>Join the cutest adventure in the Lovely world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of romantic 8 march themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x200.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 March Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁 DLC List for this game 🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Extra.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867620/100_March_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867640/100_March_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x1.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_15" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavy Storm Shadow:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802380/Heavy_Storm_ShadowPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FwmfaDVPKSa" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/dss.png?t=1709810788"/></a><br/><br/><strong>Differences between the prologue and the full version<br/>The prologue opens up a character<br/>The prologue opens up a map</strong><br/><br/><strong>Unlock the true potential of your mech and witness its constant growth and upgrades! In deserts, ice and even satellites, kill thousands of swarms to strengthen your mech!<br/>At the end of each battle you will gain valuable resources to upgrade your mech's weapons and armor, unlocking new skills and powerful equipment.<br/>Through battles, you'll gain the bonds of your mech's pilots, forming modules in different directions to shape your unique fighting style.<br/>Grow and upgrade your mech in real time to make it more and more invincible and become the ultimate weapon against the swarm!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/1y.png?t=1709810788"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/1z.gif?t=1709810788"><br/><strong>Monsters are coming at you like wave after wave, and as your mech's guns move, the monsters explode into a fog of blood and fall in pieces, painting the earth in scarlet. Operate your mech to dodge attacks, kill through the siege, and find a way to survive among hundreds of enemies!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/2y.png?t=1709810788"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/2z.gif?t=1709810788"><br/><strong>Explore your own powerful combat combo by unlocking more and more powerful weapons and skills! Become stronger by killing and choosing, picking up resources, choosing the most suitable enhancements, and finally killing the terrifying bosses head-on!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/3y.png?t=1709810788"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/3Z.gif?t=1709810788"><br/><strong> offers a rich arsenal of multiple primary and secondary weapons, as well as numerous skills with unique features. These weapons and skills will provide endless possibilities for your battles. In the future, there will be even more powerful mechs waiting to be harnessed by you! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/4y.png?t=1709810788"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/4z.gif?t=1709810788"><br/><strong>The game already offers 3 challenging maps, each with unique enemy combinations and powerful bosses waiting to be challenged for a completely different leveling experience. As the game continues to update, you will meet more new maps and new modes of play to make your Meat Pigeon adventure even more colorful. </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quilts and Cats of Calico</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1993180/Quilts_and_Cats_of_Calico/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1993180?utm_source=calico&amp;utm_medium=in_steam" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1993180?utm_source=calico&amp;utm_medium=in_steam</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Arrow.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/>Quilts and Cats of Calico is a cozy board game in which the player's main task is to make a quilt from patterned fabric scraps. By smartly combining the colors and patterns of the scraps, the player can not only score points for the completed design but also sew on buttons and attract adorable cats, who have their own preferences for bedding patterns.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Cats_running.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/><strong>Stepping beyond adaptation</strong><br/>In Quilts and Cats of Calico, based on the board game Calico, you will be immersed in a warm, cozy world full of cuddly cats. Here the quilt bends under the weight of their paws and loud purring can be heard. It's a world full of patterns and designs awaiting the master quilt maker.<br/><br/>We also have a few surprises for the Calico fans like variations of the rules and mechanics in the campaign play. In addition to the well-known gameplay scenarios, new ones await to be discovered.<br/><br/><br/><strong>Quilt solo, with friends, or with strangers</strong><br/>Whether you want to quilt solo or prefer to compete with other players, Quilts and Cats of Calico will provide you with the corresponding gameplay mode. You will have cross-platform multiplayer at your disposal, during which you can invite friends or play ranked matches against random players. The more peaceful solo mode allows you to face AI of varying difficulty levels and is the perfect tool to hone your skills in a relaxed atmosphere.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Game_modes.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/><strong>Sew your adventures in the city of cat worshippers</strong><br/>In the game, you can also enjoy the story mode campaign. An extraordinary world inspired by the works of Studio Ghibli awaits you. Here cats have great power and influence over people's lives. Take on the role of an itinerant quilter who decides to succeed in a city of cat-worshippers. Climb to the top of the city hierarchy and face the opponent who wants to dominate the world of humans and cats. Create quilts, perfect your craft, and help those you meet on your journey. Don't worry, you won't be alone - along the way, you'll meet friends and, most importantly, cats whose help can prove invaluable…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Calico_minigry_dialog_steampage_gif.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/><strong>Spend quality time with your cats</strong><br/>In Quilts and Cats of Calico, cats are active during your games. Sometimes minding their own business, and other times coming to you and your quilt. They will lazily observe the board, romp and run around, and sometimes fall into a blissful nap. They are cats, you never know. You can interact with them during the game, pet them, and shoo them away when they get in the way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Calico_glaskanie_v2.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/><strong>Extended customization options</strong><br/>The game is full of cats, but there could always be more! In Quilts and Cats of Calico, you can create your own, making your game even more wholesome! You can give it a name, choose the color of its fur, and put on different outfits. If you wish, it will appear on the board during your gameplay. It will also be possible to choose a different player's portrait and background for the game. Pick what you like best!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Calico_CatEditor_SteamPage_Gif_v2.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/><strong>Beautiful, relaxing music</strong><br/>We asked Pawel Górniak, the composer responsible for the soundtrack to the digital version of Wingspan, to create the music for Quilts and Cats of Calico. Thanks to it, you will not only be able to deeply feel the atmosphere of the game but let yourself be carried away by blissful relaxation.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classified: France '44</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2085370/Classified_France_44/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Classified: France ‘44 is a new turn-based strategy game, set in World War II during the desperate months leading up to the Allied invasion of France in June 1944.</strong><br/> <br/>Take charge of a special-ops team of Allied commandos and French resistance fighters. Recruit elite operatives to build your squad, then engage in a sweeping campaign of sabotage and destruction. Deal with competing factions to build the resistance network and strike at German targets deep in occupied territory. However, the more chaos you cause, the more you’ll draw the merciless attention of the Gestapo secret police.<br/> <br/>In exciting missions inspired by the exploits of the Allies and French, the game expands on turn-based tactical concepts, bringing authentic World War 2 combat to life. The campaign allows for multiple playthroughs that are different each time. For those who really want to test their skills, our rich Mission Creator tool allows players to create, share and download custom missions.<h2 class="bb_tag">Every Shot Counts.</h2> In Classified: France ‘44’s unique morale system, every shot taken affects you or your enemies. Suppress and break your opposition, giving you a brief window to flank your cowering targets and finish them off.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085370/extras/1._Every_Shot_Counts_v2.gif?t=1709898430"><h2 class="bb_tag">Shape the Battle.</h2> Use stealth tactics to eliminate key targets and start the fight on your terms. However, the more kills you make, the more enemies will begin to suspect that something's wrong, so be ready to unleash your ambush before they sniff you out!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085370/extras/2._Shape_the_Battle_v2.gif?t=1709898430"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build your Team. </h2>An authentic and characterful mix of heroes will be yours to choose from, each with their own story to tell. Train, customise and equip them with your growing arsenal of skills and weapons.  Raise the morale of your team by spending time around the campfire, and learning about their lives as they fight across the war-ravaged fields of occupied France.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085370/extras/3._Build_Your_Team_v2.gif?t=1709898430"><h2 class="bb_tag">Experience History. </h2>Complete challenging objectives in over 45 missions supplied to your team by the French forces. Choose which missions suit your strategy to grow the resistance and support your ultimate goals. Manage your team by sending them on strategic operations.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085370/extras/4._Experience_History_v4.gif?t=1709898430"><h2 class="bb_tag">Built to Last. </h2>Updates and expansions will grow the world of Classified: France ‘44, bringing new and exciting elements to your freedom fight. Our Classified Mission Creator and the modding tools ensure there will always be player-created content to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085370/extras/5._Built_to_Last_v2.gif?t=1709898430"><h2 class="bb_tag">On to Victory.</h2> Classified: France ‘44 is full of challenge. Work out the optimum grand strategy while deploying the best tactical play and discover the game's multiple endings. What will your D-Day look like?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085370/extras/6._On_To_Victory_v2.gif?t=1709898430"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sixty Four</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2659900/Sixty_Four/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F7YXd3tScqS" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/discord.png?t=1709871568"/></a><br/><br/>Created by a solo developer, Sixty Four is a clicker game that gradually becomes more idle with every machine you unlock, up to the the ultimate goal of full automation. Upgrade a factory in an extraordinary world. Progress to unlock new resources and machines, leading to new ways to expand and grow.<br/><br/><strong>❒ From Foundation to Complexity</strong><br/><br/>Begin your journey with a simple machine generating distinct cubes. Use combinations of cubes to unlock advanced machinery and new gameplay elements.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_3a_smaller.gif?t=1709871568"><br/><br/><strong>❒ An Evolving Factory Adventure</strong><br/><br/>Your factory is not just a collection of simple machines; it's a dynamic environment of challenges and strategy. Face new situations and discover opportunities with every innovative and abstract machine you encounter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_4a_smaller.gif?t=1709871568"><br/><strong>❒ A Fresh Mix of Gaming Mechanics</strong><br/><br/>Sixty Four combines simple yet engaging elements from idle, incremental, and strategy games. Pursue constant improvement and unravel the secrets behind messages from an unknown entity.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_5a_smaller.gif?t=1709871568"><br/><br/>Music by Jake Chudnow						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Thaumaturge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1684350/The_Thaumaturge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Thaumaturge_accolade_616x320_steam.png?t=1709742147"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/TT_claim_EN_small.png?t=1709742147"><br/><strong>The Thaumaturge is an isometric, story-rich RPG with a unique take on turn-based combat, character development features, and investigation mechanics</strong>, facing you with morally ambiguous choices – set in a world teeming with mysterious powers and strange ethereal beings called <strong>salutors</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/City_3-01.gif?t=1709742147"><br/><br/>The year is 1905. Warsaw lives under the yoke of imperial Russian tsardom. Its inhabitants constitute a diverse group of different ancestries, views, and beliefs with often conflicting interests: Russian soldiers, Jewish merchants, Polish townspeople, and more. Despite the circumstances, the city is a buzzing metropolis, where one can attend a breathtaking party with the high society, and later get robbed in one of the dark alleys of the Praga district. A city of great hopes and dreams on one hand and dark desires on the other.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Buka_2.gif?t=1709742147"><br/><br/>A <strong>thaumaturge</strong> bears both a gift and a burden at the same time. This parallel holds true for <strong>Wiktor Szulski</strong>, the game’s titular protagonist, who is drawn back to the tumultuous streets of 20th-century Warsaw by family matters. The gift of thaumaturgy is intertwined with family legacy, passed down through one's ancestors. This mystical inheritance significantly shapes Wiktor’s life journey tied around a pursuit of unearthly entities and their hosts. As only a thaumaturge can tame these ethereal entities - known to a select few as <strong>salutors</strong> - utilizing their mystical abilities to discover secrets hidden within the human soul and speak to the Darkness, no one understands quite like Wiktor how everyone suffers their own demons.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Wiktor_3-01.gif?t=1709742147"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Shape your story</strong> – as a full-fledged RPG, it allows you to alternate your choices and make you deal with the aftermath. <br/></li><li><strong>Develop your character</strong> – creating your own version of the thaumaturge will allow you to approach situations in different ways. <br/></li><li><strong>Experience unique turn-based combat</strong> and defeat your foes using human attacks and skills as well as psychic strikes delivered by salutors.<br/></li><li><strong>Influence and manipulate</strong> the temperaments of other characters to bend their will to your liking. <br/></li><li><strong>Tame the power of salutors</strong> – use the unique set of their skills to gain an advantage while exploring the world and when bringing your adversaries to their knees. <br/></li><li><strong>See the world that’s inevitably gone</strong> – explore the uncommon, heavily researched historic period of the early XX century Warsaw, where crime and luxury are often two sides of the same coin. Meet historical figures and learn about their involvement in the story. <br/></li><li><strong>Created in Unreal Engine 5</strong> to deliver a detailed &amp; beautifully crafted world.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crusader Kings III: Legends of the Dead</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2671060/Crusader_Kings_III_Legends_of_the_Dead/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							What good are grand accomplishments and heroic deeds if no one sings of them after you have gone? A royal legacy is only useful, after all, if it can provide cover and legitimacy for those who come after you. Live on in the memory of your subjects and rivals in <i>Legends of the Dead</i>, a Core Expansion for <i>Crusader Kings III</i>.<br/><br/><strong><i>Crusader Kings III: Legends of the Dead</i></strong> adds new heroic gameplay, as you stoke the flames of your fame into a towering bonfire.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671060/extras/legends-v4-opt.gif?t=1709571372"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Legends:</strong> Commission an epic retelling of your family history or build your own heroic reputation through great deeds. Promote this legend, far and wide, and see how the stories of the past reverberate through the centuries, and add more glory to legendary dynasties.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Legendary Playstyle:</strong> Leverage your living legend status through new Decisions and actions, keeping the stories of your family in the minds of a continent, strengthening the legitimacy of your rule and allowing further choices. <br/><br/></li><li><strong>Legendary Buildings:</strong> Your legendary reputation gives you access to new elite buildings, cementing your legacy for future generations.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Legendary Feasts: </strong>Poets and bards can ornament your celebrations with songs and odes to your greatness, inspiring your guests to spread the tale of your legendary generosity.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Court Chroniclers:</strong> Hire an official historian to spread the story of your dynasty’s great accomplishments, or use your poets and musicians to turn your actions into art.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Two New Legacies:</strong> A new Heroic dynastic Legacy for the heirs of legendary characters, even using the great deeds of ancestors to justify claims from the distant past, as well as a Legitimacy Legacy that promotes your dynasty as the true rulers of the realm.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671060/extras/blackplague-opt.gif?t=1709571372"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Illness and Mourning:</strong> New diseases like the Bloody Flux, Measles and Holy Fire may ravage your court, but you can honor your deceased loved ones with dignified Funeral rites, according to your faith.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>The Black Death:</strong> The greatest scourge of the Middle Ages strikes down noble and commoner alike, radically transforming the political and social environment. Prepare your realm and prepare your soul, because a rampaging plague may be the strongest enemy facing your rule.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>New Art:</strong> Both life and death are given new energy with the celebrated art style that Crusader Kings III fans have come to appreciate. A new exclusive Map Table, new varieties of clothing, unit models and holding designs for extra flavor.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vivaland: Dream House</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2606170/Vivaland_Dream_House/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2606170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1976830" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1976830</a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2606170/extras/ezgif-3-474fd0310c.gif?t=1709804132"><h2 class="bb_tag">Introducing the Vivaland Prologue: Dream House</h2><strong>Build Mode: Craft Your Dreams</strong><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in one of the core game modes of Vivaland: the Build Mode. It's a sandbox where you have control over architectural and design elements, enabling you to construct and decorate a house from the ground up!<br/><br/><strong>Get to Know the First Town of Vivaland</strong><br/><br/>The town of Vivaland offers 8 residential lots, each awaiting your personal touch. Claim your slice of the town, visit your friends' properties, and collaborate on grand projects that will redefine the neighborhood.<br/><br/><strong>Seamless Single and Co-op Experience</strong><br/><br/>Begin your Vivaland adventure either as a lone explorer or with your friends by your side – the choice is yours. You can build together with up to 8 players<br/><strong>Content</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Walls Toolkit:</strong> Build with single wall, curved wall and the room tool!<br/></li><li><strong>Doors &amp; Windows:</strong> Choose entrances and views that reflect your taste.<br/></li><li><strong>Foundations, Multiple Floors, and Stairs: </strong>Build structures that rise to new heights.<br/></li><li><strong>Furniture:</strong> Design with a vast selection of interior items.<br/></li><li><strong>Roofing:</strong> Choose from 10 distinct styles and an array of roof patterns.<br/></li><li><strong>Different styles of items:</strong>  Bohemian, Retro, Victorian, Antique, Cottagecore, Gothic, Modern, Minimalist, Industrial.</li></ul><br/><strong>Functional Freedom</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Resizable Objects:</strong> Adjusting the size of decorative objects.<br/></li><li><strong>Recolorable Furniture and Decor: </strong> Fine-tune your interior design with your color palettes. Save favorite shades and match your items.<br/></li><li><strong>Room Dimension Flexibility: </strong>Tweak the height and width of your rooms.<br/></li><li><strong>Grid Function: </strong>Precise item placement is a breeze with toggleable grid support.<br/></li><li><strong>Intuitive Controls and Snapping: </strong>Seamlessly move and arrange objects.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeeperRL</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/329970/KeeperRL/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/Peek-2018-11-28-09-43.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL is an ambitious dungeon simulator with roguelike and RPG elements. Take the role of an evil wizard and study the methods of black magic. Equip your minions and explore the world, murder innocent villagers and burn their homes. Build your dungeon, lay traps and prepare for an assault of angry heroes. <br/><br/>When you control your minions the game changes into a classic roguelike, with turn-based and very tactical combat. You can also play as an adventurer and assault dungeons made by you or other players.<h2 class="bb_tag">Dungeon management </h2>You will dig deep into the mountain and build dozens of rooms, corridors and traps. Your minions will train and produce weapons and armor. Prisoners will be tortured. You will research new technologies like alchemy, beast mutation and sorcery.<h2 class="bb_tag">Z-levels</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341">Develop your base across multiple floors by digging down into the earth or building up. Build fantastic dungeon designs or elaborate castles and towers.<h2 class="bb_tag">Roguelike mechanics </h2>The world is simulated on a very detailed level. Creatures use equipment and consumable items. There are dozens of special items, spells, attributes and special attacks. You can cut off heads and limbs and blind or poison your enemies. If you're not careful with fire, you can burn an entire forest or even your own dungeon.<h2 class="bb_tag">Large, procedurally generated maps </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-animated-gif-maker__2_.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL features a large, procedurally generated world. Explore dozens of locations, from small cottages and shops to major enemies dwelling in castles and dungeons. Uncover secrets, bring back great loot and prisoners back to your base in order to grow in power.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple playable factions</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/gif_keepers-ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>Play as a:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dark wizard researching black magic.<br/></li><li>White knight specialized in horses and angelic beings.<br/></li><li>Necromancer who crafts undead from the body parts of fallen enemies.<br/></li><li>Fragile colony of twelve dwarves.<br/></li><li>Goblin king searching for his lost wives.<br/></li><li>Collective of gnomes with a mechanized army.<br/></li><li>Lone adventurer focused on exploration.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Online map sharing </h2>KeeperRL offers the ability to download dungeons made by other players from Steam Workshop, and places them on your world map as enemies. See how others design their fortresses, fight with their minions, and steal their loot! After winning the game, you'll have the option to share your dungeon online as well.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Grindea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/269770/Secrets_of_Grindea/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/269770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Secrets of Grindea</i> is an old-school Action RPG with co-op support for up to 4 players. It is a tribute to and sometimes a parody of the old SNES games so many of us grew up with and loved! Journey through fantastical lands, and battle tons of different enemies and bosses in your quest for truth, friendship and, above all, finding the world's rarest treasures!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A rich world filled with 300+ unique, colorful characters and an engaging story to drive your journey forward.<br/></li><li>Co-op support for up to four players! Enjoy the entire storyline with your friends or call someone in to help with the more difficult challenges.<br/></li><li>Customization, customization, customization - design a character that represents you, then mix and match any of the 31 spells and skills across 9 different categories.<br/></li><li>30+ epic boss fights! Overgrown slimes, giant robots, mimics - we have it all!<br/></li><li>Side content - design your own home, fish, craft items, tame pets, partake in mini-games, grow plants - there’s plenty to keep you entertained when you want a break from the main story.</li></ul><br/>And last but not least:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Arcade Mode - Separate from Story Mode, the game includes a <strong>full roguelite</strong> version where you need to battle your way to the top on a single life, building a town of your own as you progress.  How far can you get?</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON BALL FighterZ</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/678950/DRAGON_BALL_FighterZ/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/extras/GIF_DBFZ_STEAM.png?t=1709230702"><br/><br/>DRAGON BALL FighterZ is born from what makes the DRAGON BALL series so loved and famous: endless spectacular fights with its all-powerful fighters.<br/><br/>Partnering with Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ maximizes high end Anime graphics and brings easy to learn but difficult to master fighting gameplay.<br/><br/>High-end Anime Graphics<br/>Using the power of the Unreal engine and the talented team at Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ is a visual tour-de-force.<br/><br/>3vs3 Tag/Support<br/>Build your dream team and sharpen your skills to master high-speed tag combinations.<br/><br/>Thrilling Online Features<br/>Ranked matches, interactive lobby, crazy 6-player Party Match... There is something for every taste!<br/><br/>Exclusive Story Mode<br/>Discover a never-seen-before scenario featuring Android 21, a brand new character whose creation was supervised by Akira Toriyama himself.<br/><br/>Spectacular Fights<br/>Experience aerial combos, destructible stages and famous scenes from the DRAGON BALL anime in 60FPS and 1080p resolution!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635350/United_Penguin_Kingdom/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635350/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1709984701"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635350/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1709984701"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635350/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1709984701"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635350/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1709984701"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635350/extras/Storage.gif?t=1709984701"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635350/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1709984701"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desktop Cube-Man</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/791410/Desktop_CubeMan/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/791410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a free multiplayer PC desktop game.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay concept</h2>You can simply place the cube-man on the desktop. He has some different behavior modes, such as avoiding mouse and random shooting. He can accompany you or decorate your desktop while you are working.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer</h2>The most interesting part is to play with friends, you can let your friend join your desktop, then you can chat with each other or play challenge mode together. This is the first desktop game with multiplayer mode I've ever seen too.<h2 class="bb_tag">Challenge mode</h2>In challenge mode, you will fight against enemies with the goal of surviving longer and defeating more enemies. You can just idle casually, or try to challenge higher difficulties, or team up with friends for multiplayer challenges.  Your performance in challenge mode will be recorded and included in the global rankings.<h2 class="bb_tag">Level upgrade</h2>The game is free to play with no in-app purchases, you can gain experience through idle time and unlocks more behavior modes. In addition，supporters can receive triple experiences in the game.<h2 class="bb_tag">About developer</h2>I am a amateur indie game developer. This game is designed and developed by myself only.<br/>My QQ Mail: <a href="mailto:910728069@qq.com">910728069@qq.com</a><br/>Welcome to try my another free game "Escape Expert"<br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/727180/_Escape_Expert/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/727180/_Escape_Expert/</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The shadow of the evil tower</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2600580/The_shadow_of_the_evil_tower/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600580/extras/01.jpg?t=1709971077"><br/>In order to escape the dungeon, the girl unseals the demon. This action is wrong and fatal, she does not get the demon's gratitude, on the contrary, the girl is in extreme danger. Will the poor girl be able to outrun the demon and escape this horrible place alive?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600580/extras/02.jpg?t=1709971077"><br/>It is a side-scrolling action game. The characteristic of this game is that you need to run as fast as possible. Because if you are too slow, the monster will catch up with you and eat you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600580/extras/01.gif?t=1709971077"><br/>Failure doesn't get you down, and you're confident that you'll find a way to cope with it the next time. You will truly feel strong.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600580/extras/02.gif?t=1709971077"><br/>As a side-scrolling action game, the character will have common abilities such as rolling, continuous jumping, climbing walls, etc. Our protagonist will have none of them missing. And at the beginning of the game, you will have all the abilities, and you won't leave any regrets.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600580/extras/03.gif?t=1709971077"><br/>The game includes 2 difficulties and 140 levels. There are countless mechanisms and secret paths. Each level is carefully crafted and tested. It won't be too difficult to make you feel helpless, nor too easy to make you bored.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600580/extras/04.gif?t=1709971077"><br/>All in all, I'd say it's a good piece of game. I hope it brings you joy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Koi Garden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802480/Koi_Garden/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Koi Garden is 3D Realistic Koi collecting application.<br>
<br>
*** Features ***<br>
<br>
* 20+ Koi Fish.<br>
<br>
* Cross-Breeding to get a new Koi.<br/>
<br/>
*** Tutorial <br/>
<br/>
Clean your pond, and you will get first koi.<br/>
Feed your koi. and get second koi.<br/>
<br/>
Try Cross-breeding to get a new Koi.<br/>
<br/>
Keep pond clean,and sometimes feed them again. <br/>
<br/>
Try Cross-breeding to get all koi !!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost with you</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2301900/Lost_with_you/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2301900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">About this game</h2><br/><strong>Survive with her!</strong><br/><br/>You've been through an unfortunate plane crash.<br/>Luckily, you survived, but ended up being stranded on a deserted island.<br/>But there is still hope. 'Cause you're not alone<br/>Can you survive and escape from the deserted island with her?<h2 class="bb_tag">Survival</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2301900/extras/Status.png?t=1709959637"><br/><br/>You have to manage your health, stamina, hunger and thirst. When your health reaches 0, it's game over.<h2 class="bb_tag">Choice</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2301900/extras/Selection.PNG?t=1709959637"><br/><br/>You will be given options during the conversation. One choice won't bring a big change, but your reputation will gradually change.<h2 class="bb_tag">Mini game</h2><br/>Your survival skills will be tested. Several mini-games are prepared, and the more you become proficient, the better you will survive.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthwave Glider</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1405390/Synthwave_Glider/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1405390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Drive through a beautiful 80s inspired landscape, at break neck speeds, an arcade style time attack game with amazing music, Synthwave Glider will give you a challenge as you chase after your friends high score!<br/><br/><strong>Features Include:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Great 80s inspired music<br/></li><li>Online leader board<br/></li><li>Tight controls<br/></li><li>Time trial<br/></li><li>Fun!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blade Mistress</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2358220/Blade_Mistress/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Blade Mistress is an oldschool retro styled 1990s like game where you become a lovely lady and fight your way in a magical world against creatures who threaten to destroy it. Travel to unique realms and discover the secrets of what caused this chaos. Take part of a class selection to help and air others or to become the fighter and need support from others. Blade mistress is a online multiplayer which is designed to incourage team work and player aid to each other with little to no hand holding it is your job to find out things and what is truely happening in this world.<br>
<br>
Create your own personal dungeons with Geomancy, or join other players in their own dungeons, Become a 1 of 6 classes Physical, Magaical, Creative, Beast Master, Generalist, and War Mage. Each class having a unique set of skills design to aid each other.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twinkle☆Guardians</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2725420/TwinkleGuardians/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725420/extras/aaa.png?t=1709946221"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725420/extras/aab.png?t=1709946221"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725420/extras/aac.png?t=1709946221"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725420/extras/aad.png?t=1709946221"><br/>Twinkle☆Guardians is<br/>a tower defense game about about 10 guardians who protect crystals.<h2 class="bb_tag">Anyway, It's Simple!</h2><h2 class="bb_tag">But it's a bit challenging!</h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Defend the crystal from a large number of demons and become a legendary guardian!</h2><br/><br/>・35 stages<br/>・14 different towers with 10 characters and 4 objects (gradually join)<br/>・WAVE rewind function that allows you to go back to your favorite point even if you fail.<br/>・Powerful items that can be dropped from enemies and obtained in mini-games <br/>    (difficulty level that can be cleared without using them)						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greebles</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2565450/Greebles/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2565450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2565450/extras/about-banner.png?t=1709938254"><br/><br/>Greebles is an action packed game of skill involving bulldozers, cockroaches and fish. Players attempt to navigate a maze of blocks while crushing Greebles to gain points. The more Greebles you crush, the more points you get! Just don't let them touch you!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 100 different levels with unique blocks, greebles, and specials. <br/></li><li> Local PvP or Co-op with up to 4 players.<br/></li><li> Multiplayer matches with up to 36 players.<br/></li><li> 3 difficulty levels.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">How to Play</h2><br/>Push blocks to send them sliding, time it right to scoop up greebles and crush them:<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2565450/extras/crush-greeble.gif?t=1709938254"><br/><br/>Push a block that can't move to crush it. Some blocks grant buffs to the player, like speed:<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2565450/extras/crush-special.gif?t=1709938254"><br/><br/>Be careful though, different types of blocks behave differently than regular blocks. Grenade blocks explode, pushing adjacent blocks and killing adjacent players or greebles:<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2565450/extras/push-grenade.gif?t=1709938254"><br/><br/>Bounce blocks prevent blocks from stopping when they otherwise would, and generator blocks can't be pushed, but periodically spawn new greebles:<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2565450/extras/generator-bounce.gif?t=1709938254"><br/><br/>Some generators can be crushed, others can only be destroyed by surrounding them with blocks.<br/><br/>Gameplay progresses to the next level when all greebles and greeble generators have been destroyed. <br/><br/>There are many other types of blocks, here are just a few:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Shield - protects you from greebles and sliding blocks.<br/></li><li> Freeze - slows other players, and stops greebles in their tracks.<br/></li><li> Bonus - crush these for extra points.<br/></li><li> Fireball - grants the ability to launch grenade blocks.<br/></li><li> Death Touch - protects you from greebles, and kills anything you touch.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer</h2><br/>While fun to play solo, Greebles becomes much more fun with friends. Up to 4 players can play (PvP or co-op) on a single machine, although it can get a bit crowded around the keyboard! Up to 9 machines (any platform) can connect for LAN play, for a total limit of 36 players per match!<br/><br/><br/>Available natively on Windows, macOS, and Linux. Greebles intends to be an exact replica of the original game released in 1997. (Produced in collaboration with Stairways Software)						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Planes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2586160/Paper_Planes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2586160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2586160/extras/Abouthisgame.png?t=1709928429"><br/><br/>Fly, shoot, and even nuke your friends in Paper Planes! This 2D arcade style shooter is played with up to four players, control a plane or maybe even a wizard all while trying to eliminate each other from out of the sky. Powerups can be found which will give you an edge on the competition, just be sure to avoid any hazards throughout the sky. Come fly with your friends in Paper Planes and crown yourself the victor.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2586160/extras/Gamefeatures.png?t=1709928429"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Local multiplayer PvP combat.<br/></li><li>Various types of planes with different abilities.<br/></li><li>Different maps with unique obstacles.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2586160/extras/Aboutdevelopment.png?t=1709928429"><br/><br/>This game was developed as a student project at DigiPen Institute of Technology and was created for educational purposes only. Please check out our publisher page for more information.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Princess Quest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2218030/Princess_Quest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2218030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join Princess Lilia in her adventure to take back her country in this old school RPG!<h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2><br/>After returning to Guilebern Castle, Princess Lilia, heir to the throne of the Guileland Empire, is awoken to discover an insurrection lead by Grand Minister Gordeau's faction. With the help of her maid, Anna, Lilia escapes with just the clothes on her back. Determined to retake the capital and her country, Lilia must seek cooperation from the nobles. However, the proposition that the nobles hand back to her is that she must do everything in her power to carry out their requests...<br/><br/>Will she be able to clear the multitude of quests and return safely to her castle?<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Old school, turn-based RPG combat<br/></li><li>Seek supporters and complete quests to retake the Guilebern throne<br/></li><li>Recruit NPCs including characters from Revival Quest and Alisa Quest to aid you in your journey<br/></li><li>English, Japanese and Simplified Chinese language option</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1000 Cuts: Jomaku</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2842420/1000_Cuts_Jomaku/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Jomaku (除幕)</strong> <i>"Curtain-raiser" an short act or monologue to introduce a longer kabuki play. </i><br/><br/><strong>1000 Cuts: Jomaku</strong> is a 60-90 minute preview experience of <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2412000/OneThousand_Cuts/" rel="" target="_blank">One-Thousand Cuts</a>, with a short tutorial, <strong>plenty of exploration</strong> (over a dozen hidden pettable cats, bonus lore drops, three alternative video modes, even an optional boss), <strong>unlockable upgrades,</strong> a <strong>three-phase final boss</strong>, and <strong>multiple endings</strong> based on which moral route you choose.<br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2412000/OneThousand_Cuts/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_TopGifBig.gif?t=1709927262"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/IDC.png?t=1709927262"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_IDC_240103.gif?t=1709927262"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_Steam616_TextboxInstantDeath_v1_240212.png?t=1709927262"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_MPT300x_240104.png?t=1709927262"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_MPT_240104.gif?t=1709927262"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_Steam616_TextboxDiscoverFight_v1_240212.png?t=1709927262"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/E_D.png?t=1709927262"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_E_D_240103.gif?t=1709927262"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_Steam616_TextboxHiddenLore_v1_240212.png?t=1709927262"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_AMR300x_240104.png?t=1709927262"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_AMR_240104.gif?t=1709927262"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_Steam616_TextboxLoyaltyHonor_v1_240212.png?t=1709927262"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/TCIY.png?t=1709927262"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_TCIY_240109.gif?t=1709927262"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_Steam616_TextboxChoice_v1_240212.png?t=1709927262"><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/banjotoadstudio/one-thousand-cuts" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_MiddleGifBig.gif?t=1709927262"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/pitchbook616px4.png?t=1709927262"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_Steam616_CombatSystem_v1_240212.png?t=1709927262"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_Steam616_ExploreDiscover_v1_240212.png?t=1709927262"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_Steam616_MoralStory_v1_240212.png?t=1709927262"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/pitchbook616px8.png?t=1709927262"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_Steam616_Enemies_v1_240212.png?t=1709927262"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_Steam616_Bosses_v1_240212.png?t=1709927262"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_Steam616_TextboxBoss_v1_240212.png?t=1709927262"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_Steam616_Story_v1_240212.png?t=1709927262"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/pitchbook616px.png?t=1709927262"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842420/extras/1TC_Steam616_MeetTeam_v1_240212.png?t=1709927262"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2853760/Paris_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2853760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a realistic real life simulator where you can walk around Paris<br>
Interested in playing a real life simulator. This game is for you<br>
<br>
<br>
1. Walk around Paris and see the Eifel Tower.<br>
2. Go up to the top of the Eifel tower and walk around <br>
3. See trees, NPC's <br/>
4. Experience a 3d Realistic game in first person<br/>
<br/>
Were a team of disabled creators, we are working hard and we want to build great games. Thank you for believing in us						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desert Special Forces</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2805640/Desert_Special_Forces/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2805640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Captain, you have a new mission!<br/>Desert Special Forces is about liberating enemy camps from terrorists planning attacks. The main hero is a secret agent who lands on one of these camps and aims to kill the terrorists guarding it. As a true professional, you have to succeed in record time in order not to be noticed. Once you've left, there's no going back, because we don't want people to hear about our operations. Either you're a hero, or we erase your tracks. That's why we chose you captain, so we don't make a mistake!<br/><strong>Game features :</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Killing the enemies at the military base<br/></li><li>10 levels<br/></li><li>First-person shooter</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fox Golf</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2833820/Fox_Golf/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2833820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Do we do a “little” activity? The Fox Golf game opens up a new vision of the sport of golf. The basic idea remains the same, but the difficulties and circumstances will surprise you.As a fox, the biggest competition you have ever met on the golf courses awaits you. Try your sports skills right now, aiming at the target even from the greatest distances. Humanity needs new heroes, so be one of them!<br/><br/><strong>Game features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>100 levels<br/></li><li>Fields above the clouds<br/></li><li>10 chances to miss per level</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Love and Crime</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2818340/Love_and_Crime/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2818340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Visual romantic anime novel in the otome - thriller genre with a gripping detective plot. Immerse yourself in a world of passion and secrets, where your decisions influence the storyline. At the center of this detective novel is the brave girl Hikari. Her dreams of a dangerous job, the experience of growing up, exciting romantic encounters with handsome guys and a mysterious new friend. In addition to inner experiences and love relationships, Hikari seeks to uncover the truth about the mysterious Criminal Syndicate.<br>
<br>
To love and survive? Yes! The closeness with your favorite guy and the fight against the Criminal Syndicate depend on your choices. Will you remain on the side of good? With which of the guys will you find love?<br>
7 endings of this otome novel await you!<br>
<br>
This detective novel promises something more than just entertainment - it's a story that will leave a mark on your heart. Don't miss the chance to be part of this unique anime game!						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xatrom Command</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2563490/Xatrom_Command/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2563490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Team up and shoot down waves of invading aliens.<br/><br/>A top-secret government laboratory experiment went wrong, and now invading aliens have infested the military base.<br/>Time to clean things up! Grab your weapon, recruit a friend, and start blasting wave after wave of alien scum into oblivion.<br/><br/>Obtain more powerful weapons, battle against enemies of all sizes, clear each room, and restore order to the facility.<br/><br/>Play a single player or co-op multiplayer campaign, and have a blast. <br/><br/><br/>Features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Survival mode<br/></li><li>Boss Rush mode<br/></li><li>Top-down shooter gameplay<br/></li><li>Single player or co-op multiplayer campaigns<br/></li><li>Multiple weapons and enemies<br/></li><li>Multiple difficulty settings</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One More Hound!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2546750/One_More_Hound/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2546750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>One More Hound!</strong> is a hand-draw roguelite game where you'll fight against waves of enemies with unique characteristics, unlock new powers and beat your own records one match after another!<br/>After been teleported by a mysterious creature to this Galatic arena, you will need to fight to survive round after round to see your love-one again!<br/> <br/>- Infinite Rounds<br/>- Simple Commands<br/>- Figure out how to defeat your enemies<br/>- Beat your top score rounds in your personal ranking<br/>- Create your best strategy to survive more rounds<br/>- Cute visual<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2546750/extras/gifexplosoes.gif?t=1709917792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2546750/extras/açao.gif?t=1709917792"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Days</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2075720/9_Days/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>GET READY FOR THE FIGHT, TIME IS TICKING!</strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075720/extras/GIF_02_24_02.gif?t=1709917242"><br/><br/>You have 9 Days to explore the vast world to find the best skills and items for the final fight. Choose carefully where you go and how you spend your time. Remember, you only have 9 days!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CRAFT YOUR FIGHTNING STYLE</strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075720/extras/GIF_01_24_02.gif?t=1709917242"><br/><br/>Craft your own style of fighting by mixing different Ki Attacks, Dodges and Melee Strikes together.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>YOU HAVE 9 DAYS</strong></h2>During the 9th day, the time for exploration is over. You will be confronted by Afran to determine the fate of the world.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProxOS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2239650/ProxOS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2239650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the life of developers 30 years ago with <strong>ProxOS</strong>! The simulated operating system offers everything you need to start learning assembly programming. Compete with your friends to solve progressively harder challenges in clever ways. <br/><br/><strong>Featuring:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Code written in assembly and executed on the latest 32KHz processor<br/></li><li>Best in class editor with debugging tools<br/></li><li>Custom skins and challenges<br/></li><li>Display support and keyboard input for interactive programs<br/></li><li>Manual written by your neighbour<br/></li><li>Online leaderboards without cheaters<br/></li><li>Overclocking and more? I'm not paid to reveal hidden features</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NodeRunner</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2850830/NodeRunner/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2850830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							NodeRunner is a Physics-based Roguelike Arcade game where you fling yourself from node to node while being endlessly tracked down by the Chaser, who gains upgrades of it's own over time. Collect Gold, Buy Mods and weapons to power yourself up, and eventually turn your weapons to the Chaser to take it down.<h2 class="bb_tag">Featuring:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Mouse Only Controls (Controllers are also fully supported)<br/></li><li>Fast paced physics-based movement.<br/></li><li>A variety of Items and Weapons to make your own play style.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchors Blockade Zone:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2819850/Anchors_Blockade_ZonePrologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FPZHEvJTz65" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/dss.png?t=1709912394"/></a><br/><br/><strong>Difference between Prologue and Official Edition<br/>Prologue opens up a map</strong><br/><strong>Anchor: Blockade Zone game, is a collection of gun modification, exploring the map, death drop equipment of the Cthulhu theme 2D pixel style shooter. The game puts you in the role of an agent who enters a blockade zone to investigate with the aim of finding out the cause of the strange events in the blockade zone. Your character is trapped in the blockade and has to search for food, water and other supplies in order to survive, as well as completing quests to gather information and find the truth. In the process, don't be too surprised to encounter anything unnatural, whether it's going back in time or to the future. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/1y.png?t=1709912394"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/战斗.gif?t=1709912394"><br/><strong>Experience exhilarating shooting, fight sworn battles with hostile agents, Kraken monsters, and more, and beat the truth out of the world with the weapons in your hands! Poor for tactical penetration, rich for fire coverage, it's all up to you! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/2y.png?t=1709912394"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/改枪.gif?t=1709912394"><br/><strong>We strive to make you feel the thrill of 2d shooting, so that you can feel the real shooting experience.<br/>Up to hundreds of gun accessories, allowing you to freely remodel your exclusive weapon! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/3y.png?t=1709912394"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/仓库.gif?t=1709912394"><br/><strong>Recruit agents for your exploration operations and train them to grow into excellent agents to help you complete various missions and search various maps.<br/>Each exploration map is a repeated horizontal jump across the edge of life and death for agents, with different maps having different chances of resulting in an agent's outright death. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/4y.png?t=1709912394"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/搜索.gif?t=1709912394"><br/>Explore the map carefully and make sure your agent gets back to base safe and sound every time.<br/><strong>If an agent is unlucky enough to die or return to the city with serious injuries, the items he is carrying and searching for will be dropped with him. Only items placed in the safe will be retained. </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final Dash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2845930/Final_Dash/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Final Dash, the electrifying platformer that takes you on an unforgettable journey through extraordinary worlds! Dive into a fast-paced experience filled with unique obstacles and breathtaking landscapes.<br>
<br>
In Final Dash, not only will you face meticulously designed challenges, but you'll also have the chance to create your own levels using our intuitive editor. Unleash your creativity and build amazing worlds that will challenge your friends and the community at large!<br>
<br>
Explore captivating environments, from futuristic landscapes to vibrant fantasy realms. Each level is meticulously crafted to provide visually stunning experiences and engaging gameplay that will test your reflexes and skills.<br>
<br>
Moreover, in Final Dash, the community is at the heart of the experience. Share your creations with other players, play community-made levels, and compete for top scores on global leaderboards. The fun and excitement never end in Final Dash!<br/>
<br/>
Are you ready for the ultimate challenge? Get ready to run, jump, and soar to greatness in Final Dash!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draft Day Sports: College Basketball 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2810880/Draft_Day_Sports_College_Basketball_2024/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the thrill of college basketball coaching in Draft Day Sports: College Basketball 2024. Take charge of your favorite school's program, recruit the next generation of stars, and guide your team to tournament glory. As the coach, you have control over every aspect of your program, from practice sessions to player grades, and you can exert your influence on game day from the virtual sideline. Will you build a team for the ages or strategically use the transfer portal to reload each year? The choices are yours to make!<br>
<br>
In this latest edition, Draft Day Sports: College Basketball 2024 boasts an improved user interface with a plethora of new options designed to provide more data in an easily accessible format. Exciting features include a special reveal for players making college decisions, new ratings, enhanced control over convincing players not to go pro or transfer, new camps for additional recruit information, a revamped transfer portal, and a comprehensive recruiting history. These additions solidify the game's status as the premier college basketball simulation.<br>
<br>
Immerse yourself in the game's vast amount of data, news, reports, and special features like an in-game selection show that will keep you on the edge of your seat as you anticipate your team's fate in the big dance. Draft Day Sports: College Basketball 2024 offers an unparalleled opportunity to live the life of a college basketball coach, making it a must-play for enthusiasts of the sport.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going Upstream</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2745530/Going_Upstream/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Let's paddle a canoe and climb up the river as far as we can! It's a simple game of just climbing up the river.<br/><br/>Use boosts and lateral movements skillfully to avoid obstacles and aim upstream. If you fail, you'll be swept down the river to a lower point.<br/><br/>Plan ahead and progress smartly!<h2 class="bb_tag">Objective of This Game</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745530/extras/2024-02-12_15-45-22.mp4.00_00_19_44.001.png?t=1709910613"><br/>This game is about a mysterious old man who relentlessly climbs up the river. Aim to reach the goal as quickly as possible!<h2 class="bb_tag">How to Play</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745530/extras/2024-02-12_15-45-22.mp4.00_01_31_01.002.png?t=1709910613"><br/>The controls are very simple! Use AWSD or the arrow keys to move left and right to avoid obstacles.<br/>You can dash by pressing upwards.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phenom Overdrive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748590/Phenom_Overdrive/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a highly dangerous mission through space. You will travel through strange locales and survive extraordinary threats caused by the recently appearing unexplained phenomena.<br/><br/>Your mission will be to scout the area and study the phenomena up close.  It is a highly dangerous mission with a low chance of survival and zero weaponry, due to early stage risk assessment.<br/><br/>However, your ship is equipped with an experimental state of the art Graviton-Pulse unit. With the Graviton-Pulse unit you will be able to reach almost instant inertia regardless of speed. Letting you make some difficult maneuvers. But be careful, once the pulse subsides, all momentum returns... with interests.<br/><br/>Return with as much data as you can collect. Depending on it, you’ll be rewarded at the end of your journey. Humanity eagerly awaits.<br/><br/>Features:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Navigate 30 highly dangerous levels.<br/></li><li>Physics based player movement and mechanics.<br/></li><li>360-degree directional analog input. Go towards the exact direction you press.<br/></li><li>Simple controls uses a very minimal number of buttons. Old school style.<br/></li><li>Support for controllers and mouse input.<br/></li><li>Different endings based on total phenomena discovered.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dawnsbury Days</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693730/Dawnsbury_Days/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Dawnsbury Days</strong> is a 2D turn-based tactics game with CRPG elements that's based on the rules of PF2E, the second edition of a powerful tabletop OGL ruleset.<br/><br/>You play as the Dawnsbury Four, a group of four young heroes from a small town. You choose their class, feats, spells and other abilities as you lead them through 4 character levels and 20 combat encounters on a quest to save their home town from a multitude of dangers. You will fight monsters and face dangers, but you will also make friends, acquire loot and level up, and eventually — hopefully — you will defeat whatever sinister force is behind all the dangers that have beset Dawnsbury for the last seven years.<br/><br/>The main adventure path can take about 4 hours for a single playthrough, but you can then replay it with different party compositions and besides the main adventure path, you can also try and defeat some of the powerful foes in additional scenarios in free encounter mode.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A complex OGL-based rule system which makes for strong strategic gameplay<br/></li><li>12 classes, from the Fighter to the Wizard to the Kineticist, each with different play patterns<br/></li><li>110+ feats and 70+ spells to further customize your characters<br/></li><li>20+ encounters in the main story-driven adventure path, and 10+ additional scenarios in free encounter mode<br/></li><li>Character level cap is 4.<br/></li><li>A story of childhood friends braving their first serious challenges in adventuring<br/></li><li>Support for custom maps, encounters and portraits<br/></li><li>Support for custom mods to add new ancestries, feats, rules and more</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Tactical combat</h2>Each turn, you get three actions to spend on moving, attacking, casting spells, taking combat maneuvers, drinking potions and defensive or other actions.<br/><br/>You can preview the effects and success probability of all actions before you commit and weigh your options. All combat encounters are balanced, but many are difficult: To win the game reliably and consistently on hard difficulty, you will need to make use of almost all of your options.<br/><br/>Every +1 matters: Buffing your allies, and demoralizing or flanking your enemies are often better options than making a third attack in a turn which would be affected by a very punishing multiple attack penalty anyway.<h2 class="bb_tag">A cinematic experience</h2>This game is a cinematic experience, where you fight one combat encounter after another, and these fights are interspersed only with (voiced!) cinematic cutscenes. The game doesn't waste your time: animations are lightning fast, cutscenes skippable, and you can really focus on the engaging combat experience.<br/><br/>Or you can choose an easy difficulty, and enjoy the story of the Dawnsbury Four, young adventurers grappling with their first real challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag">Story of the Dawnsbury Four</h2>Ever since the Night of the Shooting Stars seven years ago, the small town of Dawnsbury has been beset by dangers. The nearby volcano hasn't ceased erupting, support for neighbouring towns has lessened and kobold brigands terrorize the countryside. What's more, the Golden Candelabra, an artifact that protected Dawnsbury for generation, has been lost that same night.<br/><br/>But now new heroes may rise up: you play as the Dawnsbury Four, a group of childhood friends who have trained for years under the tutelage of the town mentor Roderick, and are now finally ready to embark on their first quest: to find and retrieve the Golden Candelabra and bring it back to Dawnsbury where it belongs.<br/><br/>But even that may only usher in further dangers and provoke whatever sinister force is behind all these woes...<h2 class="bb_tag">Accurate to tabletop</h2>Dawnsbury Days uses the rules of PF2E, the second edition of a powerful tabletop OGL ruleset, and strives to remain as faithful to them as possible, so that the gameplay of Dawnsbury Days mirrors your experiences when playing with friends around the table.<br/><br/>You play exclusively in turn-based mode on grid-based battlefields, and you can preview and review all dice rolls required to make attacks, saving throws or to deal damage.<br/><br/>The game also tries to replicate the elusive 'feel' of a tabletop roleplaying game, with story, characters and encounter design all in service to that goal.<h2 class="bb_tag">Deep character customization</h2>You choose your characters' ancestry, heritage, background, class, subclass, ability scores, skills, feats, spells and items — and that's just at level one.<br/><br/>On each level up (up to level 4, which is the level cap), you select from additional feats (and for spellcasters, spells) to further customize your character.<br/><br/>There is a wide variety of weapons, armor and consumable items to complement your character.<br/><br/>But you can also choose to skip all of that and use one of the eight pregen characters which are pre-built for each level, complete with items.<h2 class="bb_tag">Additional scenarios and modding support</h2>Besides the main adventure path, you can also fight additional scenarios with minimum story but with the same engaging gameplay.<br/><br/>You can also download custom encounters created by modders for an additional challenge and variety. Some of these can be really difficult and unique!<br/><br/>Dawnsbury Days is fully moddable. With code mods, you can add custom ancestries, feats, spells and even variant rules.  Documentation on how to create custom mods, including example mods, is included with the game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMERHOUSE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2533960/SUMMERHOUSE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2533960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2533960/extras/summerhouse_new_store_page.gif?t=1709984408"><br/><br/>SUMMERHOUSE is a small-scale building game and a love letter to the feeling of long lost summer afternoons.<br/><br/>Craft a neighbourhood of tiny, beautiful lived-in homes in a variety of settings: the sea, the city, or the mountains. While there are some little secrets to uncover, there are no rules, and you can’t win or lose. Just chill out, build to your heart’s content and soak up the atmosphere.<br/><br/>If relaxation and creation are your thing, this is a game for you :)<br/><br/><i>Please keep in mind that this is a small game with no goals or challenges, created by a single person🙂</i> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tales of Morrow</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1783620/Tales_of_Morrow/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1783620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1783620/extras/AbouttheGameTitle.png?t=1709910014"><br/>Create your tale in a beautiful world full of adventure and exploration! Tales of Morrow is a semi-survival, adventure, action RPG where you can build on your island, start a farm, travel to other islands riddled with ruins from a past civilization, and fight all enemies who oppose you. Here you will encounter a massive and lively environment with an extensive selection of weapons, tools and plenty to explore. So grab your sword or kick back with a fishing rod under the sunset and begin your story!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore, build, and survive</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1783620/extras/GifIsland.gif?t=1709910014"><h2 class="bb_tag">Discover ruins and conquer your enemies </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1783620/extras/GifCombat.gif?t=1709910014"><br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/>- Build anything using resources you collect from the islands<br/>- Explore procedural islands (No two islands are the same!)<br/>- Descend into dark dungeons and ancient cities<br/>- Encounter and defeat a wide array of enemies<br/>- Grab your pole and angle for countless fish<br/>- Start a farm! Scavenge and grow various crops<br/>- + much more!<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1783620/Tales_of_Morrow/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1783620/Tales_of_Morrow/</a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deterrence</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1972960/Deterrence/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1972960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Deterrence is a tower defense, real-time strategy hybrid that offers a midcore single-player experience. Play as the human race in the not-too-distant future and fight malfunctioning artificial intelligence. Choose your own conflicts in the nonlinear campaign that's complete with mission rewards and a research tree.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1972960/extras/Store1.gif?t=1709923575"><br/>Each level will put your tactical skills to the test as you will have to play an active role in helping your troops withstand the enemy onslaught whether that be repairing defenses, reallocating troops to another front, designating artillery strike zones, or destroying bridges.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1972960/extras/Store2.gif?t=1709923575"><br/>Command your troops to victory by taking advantage of everything the battlefield has to offer. Garrison troops in civilian structures for quick defense. Build artillery batteries to pound enemy advances. Jam the enemy signals to gain an advantage. Call in air strikes, artillery strikes, and warheads to turn the tide of battle.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1972960/extras/Store3.gif?t=1709923575"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Instant Action</strong><br/>No monotonous base building tech tree to construct each game. Deploy more advanced units, tactical aids, and defenses by unlocking them in the research tree.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Destructible Environments</strong><br/>Launch your attack and leave nothing standing. Level entire battlefields with powerful artillery barrages, rocket strikes, and catastrophic warheads.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Radio in Abilities</strong><br/>Call in powerful off-map tactical aids like air strikes, artillery strikes, and warheads to turn the tide of battle.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Points of Interest</strong><br/>Take advantage of everything the battlefield has to offer. Garrison troops in civilian structures for quick defenses and destroy bridges to control the flow of battle.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Simple Economy</strong><br/>Deploy and build everything on the battlefield with one currency.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Adjustable Game Speed</strong><br/>Plan moves while the game is paused, fast forward through waves, and watch action in slow motion.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Single-player campaign with 25 missions.<br/></li><li>Last Stand game mode with 5 missions.<br/></li><li>Steam leaderboards for the Last Stand game mode.<br/></li><li>9 units including aircraft and artillery to defend with.<br/></li><li>5 Defensive structures to build, including jammers and artillery.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Last Stand Game Mode</h2>Last Stand is a game mode where players are given limited money and must defend themselves against an endless onslaught of enemies. The goal is to survive the longest. Players can compete for best time of survival with the Steam leaderboards.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1972960/Deterrence/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1972960/Deterrence/</a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where is the meaning?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1693340/Where_is_the_meaning/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1693340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							«Where is the meaning?» is a single JRPG game made by two indie developers with very special attitude to this genre. The action takes place in unknown universe where the player should make conclusions what is happening around. You are the geometric figure «square» which need to reach the end of this world. But does it exists? You should find it out in this dangerous and strange adventure.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Minimalistic and not overextended unique JRPG with smoothly evolving gameplay<br/></li><li>Emotional voiceover with no language barrier<br/></li><li>You will not leave the desire to know what happens next<br/></li><li>Funny dialogs and non-pretentious characters<br/></li><li>Well-designed side-quests which you can skip on<br/></li><li>Every enemy has unique dialog<br/></li><li>You will meet tons of references easter eggs on your way<br/></li><li>Minimal tiring dialogs and battles<br/></li><li>Complimentary reviews of two friends who played the game</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Zombie Tail</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2762250/A_Zombie_Tail/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2762250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Save your best friend from the zombie invasion!<br/>​<br/>Defeat waves of zombies in this strategy defense style game. Armed with a bone and several power ups, keep the zombies at bay as you battle across several levels, by timing and managing your attacks across 4 lanes. Strategy will be key, should you use your power ups or save them. <br/>Will Roxy find her human before the zombies do!<br/>​<br/><strong><br/>- Play through 5 stages plus an unforgiving boss level.<br/>- Unlock multiple levels of difficulty to test your zombie killing strategies.​<br/>- Unlock endless level and see how far you can go, before the zombies take you over.<br/>- Unlock insane level to really test your strategy. (zombie spawn rates increased)<br/>- Upgradable main weapon. <br/>- Find all the hidden secrets..<br/>- Music progression, the first level song will add more with each completed level, to a full on song by the time you get to the boss.<br/>- 20 achievements to collect!<br/>- No ads or in app purchases!<br/>- Unlock a cheat menu to change the way the game is played.<br/>- 4 levels of difficulty, each unlocks after beating the previous level of difficulty.<br/><br/><br/>          DO YOU THINK YOU CAN<br/>          MASTER THE STRATAGY <br/>                   TO WIN?<br/>            I DARE YOU TO TRY.<br/>              YOU GOT THIS..<br/>                 ON EASY.<br/></strong><br/><br/><br/><br/>Graphics By<br/>MojoMaz<br/><br/>Game Dev, creation and code By<br/>Tazco<br/><br/>Music By Axis Granted​<br/>axisgrantedproductions​​<br/>​​<br/>Dedicated to our little Zombies Aidan &amp; Lyanna​​​​​​​​						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monuments Renovator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1257280/Monuments_Renovator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1257280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1226970/Disco_Simulator/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1226970/Disco_Simulator/</a><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2822370/Chocolate_Factory_Simulator/" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2822370/Chocolate_Factory_Simulator/</a><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FrrXhM8TF6y" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1257280/extras/joindiscordGI.png?t=1709906352"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1257280/extras/Titles1.png?t=1709906352"><br/>Monuments Renovator is a game in which you play the role of a professional monument renovator. You choose from among the world's greatest monuments, restore them to their former glory and learn about history and architecture.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1257280/extras/Titles2.png?t=1709906352"><br/>You organize, fill and paint. You rebuild collapsed walls, renew old frescoes. Do everything to bring the monument back to its glory days.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1257280/extras/Titles3.png?t=1709906352"><br/>Improve your skills in using various tools, use different materials and renovation will become more efficient and more enjoyable.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1257280/extras/Titles4.png?t=1709906352"><br/>Take care of the details when you work. Check the plans for the correctness of your work and make sure that the renovation proceeds in accordance with the project.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1257280/extras/Titles5.png?t=1709906352"><br/>The last stage is interior furnishings. Make the famous building functional as well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1257280/extras/Titles6.png?t=1709906352"><br/>Ready for the next challenge? The next great monuments are already waiting for your help.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King of the Bridge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2523120/King_of_the_Bridge/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2523120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">A BIZARRE GAME</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2523120/extras/0_c.gif?t=1709907097"><br/><br/>Defeat the troll in his homebrew game <i>"Advanced Troll Chess"</i> so you can cross his bridge. But with over twenty mind-boggling rule changes to a classic game, this will prove to be quite a challenge.<h2 class="bb_tag">THE TREACHEROUS TROLL</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2523120/extras/1_c.gif?t=1709907097"><br/><br/>This cunning foe will surely give you a hard time with his schemes, cheats and taunts! Can you defeat an opponent who has no regard for manners or rules?<h2 class="bb_tag">KNOWLEDGE IS POWER</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2523120/extras/2_c.gif?t=1709907097"><br/><br/>Decrypt the mysterious rulebook with over thirty pages and discover countless mad strategies as you play!<h2 class="bb_tag">COUNTER THE CHEATS</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2523120/extras/3_c.gif?t=1709907097"><br/><br/>Accuse your opponent if you suspect him of cheating! Guess correctly and be rewarded with the sweet taste of revenge!<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Intelligent Troll AI<br/></li><li> Multiple Endings<br/></li><li> Speedrun Mode<br/></li><li> Speed Chess Mode<br/></li><li> Lots of Easter-eggs<br/></li><li> 20+ Unique Rules<br/></li><li> 30+ Rulebook Pages<br/></li><li> 100+ Lines of Dialog<br/></li><li> 30+ Achievements<br/></li><li> Atmospheric Audio Design<br/></li><li> Handcrafted Pixelart</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORE BLASTERS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/BORE_BLASTERS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/BLAST.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_blast_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Blast your way through rocks and dirt with your machinegun drill. Carve through the ground to uncover precious ores and defeat menacing foes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/LOOT.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_loot_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Uncover ancient relics and artefacts hidden in the deep. Amass a fortune in rare gems &amp; ores.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/UPGRADE.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_mortar_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Invest in powerful upgrades and unlock new abilities, turning your humble gyrocopter into a fearsome force to be reckoned with.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/DISCOVER.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_discover_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Explore a diverse range of biomes, from treacherous volcanic caverns to lush overgrown underground forests, each with its own unique challenges and rewards.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/FEATURES.png?t=1709907021"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Intense mining action with fast-paced blasting<br/></li><li> Constant progress - even failed runs aren't punishing<br/></li><li> Diverse biomes to explore<br/></li><li> Purchase upgrades to overpower your gyrocopter<br/></li><li> Navigate the overworld to unlock new mine shafts<br/></li><li> Collect and loot rare gems, ores, and artefacts to upgrade your gear and abilities<br/></li><li> Endless replayability with procedurally generated levels</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_drones_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/><br/>Drawing inspiration from mining games like Motherload and Galactic Mining Corp, Bore Blasters takes the genre to the next level with high octane action and fast paced gameplay. Fans of digging and collecting will find plenty to love, while the addition of deadly enemies and mysterious artefacts will keep even the most seasoned miners on their toes.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/WL_arrow.gif?t=1709907021"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_missiles_frame.gif?t=1709907021"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreamscape Return</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2844580/Dreamscape_Return/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2844580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Dreamscape Return" is a simple yet challenging puzzle game. In this game, the player's task is to connect all the patterns, but there is an important rule: you cannot repeat the lines you have already walked.<br>
<br>
The rules of the game are very simple. Each level starts from a designated starting pattern. Players need to plan the path cleverly to ensure that a line connects all patterns. Carefully designing routes and thinking quickly are the keys to successfully completing each level. Players need to complete the challenge within the stipulated 5 minutes. When the challenge time is insufficient, the game provides a button option to skip this level. Players can choose to continue the challenge or directly enter the next level.<br>
<br>
"Dreamscape Return" not only exercises players' spatial cognition and logical thinking abilities, but also provides players with a pleasant and relaxing gaming experience. Get ready to take on the challenge, push your limits and have fun playing the game!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
