<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Three Kingdoms Zhao Yun</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2201710/Three_Kingdoms_Zhao_Yun/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							- Dive into 12 complete story chapters <br/>- Choose from 3 difficulty levels, with a minimum of 30 hours experience of main storyline.<br/>- Master 4 distinct weapon systems: spears, bows and arrows, swords, and steeds, supplemented by equipment systems like crafting, sets, refinement, and enchantment.<br/>- Explore no fewer than 30 expansive maps.<br/>- Encounter dozens of well-known Chinese historical figures, who will either fight by your side or become your adversaries.<br/>- Enjoy a wide range of visually striking outfits for the protagonist and companions.<br/>- Engage in several large-scale, renowned battles that truly capture the essence of the Three Kingdoms atmosphere.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/战场.gif?t=1705580289"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/连招1.gif?t=1705580289"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/大招.gif?t=1705580289"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/射箭.gif?t=1705580289"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immortal Life</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1201230/Immortal_Life/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Immortal Life is a captivating life simulation game where you strive to restore the Guiyun Sect after its near-total destruction – all while you try to achieve immortality through spiritual cultivation.</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/漫步乡野.gif?t=1705548243"><br/><br/>Decided to help your new brothers and sisters make this settlement grow and flourish into a prosperous village, you will work relentlessly with them to restore the Misty Valley by farming, cooking, and crafting decorations for your new home. As you strengthen your bonds with them, you will learn more about their lives, stories, and motivations. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/师兄弟.gif?t=1705548243"><br/><br/>As you work and improve your skills, you will ascend in your cultivation journey; and your adventures will take you far from your Misty Valley. One day you will rebuild the strength of the Guiyun Sect and restore the glory of the Misty Valley. And maybe even achieve immortal life yourself…<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Farm with Spells</h2>Roam through the countryside, using your magic to cultivate fields, and taking care of crops with enchanted tools. Manage your own farmland amidst changing seasons and weather.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/仙法种田.gif?t=1705548243"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cultivate your way to immortality</h2>Master various skills such as fishing, cooking, crafting elixirs, or making furniture. Remember, every skill is important to help you restore the Misty Valley and cultivate your soul and powers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/生活技艺.gif?t=1705548243"><br/><br/>Train your abilities and attend classes before submitting yourself to the tests that allow you to reach a new step in your cultivation journey. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/修仙生活.gif?t=1705548243"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Mystic Realms</h2>Travel to distant lands, uncover treasures and use your magic to defeat mythical creatures. There are more than 10 different Mystic Realms and you’ll have to master different abilities and strategies to find the crafting items that you need from each territory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/秘境战斗.gif?t=1705548243"><h2 class="bb_tag">Fellowship within the Sect</h2>Get to know your brothers and sisters and help them with their daily struggles to strengthen your bond. Each character has their own personality and interests in cultivation. By helping them, you’ll learn more about their lifes and motivations – and receive new items, missions, and skills. You can also invite them to share your dwellings.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/同门.gif?t=1705548243"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Home</h2>Acquire spirit stones, unlock new territories, and initiate construction projects to establish a tranquil sanctuary in the valley of your homestead. With your crafting skills and the help of your brothers and sisters, you will get new decorations and magic tools for your farm and house.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/仙府建设.gif?t=1705548243"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Cut: Samurai Duel</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2193490/First_Cut_Samurai_Duel/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A high-intensity arcade sword-fighting game where <strong>every strike is lethal</strong>. Slash, clash, parry, dodge and watch limbs fly in the atmosphere of historical feudal Japan. Choose your move carefully - <strong>the first cut is also the last.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/stg1.gif?t=1705515941"><br/><br/><strong>A refined and intuitive fighting system</strong> - Aim your sword to block attacks and strike around your opponent's guard. Parry their attacks with your own, dodge to close the distance, and interrupt them with a well-timed shove. It takes a minute to learn, and a lifetime to master.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/jan7.gif?t=1705515941"><br/><br/><strong>Customize your fighter</strong> - An array of different options to wear. Choose and colour each piece separately to make each character your own.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/stg2.gif?t=1705515941"><br/><br/><strong>Dueling with deadly results</strong> - Send heads and limbs flying as blood rains down and stains the characters and environment. Chop your opponent to pieces, or equip a wooden sword instead for a little mercy and possibly a concussion.<br/><br/>Duel your friends in <strong>local multiplayer</strong>, fight custom <strong>AI opponents</strong>, try to stay alive in <strong>Survival mode</strong>, or hunt down enemies in the <strong>Scenario mode</strong> campaign. <br/>Play with friends remotely using <strong>Steam Remote Play Together.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Bonus modes</strong> - Laser swords, custom blood, floating weapons, zombies, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/jan12.gif?t=1705515941"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warframe: Gauss Prime Access - Accessories Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748320/Warframe_Gauss_Prime_Access__Accessories_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							For more Prime Access Bundle options, click <a href="http://store.steampowered.com/sale/warframeprime/" rel="" target="_blank">here</a>.<br/><div class="bb_code"><strong>ACCESSORIES PACK</strong>
<ul class="bb_ul"> <li> ALTRA PRIME SYANDANA: A shining garment befitting the Saint of Altra.<br/></li><li> DOPPLINE PRIME ARMOR: The signature armor of Gauss Prime’s aesthetic.<br/></li><li> GAUSS PRIME BLAZARGAZE HELMET*: Style meets aerodynamics.<br/></li><li> NOGGLE STATUE - GAUSS PRIME: A small wobbly statue of Gauss Prime.<br/></li><li> GAUSS PRIME FLOOF*: A cuddly floof of golden thread.<br/></li><li> 90-Day Affinity Booster<br/></li><li> 90-Day Resource Booster</li></ul></div>Prime Warframes and Weapons in Prime Access can also be crafted from parts found in Relics in-game.<br/><br/>*Gauss Prime Access exclusive bonus item.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warframe: Gauss Prime Access - Weapons Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748310/Warframe_Gauss_Prime_Access__Weapons_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							For more Prime Access Bundle options, click <a href="http://store.steampowered.com/sale/warframeprime/" rel="" target="_blank">here</a>.<br/><div class="bb_code"><strong>WEAPONS PACK</strong><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> 1050 Platinum<br/></li><li> ACCELTRA PRIME: Engage your enemies with deadly speed. This weapon reloads even faster when its wielder sprints, faster still with Gauss.<br/></li><li> AKARIUS PRIME: Wield a golden pair of rocket launchers. Sprint to reload them faster. They reload fastest when wielded by Gauss.</li></ul></div>Prime Warframes and Weapons in Prime Access can also be crafted from parts found in Relics in-game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warframe: Gauss Prime Access - Prime Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748300/Warframe_Gauss_Prime_Access__Prime_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							For more Prime Access Pack options, click <a href="http://store.steampowered.com/sale/warframeprime/" rel="" target="_blank">here</a>.<br/><div class="bb_code"><strong>PRIME PACK</strong>
<ul class="bb_ul"><li> 2625 Platinum<br/></li><li> GAUSS PRIME: Quicksilver takes form. Gauss Prime brooks no talk of defeat.<br/></li><li> ACCELTRA PRIME: Engage your enemies with deadly speed. This weapon reloads even faster when its wielder sprints, faster still with Gauss.<br/></li><li> AKARIUS PRIME: Wield a golden pair of rocket launchers. Sprint to reload them faster. They reload fastest when wielded by Gauss.<br/></li><li> EXCLUSIVE GAUSS PRIME GLYPHS</li></ul></div><br/>Prime Warframes and Weapons in Prime Access can also be crafted from parts found in Relics in-game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominions 6 - Rise of the Pantokrator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2511500/Dominions_6__Rise_of_the_Pantokrator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2511500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are a God! You are master and ruler of a loyal nation. You have unimaginable powers at your disposal. You have claimed this world as yours. But there are others who stand in your way. You must defeat and destroy these pretenders. Only then can you ascend to godhood and become the new Pantokrator.<br>
<br>
Dominions 6 is a turn based 4x strategy game suitable for both play vs AI, player vs player.  Team play vs AI or players also works great as everyone can do their turns at once.  The game has a huge variety of units, spells, magic items and different nations to play.<br>
<br>
In Dominions you take control of a powerful being that rules a nation and aspires to godhood. The type of Pretender Gods can vary from magically powerful arch mages to huge titans or large monuments. The pretender gods have different strengths dependent on what kind of god you choose and what nation you play.<br>
<br>
When you start the game you decide what kind of god you are and how your Dominion affects your lands, followers and sacred soldiers. It is an expression of your divine might and the faith of your followers. If your dominion dies, so do you. Your dominion also inspires your sacred warriors and gives them powers derived from your dominion.<br/>
<br/>
In order to win and become the one true god you have to defeat your enemies one of three different ways: conquer their lands, extinguish their dominion or claim the Thrones of Ascension.<br/>
<br/>
Dominions is set in a fantasy world that draws inspiration from historical nations, cultures and myths. You will not encounter the elves of conventional fantasy in this game. Instead you might lead a nation of vanir from old norse myth. Aztecs, romans, israelites, greeks, kievian rus and lovecraftian horrors are just a few of the inspirational sources of the game.<br/>
<br/>
The first Dominions game was released in 2002 and was well received by strategy gamers. Since then Dominions has been much refined and Dominions series is still actively played making it one of the longest running 4x turn based strategy games.<br/>
<br/>
----------<br/>
<br/>
Dominions 6 is scaled up compared to Dominions 5 and armies are larger. We wanted to tweak the balance between conventional armies and magic. To accomplish this a couple of changes are introduced. Incomes and resources are increased, while mages are more expensive. Battlefield-wide spells are more difficult to cast and there are instead more mid-tier spells. There are some other changes with the same aim.<br/>
<br/>
The second and probably most influential change is the addition of a new magic path. No longer are illusions the domain of Air magic. Instead illusions, phantasms, dreams and the stuff of forgotten legends are manipulated with the path of Glamour. This has resulted in many new spells, items and sites being added to the game. <br/>
<br/>
A third massive change is the separation of mounts and riders. Riders and mounts now have separate stats and can be targeted individually. This change probably has less impact on gameplay than the previous one, but will still have an impact on cavalry and nations using mounted units.<br/>
<br/>
Dominions 6 features a number of new nations as well. The addition of the Glamour path has also affected several of the old nations. <br/>
<br/>
There are also a number of changes intended to ease gameplay.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cult of the Lamb: Sinful Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2646130/Cult_of_the_Lamb_Sinful_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2646130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Sin to your heart’s content with Cult of the Lamb: Sinful Pack. This pack is the perfect way to indulge for those who enjoy a gluttonous aesthetic befitting kings and queens. Vanity might be a sin, but there’s nothing wrong with that!<br/><br/><strong>Cult of the Lamb: Sinful Pack includes;</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>5 brand new Follower forms: Hammerhead, Ladybug, Tiger, Llama, Sphynx<br/></li><li>6 new Follower outfits<br/></li><li>6 new base decorations<br/></li><li>A sinful new Fleece for the Lamb!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Safety Hotline</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2357910/Home_Safety_Hotline/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/RuntimeLabel-HSH-Dark.png?t=1705432881"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/ShinyLogoOnlyGIF.gif?t=1705432881"><br/><br/><strong>Hearing noises? Seeing things? Call Home Safety Hotline! Our operators are standing by, waiting to give you the answers you need to protect your home from all manner of pests and household hazards.</strong><br/><br/>Home Safety Hotline is an analog horror inspired telephone operator simulator where you answer incoming callers' questions about what's inside their home. Read through a vast catalog of common pests and household hazards, and do your best to become an expert in home safety. You will be held responsible for what happens.<br/><br/>A new horror experiment from Nick Lives, the creator of <i>NiGHT SIGNAL</i> and <i>A Wonderful Day For Fishing</i>. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Navigate a vast catalog of safety information using the latest in 90's technology.<br/></li><li> Listen to original jazzy lo-fi music by David Johnsen while you place callers on hold.<br/></li><li> Correctly deduce what's in your callers' homes or else leave them to suffer the consequences.<br/></li><li> Learn about the various untold horrors that live inside your home.<br/></li><li> "Phobia Toggles" - An accessibility option that allows you to disable in-game images for common phobia triggers including arachnophobia and more.<br/></li><li> Unlockable Art Book detailing the game's development history.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/NumberOnlyGIF.gif?t=1705432881"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingsvein</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2276830/Kingsvein/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2276830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							All contact with the city of Kingsvein has been lost. As Wisp Slayer, your role is to investigate and exterminate whatever evil lurks there.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2276830/extras/castleBanner_616x152.gif?t=1705404781"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adventure through the castle and its outer reaches as you see fit - secret treasures and skulking beasts hide around every corner! <br/></li><li>Dynamic and deep tactical combat - toss your enemies into spikes then electrify their blood, or cover the battlefield in flames <br/></li><li>Customize your team by mixing and matching 15 different classes, each with upgradeable abilities and equippable passives <br/></li><li>Use your abilities to explore - freeze rivers with your magic, blast through cave walls, and throw chains to topple statues <br/></li><li>Ride your loyal steed in and out of combat, and train it to be as fierce as any Knight <br/></li><li>Set in the realm of Graven, a weird subterranean world of living soil and half-stone Diecast <br/></li><li>From the maker of the highly-rated <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1224290/Horizons_Gate/" rel="" target="_blank">Horizon's Gate</a>, <a href="http://store.steampowered.com/app/415920/Voidspire_Tactics/" rel="" target="_blank">Voidspire Tactics</a> and <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/643900/Alvora_Tactics/" rel="" target="_blank">Alvora Tactics</a></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2276830/extras/voidbeam616x152.gif?t=1705404781"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2744170/Artifact_SeekerPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/DS.png?t=1705399273"/></a><br/>The difference between the prologue version and the official version<br/>There is a special artifact in the prologue<br/>Characters: 2 in the prologue, at least 5 in the official version<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 3 in the final version.<br/>Systems: Tavern, Marketplace, and Endless Mode will be added to the game.<br/>Artifacts: More artifacts will be added to the game.<br/>Skills: More skills will be added in the official version.<br/>Words: More words will be added in the official version.<br/>Encounters: There will be more interesting encounters in the official version.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/11y.png?t=1705399273"><br/><strong>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1y.png?t=1705399273"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1z.gif?t=1705399273"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/2y.png?t=1705399273"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/gif1.gif?t=1705399273"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.png?t=1705399273"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.gif?t=1705399273"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong>[/b]<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.png?t=1705399273"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.gif?t=1705399273"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.png?t=1705399273"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.gif?t=1705399273"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><strong><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.png?t=1705399273"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.gif?t=1705399273"><br/>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </img></img></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sovereign Syndicate</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1674920/Sovereign_Syndicate/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1674920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1674920/extras/TitleLogo.png?t=1705355459"><br/><br/><strong><i>Explore an open world in this Victorian steampunk cRPG.</i></strong> Play as three characters with branching stories that intertwine. Investigate, interact, and take action to leave your mark on the world and its inhabitants. No random stat points here, use your skills to level them up, and trust your fate to our tarot card chance system. <br/><br/>So, how will you solve your problems? <strong><i>Combat, persuasion, magic, explosives?</i></strong> The choice is yours and all your cards are on the table; but be careful, the docklands aren’t for the faint of heart. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1674920/extras/Tarot.png?t=1705355459"><br/><br/><strong>Tarot Card Chance System</strong> – Leave your dice at home as you interact with a variety of characters. NPC’s react to your gender, race, appearance, and choice of dialogue, so you’d better look and act the part if you want the “right” results. But not everything is certain, luck plays a role and it’s all in the cards with our tarot card chance system. <br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1674920/extras/Stats.png?t=1705355459"><br/><br/><strong>Skill and Etiquette System</strong> -  The skills you use will improve your ability, while ignoring others will cause them to stagnate. Master the skills you choose and learn more about the world and its inhabitants to unlock special dialogue and skill-check options.<br/><br/>So go, see, do! And don’t be afraid to try the unconventional. Drown yourself in gin? Sure, provided you’ve got the constitution for it. Smoke that opium? Certainly, but be careful not to doze off— it might not be safe here. Put it all on black? You only live once, as they say. Even in failure you learn something…<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1674920/extras/Map.jpg?t=1705355459"><br/><br/><strong>A Rich Open World to Explore</strong> - A steampunk fantasy-inspired Victorian London awaits; filled with interesting characters and locations. Explore the back alleys, opium dens, brothels, and more at your peril, or relax and enjoy their simple pleasures. Investigate, interact, and take action to forge your own path.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1674920/extras/ThreeCharacters.png?t=1705355459"><br/><br/><strong>Three Characters, Three Different Stories</strong> – Play as three characters with stories that intertwine through the city’s docklands and unfold based on your choices.   <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Atticus Daley</strong>, an orphaned minotaur magician crawling out of the bottom of a bottle to find a sense of belonging, and his next fix. <br/></li><li> <strong>Clara Reed</strong>, a corsair with a checkered past, and a cunning woman with a rebellious streak. Follow her on a search for vengeance, and the courtesan killer.   <br/></li><li> <strong>Otto</strong>, the trusty automaton and companion of engineer Theodore Redgrave. More than just the sum of his parts, Otto wants more to life than servitude and utility.</li></ul><br/>Each character has their own mix of skills, equipment, and expertise, and they might just have to work together to succeed. Will you trust your companions, and should they trust you? Not everyone is a hero after all. <br/><br/><br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A large open world to explore, 20 different locations spread over the city’s east docklands<br/></li><li>Three playable characters<br/></li><li>Three intertwined stories to experience<br/></li><li>Branching narrative and dialogue system<br/></li><li>Character customization <br/></li><li>Tarot card chance system<br/></li><li>Single-player</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Momodora: Moonlit Farewell</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1747760/Momodora_Moonlit_Farewell/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1747760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Momodora: Moonlit Farewell" is the latest installment in the Momodora series. Join Momo, High Priestess of the village of Koho, as she embarks on a divine mission to save her people from imminent destruction at the hands of the demon hordes summoned by a malevolent bellringer.<h2 class="bb_tag">Story:</h2>Momodora: Moonlit Farewell presents the account of the greatest calamity to befall the village of Koho, five years after the events of Momodora III.<br/> Once the toll of an ominous bell is heard, the village is soon threatened by a demon invasion.<br/>The village's matriarch sends Momo Reinol, their most capable priestess, to investigate the bell and find the bellringer responsible for summoning demons. It is their hope that by finding the culprit, they will also  be able to secure the village's safety, and most importantly, the sacred Lun Tree's, a source of life and healing for Koho...<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Gorgeous pixel art and animation<br/></li><li> Action-packed gameplay focusing on melee combos, dodging enemy attacks, and firing arrows at enemies<br/></li><li> The "Sigil" system, which allows for greatly customizable play styles<br/></li><li> Intense and core-shaking boss battles<br/></li><li> Deep exploration into a world rich in lore and atmosphere<br/></li><li> Freely adjustable difficulty levels, allowing you to relax and explore the alluring world at your own pace or take on mighty foes for a real challenge</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Developer's Voice:</h2>Hello!<br/><br/>This is rdein, creator of the Momodora series. Recently my team and I have announced the latest installment in the series, “Moonlit Farewell”. This is a concluding story, following through from the events of Momodora 3. With this new tale, I also intend to close the book on many of the past games’ mysteries and questions.<br/><br/>I’m aware that many players are more familiar with the story of Kaho, which is set in a distant past. As such, I’m designing “Moonlit Farewell” to be as enjoyable as possible without prior knowledge of Momodora 1 to 3’s stories. Moreover, the series has always been focused on action and minimal stories. So please, don’t worry too much about “catching up”!<br/>Lastly, we hope to bring you our best game with this new title, using all the knowledge we’ve learned in the past 10 years. Please look forward to it!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frostrain</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735630/Frostrain/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/01_Thumnail.png?t=1705033707"><h2 class="bb_tag">Roam the frozen world</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Roam_the_frozen_world.gif?t=1705033707"><br/>Climate change has turned the world white and frozen, and the only thing moving on the planet is you, your passengers, and your train. It's a dead world, but ironically, it's all the more fascinating for it. A vivid landscape awaits you to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Keep your passengers happy</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Keep_your_passengers_happy.gif?t=1705033707"><br/>The passengers on your train will work diligently at your command, but be careful: if you don't manage their happiness properly, they might throw you off the train.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build your own train with card decks</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Build_your_own_train_with_card_decks.gif?t=1705033707"><br/>Each time you pass through a city, you'll be able to add new train cars by launching a heavy lift drone. Be careful with each choice you make. If you are lucky, you'll be able to build a better, more synergized, happily-ever-after train deck, but it won't always go as you planned.<h2 class="bb_tag">Reach the Promised Land</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Reach_the_Promised_Land.gif?t=1705033707"><br/>Lead your passengers in search of the Promised Land, somewhere on the eastern edge of the world. But the journey to the Promised Land isn't all smooth and pleasant. You'll have to pass through toxic areas, and a severe storm is brewing behind you. Pay attention to your passengers' happiness levels and lead them safely to the Promised Land. The journey is in your hands.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoardLand</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735620/BoardLand/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Create your own strategy with the dice</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/extras/Cardnals_1.gif?t=1705310503"><br/><br/>The dice is rolled!<br/>Are you going to move? Are you going to act?<br/>Different effects are applied to each die, and the numbers determine your behavior.<br/>How do you combine numbers to get the best results?<br/>Every time you pick a number, you'll have to choose carefully.<h2 class="bb_tag">Make a powerful board by strengthening the tiles.</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/extras/Cardinals_2.gif?t=1705310503"><br/><br/>Tiles get more and more powerful!<br/>Every time you act on a tile, the tile gains experience, and the tile with enough experience is upgradeable.<br/>Combine tiles with multiple properties to create the best strategy, your own board<h2 class="bb_tag">Defeat the monsters and bosses</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/extras/Cardinals_3.gif?t=1705310503"><br/><br/>Monsters disturb you!<br/>Monsters can summon Fireballs, or they can curse and cause obstacles to certain tiles.<br/>You have to move and act with the dice, avoiding these patterns every time.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Flame: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517810/The_Last_Flame_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_1.png?t=1705541234"><br/>The Last Flame is a roguelike auto-battler which focuses on build creation, strategy and decision making. Recruit special heroes, fight deadly encounters, loot and craft powerful gear, discover and create unique synergetic builds! Every run, you will need to create powerful builds that will take down your foes!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_A3.gif?t=1705541234"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_2.png?t=1705541234"><br/>The Last Flame offers an incredible amount of build diversity. Combine heroes, items, relics and origins together to create amazing builds! Hero and team building have been designed with flexibility and freedom at their core which allows you to discover and create unique synergetic builds every single run!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Builds.gif?t=1705541234"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_3.png?t=1705541234"><br/>In between the automated combats, you will have to cleverly guide your heroes through the adventure by making the smart decisions! Manage your resources, choose the optimal path in the map, make powerful builds, and strategically position and plan the combat phase!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Tactical.gif?t=1705541234"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/comingToFullVersion.png?t=1705541234"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get access to a lot more stuff! Make amazing builds with 300 items, 58 heroes, 125 relics and 60 origins.<br/></li><li>Continue the adventure in the third act, and meet the final boss in a special act!<br/></li><li>Face 30 challenging enemies and 10 bosses!<br/></li><li>Progress through 5 difficulties which will challenge your knowledge and strategy!<br/></li><li>Push your builds to their limit in the endless mode, a mode where you try to reach the highest floor!<br/></li><li>Experience the game in diverse and fun new ways with the challenge modes!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_ENDLESS.gif?t=1705541234"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summoners War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2426960/Summoners_War/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2426960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>▶Features</strong><br/><strong>[Tactical RPG play]</strong><br/>Witness the dazzling display of each monster 's unique skills.<br/>23 different Rune sets to pick and choose additional abilities for your monsters!<br/>Come up with the best strategy to win battles in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[Endless Fun]</strong><br/>Decorate your Village, battle other summoners , explore dungeons , fight in PvP battles , expand your collection, train monsters , and more.<br/><br/><strong>[The Key of Colletion RPG : Massive Collection]</strong><br/>Fire, Water, Wind, Light and Dark!<br/>5 different attributes, and 1500 different monsters!<br/>Collect as many monsters as you can and win battles with your own decks .<br/><br/><strong>[Real-time Raid]</strong><br/>Battle as a team with your greatest monsters !<br/>A real-time battle with 3 users!<br/>Defeat the boss with your fellow Summoners using various tactics.<br/><br/><strong>[Homunculus]</strong><br/>The Forbidden Summoning Magic has finally been revealed!<br/>You can Evolve the skill of your choice with this special monster.<br/>Summon Homunculus and show off your strategy in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[All about Turn-Based RPG : World Arena]</strong><br/>Enjoy a real-time battle with Summoners worldwide!<br/>Experience a breathtaking battle that starts from Pick &amp; Ban.<br/>Reveal your unique strategy to the world and win battles .<br/><br/><strong>[Guild Content]</strong><br/>A sensational Guild PvP battle in the Isle of Conquest!<br/>Explore the Tartarus' Labyrinth and dungeons with Guild Members.<br/>Make your Guild the greatest of all.<br/><br/><strong>[Dimension Hole]</strong><br/>Fight against the ancient power emerged from a new dimension!<br/>Defeat the Ancient Guardians and meet the powerful monsters with new awakening power.<br/><br/><strong>[Artifact]</strong><br/>Artifacts are now dropped with MAX power-up levels!<br/>Summoners , fight against the powerful bosses and acquire Artifacts!<br/>Enhance your monsters with various sub properties of Artifacts.<br/><br/><strong>[Progression and Farming Structure Revamp]</strong><br/>Summoner progression structure renewed and content reward greatly improved!<br/>Dive into Summoners War and experience the enhanced progression system!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portal: Revolution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/601360/Portal_Revolution/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Portal: Revolution is a fan-made mod for Portal 2 which plays before the events of Portal 2 in the dead and decaying Aperture facility.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/ezgif-7-f507c3c464_1_.gif?t=1705083406"><br/><strong>Over 40 new puzzles</strong><br/>The campaign contains 40 brand new puzzles making use of new test elements and presents existing mechanics in a new way not seen in Portal 2.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resurrected "Pneumatic Diversity Vent" element<br/></li><li> New laser cube variant<br/></li><li> Over 15 puzzles using only the blue Portal-Gun<br/></li><li> Gel Cleansing Field</li></ul><br/><strong>Difficulty</strong><br/>Portal: Revolutions puzzle difficulty starts where Portal 2 stops, but fear not. All new mechanics and advanced portal tricks are taught to you. We have ensured through rigorous playtesting that every player can solve the puzzles. Although very few chambers require portals to be fired mid-air, no puzzles require advanced tricky movement.<br/><br/>Depending on your experience with Portal 2 mechanics, you can expect about 5 to 7 hours of playtime.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/banner_story_2.gif?t=1705083406"><br/>Set inbetween Portal and Portal 2, Portal: Revolution tells a brand new story using new characters. You play as a test subject who is awoken by a personality sphere called Stirling and join his mission to find a powerful device capable of restoring Aperture to its former glory.<h2 class="bb_tag">ENGINE</h2>Portal: Revolution uses a modified version of Portal 2: Community Edition's engine, which is a custom version of the Counter-Strike: Global Offensive Source Engine branch using licensed source code provided by Valve Software.<br/><br/>This allowed us to introduce many mechanics and improvements to the engine to create an experience which would be impossible in Portal 2.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Memories</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2495450/Winter_Memories/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1705531460"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Header_EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter-Memories-Cards_GIF.gif?t=1705531460"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Trading_Others_EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_1-EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/>After the unforgettable summer memories you’ve made half a year ago, Yui, Rio, and Miyuki are back. With the change of seasons and the cold falling snow, a new page to your story is about to begin. <br/><br/>Revisit the peaceful, seaside town, and spend time catching up with your family and friends.<br/><br/>What new memories will you make this winter?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_3-EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Miyuki_EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Rio_EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Yui_EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_4-EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/><strong>A Relaxing, Adventure RPG<strong><br/><br/><strong>Explore the Beautiful, Seaside Town<strong><br/><br/><strong>Manage How You Spend Your TIme<strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pesticide Not Required: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2480450/Pesticide_Not_Required_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The free prologue for Pesticide Not Required, a game that combines auto-attacking bullet heaven roguelites with farming game mechanics to create an expansive set of strategies and build combinations. Destroy huge hordes of evil insects, grow tons of crops, create your own build path, and unlock unique characters to play with!<br/><br/>This prologue version contains similar mechanics to the main game, but has less achievements, progression unlocks, unlockable characters, weapons, maps, and enemy varieties.<h2 class="bb_tag">Create Overpowered Builds</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/extras/CombatChaosFisher.gif?t=1705210453"><br/>You are the bullet hell! Grow an arsenal of ridiculous weapons and craft your own unique build with a combination of 40+ stats. Additionally, each character has their own unique traits that keep runs fresh.<h2 class="bb_tag">Farm, Fish, and Mine</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/extras/FarmFishMineWinterGif.gif?t=1705210453"><br/>Earn vital gold and experience from growing crops, catching fish, and mining. Expand your plot to harvest huge quantities of crops and build carefully to enhance your farming, fishing, and mining capabilities.<h2 class="bb_tag">Automate Your Farm With Pets</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/extras/PetsGifAutumn.gif?t=1705210453"><br/>Recruit friendly pets that will enhance your farm, collect loot, and kill enemies.<br/><br/>Other Features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Season-themed map variations with multiple difficulty levels<br/></li><li>Many unlockable characters with special traits<br/></li><li>Persistent skill tree upgrades<br/></li><li>Quick ~20-minute play sessions<br/></li><li>Tons of achievements to unlock<br/></li><li>Full gamepad and keyboard support<br/></li><li>Go WUMBO!</li></ul><br/>Pesticide Not Required: Prologue is inspired by awesome games like Brotato, Vampire Survivors, and Atomicrops.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Esports Godfather Origin</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2739460/Esports_Godfather_Origin/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/游戏简介英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>"Esport Godfather" is a management simulation card game that revolves around the theme of MOBA esports. In this game, you will assume the role of a coach in an esports club and personally build your own team! Starting from scratch, what kind of playstyle will you devise for your team? In a constantly evolving meta, can you derive a unique understanding of what it takes to win? How will you unlock the potential of your handpicked athletes and mold them into superstars?<br/><br/>Ultimately, will you be able to become a legendary figure in the esports industry, crafting your own esports story and lifting the championship trophy?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/选手培养英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>Each athlete is unique! They all have their own strengths and weaknesses.<br/>If an athlete's efficiency in earning money increases over time, they are undoubtedly a skilled late-game specialist.<br/>Successful ambushes can unlock hidden potential, propelling some athletes onto the path of godlike.<br/>As a coach, it's your responsibility to analyze each athlete's characteristics, devise training plans tailored to their needs, and guide them on their journey to becoming superstars!<br/><br/>· Every athlete possesses distinct abilities that will impact their performance on the battlefield!<br/>· An athlete's hero pool is crucial for Ban &amp; Pick strategies!<br/>· The tactic cards utilized by athletes in matches serve as the foundation of all strategies!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/版本变更英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>The meta environment is ever-changing!<br/>Changes in the equipment pool, the structure of economic income, and the source of decisive advantages, even slight alterations to the rules can drastically shift the priorities of Ban &amp; Pick and alter the strategic approach!<br/><br/>· Equipment will be added or removed as the versions change!<br/>· The timing of crucial team fights will shift with each version update, making team composition crucial!<br/>· Does harassment grant more gold? Do kills damage towers? Each gameplay rule brings a fresh experience!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/指挥战斗英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>You have the power to command the battlefield, with athletes attentively listening to your orders.<br/>Should you play it safe and focus on farming under the towers, or launch aggressive assaults and initiate attacks?<br/>Perfect team composition requires perfect leadership! The game is ever-changing, and you must face your opponents head-on!<br/><br/>· Each hero and athlete possesses their own tactic cards. It is through creative combinations and strategic application that they become unstoppable!<br/>· Offense or defense? Aggression or caution? The outcome rests in your hands. Formulate strategies and implement tactics!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/其他内容英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>· Over 50 unique heroes in the starting lineup, each with their own special abilities!<br/>· 200+ tactic cards, granting you control over the battlefield!<br/>· Diverse athlete training options! As a mentor, it's important to tailor your teachings to each individual!<br/>· Unearth young talents and cultivate new forces in the youth training camp!<br/>· Choose sponsors, a top-tier club deserves the support of top-tier sponsors!<br/>· Trash-talking sessions, asserting dominance is a must before crucial matches!<br/>· Abundance of events, includes unexpected occurrences, athlete communication, team pep talks!<br/>· Training match plans, knowing your opponents inside out ensures victory after victory!<br/>· Regular season, playoffs, transfer periods—different decisions await you at different times!<br/>· When athletes reach their limits, you must help them break through and reach new heights!<br/>· Create a custom team logo for your club!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/工作室LOGO英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowbreak: Containment Zone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668080/Snowbreak_Containment_Zone/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Snowbreak: Containment Zone is a 3D sci-fi RPG-shooter powered by the Unreal Engine 4 that offers a next-gen, cross-platform gaming experience, sharing your progress across all of your devices. <br/><br/>The Descent of the Titans turned a once-vibrant city into the devastated wasteland of Containment Zone Aleph. As the Adjutant of Heimdall Force, bravely undertake missions alongside Manifestations with the powers of gods and unique personalities, seeking to bring this bitter winter to an end...<br/><br/>[Enjoy Hybrid Combat]<br/>Snowbreak's weaponry injects realism into a sci-fi setting, with designs closely simulating future firearms technology. This combines with the otherworldly, RPG-like skill mechanic to create a refreshing combat experience.<br/><br/>[Take on Titans]<br/>The Descent of the Titans completely changed the world, and the battlefield. Feel the thrill of battling giants in this dystopian future!<br/><br/>[Befriend Operatives]<br/>Spend time with your Heimdall Force companions in the Base system. Decorate, chat, and give gifts to grow closer!<br/><br/>[Play Co-Op in Gigalink] <br/>Tired of exploring alone? Join up with friends and fight enemies together!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703868247"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1705569806"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1705569806"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1705569806"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1705569806"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1705569806"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1705569806"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1705569806"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1704804364"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1704380508"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1704380508"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1705439381"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1705439381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1705439381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1705439381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1705439381"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Born of Bread</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1555140/Born_of_Bread/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Beings from another age are causing havoc across the land! And with their mischief comes a great threat to everyone. The unlikeliest hero, a golem born of bread, will find himself and his newfound buddies in the middle of a drama that's thousands of years in the making. Together, they will visit incredible locals and meet fascinating characters. Although he may not look like much, Loaf might be the hero this land kneads.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Sentient Bread on a Quest</h2><br/>Play as a flour golem who possesses a never-ending childlike wonder and a set of odd abilities in this 2.5D adventure game!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Cinematic_opti.gif?t=1705570384"><br/><br/>Explore the different regions of a wonderful world ripe with mysteries and team up with a colorful cast of fleshed-out characters. With the help of your buddies, face off against menacing and weird baddies and engage in a fun and quirky turn-based combat system.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Enviro_opti.gif?t=1705570384"><br/><br/><strong>A home-cooked battle system</strong><br/>Born of Bread puts a twist on turn-based combat tropes with a fun interaction system that will test your reflexes.<br/>This interactive system also features a weaknesss and resistance system that makes battles more strategic.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Combat_Opti.gif?t=1705570384"><br/><br/><strong>Team up with your buddies</strong><br/>Loaf can't do it alone. Meet new characters during your adventure, each with their own abilities and personnality. Use their unique skills to overcome threats and obstacles whether in fights or when exploring.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Buddies_opti.gif?t=1705570384"><br/><br/><strong>Stream your fights to a fake audience!</strong><br/>Your dragon buddy Dub will let you save your progression but also stream your fights to a fake audience with his little laptop! Gather more viewers and answer their demand to get rewards!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogs Huddled Together 挤在一起的狗狗们</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2723460/Dogs_Huddled_Together/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to "Dogs Huddled Together" - a therapeutic puzzle game featuring adorable dogs. Each puzzle piece is a cute dog, and you can freely adjust the difficulty. The game includes two fun puzzle modes to help you relax with hundreds of dogs!<br>
<br>
-----Game Controls------<br>
<br>
- Use the left mouse button to move a puzzle piece.<br>
- Click the right mouse button to rotate a puzzle piece.<br>
- Press the R key to rotate the selected puzzle piece.<br>
- Press the W key to shuffle and redeal.<br/>
- Press the Q key to hide or show the game UI.<br/>
- Settings allow individual toggling of the level base's frame.<br/>
- Settings allow individual toggling of the hint function.<br/>
- Settings allow individual toggling of dog sound effects.<br/>
<br/>
-----Game Features------<br/>
<br/>
- Hundreds of adorable hand-drawn dogs.<br/>
- 32 levels with varying numbers of pieces.<br/>
- Freely adjustable difficulty levels.<br/>
- Immersive puzzle experience.<br/>
- Cute dog sound effects.<br/>
- Relaxing background music.<br/>
<br/>
------------------------						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estellina</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2744550/Estellina/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dive into a vibrant, retro 3D adventure with Estellina, a fast-paced 3d platformer &amp; runner that will ignite your nostalgia for classic arcade games!<br/><br/>Embark on a journey through a colorful bright universe brimming with challenging scenarios. Solve puzzles on the fly and dodge treacherous obstacles as you race for the highest score and ultimate galactic glory.<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong>:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Thrilling On-the-Fly Puzzle Solving:</strong> Think fast and strategize your path through mind-bending puzzles that demand quick reflexes and razor-sharp wit.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Score-Chasing Frenzy:</strong> Push your limits and rack up points as you maneuver through each level. Can you claim the title of the galaxy's greatest star?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Reflex-Testing Obstacles:</strong> Dodge and weave through perilous hazards that will put your dexterity to the ultimate test. Stay focused and avoid collisions at all costs!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chalo Chalo</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/410000/Chalo_Chalo/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/410000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Really slow racing for 3 to 8 players</strong></h2>Chalo Chalo is a racing game that doesn't focus on speed, but on tactical choices and outsmarting your friends. You compete locally with three to eight players at the same time on the same screen. <br/><br/>A unique landscape is generated for each race. During the countdown you make a plan, taking into account the terrain, your opponents and the power pickups.<br/><br/>With a special power, or just a simple nudge, you can send an opponent off track, sometimes with fatal consequences. But when the others are closing in, be sure you can pull it off without harming your own position.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/410000/extras/Chalo_Chalo_players_600x240.png?t=1705579056"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Local Multiplayer</strong></h2>Please be aware that <strong>Chalo Chalo has no single player, two player or online multiplayer modes</strong>. You need three to eight people with a controller each to play.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/410000/extras/Chalo_Chalo_number_of_players.png?t=1705579056"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Note from the developer</strong></h2>Through the years we've shown Chalo Chalo at different festivals and conferences and it's especially in these settings that the game thrives. The recommended ingredients being: <br/>- A large enough group of people. You can play the game with three people, but we've always felt the game starts to shine with 5 or more.<br/>- A big screen. Bigger is better here.<br/>- A bunch of controllers. We typically used a mix of both wired and wireless Xbox 360 controllers, but any controller recognized by Windows should work.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matadouro: Grindhouse</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2745610/Matadouro_Grindhouse/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Raul Jacques, a uncompromisable detective with a past colored in red investigates a season of kidnappings thought to be related until, Maria, a medical student with a bright future, is the next unfortunate soul. Fed up with the forces lack of care, the detective goes rogue and sets off to find out what is going on until his search leads him to an abandoned slaughtered house.<br>
<br>
There he must endure horrors, uncovering a mysterious of a cannibal cult, and the inhumane experiments done to the kidnapped victims, fighting experimental monsters and cultists alike, on a struggle for survival and saving the girl.<br>
<br>
Matadouro: Grindhouse is a first person shooter survival horror, features a variety of weapons and enemies, exploration of atmospheric and gruesome environments, and puzzle solving, with backtracking and resource management like classics of horror.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>少女与机甲/Girls And Robots</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2584450/Girls_And_Robots/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2584450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In the apocalyptic world, you have to face endless monsters. Now pick up your weapons and start fighting! You must choose the right girl and robot to form a unique team to complete different challenges. Find and discover the truth of world destruction and ways to save the world. Strive to survive, evolve, find the cause of the world's destruction in the midst of gunfire and bullets, and strive to save the world from monsters!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal Race Party</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2758180/Animal_Race_Party/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In Animal Race Party, the main objective is to race through tracks, collecting gold stars to secure victory. Each player can choose from six cute animals, each possessing a unique skill that can be strategically used to gain an advantage. Get ready for an exhilarating racing experience filled with fun, competition, and unpredictable moments!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758180/extras/Movie_056cc.gif?t=1705565960"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758180/extras/Movie_057cc.gif?t=1705565960"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758180/extras/Movie_058cc.gif?t=1705565960"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758180/extras/Movie_063cc.gif?t=1705565960"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROAD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2763020/ROAD/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2763020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							ROAD<br>
<br>
A Driving / Endless Runner type game<br>
<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
<br/>
Collect Coins<br/>
Magnets<br/>
Boosters<br/>
Overcome Obstacles<br/>
Moving Plates<br/>
Rain Storms<br/>
Other Cars<br/>
Fun Music<br/>
Cool Visuals<br/>
Settings<br/>
Score Saves						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Kingdoms Zhao Yun</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2201710/Three_Kingdoms_Zhao_Yun/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							- Dive into 12 complete story chapters <br/>- Choose from 3 difficulty levels, with a minimum of 30 hours experience of main storyline.<br/>- Master 4 distinct weapon systems: spears, bows and arrows, swords, and steeds, supplemented by equipment systems like crafting, sets, refinement, and enchantment.<br/>- Explore no fewer than 30 expansive maps.<br/>- Encounter dozens of well-known Chinese historical figures, who will either fight by your side or become your adversaries.<br/>- Enjoy a wide range of visually striking outfits for the protagonist and companions.<br/>- Engage in several large-scale, renowned battles that truly capture the essence of the Three Kingdoms atmosphere.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/战场.gif?t=1705580289"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/连招1.gif?t=1705580289"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/大招.gif?t=1705580289"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/射箭.gif?t=1705580289"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combo Card Clashers: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668680/Combo_Card_Clashers_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i>Combo Card Clashers: Prologue</i></strong> is a part of the full version of the upcoming game - <strong><i>Combo Card Clashers</i></strong>, a <strong>roguelike deckbuilder</strong> meets <strong>auto battler</strong> with unique <strong>card combo</strong> battle mechanics. In the Prologue, you will play as the Mage &amp; Warrior in a procedurally-generated map. Experiment with a variety of cards, artifacts, and gear to battle through the monsters!<h2 class="bb_tag">The Prologue features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The <strong>Mage</strong> character - specializes in deadly magic using mana<br/></li><li>The <strong>Warrior</strong> character - damage is everything<br/></li><li>A variety of cards - build powerful synergies<br/></li><li>Procedurally-generated map - extended to include more nodes!<br/></li><li>Gear and Mercenary Store - You can even recruit monsters to fight for you<br/></li><li>Ascension levels - Replayability won't be an issue</li></ul><br/>What makes <strong><i>Combo Card Clashers</i></strong> unique and different from other deck-building games is the innovative <strong>Card Combo Grid</strong> which allows powerful card synergies to be built every turn. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668680/extras/EN_combat.gif?t=1705556640"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668680/extras/title-1-en.png?t=1705556640"><br/>Each turn, you add a card to the combo grid and play all cards in grid. Experiment with the different card synergies and grid placement to unlock powerful effects. Duplicate, modify, and enhance cards to unleash more potential! Build up damage and slay enemies with no-nonsense attacks, blast them with magic spells, or torture them with negative effects - all in one turn!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668680/extras/title-2-en.png?t=1705556640"><br/>A good team could also lead you to victory. Other than recruiting mercenaries in stores, you could also befriend monsters after combat to become your allies! Their special abilities could just be that trick up your sleeve to win the next fight.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668680/extras/title-3-en.png?t=1705556640"><br/>The main game offers three heroes, each with their own unique style and strength. Customize the attributes of each hero and craft their starting deck to maximize their abilities. You can also level up, equip gear, find relics and learn skills to open up new roads to progression.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668680/extras/EN_progression_path.gif?t=1705556640"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668680/extras/title-4-en.png?t=1705556640"><br/>Embark on a journey, Discover events, buy new cards, upgrade cards, get weapons and gear, recruiting monsters and mercenaries, discover relics, and using strategy to win intense tactical battles!<h2 class="bb_tag">Wishlist the Full Game</h2>The full game will have more characters, more cards, more encounters...<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2054770/_/" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2054770/_/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT FLOOR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2677650/NEXT_FLOOR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Will you be able to survive to the next floor?</h2><br/><strong>NEXT FLOOR is a score attack, fast-paced, ultraviolent fps, with a lot of guns and blood, where your objective is simple, get out of an elevator, cross a floor full of enemies, traps and explosives until you reach the next elevator.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Enemies that want to take you down at any cost, but don't worry because using your creativity, you can:<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677650/extras/creativitykills.gif?t=1705548086"><br/><br/><strong>Traps </strong>that you can use to finish enemies in the most interactive ways possible<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677650/extras/ardamilhas.gif?t=1705548086"><br/><br/><strong>And explosives,</strong> to obliterate everything you see in front of you and make everything even more cinematic..<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677650/extras/explosoes.gif?t=1705548086"><br/><br/>Featuring a series of <i>weapons (one more violent than the other), different types of kicks, slow motion, lots of violence, a hook to pull enemies and even teleportation</i>, take all your stress out on enemies and make the <strong>most creative kills to get as many points as possible</strong>, and of course, <strong>reach the highest floor you can</strong>, however, with each floor, the enemies become increasingly stronger and more deadly.<h2 class="bb_tag">Death is your playground</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677650/extras/othersteamgif_1.gif?t=1705548086"><h2 class="bb_tag">Given this, answer me, how far can you get?</h2></img></img></img></img></strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Bike Racing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2574870/Extreme_Bike_Racing/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2574870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Extreme Bike Racing is ultimate 3D Bike Racing game for all age group. There are 3 stages with 3 challenges in every stage in which player has to face different hurdles and difficulties to complete that challenge.<br>
<br>
Features<br>
1. 10 Different challenges with one demo level.<br>
2. Difficulty increases after completing of every challenge.<br>
3. Finale gets unlocked once all challenges of every stage is completed.<br>
4. Smooth gameplay exprience for all age group.<br/>
5. Various different bikes available for the player to choose from.<br/>
6. Multiplayer support in the game.<br/>
7. Multilanguage support in the game.<br/>
<br/>
Get ready for Extreme Bike Racing...						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immortal Life</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1201230/Immortal_Life/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Immortal Life is a captivating life simulation game where you strive to restore the Guiyun Sect after its near-total destruction – all while you try to achieve immortality through spiritual cultivation.</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/漫步乡野.gif?t=1705548243"><br/><br/>Decided to help your new brothers and sisters make this settlement grow and flourish into a prosperous village, you will work relentlessly with them to restore the Misty Valley by farming, cooking, and crafting decorations for your new home. As you strengthen your bonds with them, you will learn more about their lives, stories, and motivations. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/师兄弟.gif?t=1705548243"><br/><br/>As you work and improve your skills, you will ascend in your cultivation journey; and your adventures will take you far from your Misty Valley. One day you will rebuild the strength of the Guiyun Sect and restore the glory of the Misty Valley. And maybe even achieve immortal life yourself…<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Farm with Spells</h2>Roam through the countryside, using your magic to cultivate fields, and taking care of crops with enchanted tools. Manage your own farmland amidst changing seasons and weather.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/仙法种田.gif?t=1705548243"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cultivate your way to immortality</h2>Master various skills such as fishing, cooking, crafting elixirs, or making furniture. Remember, every skill is important to help you restore the Misty Valley and cultivate your soul and powers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/生活技艺.gif?t=1705548243"><br/><br/>Train your abilities and attend classes before submitting yourself to the tests that allow you to reach a new step in your cultivation journey. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/修仙生活.gif?t=1705548243"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Mystic Realms</h2>Travel to distant lands, uncover treasures and use your magic to defeat mythical creatures. There are more than 10 different Mystic Realms and you’ll have to master different abilities and strategies to find the crafting items that you need from each territory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/秘境战斗.gif?t=1705548243"><h2 class="bb_tag">Fellowship within the Sect</h2>Get to know your brothers and sisters and help them with their daily struggles to strengthen your bond. Each character has their own personality and interests in cultivation. By helping them, you’ll learn more about their lifes and motivations – and receive new items, missions, and skills. You can also invite them to share your dwellings.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/同门.gif?t=1705548243"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Home</h2>Acquire spirit stones, unlock new territories, and initiate construction projects to establish a tranquil sanctuary in the valley of your homestead. With your crafting skills and the help of your brothers and sisters, you will get new decorations and magic tools for your farm and house.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/仙府建设.gif?t=1705548243"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ninja Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2546680/Ninja_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2546680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Ninja Maker</strong> is a 3D platformer game that you can create your own levels. Unleash your creativity and design the levels of your dreams!<h2 class="bb_tag">Campaign:</h2>Explore 5 worlds with 25 different levels. Find all the collectibles while fighting with various enemies. Be careful! At the end of every world, a boss fight waiting for you!<h2 class="bb_tag">Create, Play and Share:</h2>Build levels however you want! Add blocks, enemies, coins, obstacles, traps and others. Share your levels and play other levels created by players around the world.<h2 class="bb_tag">Block-Based Programming:</h2>Make your own gameplay by adding logic to blocks.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gachapon</h2>Collect coins to buy gachapons and unlock new characters.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fun combat: fight various enemies with your katana and shuriken<br/></li><li> Discover secrets with an 360° interactive camera<br/></li><li> 5 worlds and 25 different levels<br/></li><li> Block-based programming<br/></li><li> Level editor</li></ul><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2546680/extras/ninja_3.png?t=1705524200"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Cut: Samurai Duel</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2193490/First_Cut_Samurai_Duel/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A high-intensity arcade sword-fighting game where <strong>every strike is lethal</strong>. Slash, clash, parry, dodge and watch limbs fly in the atmosphere of historical feudal Japan. Choose your move carefully - <strong>the first cut is also the last.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/stg1.gif?t=1705515941"><br/><br/><strong>A refined and intuitive fighting system</strong> - Aim your sword to block attacks and strike around your opponent's guard. Parry their attacks with your own, dodge to close the distance, and interrupt them with a well-timed shove. It takes a minute to learn, and a lifetime to master.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/jan7.gif?t=1705515941"><br/><br/><strong>Customize your fighter</strong> - An array of different options to wear. Choose and colour each piece separately to make each character your own.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/stg2.gif?t=1705515941"><br/><br/><strong>Dueling with deadly results</strong> - Send heads and limbs flying as blood rains down and stains the characters and environment. Chop your opponent to pieces, or equip a wooden sword instead for a little mercy and possibly a concussion.<br/><br/>Duel your friends in <strong>local multiplayer</strong>, fight custom <strong>AI opponents</strong>, try to stay alive in <strong>Survival mode</strong>, or hunt down enemies in the <strong>Scenario mode</strong> campaign. <br/>Play with friends remotely using <strong>Steam Remote Play Together.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Bonus modes</strong> - Laser swords, custom blood, floating weapons, zombies, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/jan12.gif?t=1705515941"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEST TEST TEST</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667690/TEST_TEST_TEST/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667690/extras/2023_08_02_Teaser.gif?t=1705552043"><br/><br/>TEST TEST TEST is a retro pixel-art point-and-click puzzle adventure where you must escape a time loop as an overworked office employee.<br/>Find clues, gather information, and solve cryptic puzzles with alternate reality game elements.<br/>Will you able to release yourself from the clutch of time itself? Or will you be stuck in this reality forever?<br/><br/> ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟<br/>                                                                 FEATURES<br/> ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore various areas, from your own apartment room to the big corporate office building.<br/></li><li>Non-linear puzzle with Alternate Reality Game elements<br/></li><li>15 minutes time loop<br/></li><li>Hand-drawn retro pixel-art aesthetic with modern touches</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Night in Kawami</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2615810/One_Night_in_Kawami/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Welcome to the City of Rivers!</h2><br/>In <strong>One Night in Kawami</strong>, you play Max, who is about to meet an online acquaintance for the first time: Tanya. She will be your friendly guide in this metropolis where tradition and technology converge - but other than checking the sights, are there <i>other</i> reasons for this meetup? Only one way to find out...<h2 class="bb_tag">It's Your First Time In the Big City; Make It Count</h2><br/>You will get a first look at a longer story in this short visual novel penned by <strong>Jigu</strong> (<i>Cobra Kai 2: Dojos Rising</i>, <i>A Match Made in Limbo</i>). This fifteen-minute tale offers slightly different outcomes on the final stretch.<br/><br/><i>(Feel free to save and load it before pressing the button. Once you get there, you will know.)</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Original Visuals by Brazilian Artists</h2><br/>Featuring character art by <strong>SlowPumpkins</strong> and backgrounds by <strong>Nanda Doti</strong>, get ready to meet Kawami's coolest citizens...<h2 class="bb_tag">Dunking on Annoying Wannabes</h2><br/>... and some other guy, apparently? No one knows who he is or cares. <i>Every</i> city has one of those, I guess.<h2 class="bb_tag">Distorted Guitars!</h2><br/>If you are as into indie &amp; alternative rock as we are, put on your phones for this. <strong>One Night in Kawami</strong> features a curated soundtrack to explore the City of Rivers' nightlife. (Creative Commons, full credits in the game)<h2 class="bb_tag">About <strong>One Night in Kawami</strong></h2><br/>This is <strong>Brand New Whatever</strong>'s first foray into in-house development and self-publishing. It is an expanded and improved remake of <strong>Out of Phase Synchronicity</strong>, an interactive fiction text adventure Jigu submitted to <i>IntroComp 2020</i>.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontline Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2275220/Frontline_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2275220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2275220/extras/banner-boom.gif?t=1705511071"><br/><br/>Frontline Survivors is an intense top-down shooter with roguelite elements that puts you in the boots of a soldier fighting for survival on the battlefield. With countless enemies coming at you from all sides, you will need to use all your skills and strategy to stay alive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2275220/extras/banner_buddies.gif?t=1705511071"><br/><br/>As you progress through the game, you'll have the opportunity to level up and choose upgrades that can improve your weapon efficiency as well as give you a range of special abilities. Whether you want to focus on skills and speed, or go in guns blazing, there are plenty of options to suit your playstyle.<br/><br/>With immersive gameplay, challenging enemies, and a range of customizations to unlock, Frontline Survivors is a must-play for any fan of top-down shooters. <br/><br/>Are you ready to join the fight and emerge as a survivor on the frontlines?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2275220/extras/banner-sniper.gif?t=1705511071"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Capture camps and destroy objectives to conquer the battlefield<br/></li><li> Command allies to help you beat the enemy<br/></li><li> Upgrade your character in various ways<br/></li><li> Multiple characters to choose from with their own skills and gameplay<br/></li><li> Unlock new weapons to obliterate your enemies</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>77th: The Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2619110/77th_The_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The 77th: The Game is a first-person singleplayer puzzle game. To climb the ranks of the community and advance through the semi-linear narrative, you must solve the various diagetic puzzles. Use your creativity and attentiveness to get through the story and unveil all the game has to offer.<h2 class="bb_tag">Achievements</h2>Unlock achievements by solving puzzles in specific ways and managing to perform certain actions. This awards you who have both skill and creativity. Can you unlock them all?<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple Endings</h2>Reach the different endings by completing the game in various ways. Try out different actions in every playthrough, and be creative to reach ends, to see all the outcomes that could be.<h2 class="bb_tag">Underlying Lore</h2>Uncover the deep underlying lore. Pay attention to every detail to explore and understand the vast background of the community.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tedram</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2269680/Tedram/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2269680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Tedram is a simulation and casual game of a random guy that works in various jobs, that is between making pizzas, restock the pizzeria with supplies, collect garbage with a Truck. Between that you need to have the best strategy for the time you spend in each job, for that you have available various vehicles, between a car and, two trucks. At the same time you can deliver pizzas, but remember dont run out of stock, and try to make more money as possible and have fun.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Click The Button</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2577760/Just_Click_The_Button/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FW9p6sm2ByZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577760/extras/discrodforsteam.png?t=1705507143"/></a><br/><strong>Just Click The Button takes the clicker genre and combines it with the arena shooter-reverse bullethell genre.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577760/extras/gif1.gif?t=1705507143"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577760/extras/gif2.gif?t=1705507143"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577760/extras/gif3.gif?t=1705507143"><br/><br/>Just Click The Button is a game about clicking on a button. The more you click the button, the more the game evolves. Level up, acquire new abilitites, choose your playstyle, and build a powerful button!<br/><br/>The game can be played idefenetly, allowing you to aquire (almost) every single ability, which will then cause there to be way too much stuff going at once. Or attemt to beat the game. The game can be beated via 1 of 4 endings. Some builds will make certain endings easier than others, which encourages you to choose specific abilities for whatever ending you will attempt.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577760/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter__3_.gif?t=1705507143"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577760/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter__2_.gif?t=1705507143"><br/><br/>Also check out Treasure Chest Clicker!<br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422090/Treasure_Chest_Clicker/?curator_clanid=43674917" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422090/Treasure_Chest_Clicker/?curator_clanid=43674917</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autumn Spirit</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2462830/Autumn_Spirit/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2462830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2462830/extras/title_synopsis.png?t=1705506499"><br/><br/>The world is slowly crumbling and you are falling apart with it. In an attempt to find a semblance of peace and to rethink your future you go into exile in a remote corner to enjoy the calm of nature. But you are not alone on these mountains, another soul in pain is on your land, a ghost grounded on earth by regrets. Deciding to free him of his curse, you might find peace yourself in the process.<br/><br/>Autumn spirit is a melancholic story about love and the modern anxiety of feeling powerless in this chaotic world. Featuring a dog. A very good boy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2462830/extras/title_characters.png?t=1705506499"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2462830/extras/clarisse_bio.png?t=1705506499"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2462830/extras/Nathan_bio.png?t=1705506499"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2462830/extras/title_features.png?t=1705506499"><br/><br/>- Star-crossed lovers, lonely together and more cute relationship tropes to chill on a rainy day.<br/><br/>-  A beautiful modern and melancholic love story tinted by humor. <br/><br/>- Plenty of  personality and bickering choices! <br/><br/>- Around 30,000 words (approximately 2h per playthrough)<br/><br/>- Burtonesque art style and soft atmospheric music <br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><i>Autumn spirit was made in one month for Spooktober 2022</i> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distant Sun</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2276140/Distant_Sun/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2276140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Distant Sun is a singleplayer, story-rich, sci-fi game based on character dialogue, puzzle solving, the choices you make and the impact of its results. <br/><br/>Set in the late 2100s, there's not much space in space. Under the backdrop of rising tension between the nations of Earth, Pioneer Research has embarked on the noble task of figuring out how to expand humanity throughout the cosmos but something odd happened there.<br/><br/>What happened in Pioneer Station? Puzzle together and save the lives of those that remain and uncover a conspiracy on a solar scale. Sift through corporate emails, hack administration rights, and talk with research personnel to unravel the mysteries, but do mind that the saying "ignorance is bliss" applies.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features of the game</h2><br/>- Choose your story<br/>The decisions you make advance the story in unique ways. Whether through dialogue with other characters, avoiding confrontation, or outsmarting your adversaries, this will effect the ending of the game.<br/><br/>- Dialogue tree<br/>The dialogue tree guides player conversations and is an essential part of the story. Talk with NPCs and discover more about what happened in Pioneer Station and the conspiracies that lies beneath.<br/><br/>- Companions<br/>You do not have to go in alone. Your crewmates Wonglei and Hailey will be there to back you up with firepower and advice.<br/><br/>- Character creator<br/>Customize your character's appearance with the game's in depth character editor.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitty Knight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2751370/Bitty_Knight/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2751370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bitty Knight is a fast-paced, challenging 2D top-down mini-roguelike with random levels and 30+ powerups. No two plays are ever the same and it is completely free-to-play. The game centers on a tiny knight stuck in a small dungeon and you have to reach the final boss to escape.<br/><br/>Collect upgrades to survive as you make your way to the final level, there are no saves and if your character dies you will have to restart. Collect keys, unlock chests, find gems, kill enemies and shop to upgrade or smash power-up blocks to find loot and your way to the end.<br/><br/>Be warned, some loot has negative effects and collecting loot blindly can have consequences that will make the game much harder.<br/><br/><strong>Note:</strong> <i>if you have issues, find a bug or have something to say then please post in the Community Hub for assistance</i> <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Completely free-to-play <br/></li><li>Random dungeons &amp; loot - no game is ever the same<br/></li><li>2D Top-down retro pixel graphics<br/></li><li>30+ Power-ups to collect with stacking<br/></li><li>Permadeath - no character upgrades or saves<br/></li><li>Hardcore mode if you prefer a real challenge<br/></li><li>Low system requirements - should run on most PCs</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2751370/extras/BittyKnight.jpg?t=1705505857"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renovation Plan</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2638900/Renovation_Plan/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Come and immerse yourself in this relaxing and leisurely home decoration game!The lovely cartoon art style and soothing background music will bring you a relaxed and pleasant game experience. <br>
<br>
Dear decorator, a task full of challenges and fun awaits you.According to the design drawing, put various furniture in the proper place, showing your aesthetics and skills.Each room has different usage scenarios, from bedroom to living room, from kitchen to bathroom, you need to choose the appropriate furniture and decoration style according to different scenarios.Not only that, there are also gorgeous large apartments waiting for you to challenge.<br>
<br>
Come and try it, let's find the fun of decoration in this game together!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VRidge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2677750/VRidge/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							VRidge connects your mobile device to your PC, transforming it into a powerful SteamVR-compatible virtual reality headset. It will then stream SteamVR apps to your mobile device as a high-performance video with full head and controller tracking. All you need is a mobile or cardboard VR viewer to enjoy the experience!<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677750/extras/connect-bg.png?t=1705523662"><h2 class="bb_tag">Getting started</h2><ol><li>Install RiftCat client application on your computer via Steam.<br/></li><li>Install VRidge on your mobile device and place it inside your mobile VR viewer.<br/></li><li>Launch both apps.<br/></li><li>Follow the built-in instructions in the RiftCat application to connect them via WiFi.<br/></li><li>Enjoy!</li></ol><h2 class="bb_tag">Test your setup first</h2>Try out your <strong>VRidge hardware setup</strong> with the <strong>Demo version</strong> to ensure everything works correctly before making a purchase.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677750/extras/lab_cat.png?t=1705523662"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little Elf Tanks</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2330780/Little_Elf_Tanks/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330780/extras/title_crop.gif?t=1705558397"><br/><br/>Embark on an exciting journey in this thrilling bug blasting adventure! Choose one of four playable characters and join the battle to free your fellow elves from the grasp of a wicked spider army. Each playable character comes with their own set of unique abilities and strengths, giving you the freedom to tackle obstacles in your own way. But beware, your foes won't make your mission easy. In addition to the hoards of gross creepy crawlies, several big boss fights lie in wait to test your skills!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fast paced overhead shooting gameplay.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 60 enemy encounters spanning 5 levels.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>4 playable characters.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Three difficulty settings. Easy, Normal, and Hard.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Several challenging boss battles.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Unlockable boss rush mode.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Charming pixel art and cartoon graphics.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>An amazing soundtrack.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The bugs bleed green goo and it's super gross.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Case Should Remain Unsolved</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2676840/No_Case_Should_Remain_Unsolved/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i>"I remember how surprised I was when I first saw this case. Everyone involved was lying, for one reason or another."</i></strong><br/><br/><strong>#No_Case_Should_Remain_Unsolved</strong> is a detective game where players uncover and piece together memory fragments to solve a long-forgotten case. Follow former police detective Jeon Gyeong as she acquires clues and testimony relating to the case of a missing girl.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676840/extras/MainPic.gif?t=1705503627"><h2 class="bb_tag">#No_Case_Should_Remain_Unsolved</h2>February 5, 2012. A little girl named Seowon is reported missing from a playground. Police launch an investigation and question witnesses and suspects, but Seowon's case is never solved.<br/>Twelve years after Senior Inspector Jeon Gyeong's retirement, she is visited by a young police officer: a woman who pleads with her to reexamine Seowon's case.<br/>But with each uncovered memory, only one thing becomes clear: everyone in Seowon's vicinity was lying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676840/extras/Ending_2.gif?t=1705503627"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Experience an imaginative reasoning system where players connect memories like pieces of a jigsaw puzzle.<br/></li><li>Uncover passcodes, keys, 54 conversations, and two hidden truths.<br/></li><li>Over the course of a 2-3 hour playthrough, players will learn why Seowon's disappearance is the only case Jeon Gyeong has left unsolved.<br/></li><li>Also featuring an original soundtrack by Seongyi Yi, composer of Legal Dungeon and The Wake!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yuuna and the Haunted Hot Springs The Thrilling Steamy Maze Kiwami</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2436340/Yuuna_and_the_Haunted_Hot_Springs_The_Thrilling_Steamy_Maze_Kiwami/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Want to dive into a bath? Or into a dungeon?</strong><br/><strong>"Yuuna and the Haunted Hot Springs" is now an RPG that's pushing all sorts of boundaries!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/extras/dungeon.gif?t=1705503627"><br/><br/>Yuuna and the Haunted Hot Springs makes its video game debut as a genuine roguelike RPG!<br/>In order to save Kogarashi, search through expansive dungeons that change layout every time you enter!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/extras/onsen2.gif?t=1705503627"><br/>Jump in the hot spring to power up! Watch out for damage to your clothes!<br/>A new story of hauntings, hot springs, and high adventure awaits you!<h2 class="bb_tag">Adventure, apparitions, and a hot spring... A brand-new story that's quite literally bursting at the seams!</h2><br/>Featuring a story unique to the game with special event images that can't be seen anywhere else<br/>and character interactions fully voiced by the star-studded cast of the animated series!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/extras/adv_en.png?t=1705503627"><br/><br/>One weekend-<br/>After hearing a strange noise coming from the Yuragi Inn's storage, Kogarashi and the rest of the Inn's residents decide to do a bit of spring cleaning,<br/>but they accidentally knock over a chest they find inside.<br/>From inside the miniature garden they find within, a girl's voice can be heard.<br/>"Kogarashi...! You've come back!"<br/>At that moment, a powerful gust plucks Kogarashi off his feet, and sucks him into the miniature garden!<br/>Will the others be able to rescue Kogarashi?!<h2 class="bb_tag">Anything could happen! Push through dungeons that'll push you to the limit!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/extras/dungeon2_jp.png?t=1705503627"><br/>Conquer the dungeons' challenges!<br/>Jump into battle with Yuuna, Sagiri, Yaya, and even more playable characters!<br/>Bring your favorite characters and rescue Kogarashi!<h2 class="bb_tag">You can push the limits of bathing too... Refresh yourself and get powered up in the Resonant Spring!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/extras/furo2_en.png?t=1705503627"><br/>A relaxing soak in the hot spring might relieve the exhaustion of your adventure, but could evil spirits be drawn in too?!<br/>Team up with Koyuzu to clear out both the steam and the spirits!<br/>As you do, you might even notice some characters have changed!<h2 class="bb_tag">From adorable to...alluring?! Change freely between over 15 kinds of costumes!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/extras/costume2.png?t=1705503627"><br/>More than 15 kinds of both familiar and brand-new outfits appear!<br/>Dress Yuuna and friends up in your favorite costumes!<br/>Of course, both the in-game sprites and the character illustrations will change to match!<br/>Each costume has different abilities, so make use of them when delving into dungeons!<h2 class="bb_tag">"It's too difficult... I can't beat this..." No worries! The storage is stuffed fit to burst with helpful items!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436340/extras/kura_en.png?t=1705503627"><br/>For any players who don't relish challenging dungeons,<br/>you can make use of handy support items right from the start!<br/>Naturally that includes costumes too, so get dolled up in your preferred outfits and conquer the dungeons!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's Up There?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2756610/Whats_Up_There/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2756610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>What's Up There?</strong> is a unique meditative platformer game. Your only goal is to climb the ladder as far as you can. Jump over the steps again and again to reach the top eventually. But one mistake and you can fall to the very bottom losing all your progress. But use a simple blink system if you smart or fast enought to undo a fatal mistake.<h2 class="bb_tag">GAMEPLAY</h2>Calm and cozy journey at the beginning but with insane risks as you become closer to the top<h2 class="bb_tag">GRAPHICS</h2>Nice neon style graphics with minimalistic environment so nothing distracts you from your goal<h2 class="bb_tag">THE JOURNEY</h2>Climb thousands of steps to unravel the mystery of what is happening. Find out the reasons for everything that is happening here<h2 class="bb_tag">SECRETS AND ENDINGS</h2>Reach the top and find a true game end. Or stuck here forever halfway to the goal						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nephenthesys</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2660400/Nephenthesys/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2660400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Blast off on a treacherous mission to recover an unidentified energy source amidst an alien onslaught!</h2><br/><br/>Nephenthesys is a vertical scrolling shoot’em up presented in widescreen top-down 3D style. Blast through a huge variety of enemy ships, collect power-ups for wider shot spreads and special bombs, then face off against screen-filling bosses. This mission will take you through caverns, waterways, cityscapes and more. Do you have the skills to see it through?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2660400/extras/Nephenthesys_gif_01.gif?t=1705494750"><br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Experience old-school shoot’em up action inspired by arcade genre classics!<br/></li><li>Choose from a variety of ships with unique stats and shot types.<br/></li><li>Face off against enemy swarms and collect power-ups!<br/></li><li>Navigate caverns, waterways, cityscapes and other unique environments.<br/></li><li>Take on screen-filling bosses at the end of each stage.<br/></li><li>Enjoy a light story conveyed through comm dialogue!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2660400/extras/Nephenthesys_gif_02.gif?t=1705494750"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2660400/extras/Nephenthesys_gif_05.gif?t=1705494750"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twizzle Puzzle: Reptiles</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2757530/Twizzle_Puzzle_Reptiles/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Twizzle Puzzle: Reptiles - is the perfect puzzle game for a fun and rewarding pastime.<br/>Your goal is to assemble a picture of cool reptiles that has been cut into an equal number of pieces.<br/>Rotate the pieces to create the full picture, but think logically about the connections and solve the puzzle. <br/>There are 50 levels to complete, and the challenge becomes increasingly difficult as you progress.<br/>Enjoy a relaxing time connecting the pieces to create a beautiful picture of reptiles<br/><br/>In Twizzle Puzzle: Reptiles:<br/><br/>•50 levels<br/>•Beautiful art<br/>•Simple controls (mouse)<br/>•Achievements<br/>•Relaxing music<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757530/extras/3.png?t=1705494741"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757530/extras/1.png?t=1705494741"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757530/extras/2.png?t=1705494741"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757530/extras/4.png?t=1705494741"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trupki</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422310/Trupki/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Most simple puzzle game ever possible.<br/>Sliding tiles by rows or columns so that the final shape, made of tile elements, appears!<br/>Game guides you step by step from super simple one turn easy levels through more comprehensive up to almost insane difficulty.<br/>Variability of the game is modified by logical obstacles which may limit or completely distort basic workings of tile movement.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422310/extras/DividersV301.png?t=1705508864"><br/><br/>Many players claim that out of the box approach for every level is a must and so Trupki is great tool for developing this ability!<br/>Game plays with total minimalism but insist on aesthetic even in case of level design. However game is not short on levels.<br/>Offers over 300 levels in all difficulties and expected tens of hours of struggle and a-ha moments.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422310/extras/DividersV302.png?t=1705508864"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creature Summon: Showdown Moment</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2751800/Creature_Summon_Showdown_Moment/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2751800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A creative first-person card game that mimics VR perspective and operation. Combining science fiction and magic, it features a non-traditional card game mode and a 3D spatial UI. Players can throw cards to any position (with physics system) by using the mouse quickly.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2>· Unique gameplay mechanism: The game mimics the way VR throws objects. In this game, players can drag and throw cards with the mouse. Cards use physical systems, and where they are thrown depends entirely on player operations. The game also comes with 10 dance actions, and players can dance and throw cards for high immersion.<br/><br/>· Gameplay: You can only summon up to 5 creatures on the field at the same time. Once your creatures reach 5, throwing cards again will not summon more creatures. You need to wait for the number of monsters to drop below 5 before picking up cards and throwing them again. After the creature is summoned, it will prioritize attacking or occupying flags against the creatures it restrains. (Ranged creatures will not actively occupy flags, only melee creatures will occupy flags).<br/><br/>· Creature factions: There are currently 5 factions, which will increase to 9 in the future. Each faction has more than 10 creatures, and the total number of creatures will exceed 100.<br/><br/>· Realistic models: Further enhance immersion.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer Online</h2>Play with friends in the Steam lobby and enjoy multiplayer mode, it's even more fun and free!<br/><br/>· PS:<br/>The gameplay of this game may be unique. Players who play for the first time should take a look at the text description in "Tutorial" to understand the game rules and mechanism before playing. Due to budget issues, no professional translation experts were hired. Except for Chinese, all localized languages of this game are translated by translation software. If there are any translations that are difficult to understand, please send me an email for correction.<br/>For more fun, please experience it in the game personally. Many fun cannot be expressed in words. :P<h2 class="bb_tag">Thanks</h2>I hope everyone likes the creative gameplay of this game.<h2 class="bb_tag">Finally, please forgive me</h2>This game is developed by only one person, all the assets are purchased from the store, and the style is not consistent. If you have any gameplay suggestions, please email me. I might not be able to handle the art aspects, as I have no knowledge in that area. Apologies for the inconvenience...						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominions 6 - Rise of the Pantokrator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2511500/Dominions_6__Rise_of_the_Pantokrator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2511500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are a God! You are master and ruler of a loyal nation. You have unimaginable powers at your disposal. You have claimed this world as yours. But there are others who stand in your way. You must defeat and destroy these pretenders. Only then can you ascend to godhood and become the new Pantokrator.<br>
<br>
Dominions 6 is a turn based 4x strategy game suitable for both play vs AI, player vs player.  Team play vs AI or players also works great as everyone can do their turns at once.  The game has a huge variety of units, spells, magic items and different nations to play.<br>
<br>
In Dominions you take control of a powerful being that rules a nation and aspires to godhood. The type of Pretender Gods can vary from magically powerful arch mages to huge titans or large monuments. The pretender gods have different strengths dependent on what kind of god you choose and what nation you play.<br>
<br>
When you start the game you decide what kind of god you are and how your Dominion affects your lands, followers and sacred soldiers. It is an expression of your divine might and the faith of your followers. If your dominion dies, so do you. Your dominion also inspires your sacred warriors and gives them powers derived from your dominion.<br/>
<br/>
In order to win and become the one true god you have to defeat your enemies one of three different ways: conquer their lands, extinguish their dominion or claim the Thrones of Ascension.<br/>
<br/>
Dominions is set in a fantasy world that draws inspiration from historical nations, cultures and myths. You will not encounter the elves of conventional fantasy in this game. Instead you might lead a nation of vanir from old norse myth. Aztecs, romans, israelites, greeks, kievian rus and lovecraftian horrors are just a few of the inspirational sources of the game.<br/>
<br/>
The first Dominions game was released in 2002 and was well received by strategy gamers. Since then Dominions has been much refined and Dominions series is still actively played making it one of the longest running 4x turn based strategy games.<br/>
<br/>
----------<br/>
<br/>
Dominions 6 is scaled up compared to Dominions 5 and armies are larger. We wanted to tweak the balance between conventional armies and magic. To accomplish this a couple of changes are introduced. Incomes and resources are increased, while mages are more expensive. Battlefield-wide spells are more difficult to cast and there are instead more mid-tier spells. There are some other changes with the same aim.<br/>
<br/>
The second and probably most influential change is the addition of a new magic path. No longer are illusions the domain of Air magic. Instead illusions, phantasms, dreams and the stuff of forgotten legends are manipulated with the path of Glamour. This has resulted in many new spells, items and sites being added to the game. <br/>
<br/>
A third massive change is the separation of mounts and riders. Riders and mounts now have separate stats and can be targeted individually. This change probably has less impact on gameplay than the previous one, but will still have an impact on cavalry and nations using mounted units.<br/>
<br/>
Dominions 6 features a number of new nations as well. The addition of the Glamour path has also affected several of the old nations. <br/>
<br/>
There are also a number of changes intended to ease gameplay.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lab and Dungeons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658960/The_Lab_and_Dungeons/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Summary</h2>The Lab and Dungeons is a blend of roguelike action and shooter RPG, set on an island ruled by robots during a human-robot war. You play as a small robot that has mysteriously powered up recently. Your mission is to mine ores, forge weapons, and confront aggressive robots in the unpredictable, procedurally generated dungeons. Collect items to invent more unique weapons and boost your abilities. From light skirmishes to intense bullet storms with physics enabled, play solo or online co-op with friends, are you ready to take on the challenge and unravel the island’s secret?<h2 class="bb_tag">“Never the same dungeon twice”</h2>Explore 6 major procedural dungeons and extra boss rooms! New explorations intensify challenges in old dungeons.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658960/extras/SixDungeons560220rev2.gif?t=1705485652"><h2 class="bb_tag">Weapons</h2>Defeat enemies your way: use ranged, melee, deployable weapons, or even a tiny black hole!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658960/extras/Weapons450140.gif?t=1705485652"><h2 class="bb_tag">Physics</h2>Newton’s laws apply! Take advantage of physics reactions!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658960/extras/Physics200160.gif?t=1705485652"><h2 class="bb_tag">Collection Room</h2>Display your favorite items and make it your own style!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658960/extras/CollectionRoomGif.gif?t=1705485652"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Modes</h2>Play solo or online / LAN co-op!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658960/extras/Coop.gif?t=1705485652"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrades</h2>Upgrade your abilities and unlock weapons to become stronger!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658960/extras/UI430240.gif?t=1705485652"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>6 major dungeons filled with countless varieties of procedurally generated floors.<br/></li><li>40+ unique enemies that challenge your exploration.<br/></li><li>Exciting physics-enabled combat where enemies can take ores and items, and even damage each other.<br/></li><li>Single player mode, Steam Online or LAN co-op for up to 4 players.<br/></li><li>3 categories of 60+ weapons: ranged, melee, and deployable.<br/></li><li>130+ levels across 9 specs to upgrade.<br/></li><li>3 difficulty levels.<br/></li><li>5 save slots with Steam Cloud supported.<br/></li><li>Steam achievements.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat Warrior</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2640520/Cat_Warrior/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2640520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Cat Warroir</strong> is an action-platformer of retro and cute style about a cat knight on his way to recapture his stolen treasure.<br/>Deep into the exciting and dangerous fantasy world,defeat the challenging big boss with your slash, dash, jump, walljump and other skills to find the treasure back!<h2 class="bb_tag">Feature</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Addictive gameplay</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>4 unique challenge worldsand 30 handmade levels.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Beautiful pixel-art graphics;</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A cute cat</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
