<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Vampire Survivors: Emergency Meeting</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2690330/Vampire_Survivors_Emergency_Meeting/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							The Survivors are desperate to hunt vampires, but are running out of places to look. Only one option remains: Be the bullet hell... in space! <br/><br/>Gather your most trusted Crewmates, prepare to eject the Impostors, and try to survive while mowing down thousands of extra-terrestrial foes in this expansion for Vampire Survivors. Turn classic Among Us tasks into outrageous weapons, upgrading your abilities after every roguelite run to overcome impossible odds with ease. Be alert to subterfuge as you explore the vast weirdness of the Polus Replica and keep your wits about you, as suspicious eyes are always watching 👀.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features <strong>20-in-game only</strong> unlocks, no Steam achievements. For more info please see the FAQs here:</h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fponcle.games%2Femergency-meeting.html" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://poncle.games/emergency-meeting.html</a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/extras/1_Characters_ENG.png?t=1702898514"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/extras/Amongus_Chars_big.gif?t=1702898514"><br/>A cast of courageous Crewmates assembled to take on the tumultuous tasks, including: <br/><br/>Crewmate Dino - Starry-eyed, optimistic, and unfortunately extremely tasty. Dino is a jack-of-all-trades who boosts stats whenever a task is completed (i.e. when you level up a weapon). <br/><br/>Engineer Gino - Few Crewmates come as close to truly competent task-work as Gino, who offers a selection of passive weapons from their toolbox every few levels. <br/><br/>Ghost Lino - Good Crewmates don't let a silly thing like death get in the way of their tasks. Lino can float through walls at will and can't be hurt, but can't deal damage either... what could be the goal of such suspicious game design?! <br/><br/>Shapeshifter Nino - Look at this bean! They can do all kinds of... wait, where did they go? And where did this snowman come from? Oh well, I'm sure you'll figure it out. <br/><br/>Guardian Pina - Everyone needs an angel on their shoulder. Pina isn't just there for moral support, though - they boost the defences of all nearby allies, and they love taking out the garbage. <br/><br/>Impostor Rina - A fellow Crewmate that is in no way some kind of duplicitous, well-disguised killer. One hundred percent all-natural-bean, right here. Nothing to see or think about. <br/><br/>Scientist Mina - Mina's scientific skill is matched only by their intense clumsiness. Thankfully, dropping potentially hazardous chemicals has a major upside when you're besieged by extra-terrestrial monsters. <br/><br/>Horse - It's a horse. Neigh, etc. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/extras/1_Weapons_ENG.png?t=1702898514"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/extras/WeaponIcons.png?t=1702898514"><br/>Transform your tasks into powerful weapons to defend yourself from Impostors, Shapeshifters, and all manner of extra-terrestrial weirdos. Blast away baddies with the supermassive sound waves of your Report! weapon, slice angry aliens in half with Lucky Swipe, and drop duplicitous foes to their doom with Just Vent. Lonely Survivors should seek out Mini Crewmates to empower their Task-based weaponry (or just for general companionship). <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/extras/1_Stage_ENG.png?t=1702898514"><br/>Polus Replica - an eerily accurate replica of the scientific base on Polus. This planet is packed with bizarre biomes ripe for exploration by Survivors and Crewmates, with tasks and treasure chests galore. Unfortunately, its also accidentally being invaded by your average space dwellers, like aliens, robots, and ducks. Expect the unexpected and do NOT trust the bins. Never trust the bins. Or the chicken nuggets. In fact, it's a good idea to remain alert at all times and not trust anything. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/extras/StageMap.png?t=1702898514"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/extras/1_Tracks_ENG.png?t=1702898514"><br/>♫ Emergency Meeting<br/>♫ Hide and Survive<br/>♫ No Ducks Among Us<br/>♫ No Aliens Among Us<br/>♫ No Ghosts Among Us<br/>♫ No Vampires Among Us						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1702928763"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1702928763"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1702928763"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1702928763"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1702928763"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1702928763"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1702928763"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trinity Fusion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1911360/Trinity_Fusion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take control of your parallel selves on a mission to save the dying multiverse. Explore dark, sci-fi worlds and engage in fast-paced, smooth and precise combat.<h2 class="bb_tag">A rogue-lite journey through the multiverse</h2>The various branches of the multiverse are always changing. Fight through a combination of procedurally-generated levels as well as hand-crafted challenges and arenas that will put your skills to the test. Levels with 3D graphics are seamlessly constructed out of hundreds of custom-made rooms.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/extras/Ranger_Factory.gif?t=1702915094"><h2 class="bb_tag">High-intensity combat</h2>With weapons and attack systems that leverage our previous experience working on fighting games. You’ll slide, dash and dodge between enemy attacks and strike back with an arsenal of satisfying special weapons and abilities.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/extras/Ranger_City_Walls_GIF_Cleanup.gif?t=1702915094"><h2 class="bb_tag">Three characters, three universes to explore</h2>Each of your parallel selves has their own world with multiple biomes to explore, as well as their own sets of unique abilities and weapons. Travel through a universe of desolate wastes and caverns roamed by mutant creatures, escape the endless forges and labs of a world ruled by machines, and survive the dangerous sky cities of a post-human society.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/extras/Player_Running_Cleanup.gif?t=1702915094"><h2 class="bb_tag">Constant Progression</h2>Unlock permanent upgrades in the Hub and discover new starting points for your run as you reclaim major locations in each universe. Finding yourself getting stuck in one area? Start your next run in a different one! No matter where you die, or which starting point you pick, you're making progress somewhere.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1911360/Trinity_Fusion/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1911360/Trinity_Fusion/</a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Cutter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1924430/Cookie_Cutter/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Void. The Matter. The Megastructure. A dystopian world with an egomaniac leader determined to unveil the secrets of the universe. INFONET promised a utopia built on the backs of tireless androids called Denzels. It was a lie. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/Cherry.gif?t=1702760603"><br/><br/>200 years later the planet is decaying and the mysterious Red Seed has been stolen. Raz, a renegade mechanic, searches a hidden lab and discovers the Denzel Cherry, butchered and left for dead, clinging to life by sheer will alone. Her creator—and the love of her life, Doctor Shinji Fallon—has been taken by a demented sicko and Cherry intends to make him—and anybody or anything who gets in her way—pay.<br/><br/>Fueled by love and powered by rage, join Cherry on a blood-soaked quest for revenge as she explores the massive Megastructure and eviscerates the armies of INFONET in an unforgettable over-the-top 2D platformer that breaks tropes and bones.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Subversive_Metroidvania.png?t=1702760603"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Subversive_Metroidvania.gif?t=1702760603"><br/>Cookie Cutter is unabashedly irreverent, violent, and risqué. Become Cherry, a badass android on a rage-filled and love-driven quest. To save her beloved creator she’ll explore and fight her way through a unique illustrated sci-fi dystopian world as she chainsaw-murders anybody who stands in her way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Hand-drawn_Action.png?t=1702760603"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Hand-Drawn_Action.gif?t=1702760603"><br/>Every frame of this immersive experience is drawn by hand with copious amounts of love. That means epic, fall-out-of-your-chair visuals. Grotesque bugs and menacing robots. Gargantuan bosses. Ridiculous weapons, special moves, and brutal gory finishers. All of it brought to life with benchmark 2D animation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Epic_Combat_Abilities.png?t=1702760603"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC__Epic_Combat_Abilities.gif?t=1702760603"><br/>Whether you’re ripping the wings off overgrown mosquitos, impaling mini-bosses, crushing robots on Cherry’s motorcycle, or kick-punch-uppercut-stomping waves of foes with complex combos, you won’t find a better fighting experience with responsiveness and all the flair you could ask for in a Metroidvania.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Rage-Filled_Spectacle.png?t=1702760603"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Rage-Filled_Spectacle.gif?t=1702760603"><br/>Far future dystopia? Check. An android companion turned rage-filled killer? Check. Over-the-top characters and enemies? Check. Buckets of blood? Of course. Experience our bizarre tale, inspired by Japanese manga and Quentin Tarantino films, through 10 huge zones, each weirder than the next.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1702674942"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WITCH ON THE HOLY NIGHT</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2052410/WITCH_ON_THE_HOLY_NIGHT/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2052410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2052410/extras/WITCH_ON_THE_HOLY_NIGHT_About_this_game.gif?t=1702631006"><br/><strong>Product Description</strong><br/>TYPE-MOON, known for the wildly popular mobile game "Fate/Grand Order" and the epic visual novel "Tsukihime," is releasing a remaster of the 2012 hit "Witch on the Holy Night. Experience a coming of age story set in the vibrant, bustling 1980s, which follows an innocent young man and two young "witches." Updates added since the original release include long-awaited fully voiced characters as well as visuals remastered in full HD, bringing the experience to life with unparalleled quality and fidelity. Masterful manipulation of visual elements imbues combat scenes with nail-biting tension, but also breathes life into the characters' everyday activities. Animated graphical elements bring an entirely new level of depth to the reading experience as well!<br/><br/><strong>STORY</strong><br/>In the mansion on the hill, there lived two witches...<br/><br/>It is the late 1980s—the twilight of an era of beauty and vigor.<br/>A boy moves to the city, barely missing two witches living in modern times.<br/><br/>The boy leads a completely ordinary life.<br/>She carries herself with gallant pride.<br/>The girl lives a sleepy, hidden life.<br/><br/>Each walks a starlit path.<br/>One would never expect their paths to cross.<br/>The story of how these three disparate people came together is soon to be told.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons of Sundaria</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/587520/Dungeons_of_Sundaria/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/587520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">The Dungeons:</h2> <br/>* 8 Huge Dungeons filled with hundreds of fiendish monsters and dozens of diabolical bosses.<br/>* Three Levels of Difficulty: Normal, Hard, and Nightmare.  <br/>* Online single player or co-op up to 4-players.<br/>* Local Split-screen multiplayer co-op up to 4-players (only requires a single game copy).<h2 class="bb_tag">Make your Hero:</h2> <br/>* 7 Races: Human, Dwarf, Elf, Halfling, Orc, Goblin and Drog'al (lizard).<br/>* 5 Classes: Champion, Ranger, Cleric, Wizard, and Rogue. <br/>* Customize the appearance of your Hero.<h2 class="bb_tag">Become a Legend:</h2> <br/>* Collect a huge variety of Weapons, Armor, and Accessories to customize your Hero and grow in power.<br/>* Craft powerful equipment and become a force of reckoning.  Multiple tiers of armor and weapons.<br/>* Embrace the Heroism system, allowing you to continually increase the power of your Hero.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1702562956"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1702562956"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1702000678"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1702000678"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood West</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_steam_text_header.png?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>Weird West legends meet eldritch horror in <strong>BLOOD WEST</strong>, an immersive stealth FPS. Become the Undead Gunslinger, doomed to roam the barren lands until he finds the means to purge their curse and free his soul. No, this isn’t your typical Wild West desperado redemption arc. This is a damnation arc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_episodes_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The Canyons, the Swamp, and the Mountains. Each swarming with abominable monsters and unholy demons, these are open-ended worlds for you to explore freely at your own pace. It will take the player over 20 hours on average to complete all three scenarios, and over 35 if they want to see everything the barren lands have to offer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_stealth_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/><strong>Blood West</strong> is a stealth FPS inspired by the genre classics such as the Thief series (whose fans will be happy to hear the voice of Stephen Russell, the actor voicing the master-thief Garrett, returning here as the protagonist), S.T.A.L.K.E.R. games, or - from the contemporary catalog - Hunt: Showdown. The gameplay rewards the careful approach: scouting the area, stalking your enemies, and striking from the shadows. Can you figure out a way to clear a fort full of ghouls and monsters without raising an alarm?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_horror_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The Barren Lands present the player with a nightmarish, twisted vision of the Wild West legends. The curse that has befallen the realm has corrupted every living thing, defiled the land itself, while summoning restless spirits and dark entities. In this mixture of gunslinger pulp and Lovecraftian horror, dark occult magick presents just as much of a threat as sudden lead poisoning.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_characters_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>In <strong>Blood West</strong> you will meet many colorful, yet strangely twisted, fully-voiced NPCs. Just as much prisoners of the Barren Lands as you are, they will sometimes share their unusual stories and send you on various missions. Play nice and they might reward you or become your allies. Cross them and risk their wrath.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_secrets_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The game won’t hold your hand. You’ll have to explore the land for yourself (buying a map from a vendor might prove useful!), and figure out your own way to approach quests. As you poke around the three expansive maps, keep an eye out for hidden places and secret stashes. There’s gold in the mountains! Fair warning - it’s probably cursed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_brutal_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>If sneaking around isn’t exactly your thing, or you feel that you have a power advantage over your enemies, you can always take the head-on approach and meet your enemies guns blazing. <strong>Blood West</strong> comes from the creators of the fan-favorite boomer shooter <strong>POSTAL: Brain Damaged</strong>, so much gratuitous fantasy violence and pixelated blood splatter is to be expected!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_inventory_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>One man’s hell might be another hoarder’s paradise! From simple one-use items like bandages, through medical tinctures, explosives and incendiaries, straight to arcane artifacts that - once slotted - can change the way you play the game, the Barren Lands are just filled with STUFF. There are tons of useful items to discover, and there’s a special player’s stash crate for all those super-rare potions that you’ll hoard and never use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_weapons_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>A gunslinger without a gun would be just a regular slinger. Where’s the fun in that? <strong>Blood West</strong> makes sure you’ll have plenty of weapons to choose from. Revolvers, rifles, shotguns, carabines - a great variety of firearms, from standard army-issue to those infused with powerful magic, or straight-up possessed. And if you prefer not to cause a ruckus, there’s a wide selection of hand-to-hand combat weapons and archery weapons to pick your favorites from.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_skills_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The RPG-like perk-based progression system in <strong>Blood West</strong> will allow you to highly customize the gameplay experience to your liking. Become a stealthy hunter, a revolver-fanning gunman or a relentless berserker. You will gain experience and progress through the skill tree, while discovering new artifacts in each of the scenarios that will bestow on you additional abilities. Combining skills and load-out creates more possible playstyles than you’d normally be able to explore in one playthrough.<h2 class="bb_tag">Are you ready to take back the frontier from the dark forces of demonic corruption and earn the right to move on to a better world? The Barren Lands call you, Gunslinger!</h2><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1702394215"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1702394215"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1702394215"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1702620270"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1702620270"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinball M</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2337640/Pinball_M/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-1.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-2.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free<br/>- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage<br/>- Thrilling competition<br/>- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation<h2 class="bb_tag">Sink your teeth into these tables as purchasable DLC: </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">- Chucky's Killer Pinball:</h2> Step into a twisted realm where the innocent becomes sinister, and the playful turns menacing. Navigate through an eerie playfield where Chucky lurks in the shadows, ready to pounce.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Dead by Daylight™️ Pinball:</h2> Become the hunter or even the hunted in a thrilling fusion of classic pinball and the excitement of one of the most popular horror games ever created.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Duke Nukem's Big Shot Pinball:</h2> Enjoy the biggest, grooviest, most BADASS pinball table ever made packed with guns and babes. Push start and play with balls of steel!<h2 class="bb_tag">- The Thing Pinball: </h2>Use your pinball skills and battle against the shape-shifting alien through the arctic chill of U.S. Outpost #31. Can you trust anyone, even yourself?<br/>- Even more coming...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-4.png?t=1701703297"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astral Ascent</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1280930/Astral_Ascent/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Astral Ascent is a 2D platformer rogue-lite game set in a modern fantasy world. As one of 4 Heroes with very different personalities, you must escape from <i>the Garden</i>, an astral prison guarded by 12 powerful and vicious bosses, the Zodiacs.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CREATE YOUR OWN PLAYSTYLE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Gif_playstyle.gif?t=1702570155"><br/>Unlock dozens of unique spells for your 4 distinct characters. Optimize your own build or try out new ones to take down 12 powerful bosses. Get stronger with time to match up with your foes. Each run will test your skills and your reactivity.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TWELVE ALMIGHTY BOSSES TO FACE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Zodiacs.gif?t=1702570155"><br/>The Zodiacs are 12 experienced guardians dispatched over 4 gorgeous worlds. They’ll bring to the battlefield unique attacks, abilities, and patterns, backstories to uncover, and reasons to be fighting you. Get yourself warned!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>4 PLAYABLE CHARACTERS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/4_Character_banniere_steam7.png?t=1702570155"><br/><i>Unique characters. Unique weapons. Unique ways to play.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Ayla:</strong> The sole survivor of her guild of assassins, she uses her twin daggers to eliminate her enemies before they can react. Her speed and proficiency are unmatched.<br/></li><li><strong>Kiran:</strong> This orphan learned life the hard way. He uses his strength to deliver attacks powerful enough to create shockwaves. Brutal.<br/></li><li><strong>Calie:</strong> This talented sculptor wants her freedom back. She will use her magical gemstones to pierce enemy defenses and shred them to bits. She is unforgiving.<br/></li><li><strong>Octave:</strong> Trained by a powerful witch, this young fighter summons ethereal guns to attack his foes. When needed, he can conjure bigger weapons as well. Lethal in all cases.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A STORY THAT OPENS UP, ONE PIECE AT A TIME</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/ZimZim2.png?t=1702570155"><br/>Astral Ascent is a rogue-lite infused with narration. Replayability is part of our story which will be unraveled piece by piece. As you get stronger, you will discover more about the characters, their motivations, and the secrets of the world they’re trapped in.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>LOCAL CO-OP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Coop.gif?t=1702570155"><br/>The weight of destiny is too heavy to carry by yourself? Don’t worry and bring a friend to play in our <strong>two-player co-op</strong> mode. Fight and crush your enemies together in local co-op or online using the <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/remoteplay?snr=1_614_615__1601" rel="" target="_blank"><strong>Steam's Remote Play Together</strong></a> feature.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A VAST, COLORFUL FANTASY WORLD WAITING TO BE EXPLORED</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Panning.gif?t=1702570155"><br/>Dash across gigantic landscapes. Explore original and hand-crafted areas. Discover the world created by our artists, with a gorgeous art and frame-by-frame animation.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1702747783"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons 4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1643310/Dungeons_4/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Once upon a time in a realm far, far away, everything was lush and green. The unicorns mingled among the trees and the elves and humans lived peacefully in harmony with their surroundings. Yet somewhere at the edge of a clearing half-hidden among the trees, obscured by a rising veil of fog in the hazy half-darkness of a weather-beaten hut, a shape huddles over a large and ominously glowing crystal ball. A mumbling voice sings ancient formulae, urging the swirling glowing mists inside the crystal to part and give an insight into the future.<br/><br/>“All is in flux, nothing seems certain. Come, oh vagaries of space and time, separate the veil and show us what is yet to come”, the voice grumbles with the hint of an eye faintly reflecting the glow in front of its hood. The shape’s audience, only barely visible in the dim light, leans in closer and listens intently. “Time ebbs and flows, forming pools and wrinkles… but when the mists part only vague images rise from beyond the veil. Shhhh—don’t come too close, you don’t want to disturb my delicate magical weavings do you?” The shape, still bent over the orb, mutters and shoos the other back a bit more into the shadows. “Ah, now it seems to be clearing a little. I can see… something… several somethings, hints of voices echoing in the haze. A baby, something happening on Hill Doom and the coming together of the Council of Snots – what could all this mean?”<br/><br/>In a flash, the light reflected in the eye turns red and a distant evil laughter echoes through the woods. Stay tuned for the return of the Soothsaying Evil!</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/dungeons-4.gif?t=1701355158"><br/><br/>The Absolute Evil and its trusted *cough* servant, the Dark Elf Thalya, return in <strong>Dungeons 4</strong> after the events of its fabulous predecessor to bring about their triumph over the forces of good once more.<br/><br/><strong>Build a cozy and comfortable Dungeon</strong> to suit your creatures’ needs and rule over them, then send them out into the Overworld to kindly remind the good people living there that the Absolute Evil rules over their lands. <strong>Gather your Evilness</strong> in new and dynamic ways <strong>and unleash it upon</strong> the lush green forests and plains of <strong>the Overworld</strong> to turn them over to the dark side. But make sure that <strong>your Dungeon is well-secured</strong> by traps and defended by your creatures, for those pesky Overworlders won’t just twiddle their thumbs while you <strong>turn their land into the Absolute Evil’s most pleasurable holiday paradise</strong>.<br/><br/>But what is that noise? <i>“Gold, gold, gold and gems, gold and gems and gold!”</i> The ancient song echoes throughout the underworld, accompanied by the clanging steel of hammers and axes. <strong>The Dwarves have arrived</strong> to claim their share of the abundant resources and together with the Elves and Humans of the Overworld, they send out their raiding parties to find the Dungeon’s heart.<br/><br/>Dungeons 4 keeps the spirit of its predecessor, but everything is now <strong>bigger, better, and with even more dynamic Evilness™</strong>.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-1_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Everything is better with Dwarves™:</strong> The Dwarves have arrived to build their underground strongholds and the hardy little fellows (although they don’t like being called that) compete with the Ever-Expanding Evil for space and resources.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-2_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>It makes your Dungeon great again:</strong> Dungeons are up to four times larger than before and there are many more creatures who wait for the All-Commanding Evil’s orders to conquer the Overworld. Now the time has come for massive armies and truly sprawling dungeons!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-3_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Ripe for the taking:</strong> The Overworld is bigger than ever before. Gain Evilness by beating Mini Bosses like the obsessively harmonious Unicorn and use it to transform the Overworld into stunning biomes of pure evil.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-4_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>New and shiny:</strong> An ability-based Perk system for Thalya, the Absolute Evil’s trusted *cough* and most loyal subordinate, grants her impressive new powers. The Absolute Evil can now enjoy taking over the world, governing the creatures and slapping subordinates even more with the customizable Evil Hand.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-5_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Minions, everywhere:</strong> The Horde, the Undead and the Demons wait to do the Absolute Evil’s bidding, with more creatures than ever eagerly following the gesturing Evil’s orders, and Snots will play a much more prominent role this time.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-6_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Many ways to tell the story:</strong> A long campaign, narrated by the beloved English Narrator from previous titles, as well as several skirmish maps all to challenge your rule as the Absolute Evil.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-7_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Change the world:</strong> Spread your Evilness across the Overworld to bring lush and green environments over to the dark side, now shining even more vibrantly and beautifully evil as you spread your evilness across many new biomes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-8_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Work together, slay together:</strong> 2-player co-op multiplayer with both players managing one Dungeon together. All maps from the skirmish mode and the campaign are playable in co-op.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Bridge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1779080/Project_Bridge/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1779080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A mysterious void appeared out of nowhere and is swallowing the world! <br/>Why? Well, our developers don’t know or simply won’t tell us. It is what it is...<br/>Anyway, your mission for now is to get as far away from it as you can!<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Online &amp; local multiplayer co-op for up to 4 players, single player mode included. <br/> </li><li> Over 23 unlockable characters and many different types of levels, incl. forests, caves, deserts.<br/> </li><li> Procedurally generated maps  and non-linear level progression - no level is ever the same!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">GOTTA RUN FAST!</h2>Cooperate with your team: gather resources, craft building materials, construct bridges over obstacles and avoiding all dangers along the way! Everybody has to do their part in this race with time in order to escape the void and reach the end of the level.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1779080/extras/pbgif7.3.gif?t=1702930809"><h2 class="bb_tag">ANIMALS TOGETHER STRONG!</h2>Friends are one of the best things in life, especially if you can play Project Bridge together! Help each other carry heavy items, arrange essential resources and escape the dangerous void. Don't worry if all of your friends are busy, you can play the game alone as well.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1779080/extras/pbnewgif2.1.gif?t=1702930809"><h2 class="bb_tag">I LIKE BRIDGES!</h2>It really doesn’t matter that you skipped your civil engineering 101 class at school (was there even one?). You’ll figure out how to build bridges from resources found along the way in no time, easy-peasy lemon squeezy. Keep in mind that a simple wooden bridge may not always hold though, better craft some nails to strengthen it!<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1779080/extras/pbnewgif13.1.gif?t=1702930809"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE MIGHTY OMNOMNATOR</h2>The name of this fine piece of machinery and pinnacle of engineering says it all, right? Need some wood for your bridges? Give the omnomnator some trees and all is done. Need some nails? Find some ore, throw it into the OMNOMNATOR and there you go.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1779080/extras/pbnewgif3.1.gif?t=1702930809"><h2 class="bb_tag">GET NEW SKILLS!</h2>Between levels you can catch a breath in the temple - a place where you'll be able to acquire new skills and improve the ones you already have. After doing so you'll be able to pick the next level and continue on your quest, ready for everything the game throws at you!<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1779080/extras/pbgifnew12.1.gif?t=1702930809"><h2 class="bb_tag">MR WORLDWIDE</h2>Always wanted to travel? Well, now you have no other choice, so might as well enjoy it.<br/>Explore all the different biomes, including forests, deserts, caves, mines and others. <br/>How far will you be able to go?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1779080/extras/pbnewgif16.1.gif?t=1702930809"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal Trail ☆ Girlish Square 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2601750/Animal_Trail__Girlish_Square_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2601750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">STORY</h2><br/>Nakamori Taiga used to be just your average idol fanboy, cheering on the underground idol group, Animal Trail ☆ Girlish Square. However, he ended up stumbling upon his favorite idol group’s secret.<br/><br/>And that secret is…<br/><br/>-They are not only idols but magical girls as well<br/>-They’re helping to stop the enchanted realm of Hemdesmel from collapsing<br/>-To do this, they must work together to find an energy source called “Pal” which is released by humans in times of immense joy<br/><br/>Having discovered their secret, there was no going back. Soon, he became the manager Animal Trail desperately needed (not that he was given much choice in the matter). Still, for an idol otaku like him, getting to manage his favorite group was like a dream come true. One by one, he began connecting with each of the girls, helping them to reach their full potential. Now directed by Taiga, their marketing efforts also began to bear fruit. Animal Trail ☆ Girlish Square was finally starting to gain momentum, establishing themselves as a powerhouse in the indie idol sphere.<br/><br/>Amidst this flurry of successes came an offer they couldn’t refuse: an invitation to the so-called Tokyo New Idol Festival. It promised to be a huge, nationally televised event backed by a big-shot production company, and it was happening right in their backyard! The goal? To decide who were the best indie idols out there, once and for all. Is this their big chance? Their golden ticket to stardom? Can they even make the cut? Animal Trail once again finds itself at a crossroads, with the girls’ collective dream on the line.<br/><br/>The stage is set: it’s time to kick things off with another roar!<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Beautiful art by Shiromochi Sakura<br/></li><li>Magical girl idols with animal ears<br/></li><li>Fun and engaging story by Oumiya Yuu (NEKO-NIN, DraPri)<br/></li><li>Full Japanese voice acting (excluding the MC)<br/></li><li>Kinetic visual novel, there is only a single ending<br/></li><li>Gallery to revisit favorite CGs and listen to your favorite in game music tracks<br/></li><li>Ability to favorite specific voice lines</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eresys</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1918970/Eresys/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1918970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1918970/extras/insmouth2.gif?t=1702922371"><br/>Eresys is an online co-op/offline singleplayer horror game inspired by H.P Lovecraft which focuses mainly on teamwork. A party of 4 players face together the fears of the Lovecraftian Universe. Featuring smart AI mechanics with horrifying entities that will make you regret stepping into the forest.<br/>Only by working together and using the order of the occult will you be able to stand a chance.<br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1918970/extras/eyeONline.png?t=1702922371"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1918970/extras/environment.png?t=1702922371"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1918970/extras/ezgif.com-gif-maker_2_.gif?t=1702922371"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Visuals</strong> - Immersive environment with delicate presentation of monsters and characters.</li></ul><br/><strong>Story</strong> - After being expelled from the cult, a deranged former member has opened a Void Portal on a secluded island, unleashing horrific entities that have already claimed the lives of many. You and your fellow cultists must work together to send the entities back to where they came from and seal the portal to prevent further destruction. To accomplish this, you must locate and gather the resources needed to make offerings at the altars and perform the final ritual. Time is of the essence, can you and your team complete the task before the entities overrun the island and unleash their terror on the world beyond?<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Smart AI</strong> - Those entities are not your typical kind of “Monsters”. They will calculate all your choices and actions. This will also have an immediate impact on their AI and create new ways to devour you.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1918970/extras/Gifsteam2.gif?t=1702922371"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Unexpected Events</strong> - It could be a small coin or an idol, anything that is linked to the occult that could trigger a surprising and unexpected event. You never know what is hiding behind each item.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Safe Houses</strong> - Houses and other buildings can provide temporary safety. Hidden lootable items and resources can be found, which you will need to complete the final ritual.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Caves</strong> - Caves can offer a brief respite from danger and a source of resources, but be wary - they may also conceal sinister surprises.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>The Book</strong> - Players must decide who carries the powerful tome, the book of the order, which can banish the ancient entity once it is complete.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1918970/extras/gifsteam3.gif?t=1702922371"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Pages</strong> - The book of the order has missing pages, to complete the final ritual, you will have to gather every missing page.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Victims</strong> - The enchanted victims and other resources can be found around the island which was used by the cultist. You have to gather their blood and fill your vials with it.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1918970/extras/GIfsteam1.gif?t=1702922371"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>The Oil Lamps</strong> - The Entities have been in the void for eons and they are not familiar with the Light. Stick together with your teammates with at least 2 lamps lit. This will be one of the many ways to keep them at a distance. Remember that you will need oil to refill the lamps.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Altars</strong> - Altars are a manifestation from the necroworld summoned by the expelled cultist. Offer them blood and they will reward you with blood spheres.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1918970/extras/SiteSteam.png?t=1702922371"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battlemon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2236220/Battlemon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2236220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Battlemon is a fighting game where you collect and battle your friends using the vast array of small, cute and vibrant characters in the game. Each Battlemon has a specific move set, modes, hp, and other stats!There are many powerful different Battlemon to choose from, with even more being gradually added through updates.<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
-Fast Paced Battles which take place in real time<br>
-Events, such as raids and bosses<br>
-A huge cast of stage, and Battlemon to obtain!<br>
-And more!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No More Snow</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2244970/No_More_Snow/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2244970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2244970/extras/forest.gif?t=1702920780"><br/><br/>Introducing “No More Snow”, the thrilling top-down shooter game where Santa Claus must fight against Krampus and his mischievous minions! With cartoonish low poly graphics, “No More Snow” takes players on an adventure through 10 unique levels, including the snowy mountains, a spooky graveyard, and Santa’s very own workshop.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2244970/extras/factory.gif?t=1702920780"><br/><br/>In “No More Snow”, players will have access to a wide variety of weapons, including rifles, shotguns, and even a flamethrower. Don’t forget about the powerful melee weapons, such as a trusty axe and a deadly candy cane. With these tools at your disposal, take on an army of monsters, including snowmen, zombies, and even evil elves.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2244970/extras/boss.gif?t=1702920780"><br/><br/>But beware, as you journey through the game, you’ll face off against 8 challenging boss fights, including the grim reaper, the snowman king, and of course, Krampus himself. Will you be able to save Christmas from the clutches of evil and bring peace to the North Pole? Play “No More Snow” and find out!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2244970/extras/gnome_horde.gif?t=1702920780"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movavi Video Suite 2024 Steam Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2576020/Movavi_Video_Suite_2024_Steam_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2576020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							Make your every video project a breeze: be it a montage of your gaming content, video presentation for your colleagues, even a digital family archive! Edit videos on a handy timeline, record your screen and audio in a click, convert media files at incredible speed. <br/>Level up your videos with AI and easily create projects you’ll be proud of.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2576020/extras/Main_page_XL_v1_EN.png?t=1702920722"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Highlights</h2></strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Revamped timeline for easier editing</strong><br/>Experience a clearer and more intuitive timeline in the latest update. The optimized timeline ensures a faster and more enjoyable editing process.<br/></li><li><strong>Frame-precise cuts in a click</strong><br/>Cut your videos precisely the way you want them and leave in only the stuff that matters with the new Blade tool.<br/></li><li><strong>Pro-quality color correction</strong><br/>Enhance colors instantly using the next-level color correction. Captivate more viewers with visually stunning videos.<br/></li><li><strong>Improved AI motion tracking</strong><br/>Let AI attach any moving graphics to objects in your footage – with just one click.<br/></li><li><strong>Optimized overlay effects</strong><br/>Each overlay effect now offers 13 blending modes for you to explore. Try them out and find that perfect match for your video.</li></ul><br/><br/><strong>Edit videos easily like one-two-three</strong><br/>Video-editing process becomes easier than ever. All the tools are right at your fingertips, so you don’t waste any minute. Cut videos, combine your footage in the most engaging way on a frame by frame timeline, add sleek transitions, apply mind-blowing effects, and share your unique in-game moments with the community! <br/><br/><strong>Create videos from scratch</strong><br/>Record your webcam or make screencasts right from the app. Complement your footage with a voice-over to create a captivating story.<br/><br/><strong>Let the AI do the job for you</strong><br/>Movavi Video Editor meets the needs of modern gamers and content creators with its striking AI tools: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>AI background removal replaces the original background in your videos seamlessly without the need for a green screen. Change the scene setting just in a few clicks.<br/></li><li>AI motion tracking helps you captivate your audience with the unusual moving graphics. Spotlight your in-game character, draw attention to specific actions, or follow a moving object with a fun pic.<br/></li><li>AI denoiser reduces all the unwanted sounds from your videos in a single click. Let your commentary or the game's sound effects shine through without distracting noises.</li></ul><br/><strong>Level up your clips with stunning effects</strong><br/>Polish your videos with awesome built-in effects: titles, stickers, transitions, overlays, music, frames, LUTs, backgrounds, intros, and more! Enhance your visuals and tailor content to your unique style.<br/><br/><strong>Convert media files</strong><br/>Forget about fussing with formats: convert your videos, music, and images from and to any format in the blink of an eye. Compress large videos with no loss of quality to save space on your hard drive. Easily find and add subtitles for your favorite flicks. Upscale the resolution of your videos with AI to enjoy them on bigger screens.<br/><br/><strong>Record your screen</strong><br/>Effortlessly capture screens and the attention of your viewers. Create engaging video lessons, make killer presentations and software demos, record super-clear tutorials for your colleagues, capture must-attend webinars. Make your screencasts extra informative: highlight mouse and keyboard clicks, draw on videos in real time, and add a webcam to show who the real hero is.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total Vengeance</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2544870/Total_Vengeance/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2544870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>"Total Vengeance" </strong>is a gripping survival horror game that immerses players in a world of mystery, danger, and the unrelenting pursuit of survival. In this atmospheric and heart-pounding experience, players must navigate through a suspenseful narrative while mastering the art of resource gathering, puzzle solving, and combat to escape the clutches of an eerie and malevolent gas station.<br/><strong><br/>Overview:</strong><br/>Uncover the chilling secrets of an abandoned gas station as you step into the shoes of a protagonist whose journey takes a harrowing turn when his truck breaks down near the station. As darkness falls, it becomes evident that the gas station holds a nightmarish secret that must be unraveled before it's too late. Survival hinges on your wits, courage, and determination to outwit the lurking terrors that await.<br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/><br/><strong>Engrossing Survival Horror: </strong>Immerse yourself in an intense survival horror experience where every corner conceals danger, and every choice can lead to life or death.<br/><strong><br/>Mysterious Narrative: </strong>Embark on a riveting journey to uncover the dark secrets of the abandoned gas station and the horrors that dwell within.<br/><br/><strong>Exploration and Resource Management: </strong>Navigate an open-world environment teeming with hidden areas, puzzles, and clues. Scavenge for resources like food, water, and medical supplies while managing your inventory to survive the ordeal.<br/><br/><strong>Challenging Puzzles:</strong> Encounter intricate puzzles and obstacles that will test your logic and creativity as you strive to unlock doors and access vital areas.<br/><br/><strong>Terrifying Enemies: </strong>Confront mutated creatures, once-human entities twisted by the station's malevolent secret. Engage in intense combat or choose to evade and survive.<br/><br/><strong>Realistic Atmosphere: </strong>Immerse yourself in a meticulously designed environment that captures the eerie ambiance of an abandoned gas station and its surroundings.<br/><strong><br/>Weaponry and Tools:</strong> Utilize an array of weapons and tools at your disposal to defend yourself against the horrors that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Art Style: </strong>Experience a realistic and detailed art style that heightens the sense of immersion and amplifies the feeling of isolation.<br/><br/><strong>Engaging Narrative:</strong> Uncover a rich storyline through immersive gameplay and discover the interconnected stories of the characters who inhabited the gas station.<br/><br/><strong>Survival Mechanics:</strong> Keep your hunger, thirst, and radiation levels in check, making critical decisions to maintain your strength and vitality.<br/><br/><strong>"Total Vengeance" </strong>beckons players to embrace their survival instincts, uncover the truth shrouding the gas station, and ultimately escape the clutches of an otherworldly horror. Are you ready to face the darkness and survive the night?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politon: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2701730/Politon_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Politon: Prologue" is the free prologue version of "Politon". This prologue includes a tutorial, game mechanics, and the prologue of the main story inside. Only Single-player modes are available. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701730/extras/politon_wishlist.png?t=1702924624"><h2 class="bb_tag">Politon</h2>Politon is a turn-based strategy game with easy-to-understand mechanics and various game modes. Whether you want to defeat your friends online by employing your strategies or enjoy single-player game modes, Politon offers a variety of hex-based maps with different terrains. You'll need to manage your economy while expanding your territories and defend your region against rival invasions. Are you ready to experience the joy of utilizing countless strategies using Politon's simple and profound game mechanics?<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer</h2><br/>Through the <strong>online</strong> gaming experience, you can engage in battles with your friends or opponents from across the world. By creating your own online game lobby, you can customize turn mechanics and various map types according to your preferences. In the "Challenge" mode, you can test yourself against players worldwide who have made it to the leaderboards, competing for rankings and trying your skills against various mechanics.<h2 class="bb_tag">Single Player</h2><br/>In the <strong>Scenario</strong> mode, you can progress through Politon's story and get to know the world of Politon closely. With a rich pool of characters, you'll have hours of gameplay ahead of you as you witness events unfolding in the kingdom. In the "Skirmish" mode, you can practice without entering online battles, developing your new strategies, and getting familiar with different map types.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701730/extras/politon.gif?t=1702924624"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay and Mechanics</h2><br/>Politon offers two different turn mechanics: Standard and Arena. The game features 4 unit types, 3 building types, and hex grid maps waiting to be conquered. The unit types are arranged from weakest to strongest: Peasant, Militia, Baron, and Knight. Each hex grid allows placing one unit or building, and each unit has one movement point per turn. To afford the cost of units and their maintenance, you must expand your territory and strengthen your economy by building Farms. You can opt to place Outposts or Watchtowers to form defensive lines. Enhance your economy by collecting resources from the terrain or strategically spreading your influence by waiting for a few turns. The joy of victory lies in achieving the highest score or eliminating all your opponents, depending on the game mode.<br/><br/>We are working hard on Politon, and you can join our Discord channel to stay updated about the latest updates!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701730/extras/gameplay1.gif?t=1702924624"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/developer/pinq" rel="" target="_blank"><br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701730/extras/follow_dev.png?t=1702924624"/></a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goliath Depot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2479030/Goliath_Depot/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479030/extras/title_for_marketing.gif?t=1702927421"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479030/extras/potential_gif_steam2.gif?t=1702927421"><br/><br/><strong>Goliath Depot</strong> is a door-slamming 2D arcade platformer in the style of the early 80's. Close all doors, kick away the enemies and rack up your score in 4 worlds filled with single-screen levels inspired by tough-as-nail retro arcade platformers. Are you good enough to lift the curse of the Goliath Depot?<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Pick-up-and-play arcade gameplay<br/></li><li> 4 worlds with unique themes and gimmicks<br/></li><li> Play in solo or local co-op (*2 controllers are required for local co-op)<br/></li><li> Graphics and music inspired by the 1980<br/></li><li> Unlockable modes and power ups<br/></li><li> Online leaderboards<br/></li><li> Speedrun-mode!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479030/extras/just-like-1985.gif?t=1702927421"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479030/extras/juice_added_to_game_socials6_resize_2.gif?t=1702927421"><h2 class="bb_tag">The Goliath Corporation</h2><br/>Founded in the 1970's, the Goliath Corporation is a store chain owned by an evil maniac. On a winter storm night in 1985, George notices during his night shift that suspicious doors appeared all over the Goliath complex spawning evil products everywhere. Quickly, he tries to close them all to seal them away and alert the CEO at the Head Quarter. Can he do it before it's too late?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xmas Clash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2673690/Xmas_Clash/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Santa Claus and his christmas elfs to stop the angry babies, toddlers, and kids from getting to the workshop and take all the toys for themselves.<br>
Use strategy and management to secure the road to the workshop. And help save christmas!<br>
<br>
How do you stop an angry kid, that doesn't behave up to christmas?<br>
You give the coal!<br>
<br>
And you can give them coal with various different helpers. Elfs, Reindeers, Snowmans etc.<br/>
<br/>
The game comes with 10 levels. And lots of waves to defeath.<br/>
This is a casual game, so if you want a hyper focused, extremely hard, and total concentration game. This is not for you. This is a Holiday game, where you relax and play the best genre in the world. Tower Defense.<br/>
<br/>
The game is a 100% pay once and play. It is a 'simple' tactical tower defense game.<br/>
There will be updates every year once we reach christmas, so play this year. Enjoy it. And play an updated version next year too! And next year! and next year! Yea you see the pattern.<br/>
<br/>
Get in an help save christmas. Come on!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERONE - First Encounter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1203940/ZERONE__First_Encounter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1203940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Machine Empire VS Resistance</strong><br/><br/>Zerone's Early Access is now available! <br/>This is a VR FPS game about Resistance fights against the Empire army that dominates humanity. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1203940/extras/zerone0624.png?t=1702913993"><br/><br/><br/><strong>PVE mode: Resist the Empire army. </strong><br/>Multiplay is possible for up to 3 players. <br/>Players become resistant and must defeat the Empire bosses within a set time. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1203940/extras/HighresScreenshot00103.png?t=1702913993"><br/><br/><strong>PVP mode: Overpower the resistance.  </strong><br/>Up to 4 players will battle in 1vs2. One person will fight as the boss of the Empire army. <br/>The Empire players must continue to attack the resistance for a certain period of time and survive. <br/>Resistance players' goal is to defeat the Empire players within time. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1203940/extras/HighresScreenshot00144.png?t=1702913993"><br/><br/>All battles are fast-paced. We wanted VR beginners to enjoy the fun shooting game through the high-quality graphics of Unreal Engine 5. <br/>This is a great game to take your first VR gaming experience! <br/><br/>“Zerone” has now taken its first steps! <br/>We have a lot of love for  "Zerone", and we are working hard to include multiple modes and expandable content in the game in the future.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staff Runner</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2655660/Staff_Runner/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2655660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Unleash your inner musical maestro with Staff Runner, the captivating educational game that transforms sheet music learning into an exciting adventure. Say goodbye to dull lessons and hello to a fun, interactive way to read sheet music.<br>
<br>
🎵 What is Staff Runner?<br>
Staff Runner is a revolutionary educational game that takes you on a journey through the world of sheet music. Dive into a vibrant, gamified environment where you'll master the art of reading musical notation effortlessly.<br>
<br>
🎮 Key Features:<br>
🎵 Gamified Learning: Staff Runner makes the process of learning to read sheet music an engaging and enjoyable experience.<br>
🌟 Adventure Mode: Embark on an epic musical quest through various levels, each packed with challenges and rewards.<br/>
🎼 An Endless Runner Mode with Online Leaderboards waiting for you to top the charts<br/>
🥇 Progress Tracking: Keep track of your achievements and watch your skills improve as you conquer each level.<br/>
🎉 Rewards and Recognition: Earn badges and accolades for your musical achievements and keep the motivation flowing.<br/>
<br/>
📚 Why Choose Staff Runner?<br/>
Unlock a world of musical possibilities and join countless others in their quest to become sheet music experts. Whether you're a seasoned musician or just starting your musical journey, Staff Runner offers something for everyone.<br/>
<br/>
🎁 Perfect for Music Enthusiasts, Students, and Teachers<br/>
🏆 Boost Your Musical Confidence and Competence<br/>
🤩 Fun and Engaging, Making Learning Enjoyable<br/>
🌐 Accessible Anytime, Anywhere<br/>
<br/>
Are you ready to master the language of music in a way that's both entertaining and educational? Staff Runner is your ticket to becoming a sheet music virtuoso. Don't miss your chance to embark on this extraordinary musical adventure!<br/>
<br/>
Get started with Staff Runner and unlock the world of sheet music with the joy and excitement of gaming.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom of Bärn</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2711240/Kingdom_of_Brn/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2711240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Kingdom of Bärn:<br>
Dive into the enchanting world of Kingdom of Bärn, a mesmerizing RPG experience that combines the charm of low-poly graphics with an expansive open world filled with quests, crafting, and epic battles. Immerse yourself in a captivating story, conquer challenging quests, and face off against a colossal bear as the ultimate final boss!<br>
<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
<br>
Expansive Open World: Explore vibrant landscapes in charming low-poly style.<br/>
<br/>
Quests and Adventures: Engage in a rich narrative with challenging quests and intriguing characters.<br/>
<br/>
Diverse Enemies: Battle a myriad of creatures with unique abilities and attack patterns.<br/>
<br/>
Epic Bear Boss Battle: Face the ultimate challenge in an epic showdown against a colossal bear.<br/>
<br/>
Immersive Soundtrack: Enhance your gaming experience with an atmospheric soundtrack.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Get ready to embark on a legendary journey in the Kingdom of Bärn. Are you brave enough to face the bear and become the hero this realm needs? Purchase now and experience the magic of Bärn!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medieval Idle: Quest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2359800/Medieval_Idle_Quest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2359800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Medieval Idle: Quest</strong> is a captivating game that will transport you back to the middle ages. This idle game combines the elements of simulation and strategy to create a truly engaging experience for gamers of all ages. As you embark on your quest, you will find yourself in the role of a medieval lord, seeking to build a powerful kingdom by mining resources, upgrading your castle, and completing various quests.<br/><br/>The game is designed to challenge your skills as you progress through various levels. You start with a basic house that you can upgrade up to level 23. To upgrade your house, you will need to gather resources such as wood, stone, and iron. These resources can be obtained by mining in the nearby forest or quarry. You can also harvest crops in your fields to gather food resources for your workers.<br/><br/>As you progress in the game, you can buy more powerful pickaxes to mine resources faster. These pickaxes will allow you to gather resources in less time and with less effort. You can also hire workers to mine for you, and upgrade them to mine even more and faster. Upgrading your workers will require more resources, but the benefits of having skilled workers will be worth the effort.<br/><br/>One of the exciting features of Medieval Idle: Quest is the ability to craft armor. As you mine resources, you can use them to craft armor for your knights. Armor is essential for your knights as they venture out on quests to battle various enemies. The armor will provide your knights with the protection they need to face the dangers that lie ahead.<br/><br/>Completing quests is another important part of the game. You will receive quests from various characters, and each quest will require you to gather specific resources or craft certain items. Completing quests will reward you with experience points, resources, and gold. As you gain experience points, you will level up and unlock new features and abilities.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutants &amp; Zombies</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713900/Mutants__Zombies/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Mutants &amp; Zombies is a first-person shooter (FPS). A zombie apocalypse has occurred in the world and the survivors have to hide in safe shelters. You have to take on the role of an ordinary tramp and try to survive in this harsh world! Explore dangerous locations, kill zombies and mutants, complete various tasks and most importantly, do everything necessary to survive!<br>
<br>
Peculiarities<br>
- Pleasant music<br>
- Colorful graphics<br>
- Dangerous opponents						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entogious</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375960/Entogious/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Fight your way through your goals, you want to get rich? why work just kill the rich man and take his money. Take the easy way out? or so you think.<br/>Fight with an angel’s heart. Use your enemies kidneys to fight. Poison them with YOUR liver. Because Why not?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375960/extras/0001.gif?t=1702900944"><br/>Enjoy Your World’s Psychedelic And Unique Visuals While Torturing Your Worst Enemies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375960/extras/sdawdweee22-export.gif?t=1702900944"><br/><br/>Truly Why Punch Harold When You Can Stab Him With Your Kidney Stones?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375960/extras/sdadw-export.gif?t=1702900944"><br/><br/>And That All Happens In Real-Time-Turn-Based Combat???? I don’t even know how to describe it myself.<br/><br/>Explore, Fight &amp; Find.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Rabbits 兔子在哪里</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2685250/Where_Rabbits/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find 100 Rabbits.<br/>A carefully hand drawn 4K scene filled with cute characters.<br/>The process is short and won't take up too much player time.<br/>You can choose your favorite dyeing for the convenience of color blind players.<br/>Extremely easy to achieve.<br/>Automatically save and read files.<br/>There is a local timer ranking.<br/>No punishment, easy and enjoyable.<br/>You can play games with family and friends on the same computer, suitable for all ages.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685250/extras/说明.jpg?t=1702896820"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Ninja Painter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2424970/Perfect_Ninja_Painter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2424970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ninjas have never been... painting! Prepare for a colorful, fast-paced adventure!<br>
<br>
Perfect Ninja Painter is a colorful arcade puzzle game that's so much fun, it's hard to stop. Paint the walls through 50 levels and try to get all stars!<br>
<br>
The original Ninja Painter game has been played more than 100 million times on Flash, the web and mobiles since 2011, and now it's time to get this great experience in HD.<br>
<br>
- Explore the 5 locations<br>
- Complete 50 levels<br/>
- Have a lot of old-school fun!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESC BACKROOMS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2701240/ESC_BACKROOMS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							ESC BACKROOMS is  first person psicological horror exploration game when you play a role of sherif who come to town to investigate a missing girl.<br>
You have to solve puzzles ,find items and explorer dark ambient.<br>
Explore, think, interact  various nostalgic, dreamlike, uncanny environments.<br>
<br>
Sheriff was getting ready to give up when he heard about a strange environments on the outskirts of town. It was said to be quiet and isolated, and no one had gone near it for years. He decided to take a chance and investigate it.<br>
<br>
Features<br/>
Story driven first person psicological horror experience<br/>
Explore,interact with items,solve puzzles and find a key.<br/>
Atmospheric low poly ambient.<br/>
Atmospheric sounds.<br/>
Enjoy						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost in Space</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2704050/Lost_in_Space/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Story company</h2><br/>A fascinating story awaits you in a single company, or call your friends and go through a joint story company of 2 to 4 people.<br/><br/>Riddles, choices, special fears of each of the characters, all this affects the plot and the lives of the crew members.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704050/extras/Оформление_EN4.gif?t=1702891851"><h2 class="bb_tag">Each hero is unique</h2><br/>You have to manage a team of crew members of the intersystem cargo ship "SOMNIUM", each hero has his own character, characteristics, skills and fears<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704050/extras/герой.jpg?t=1702891851"><br/><br/><strong>CAPTAIN VALERY GROMOV</strong><br/>A serious, purposeful coordinator, only he can unite the team in this fight for survival<br/><br/><strong>ENGINEER ALICE WAGNER</strong><br/>A girl who is weak in spirit, but irreplaceable in repairing a ship; only with her can the ship survive<br/><br/><strong>DOCTOR IRINA KNYAZEVA</strong><br/>A secretive and stubborn woman with her own secrets, but only with her the crew will not die from their injuries.<br/><br/><strong>PILOT DMITRY SINITSYN</strong><br/>Knows his ship like the back of his hand, can go where others cannot, but a strong load can harm him<br/><br/><br/><strong>Madness system</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Save the heroes' minds</h2><br/>Each hero gradually goes crazy, the lower the mind parameter, the more the hero sees events beyond the control of reason, and the more accidents on the ship, the greater the chance of succumbing to madness and even harming his friends<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704050/extras/глаз2.jpg?t=1702891851"><h2 class="bb_tag">Card and music collection system</h2><br/>Large collection of 85 animated digital maps and 12 music tracks The collection opens as you progress in the company, collect the entire collection<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704050/extras/карты4_en.jpg?t=1702891851"><h2 class="bb_tag">Atmospheric Sci-fi design and sound</h2><br/>The game is made in the style of science fiction, we guarantee maximum immersion into the atmosphere of the future and fascinating space<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704050/extras/арт.jpg?t=1702891851"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KOIBUMI</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668630/KOIBUMI/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Koibumi</strong>.<br/>It is a letter confessing love. A so-called love letter.<br/>All you need to convey your feelings is love, courage and a little luck.<br/>You become the love letter and deliver your feelings to that girl.<br/>Whether this love will succeed or not is up to you.<br/><br/><strong>Objective of the game:</strong><br/>You control a paper airplane and fly through the sky to deliver your love to her.<br/>However, the paper airplane is fragile and if it hits something, it will crash and the game over.<br/>If you just want to deliver it, it will be easy.<br/>It may be difficult to collect hearts and fill them with feelings.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Card Fuse</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2698680/Card_Fuse/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A deck building roguelike where you will combine your cards with new ones you find, obliterating enemies with the cards that you make and becoming more powerful with each card you fuse.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698680/extras/card_demostration.gif?t=1702891242"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><i>Strategic Deckbuilding</i>: You will need to think ahead on what cards to combine and find what abilities work best with each other. Think carefully of each ability you add to your card or let chaos take over you and get many different abilities on your cards!<br/></li><li><i>Define your build</i>: While fighting enemies you will gain XP that will allow you to unlock special skills. These skills will let you focus your build on any direction you wish to take it.<br/></li><li><i>Randomly generated paths</i>: Go through a new map each game that is generated from a predetermined variety of enemies and events. Find rare enemies or cards that will make your run stand out from others.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698680/extras/fusion_demostration3.gif?t=1702891242"><h2 class="bb_tag">Card Fuse comes with:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>30+ unique abilities your cards can have.<br/></li><li>120+ cards to improve your deck with.<br/></li><li>30+ skills to improve your strategy.<br/></li><li>70+ unique combat encounters.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aegis Dilemma: Veritas Omnia Vincit</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2721880/Aegis_Dilemma_Veritas_Omnia_Vincit/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2721880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Aegis Dilemma is now here on steam!<br/><br/>Several centuries have passed since the Blight Era ended. All the suffering of the time seems to be over. Enter the journey of Jules, a normal mercenary thrust into unusual circumstances. Follow her journey to find the truth about herself and her close friends….<br/><br/><br/><br/><strong>All to resolve the Dilemma. All for the Grand Library. Veritas Omnia Vincit</strong><br/><br/>A short 1 hour Visual Novel that explores the duality of humanity, and the mystery of which how the Aegis Dilemma came about. <br/><br/>MEET THE CHARACTERS<br/><br/><strong>Jules the Survivor.</strong> A seducer, killer and a mercenary. Master of Infirma Punctium. she takes on a job which changes her life forever....<br/><br/><strong>Cigar the Raider.</strong> A bandit chief of the Sorol Plains. Master of the control of hate and Odium Arts. His raiding of a particular person changes his life forever...<br/><br/><strong>Adeline the Hero of the Federation</strong>. A Former Konrad Federation officer. She struggles to accept her past which changed her life forever...<br/><br/><strong>Metcha the Tenebris Flammae</strong>. A mysterious girl with no remorse yet has a childlike attitude. Her encounter with Septium changed her life forever...<br/><br/><strong>Septium and Novem the Librarians</strong>. Former friends now turned enemies. Their service to the Grand Librarian changed their life forever....<br/><br/><br/>Keywords: Aegis, Aegis Dilemma, Veritas Omnia Vincit, Latin, Adventure, Visual Novel, Philosophical, Linear, Story Rich, Story, Free, Descriptive Combat, Mystery						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REFICUL 666</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1557190/REFICUL_666/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1557190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							As darkness descends upon the world. all contact is lost. Set in a small town in North America, will you survive the dark new world? Prepare for a challenging and creepy indie horror game.  Features an open-world town, powerful magical relics, and an unsettling atmosphere in this creepy Post-apocalyptic Indie survival horror game.<br/><br/>Reficul 666 is an indie open-world horror game with a very different kind of apocalyptic scenario. Follow clues to find your friends and find out what has happened as you explore an open-world town in the darkness of night. All power is out and lighting will be key to survival.   Look around the town for more supplies and other items and relics as you venture further into the dark.<br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Open-world - Survival Horror game with Rogue-Like elements<br/></li><li>First Person Survival horror<br/></li><li>One Hell of an Atmosphere<br/></li><li>Challenging gameplay with random enemies with each new game<br/></li><li>Immersive environment with a tense atmosphere and a real sense of dread<br/></li><li>Explore the town to find a variety of items and clues<br/></li><li>Powerful magical relics with unique and awesome powers<br/></li><li>No jump scares, the game creates the atmosphere and random events to bring the element of surprise<br/></li><li>Procedural lighting that lights up the environment around you</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VFurrika!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2720270/VFurrika/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2720270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2720270/extras/VfurrikaLOGO.png?t=1702886644"><br/><br/><strong>About VFurrika!</strong><br/>VFurrika! is an addictive puzzle game that combines the charm of your favourite VFur streamers with strategic gameplay.<br/>Drop your favorite furry VTuber into a glass and witness them merging into other VTubers upon contact!<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/>The game is simple: Aim and drop randomly-generated VTubers heads into a glass.<br/><br/>Have 2 of the same heads touch each other for them to merge into a bigger head of another type.<br/>This kind of gameplay allows combos to be made, but only if you’ve got skills!<br/><br/>Once the glass is filled to the brim, the game is over, but you can upload your score to the Leaderboards. Try beating your friends’ scores!<br/><br/><u>Features:</u><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Leaderboards<br/></li><li>Addictive Gameplay<br/></li><li>Recognizable Faces<br/></li><li>Cute Visuals</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only Up 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653170/Only_Up_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In the captivating and intuitive game "Only Up 2" players are faced with a clear but challenging mission: navigate through the obstacles, maintain your balance, and keep climbing until you reach the very top. <br/><br/>Climb out of the favellas and secure the highgrounds in the biggest map and journey you've ever seen before!<br/><br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Biggest map yet<br/></li><li>Speedrunning features<br/></li><li>Steam Leaderboards<br/></li><li>New Multiplayer System</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Westale: Peelgrimage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1141760/Westale_Peelgrimage/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1141760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1141760/extras/一个角色英文.png?t=1702888287"><br/>Each character has 3 forms, with each form has different appearance and skills. Player can evolve into new forms through "Sarira" in the game. For example, Sun Wukong can be evolved from “Rookie” to “Heavenly Might”, and then to "Divine Monkie". With each evolution, your power can be increased by more than double.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1141760/extras/三阶进化.gif?t=1702888287"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1141760/extras/变身神仙英文.png?t=1702888287"><br/>Player can transform into various immortals from "Journey to the West" for a period of time in the game, such as “Aspects of Lightning”, "Opulence", "Manjusri", "Xingtian", and etc. Each immortal comes with different abilities that help improve your survival rate among monsters.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1141760/extras/变身.gif?t=1702888287"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1141760/extras/无厘头英文.png?t=1702888287"><br/>Westale:Peelgrimage designed many creative weapons and items based on the Survivor-like games. Have you ever heard that "Bullet Screen" can kill monsters? Have you ever seen someone kill monsters with a pencil? How about generate a "Black Hole" and suck in a ton of monsters? We make these things possible for you! And in this game, there are even more possibilities beyond these!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1141760/extras/弹幕_610x339_5s.gif?t=1702888287"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1141760/extras/两两组合英文.png?t=1702888287"><br/>Acquire specific magical treasures that can be combined to a super-powerful relics, unleashing powers greater than the sum of their parts. The game features up to 20 artifacts with various effects, each capable of instantly transforming your combat experience!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1141760/extras/画骨龙_610x339_13s.gif?t=1702888287"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1141760/extras/游戏特色英文.png?t=1702888287"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1141760/extras/割草9s版本_610x339_9s.gif?t=1702888287"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Unlock 7 characters with different styles. Evolve them into three different states to maximize their power.<br/></li><li>Explore combinations of over 200 diverse of weapons, magical treasures and items.<br/></li><li>Synthesize extraordinary relics for a more exhilarating and explosive hack and slash experience.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dice Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2685170/Dice_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685170/extras/Eng-Title1.png?t=1702864386"><br/>Different kinds of dice enemies come one after the other. You take on the role of a rolling dice that keeps bouncing up and down to crush your enemies.<h2 class="bb_tag">Exciting game groove</h2>Varied enemies and barrier will restrict your movement range greatly. It's time to show off your handling skills to flatten more enemy in limit time or undless wave.<h2 class="bb_tag">Diverse Items selection</h2>Earn points by defeating enemies and exchange them for powerful props: Invincibility, Instant Kill, Time Stop ect... You can always find your favorite props to take the lead in the dice battle.<h2 class="bb_tag">Select mode&amp;difficulty</h2>Story mode and endless now available on easy&amp;hard difficulty. Play in suitable field to practice your skills. Reach higher and have the last laugh.<h2 class="bb_tag">Rules that needed to be known</h2>🎲 Players need to continuously eliminate enemies on the field to reach higher levels or scores.<br/>🎲 The Dice's HP point is displayed in the upper left corner of the interface. One HP point will be deducted when the dice touches an enemy or an enemy bullet.<br/>🎲 The dice has 3 life points by default. You'll lose the game round when this point is reduced to 0.<br/>🎲 Be sure to bring items before starting the game. Equip the item to help you win the game more easily. ( The item would only be consumed if it's used during a round )						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darksword: Battle Eternity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2485000/Darksword_Battle_Eternity/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Darksword is an exciting, original non-stop VR action RPG.  Venture deep into the world of the Twisted Corridors and defeat your enemies in style.  Develop your own style of combat, exploit enemy weakness, and collect materials to get more powerful weapons! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485000/extras/001.gif?t=1702864221"><br/><br/>Play the story mode and compete globally through the leaderboard system!  Show off your skills, build teamwork, and get even more rewards in the multiplayer Co-Op mode!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485000/extras/02.gif?t=1702864221"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girls Hobby in LOVE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2715960/Girls_Hobby_in_LOVE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715960/extras/vvv.gif?t=1702863734"><br/>Six girls have a hobby group. One likes to listen to music, another likes to draw, and the third likes to read. Each girl is special in her interests. When you come to the clubs and want to choose which one to join, each girl wants you to choose her club! A ruthless scene of jealousy, frowns and distrust between the girls unfolds, because each one wants you to choose her!  Which one will you like more?<br/><br/>Easy win: Keyboard <strong>Сtrl+D</strong> - Complete Level<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715960/extras/zzz.png?t=1702863734"><br/>In the game, your goal is to collect the puzzle in order to restore the pictures. (◕‿◕)♡<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715960/extras/1-2.gif?t=1702863734"><h2 class="bb_tag">Special Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎻   Live2D dynamic character<br/></li><li>🎨   CG Gallery Mode<br/></li><li>🎾   Well-drawn CGs<br/></li><li>♟️   Relaxing music<br/></li><li>📚   Puzzle game</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heart-S-Truck</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2671740/HeartSTruck/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671740/extras/About_this_game.png?t=1702849379"><br/>In "Heart-S-Truck," brace yourself for a platforming odyssey set in a whimsical universe where the fate of humanity rests on the wheels of brave delivery trucks. As a valiant truck with a vital mission, you'll navigate treacherous paths demanding precision, velocity, and unwavering focus.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671740/extras/gameplay_features.png?t=1702849379"><h2 class="bb_tag">Forge Bonds with Quirky Characters </h2>Dive into deep interactions with the world’s vibrant residents. Listen to their stories, share in their dreams, and knit the threads of a scattered community together by fulfilling critical deliveries in their time of need.<h2 class="bb_tag">Conquer the Physics of Platforming</h2>Face the thrilling challenge of a physics-based driving platformer. Mastery over momentum and the art of balance is key as you turn each delivery into a heart-pounding trial.<h2 class="bb_tag">Revel in a Vivid, Hand-Painted World</h2>Journey through an enchantingly painted world that invites you to explore a spectrum of stunning and diverse environments, each alive with color and motion.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671740/extras/About_developmen.png?t=1702849379"><br/>Heart-S-Truck is an intermediate game project at the University of Southern California by Rosemary Wu and Yufei Xiao, in collaboration with students from Berklee College of Music. For more information, please visit our publisher page. To learn more about the USC Games program, the #1 game program in the world, check out the USC Games website, linked to the right.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Null Gravity Labyrinth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2701170/Null_Gravity_Labyrinth/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find and touch the golden cube to exit this abstract labyrinth. <br>
When touching a spinning cube all elements with the same color as the cube will disappear and new paths will form. <br>
When you touch a portal it will teleport you to the connected portal of the same color. <br>
Currently only level 1 and 2 are playable.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nudel Tag</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1149280/Nudel_Tag/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1149280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In <strong>Nudel Tag</strong>, challenge your friends to get the most tips, in a crazy ramen restaurant !<br/>Find up to 4 controllers, to have the most fun, and see who is the best waiter in the house !<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1149280/extras/Gif_01.gif?t=1702832317"><br/><br/>You need to bring plates, from the chef, to the customers, easy, right ?<br/>Well, unless the other waiters steal your plates and cash in your precious tips !<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1149280/extras/Gif_02.gif?t=1702832317"><br/><br/>How can you get more chances to get some tips ? <br/>Well, you can always spend what you got so far in bonuses <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1149280/extras/Gif_03.gif?t=1702832317"><br/><br/>Have fun with this party game !						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Castle Kingdom Wars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2284390/Castle_Kingdom_Wars/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2284390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Defend your castle and crush your opponent's castle.<br>
<br>
Unlock new heroes and improve them to defeat your enemies. Upgrade your castle and unlock more features.<br>
<br>
Make your own strategy to beat your enemies. Characters have different skills so you can defeat your enemy with different tactics. Knight, swordsman, archer, skeleton, mage, catapult and much more hero are ready to fight for you.<br>
<br>
There are 2 game modes in this game:<br>
<br/>
1- You can play singleplayer and play agains ai. there are lots of different levels in singleplayer mode.<br/>
<br/>
2- There is also a battle simulator sandbox mode. Spawn warriors in the battle arena and see how they fight against each other at the battlefield. You can spawn any hero and watch hero wars. There is no character limit at this mode so you can play with lots of heroes at battle simulator.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neon Geometry Dash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2704460/Neon_Geometry_Dash/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You have different levels, where you will have to travel down space, moving left and right avoiding collisions.<br>
<br>
Each level is a new adventure with new mechanics and soundtracks.<br>
<br>
Neon: Geometry Dash has the following features:<br>
<br>
• Rhythm-based Action game.<br/>
• Many levels with unique soundtracks!<br/>
• Vertical action game with simple look but addictive mechanics.<br/>
• Practice mode.<br/>
• Very easy but challenging game.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1702928763"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1702928763"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1702928763"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1702928763"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1702928763"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1702928763"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1702928763"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
