<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Garten of Banban 6</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2499800/Garten_of_Banban_6/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Explore the forgotten levels of Banban’s Kindergarten. Survive the new terrors that reside below. Uncover the truth behind the place, and find the whereabouts of your missing child…</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/extras/all.gif?t=1703084211"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive the never-entered levels of Banban’s Kindergarten:</h2>After the events of Garten of Banban 4, you are forced to run away and delve even deeper into the mysterious establishment that is Banban’s kindergarten. You are heading down to where no human dares to be.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/extras/corner.gif?t=1703084211"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/extras/fly.gif?t=1703084211"><h2 class="bb_tag">No more friends to make…</h2>You have run out of friends to make. From now on, you only meet new enemies who will make sure you never feel alone! In Banban’s Kindergarten, there are enemies to be made in every corner!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/extras/fall.gif?t=1703084211"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/extras/liminal.gif?t=1703084211"><br/><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/intent/user?screen_name=Euphoric_Bros" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/extras/TwitterNew.png?t=1703084211"/></a><br/><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@EuphoricBrothers?sub_confirmation=1" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/extras/YoutubeNew.png?t=1703084211"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cygnus Enterprises</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1963520/Cygnus_Enterprises/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1963520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cygnus Enterprises is proud to be the first full game with smart AI NPCs that respond to players in real time, react to the environment and even perform actions.<br/>Disclaimer: AI NPCs are powered by Inworld. Team Miaozi takes no responsibility for the AI generated content. AI NPCs may incur separate costs or become unavailable in the future. AI NPCs can be disabled by the user at any time. Traditional human-written narrative and human VO will always remain playable.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1963520/extras/header.png?t=1702980427"><br/><br/>Cygnus Enterprises combines action RPG and base management elements, and is set on the alien frontier world of Mytilus.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>FAST-PACED ACTION SHOOTER RPG </strong></h2><br/> Battle hostile alien creatures and shoot your way through exotic locations. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1963520/extras/Gif1.gif?t=1702980427"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>  BUILD AND MANAGE YOUR BASE </strong></h2><br/>Gather resources, construct buildings, and research new technologies. Entice new settlers to visit, live, and work on your base. Manage your employees to ensure prosperity and happiness.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1963520/extras/Gif2.gif?t=1702980427"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>LOOT, CRAFT AND TRADE</strong></h2><br/>Gear up your character with hundreds of unique items, including more than 50 weapons.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1963520/extras/Gif3.gif?t=1702980427"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>BE WHO YOU WANT TO BE </strong></h2><br/>Customize your appearance and choose skills freely from six distinct skill trees.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1963520/extras/Gif4.gif?t=1702980427"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703066753"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703066753"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703066753"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703066753"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703066753"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703066753"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>战姬军团</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2389120/_/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2389120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Game gift pack:<br>
tm-Fate111<br>
tm-Fate222<br>
<br>
<br>
Customer service QQ group: 761159994<br>
Customer service email: wangquan0630@outlook.com<br/>
Contact customer service and receive a gift package<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Promotional introduction to "Legion of Valkyrie"<br/>
<br/>
Step into the mysterious world and write your legend!<br/>
<br/>
In "Legion of Warriors", you will travel through time and face a shocking adventure. The mysterious world hundreds of years ago was covered by a devastating magical war, and you will become a fearless adventurer on this land. Challenge destiny, uncover the mystery, and create a legend full of miracles and challenges.<br/>
<br/>
Game features at a glance:<br/>
<br/>
🌟 Diverse partner system: Make friends from various races, each with unique skills and personality. Through spiritual communication and cooperation, form the strongest adventure team to conquer unknown threats together.<br/>
<br/>
🌿 Rich and diverse life system: In addition to exciting adventures, you can also experience various activities such as planting, mining, fishing, etc. in your home to obtain precious resources, strengthen your character, and improve your strength.<br/>
<br/>
⚔️ Strategic card battle: Use skills and magic skillfully in battle, fight side by side with your partners, formulate strategies, and defeat powerful enemies. Each battle is a battle of wits, adding layers of depth to your adventure.<br/>
<br/>
🌍 Explore the mysterious world: travel through misty forests, ancient ruins, mysterious mazes, and unlock countless mysteries and treasures in the Corridor of Destiny. Every step may reveal the secrets of this mysterious world.<br/>
<br/>
🤝 Social interaction and guild system: Communicate with NPCs and meet interesting characters. Join a guild, team up with other players for adventures, challenge powerful world bosses, and win generous rewards.<br/>
<br/>
The time has come for your adventure to begin!<br/>
<br/>
"War Princess Legion" will take you on an adventure through destiny to explore unknown miracles and challenges. In this mysterious two-dimensional world, you will personally experience a legendary story. Are you ready? Embark on your adventure and enter "War Girl Army"!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vampire Survivors: Emergency Meeting</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2690330/Vampire_Survivors_Emergency_Meeting/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							The Survivors are desperate to hunt vampires, but are running out of places to look. Only one option remains: Be the bullet hell... in space! <br/><br/>Gather your most trusted Crewmates, prepare to eject the Impostors, and try to survive while mowing down thousands of extra-terrestrial foes in this expansion for Vampire Survivors. Turn classic Among Us tasks into outrageous weapons, upgrading your abilities after every roguelite run to overcome impossible odds with ease. Be alert to subterfuge as you explore the vast weirdness of the Polus Replica and keep your wits about you, as suspicious eyes are always watching 👀.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features <strong>20-in-game only</strong> unlocks, no Steam achievements. For more info please see the FAQs here:</h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fponcle.games%2Femergency-meeting.html" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://poncle.games/emergency-meeting.html</a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/extras/1_Characters_ENG.png?t=1702898514"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/extras/Amongus_Chars_big.gif?t=1702898514"><br/>A cast of courageous Crewmates assembled to take on the tumultuous tasks, including: <br/><br/>Crewmate Dino - Starry-eyed, optimistic, and unfortunately extremely tasty. Dino is a jack-of-all-trades who boosts stats whenever a task is completed (i.e. when you level up a weapon). <br/><br/>Engineer Gino - Few Crewmates come as close to truly competent task-work as Gino, who offers a selection of passive weapons from their toolbox every few levels. <br/><br/>Ghost Lino - Good Crewmates don't let a silly thing like death get in the way of their tasks. Lino can float through walls at will and can't be hurt, but can't deal damage either... what could be the goal of such suspicious game design?! <br/><br/>Shapeshifter Nino - Look at this bean! They can do all kinds of... wait, where did they go? And where did this snowman come from? Oh well, I'm sure you'll figure it out. <br/><br/>Guardian Pina - Everyone needs an angel on their shoulder. Pina isn't just there for moral support, though - they boost the defences of all nearby allies, and they love taking out the garbage. <br/><br/>Impostor Rina - A fellow Crewmate that is in no way some kind of duplicitous, well-disguised killer. One hundred percent all-natural-bean, right here. Nothing to see or think about. <br/><br/>Scientist Mina - Mina's scientific skill is matched only by their intense clumsiness. Thankfully, dropping potentially hazardous chemicals has a major upside when you're besieged by extra-terrestrial monsters. <br/><br/>Horse - It's a horse. Neigh, etc. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/extras/1_Weapons_ENG.png?t=1702898514"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/extras/WeaponIcons.png?t=1702898514"><br/>Transform your tasks into powerful weapons to defend yourself from Impostors, Shapeshifters, and all manner of extra-terrestrial weirdos. Blast away baddies with the supermassive sound waves of your Report! weapon, slice angry aliens in half with Lucky Swipe, and drop duplicitous foes to their doom with Just Vent. Lonely Survivors should seek out Mini Crewmates to empower their Task-based weaponry (or just for general companionship). <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/extras/1_Stage_ENG.png?t=1702898514"><br/>Polus Replica - an eerily accurate replica of the scientific base on Polus. This planet is packed with bizarre biomes ripe for exploration by Survivors and Crewmates, with tasks and treasure chests galore. Unfortunately, its also accidentally being invaded by your average space dwellers, like aliens, robots, and ducks. Expect the unexpected and do NOT trust the bins. Never trust the bins. Or the chicken nuggets. In fact, it's a good idea to remain alert at all times and not trust anything. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/extras/StageMap.png?t=1702898514"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690330/extras/1_Tracks_ENG.png?t=1702898514"><br/>♫ Emergency Meeting<br/>♫ Hide and Survive<br/>♫ No Ducks Among Us<br/>♫ No Aliens Among Us<br/>♫ No Ghosts Among Us<br/>♫ No Vampires Among Us						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1702928763"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1702928763"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1702928763"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1702928763"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1702928763"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1702928763"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1702928763"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trinity Fusion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1911360/Trinity_Fusion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take control of your parallel selves on a mission to save the dying multiverse. Explore dark, sci-fi worlds and engage in fast-paced, smooth and precise combat.<h2 class="bb_tag">A rogue-lite journey through the multiverse</h2>The various branches of the multiverse are always changing. Fight through a combination of procedurally-generated levels as well as hand-crafted challenges and arenas that will put your skills to the test. Levels with 3D graphics are seamlessly constructed out of hundreds of custom-made rooms.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/extras/Ranger_Factory.gif?t=1702915094"><h2 class="bb_tag">High-intensity combat</h2>With weapons and attack systems that leverage our previous experience working on fighting games. You’ll slide, dash and dodge between enemy attacks and strike back with an arsenal of satisfying special weapons and abilities.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/extras/Ranger_City_Walls_GIF_Cleanup.gif?t=1702915094"><h2 class="bb_tag">Three characters, three universes to explore</h2>Each of your parallel selves has their own world with multiple biomes to explore, as well as their own sets of unique abilities and weapons. Travel through a universe of desolate wastes and caverns roamed by mutant creatures, escape the endless forges and labs of a world ruled by machines, and survive the dangerous sky cities of a post-human society.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/extras/Player_Running_Cleanup.gif?t=1702915094"><h2 class="bb_tag">Constant Progression</h2>Unlock permanent upgrades in the Hub and discover new starting points for your run as you reclaim major locations in each universe. Finding yourself getting stuck in one area? Start your next run in a different one! No matter where you die, or which starting point you pick, you're making progress somewhere.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1911360/Trinity_Fusion/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1911360/Trinity_Fusion/</a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Cutter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1924430/Cookie_Cutter/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Void. The Matter. The Megastructure. A dystopian world with an egomaniac leader determined to unveil the secrets of the universe. INFONET promised a utopia built on the backs of tireless androids called Denzels. It was a lie. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/Cherry.gif?t=1702760603"><br/><br/>200 years later the planet is decaying and the mysterious Red Seed has been stolen. Raz, a renegade mechanic, searches a hidden lab and discovers the Denzel Cherry, butchered and left for dead, clinging to life by sheer will alone. Her creator—and the love of her life, Doctor Shinji Fallon—has been taken by a demented sicko and Cherry intends to make him—and anybody or anything who gets in her way—pay.<br/><br/>Fueled by love and powered by rage, join Cherry on a blood-soaked quest for revenge as she explores the massive Megastructure and eviscerates the armies of INFONET in an unforgettable over-the-top 2D platformer that breaks tropes and bones.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Subversive_Metroidvania.png?t=1702760603"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Subversive_Metroidvania.gif?t=1702760603"><br/>Cookie Cutter is unabashedly irreverent, violent, and risqué. Become Cherry, a badass android on a rage-filled and love-driven quest. To save her beloved creator she’ll explore and fight her way through a unique illustrated sci-fi dystopian world as she chainsaw-murders anybody who stands in her way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Hand-drawn_Action.png?t=1702760603"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Hand-Drawn_Action.gif?t=1702760603"><br/>Every frame of this immersive experience is drawn by hand with copious amounts of love. That means epic, fall-out-of-your-chair visuals. Grotesque bugs and menacing robots. Gargantuan bosses. Ridiculous weapons, special moves, and brutal gory finishers. All of it brought to life with benchmark 2D animation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Epic_Combat_Abilities.png?t=1702760603"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC__Epic_Combat_Abilities.gif?t=1702760603"><br/>Whether you’re ripping the wings off overgrown mosquitos, impaling mini-bosses, crushing robots on Cherry’s motorcycle, or kick-punch-uppercut-stomping waves of foes with complex combos, you won’t find a better fighting experience with responsiveness and all the flair you could ask for in a Metroidvania.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Rage-Filled_Spectacle.png?t=1702760603"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Rage-Filled_Spectacle.gif?t=1702760603"><br/>Far future dystopia? Check. An android companion turned rage-filled killer? Check. Over-the-top characters and enemies? Check. Buckets of blood? Of course. Experience our bizarre tale, inspired by Japanese manga and Quentin Tarantino films, through 10 huge zones, each weirder than the next.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1702674942"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WITCH ON THE HOLY NIGHT</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2052410/WITCH_ON_THE_HOLY_NIGHT/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2052410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2052410/extras/WITCH_ON_THE_HOLY_NIGHT_About_this_game.gif?t=1702631006"><br/><strong>Product Description</strong><br/>TYPE-MOON, known for the wildly popular mobile game "Fate/Grand Order" and the epic visual novel "Tsukihime," is releasing a remaster of the 2012 hit "Witch on the Holy Night. Experience a coming of age story set in the vibrant, bustling 1980s, which follows an innocent young man and two young "witches." Updates added since the original release include long-awaited fully voiced characters as well as visuals remastered in full HD, bringing the experience to life with unparalleled quality and fidelity. Masterful manipulation of visual elements imbues combat scenes with nail-biting tension, but also breathes life into the characters' everyday activities. Animated graphical elements bring an entirely new level of depth to the reading experience as well!<br/><br/><strong>STORY</strong><br/>In the mansion on the hill, there lived two witches...<br/><br/>It is the late 1980s—the twilight of an era of beauty and vigor.<br/>A boy moves to the city, barely missing two witches living in modern times.<br/><br/>The boy leads a completely ordinary life.<br/>She carries herself with gallant pride.<br/>The girl lives a sleepy, hidden life.<br/><br/>Each walks a starlit path.<br/>One would never expect their paths to cross.<br/>The story of how these three disparate people came together is soon to be told.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1702562956"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1702562956"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1702000678"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1702000678"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1702394215"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1702394215"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1702394215"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1702620270"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1702620270"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SteamWorld Build</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2134770/SteamWorld_Build/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-Homestead.png?t=1702026390"><br/>One final landrush! The planet is dyin', Astrid, and it's dig or die trying! <br/><br/>That mine under our town is sitting empty, and wouldn't you know there's rumours of ancient tech down there that might help us out of this predicament. Round up the posse, circle the wagons, and let's get to buildin' a new home! Collect resources above ground and ores down below so we can get those wealthy bots in here to help us build bigger, and we can get the heck out of here!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_1.gif?t=1702026390"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_manage.png?t=1702026390"><br/>As your borders expand, new steamfolk will find their way to you! Every bot is crotchety in their own way, and it's up to you to keep them steaming along. Barter to boost efficiency, keep goods flowing to and from the mines and keep everyone happy to make them work their darndest and hardest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_2.gif?t=1702026390"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-DIG-DEEP.png?t=1702026390"><br/><br/>Stare into the abyss long enough and it might just stare back... we're going looking for riches and something down there doesn't want to share! Have gun, dig gravel, and make sure the mines don't collapse upon you as you defend yourselves from the creepy crawlies that lurk within...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_3.gif?t=1702026390"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_features.png?t=1702026390"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break ground on a bustling SteamWorld town, inspired by the Old West.<br/></li><li>Keep your steambots from getting cranky by ensuring their complex needs get met<br/></li><li>Dig deep and spread wide to produce resources to aid your search for ancient technologies<br/></li><li>Defend your mine from the creepy varmints that lurk deep below your town<br/></li><li>Trade resources at the local train stop and welcome special visitors who'll lend a hand<br/></li><li>Five distinct maps littered with secrets for the discerning SteamWorld explorer to find<br/></li><li>Developed from the ground up for both mouse and controller, whichever takes yer fancy.<br/></li><li>Four difficulty levels, including a sandbox difficulty for when you just want to Build!</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinball M</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2337640/Pinball_M/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-1.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-2.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free<br/>- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage<br/>- Thrilling competition<br/>- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation<h2 class="bb_tag">Sink your teeth into these tables as purchasable DLC: </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">- Chucky's Killer Pinball:</h2> Step into a twisted realm where the innocent becomes sinister, and the playful turns menacing. Navigate through an eerie playfield where Chucky lurks in the shadows, ready to pounce.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Dead by Daylight™️ Pinball:</h2> Become the hunter or even the hunted in a thrilling fusion of classic pinball and the excitement of one of the most popular horror games ever created.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Duke Nukem's Big Shot Pinball:</h2> Enjoy the biggest, grooviest, most BADASS pinball table ever made packed with guns and babes. Push start and play with balls of steel!<h2 class="bb_tag">- The Thing Pinball: </h2>Use your pinball skills and battle against the shape-shifting alien through the arctic chill of U.S. Outpost #31. Can you trust anyone, even yourself?<br/>- Even more coming...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-4.png?t=1701703297"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1702747783"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few Nights More: Genesis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713070/Few_Nights_More_Genesis/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Please note: This is a free prologue and it includes act 1, and only 1 playable character and blood school is playable, The maximum heritage gained is limited to 50, and the maximum difficulty can be set to 2. As well only one castle will be available. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Blood3.gif?t=1703099053"><br/><br/><strong>Conquer castles and claim your birthright!</strong><br/> <br/>The fight to reclaim your place in this world begins. Rebuild lost ruins, make them stronger and defend them against your enemies. After you regain your strength, move on to conquer more territories and eventually claim your birthright.<br/><br/>Few Nights More offers the unique fusing of castle management and turn based rogue-like combat. Fight against humanity, the undisputed masters of this world in your absence. Choose between eight different Vampire Lords, each with their own ambition and history. Find your trinkets, skills and perks along your way. Design your very own castle by placing the right rooms, adding decors that directly contribute to your army and your Vampire Lord. Conquer more castles so your influence and power grow, until you claim your birthright.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Ferocity3.gif?t=1703099053"><br/><br/><strong>Core Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Design your castle by adding new Rooms, Traps and Minions. Stack up on some buffs with shiny decors to get ready for the invasion screen to defend it to the end of every night!<br/> <br/></li><li> Choose among 7 different Vampire Lords with unique History, Gameplay and Abilities.<br/> <br/></li><li> Master 1 out of 3 Disciplines each time you play, each with 60 unique skills.<br/> <br/></li><li> Acquire new random skills, perks and trinkets to survive the nights.<br/> <br/></li><li> Excel in either being a Prestigious Vampire, a Seductive one, or master a Terrifying presence against your enemies.<br/><br/></li><li> Test the builds you made against a variety of Hunters, Veterans and Unique Bosses in an action packed turn based combat system.<br/> <br/></li><li> Endure three acts across 12 difficulty levels, striving to survive and progress. Accumulate Heritage Points to enhance your lord's starting stats, skills, and unlock new castles and talents unique to each lord.<br/><br/></li><li> Engage in the boundless challenge of Infinity Mode, where you can continuously test your limits without relying on a castle. Each night, you will be presented with three options to advance, growing stronger as you push yourself to see how far you can go.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Girls</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2722570/Christmas_Girls/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722570/extras/vvv.png?t=1703095815"><br/>It's Christmas time! Everyone is looking forward to it, including our girls! They have already put on their Christmas hats, so they are ready! Find all the gifts and don't get trapped.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722570/extras/1-2.gif?t=1703095815"><br/><br/>In the game, your goal is to collect gifts and not get trapped. Solve the puzzles in the correct order and collect all the gifts!🎁<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722570/extras/zzz.png?t=1703095815"><h2 class="bb_tag">Special Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎄   Well-drawn backgrounds and CGs<br/></li><li>❄️   Live2D dynamic character<br/></li><li>🥂   Christmas mood<br/></li><li>⛄   CG Gallery Mode<br/></li><li>🎅   Relaxing music<br/></li><li>🎁   Puzzle game</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OG Puzzlers: Fall 2K23</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2714900/OG_Puzzlers_Fall_2K23/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2714900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>OG Puzzlers: Fall 2K23</strong> is an casual puzzel game stunning images of coloured leafs made in fall 2023. You have to assemble a single image from random generated indivdual pieces. <br/>Combine all of the smart singel frames into one big image and unlock the next level.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 12 Levels<br/></li><li> 4x4 frames<br/></li><li> casual puzzle adventure<br/></li><li> auto saving<br/></li><li> simple mouse control<br/></li><li> 100 steam awards</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OG Memory:  Fall 2K23</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2715000/OG_Memory__Fall_2K23/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>OG Memory: Fall 2K23</strong> is an casual memory game with stunning leafs images made in Fall 2023. You have to find all of the correct pairs to complete the game. your best round will be count and always be displayed in game, to compare your rounds. try to reduce your turns every game and set up your new record.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 12 stunning different memory cards<br/></li><li> 24 memory cards in total<br/></li><li> casual memory adventure<br/></li><li> auto saving<br/></li><li> count of ur best round<br/></li><li> simple mouse control<br/></li><li> 100 steam awards</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolls</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2335220/Dolls/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2335220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Escape from this dark dimension and return to reality!</h2><br/>On an ordinary day, a student is suddenly and mysteriously transported to a parallel reality: an abandoned place immersed in darkness. Surrounded by sinister dolls and with no sign of human life, her mission is clear: find a way out of this nightmare and return to the real world.<br/><br/>"Dolls" is a first-person horror game that immerses the player in a dark environment filled with dimly lit corridors and disturbing sounds. Discover the hidden secrets in this macabre setting and unravel the mysteries behind this terrifying experience.<br/><br/><br/><strong>Be careful in the dark, there may be beings who do not welcome your presence!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2335220/extras/GifDolls01.gif?t=1703093635"><br/>Amidst the shadows and wreckage of this abandoned place, it is essential to remain vigilant, as dangerous creatures roam the dark corridors, sensing your presence. Proceed with extreme caution and avoid looking back at all costs.<br/><br/><br/><strong>Try to escape as quickly as possible before going insane in the darkness.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2335220/extras/GifDolls02.gif?t=1703093635"><br/>Explore the darkness, solve puzzles, and run to find an exit, but this won't be an easy task, as the inhabitants of this dimension are keenly aware of your presence!<br/><br/><br/><strong>And uncover all the secrets of this shadowy place.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2335220/extras/GifDolls03.gif?t=1703093635"><br/>What is this place? Who are these dolls? How did I end up here? Embark on the exploration and unravel the mysteries of this dark reality while searching for an exit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>See the game world through the eyes of the main character, providing an immersive first-person experience.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Enjoy a heavy and ominous atmosphere that keeps the tension at its peak, immersing you in horror.</li></ul> <ul class="bb_ul"><li>Navigate detailed environments and explore eerie locations to uncover secrets and find essential items.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Immersive and unsettling sounds heighten the suspense and fear throughout the game.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Uncover a compelling story while unraveling the mysteries of the alternate reality.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OG Memory: Kira Maus</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713940/OG_Memory_Kira_Maus/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>OG Memory: Kira Maus</strong> is an casual memory game with cute dog images. You have to find all of the correct pairs to complete the game. your best round will be count and always be displayed in game, to compare your rounds. try to reduce your turns every game and set up your new record.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 12 stunning different memory cards<br/></li><li> 24 memory cards in total<br/></li><li> casual memory adventure<br/></li><li> auto saving<br/></li><li> count of ur best round<br/></li><li> simple mouse control<br/></li><li> 100 steam awards</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Present</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2694380/The_First_Present/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							For this christmas you want to please your mother with the greatest gift. A piece of meat is a highly sought-after present in this medieval era.<br/>Explore the forest, find what you are looking for and get back home. Easy until a supernatural entity starts to be curious about you !<br/>The forest starts to change, reshaping to the will of this entity. It wants to play with you, it wants to hunt you.<br/>You better be cautious with each of your movements and find something to protect yourself !<br/><br/><strong>Mechanics:</strong><br/><br/>The core gameplay will alternate between free roam and point and click style.<br/>Good reflexes and decision making are the keys to surviving the night !<br/><br/><strong>Levels:</strong><br/><br/>Once the night starts to fall, you will have to go throught 4 levels.<br/>Each level has the same common objective, upgrade your toy !<br/>But they also have a unique quirk to them !<br/>You will have to find the best strategy for all differents levels.<br/><br/><strong>Challlenge yourself:</strong><br/><br/>You will be able to unlock multiple endings.<br/>They all have their own diffculty, if you are up for the challenge !						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diabetor &amp; The Sugar Monsters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2589490/Diabetor__The_Sugar_Monsters/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2589490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							DIABETOR AND THE SUGAR MONSTERS!<br>
Diabetor was wreaking havoc on diabetics across the nation. He convinced diabetics it was healthy to eat high carb diets and it was destroying their A1C causing horrible complications and unhealthy lifestyles. The world needed a hero, and it came in the form of a middle-aged husband and father named Spencer. Years ago, he read a book that held the secret on how to defeat Diabetor. He first used this knowledge to reverse his diabetic complications and lower his A1C from 7.1 to 4.7. With his newly gained powers he became the Insulator! It was now time to defeat Diabetor and his evil sugar monsters!<br>
<br>
Diabetor and the sugar monsters puts you in direct control of fighting the sugar monsters using you insulin launcher. Learn about what foods are good for you to consume and beat through a multitude of enemies, levels, and bosses in this action packed adventure! Diabetor and the sugar monsters was initially released as an educational game for the game boy and it is now reaching new audiences as a stand alone PC game! The goal is to teach people about their Diabetes in a way that is fun and not very hard. Learn facts about Diabetes such as what foods are healthy for your diet and goals to trying to avoid sweets. <br>
<br>
Expect to fight through 8 completely diverse worlds and defeat 6 bosses that represent the sugar monsters. In the end you will battle Diabetor himself to save the world!						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kitty Survivors: Rogues of Catmere</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2217740/Kitty_Survivors_Rogues_of_Catmere/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2217740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2217740/extras/Gameplay_Gif.gif?t=1703099814"><br/><br/>On Kitty Survivors you play as members of a cat guild hired to protect the Kingdom of Catmere. Fight off hordes of cursed creatures in a land of magic, explosions and of course… KITTENS! Try to survive long enough to find yourself face to face with your greatest enemy, the great Dr. Walter Spray.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build you way to victory</h2>Choose several combinations of perks and try to find the perfect one for you! You might want to give birth to a kitten that will aid you in battle or perhaps you want to get explosive diarrhea to obliterate your enemies. It's all up to you!<h2 class="bb_tag">The Forge</h2>A wooden trunk, a dwarf beard and a muscular chinchilla, what do those things have in common? Well, in the wrong hands, nothing, but you’re an experienced blacksmith that can use anything you want to forge the ultimate weapon!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2217740/extras/Forge_Gif.gif?t=1703099814"><h2 class="bb_tag">Pets</h2>You can obtain eggs in your runs and hatch them to receive loyal companions. Use them in battle, feed them apples and watch them evolve into their ultimate form!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2217740/extras/Evolution_Gif.gif?t=1703099814"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Auto and manual options for firing and aiming<br/></li><li>Runs that can be done in 15 minutes<br/></li><li>Unique builds every run<br/></li><li>Characters with different skills<br/></li><li>Pets with leveling system and evolutions<br/></li><li>Weapon crafting, with over a thousand combinations<br/></li><li>Six types of weapons: Bow, Staff, Boomerang, Minigun, Shotgun and Fish<br/></li><li>Unique and funny perks<br/></li><li>Elites and Bosses<br/></li><li>Permanent upgrades</li></ul><br/>Thanks for reaching this far! I'm a solo indie developer and I really appreciate your interest in my game! Defeat creatures, try different builds, have fun. Oh, and don’t forget to share it with your friends! Anyway, thank you again and I hope you have a great day!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>o---o</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287040/oo/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An arcade game styled after classic titles of the first generation of consoles. Gameplay set in the cybernetic sphere, accompanied by electronic music matching the game's visuals.<br>
You are the result of a project code-named O---O, an alter-ego, a mechanical expression of your soul particle. You travel through the corridors of digital reality in order to annihilate the enemy of the system.<br>
The main rule of the game is not to die. Each time the core comes into contact with an object, you are destroyed, which means you return to the last checkpoint. The number of lives for each location is limited.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue Slime</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2723590/Rogue_Slime/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Note:</strong><br/><i>Parts of this games revenue goes to charity. Check under the description</i><br/>Dive into the squishy world of "Rogue Slime," an adventurous journey of a unique slime character in a visually rich, isometric 2D roguelike world. In this action-packed game, players guide a brave little slime through labyrinthine dungeons, encountering a variety of enemies and mysterious environments.<br/><br/>"Rogue Slime" is a randomly generated action-adventure game with a twist of roguelike elements. As you control the main character, a slime with the ability to shoot slime balls, you navigate through an ever-changing landscape filled with challenges and surprises. The game features a collection of passive and active items, each offering unique effects and abilities to power up your slime, and powerups that are earned through leveling.<br/><br/>Each playthrough offers a new experience with varied items, enemies, and room layouts. Players will find themselves captivated by the dynamic gameplay and the depth of strategy required to progress through the game's engaging levels. Will you evolve and adapt, overcoming the odds to guide your slime to victory?<br/><br/>Embark on this slimy adventure and uncover the secrets of "Rogue Slime," where every play is a unique dive into an ever-evolving dungeon of delight and danger!<br/><br/><strong>Charity</strong><br/>The author of this game has been helping out in the Ukraine war, working as a volunteer doing humanitarian work.<br/>Because of this, half of the revenue of this game will be donated towards helping those most effected by the horrible effects of war.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garten of Banban 6</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2499800/Garten_of_Banban_6/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Explore the forgotten levels of Banban’s Kindergarten. Survive the new terrors that reside below. Uncover the truth behind the place, and find the whereabouts of your missing child…</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/extras/all.gif?t=1703084211"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive the never-entered levels of Banban’s Kindergarten:</h2>After the events of Garten of Banban 4, you are forced to run away and delve even deeper into the mysterious establishment that is Banban’s kindergarten. You are heading down to where no human dares to be.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/extras/corner.gif?t=1703084211"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/extras/fly.gif?t=1703084211"><h2 class="bb_tag">No more friends to make…</h2>You have run out of friends to make. From now on, you only meet new enemies who will make sure you never feel alone! In Banban’s Kindergarten, there are enemies to be made in every corner!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/extras/fall.gif?t=1703084211"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/extras/liminal.gif?t=1703084211"><br/><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/intent/user?screen_name=Euphoric_Bros" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/extras/TwitterNew.png?t=1703084211"/></a><br/><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@EuphoricBrothers?sub_confirmation=1" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2499800/extras/YoutubeNew.png?t=1703084211"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Ship Survivor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2714510/Star_Ship_Survivor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2714510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							When player start survive, can move with igniting engines. Ship can move all direction(using arrow keys or 'w,a,s,d' keys) but can't rotate. When ships contact with other blocks(not enemies's blocks) this blocks will dock with player's ship. Blocks are 3 types, protect, attack, support. Protect type block will protect from enemy's attack. Attack type block will attack enemy's block automatically. And certain timed, station will generate. Ship will attack this station too and if station destroyed, some blocks will generate randomly. Support type blocks are just support ship automatically.<br>
Certain timed, enemy boss will generate. This enemy is very powerful. If your ship destroyed, don't worry. Your surviving action will upgrade your level and this level will reinforce your start block mass.<br>
Survive. You can do it.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lazarus A.D. 2222</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2451460/Lazarus_AD_2222/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Immerse yourself in a dystopian world where humanity, as a result of its actions, has brought the planet to the brink of contamination. You live in a city built above the clouds of radioactive dust, devoid of a sense of purpose, participating in yet another "Groundhog Day" of the main character. Your task is to descend beneath the surface of the city to repair the autonomous system that ensures the functioning of the city's inhabitants. Is it just another routine malfunction, or will today be the day that changes you forever? It's time to answer the question of what your path and truth are.<br>
<br>
Hand-drawn graphics<br>
One of the unique features of our game is hand-drawn graphics. In the age of artificial intelligence, games created from AI-generated assets and photos, we have prepared hand-drawn graphics, scenes, and animations that create a unique atmosphere in Lazarus. An exceptional game deserves exceptional visuals, and Lazarus delivers just that. Your gameplay is the result of a significant amount of our time and energy. After all, what wouldn't we do for a loyal player?<br>
<br>
Immerse yourself in the game atmosphere<br>
We have prepared a approximately 2-hour-long story written in a language that allows you to enter the body and mind of the main character. You will encounter both childish, humorous conversations and internal dialogues, as well as a serious quest for the meaning of life and purpose in this world.<br>
<br/>
Make choices<br/>
Make choices that will impact the further gameplay. Do you believe in the butterfly effect? If so, you have the option to experience it firsthand during the gameplay.<br/>
<br/>
Different layers of gameplay<br/>
You can experience the game on different levels, allowing you to play it multiple times without feeling bored. It's not obvious at first glance, so if you're looking for something more in games, you will find a hidden message and a parallel story here. This doesn't mean you can't focus solely on the main storyline of the game and interpret it literally. That's one of the magical elements of Lazarus.<br/>
<br/>
Achievements<br/>
Achievement Hunter, we have prepared Achievements that will enrich your collection. Of course, not all of them will be easy to obtain. In the end, you will be able to compare yourself in this regard against other players in "Lazarus a.d. 2222". Are you up for the challenge of unlocking all the Achievements?<br/>
<br/>
Mini-games<br/>
At certain moments, it's worth taking a break from the main story and playing mini-games that add variety to the gameplay. Show off your wit, agility, and logical thinking by playing mini-games.<br/>
<br/>
Gamepad support<br/>
In Lazarus, you can play with a gamepad. If you have played with a gamepad, let us know if you enjoyed the game's controls on it.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journey To The Wand</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693470/Journey_To_The_Wand/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Journey To The Wand" is a challenging platform game with anime-style graphics.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693470/extras/steamlogo.png?t=1703080082"><br/><br/>Story:<br/><br/>In a village, there lived a wizard named Elowen. Elowen gazed at the clouds through her window as she slept at night, and when she woke up in the morning, she wanted to cast a spell and fly into the clouds with her wand. She performed the spell, took her wand with her, and just as she was about to fly into the clouds, her spell failed. Elowen remained on Earth, while her wand, along with some earthly objects, flew into the clouds. Elowen embarked on a journey using her human abilities to retrieve her wand.<br/><br/><br/>Main Features of the Game:<br/><br/>Challenging Platforms: Players will navigate Elowen through various challenging platforms, requiring jumps, runs, and climbs.<br/><br/>Graphics and Atmosphere: The game captivates the player with high-quality anime-style graphics and atmosphere.<br/><br/>Various Traps: The game consists of levels not only with straightforward objects but also with physical features and objects with various movements, creating diverse and dynamic challenges.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kill Santa</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2712410/Kill_Santa/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Santa and his helpers are threatening to sabotage Christmas and it's your job to teach him a lesson! Grab as many weapons as possible and kill all his helpers. Follow Santa throughout the world and kill him when you get the chance! Beware he has a lot of body doubles threatening to derail your mission!<br/><br/>Features<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Single-Player story mode! Chase Santa through different levels and kill the real one to win!</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Lot's of fun weapons scattered across every level.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Have fun blowing up Santa's helpers with an RPG</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freeplay maps let you run around with guns and kill Santa</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finite State Automaton Challenges 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2681980/Finite_State_Automaton_Challenges_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2681980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Finite State Automaton Challenges 2. It is the second episode of Finite State Automation Challenges. In this game, you will play with the simplest automaton model, Finite State Automaton, and use it to cope with 40 challenges from variants of the previous episode, character string manipulation, computer science, and mathematics.<br/><br/>If you are unfamiliar with Finite State Automaton, We highly recommend playing <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2629030" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2629030</a> first or learning Finite State Automaton online in advance.  <br/><br/><u>The criterion for judging whether it is suitable to play this game is whether you can answer the following question</u>:<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2681980/extras/aaauto.jpg?t=1703074122"><br/>The above picture shows a finite-state automaton. The first state with two colors denotes that it is both a beginning and accepting state. So, what is the pattern of strings accepted by this automaton?<h2 class="bb_tag">Two Major Updates</h2>We're making the game even more challenging and fun by introducing two major updates:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A state can be both beginning and accepting.<br/></li><li>Some challenges require you to create a deterministic automaton (thanks for the suggestions from players), which means:<br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>There is at most one begin state.<br/> </li><li>Empty edges are not allowed, i.e., each edge must contain at least one character.<br/> </li><li>For a character, a state can transit to at most one state, i.e., no conflict edges.<br/> </li></ul></li></ul>Besides, we add red spots to denote each challenge's difficulty so that you can take your own route through the challenges.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micro macro farm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2685810/Micro_macro_farm/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Start planting seeds and watching them grow on your small garden, while you do other things.<br/>Harvest and produce items to gain money and experience. Use this money to unlock new seeds, buy machines or even expand your garden.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>25+ Seeds / Plants<br/></li><li>8+ Machines<br/></li><li>30+ Recipes<br/></li><li>Level progression<br/></li><li>Idle gaming</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">PLANT SEEDS AND WATCH THEM GROW</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685810/extras/PlantAndGrow.gif?t=1703069723"><h2 class="bb_tag">COOK AND PRODUCE DELICIOUS FOOD</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685810/extras/Cooking.gif?t=1703069723"><h2 class="bb_tag">SELL PRODUCTS TO GAIN MONEY AND EXPERIENCE</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685810/extras/OrderTableSteam.gif?t=1703069723"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Mage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2333420/Dungeon_Mage/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2333420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Collect, fight, explore, craft, build and venture deeper: The dungeon is a dangerous place and harbors countless evils trying to lay waste to you while you are uncovering the secrets of the structures within. Carve out your place within the ecosystem of the dungeon, unravelling its mysteries, engaging in thrilling combat or even kicking your feet up while you fish for long forgotten treasure. Manifest yourself in the dungeon - you just have to be strong enough to do so.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2333420/extras/6.png?t=1703068739"><br/><br/>This free community-driven dungeon exploration game features a vast amount of content to explore, tons of enemies to defeat and countless items to obtain. Our community's contribution is helping the game reach its full potential by continously providing feedback, contributing ideas and play-testing the on-going free updates this game receives.<br/><br/>Are you ready to face the dungeon on your own?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2333420/extras/10.png?t=1703068739"><br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/>- Fast-Paced Combat<br/>- Combing Items For Powerful Weapons<br/>- Dungeon Fishing<br/>- Randomized Exploration<br/>- Free Content Updates<br/><br/>Credits to:<br/><br/>- Programming: greenpixels<br/>- Art: greenpixels, ePics, RunninBlood, Anokolisa, LYASeeK, Penusbmic, Elthen's Pixel Art Shop, unTied Games<br/>- Audio: Paninjin, Abstraction, Ancient Games, MakotoHiramatsu<br/>- Helper Assets: GMLive, Post-Processing FX						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BossHunter VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2439730/BossHunter_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2439730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embrace an entirely new dimension of gaming with BossHunter VR, where you are not just a player, but a commanding force in a world teeming with formidable foes. This immersive, cutting-edge virtual reality experience serves as the first version of the game that pushes the boundaries of the VR gaming landscape.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2439730/extras/Boss_Hunter_Trim__4_.gif?t=1703079041"><br/><br/>Set in a universe where danger lurks at every turn, BossHunter VR challenges you to confront and conquer a variety of unique and intriguing adversaries. The thrill of the hunt is palpable in this game, where each enemy encounter is a test of your strategy, skill, and strength. With each boss you defeat, you'll uncover deeper layers of the game's rich narrative and immersive environments.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2439730/extras/monkey_shoot.gif?t=1703079041"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2439730/extras/rampage.gif?t=1703079041"><br/><br/>However, what truly sets BossHunter VR apart is its ground-breaking voice command mechanic. Imagine shouting a command and your weapon responding in kind. This feature allows you to directly control your weaponry using your voice. Whether you're ordering a swift sword strike or commanding a gun to fire a hail of bullets, your words become a powerful tool in your battle arsenal. This innovative mechanic heightens the sense of immersion and involvement, taking the interactivity of VR to the next level.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2439730/extras/sevarog.gif?t=1703079041"><br/><br/>In BossHunter VR, you're not just a player in the game—you're a part of the game. You'll feel the rush of adrenaline as you charge into battle, the satisfaction of outsmarting a tough opponent, and the triumph of watching a powerful boss fall before your might. With the game's advanced graphics and physics engine, every explosion, sword clash, and bullet fired feels incredibly real and satisfying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2439730/extras/arrow_shoot.gif?t=1703079041"><br/><br/>The first version of the game serves as a shining example of the potential of VR gaming, showcasing advanced mechanics and features that could shape the future of the industry. BossHunter VR is not just a game; it's an experience that will captivate, challenge, and thrill you in equal measure.<br/><br/>Prepare to step into a world where your voice carries power, where every fight is a pulse-pounding dance of death, and where only the strongest will survive. Welcome to the thrilling, immersive universe of BossHunter VR. This is not just virtual reality; this is reality redefined.<br/><br/>Please note: This is the first version of the game, we highly value your feedback. Your thoughts, suggestions, and criticisms will help us refine and improve BossHunter VR, bringing it closer to the ultimate VR gaming experience we strive to provide.<br/><br/>Are you ready to make your mark in the world of BossHunter VR? Strap on your headset, grab your weapons and prepare to command like never before. The hunt is on!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER LIFTPIA</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2725080/SUPER_LIFTPIA/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pick up the enemy and throw it!<br>
This is an action game drawn with dots that gives you a nostalgic feel.<br>
The difficulty level is set to low.<br>
<br>
The main character of this game, Lifton, is skilled at "lifting up" his enemies.<br>
If you step on an enemy and flip them over, you can lift them up.<br>
Enemies can be lifted up in two layers.<br/>
<br/>
The lifted enemy can be swapped up and down with the up key. And you can throw the enemies in the lower row by pressing the X key.<br/>
If you lift a specific enemy, that enemy may exhibit mysterious abilities.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
*This game does not use any text other than the title and staff roll.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rallyallyally</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1830540/Rallyallyally/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1830540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Rallyallyally is a chaotic, local multi-player, party racing game where you compete with other drivers to roll out the road, carve up the landscape and decide the route to the finish line. As the leader of the race, you’re in control of the track, you decide the path to victory. But to hold on to that lead you’ll need to use your skill, reflexes, and a giant boxing glove on a spring. Mostly the boxing glove. <br/><br/><i>Some people go where the road leads them, others make their own paths.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1830540/extras/road.gif?t=1703063447"><br/>Make your own tracks. No pre-made courses in this game, that’s your job (if you’re fast enough)!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1830540/extras/multiplayer.gif?t=1703063447"><br/>Play with up to 8 players on one screen!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1830540/extras/cars.gif?t=1703063447"><br/>Obviously. And they’ve all got wheels! There are 15 different cars to drive, from monster trucks to double decker buses, tractors to sports cars.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1830540/extras/customisation.gif?t=1703063447"><br/>Change your car’s appearance to suit you, choosing between colours, decals, rims and more. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1830540/extras/powerups.gif?t=1703063447"><br/>Loads of powerups! Like a big boxing glove or even a grappling hook, just make sure you use them at the right moment!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DARK FOREST</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693340/DARK_FOREST/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dark forest; It is a TPS (Third Person Shooter) survival game that aims to find a lost treasure by fighting mutant wolves, legendary guards and mythological beings.<br/><br/><br/>You are struggling alone. Are at middle of forest where no one can give you a hand. There is nobody besides you. A forest nobody dare to get there, even if they do so, they can't go out of forest alive. It is that kind of mysterious forest that you are looking for a treasure, in order to find it you clashing with gods, guards and mutant living beings in it. Your bravery will lead the way.<h2 class="bb_tag">Story Mode</h2><br/><br/>A treasure that has been lost for centuries… a treasure guarded by the god Horus and destroyed by any being that dared to approach! 20 different traces were identified, almost all of them were visited, but no results were obtained from anywhere. But only in one place! A god awaits you at the end of the adventure in this forest, which is full of mutant wolves and where legendary invincible warrior guards are found when you delve into its depths. The god Horus can only be defeated with the legendary sword, and with this sword he can kill a god only in the hands of the chosen one. The most important condition for success in this adventure is to be the chosen one for the treasure. So are you that chosen one? If you believe that you are the chosen one, the Dark Forest awaits the owner of the treasure. You have to overcome the mutant wolves, fight the guards and finally win a relentless fight with the god Horus, the guardian of the treasure.<h2 class="bb_tag">Fight to live</h2><br/><br/>Gods, Guardians and Mutant wolves. Destroy them all. You must survive in this jungle.<h2 class="bb_tag">Weapons</h2><br/><br/>Pistol, rifle, machete, knife and legendary sword. This sword can even kill a god.<h2 class="bb_tag">Realistic Weather</h2><br/><br/>Real weather and rain effect. You will feel like you are at home.<h2 class="bb_tag">High-End Graphics</h2><br/><br/>Realistic images make you feel like you're in the game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil Coin</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2724810/Oil_Coin/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A game in which you need to explore new oil fields. For this you will have different ways, such as moles, geologists and so on. Build towers, oil storages, pump your production, improve buildings and warehouses. Hire workers, guards, fight off or buy off raiders. Buy new lands. <br>
<br>
Features:<br>
<br>
-enjoyable graphics;<br>
-simple controls;<br>
-interesting gameplay;<br>
- light music;<br/>
- unforgettable adventures;						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orbius</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2704720/Orbius/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704720/extras/orbiusHeaderCapsule.png?t=1703059258"><br/><br/>You start with the ability to drop 4 orbs of varying sizes. Anytime an orb touches another of the same orb, a newer, bigger orb is created, and your score is increased. But as your score increases, you must choose between multiple spells that make the game even more difficult. Spells that increase orb sizes, cause explosions, or force you to destroy existing orbs are what make this game feel different every new playthrough.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cover Yourself in Blood</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2725460/Cover_Yourself_in_Blood/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>blood</strong> floats on <strong>blood</strong><br/><br/>1) wait for it to <strong>blood</strong><br/><br/>2) cover yourself in <strong>blood</strong><br/><br/>3) <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725460/extras/troldge.jpg?t=1703059253"><br/><br/>Cult classic 3D horror parody game, now on Steam!<br/><br/>With now <strong>skins</strong> featuring "The NecroCat", "Long Toe", "The Grand Stroker", "Flame Face", "KirbyPeter", and more to equip and "Cover Yourself in Blood".<br/><br/>Break your high score because the game now has <strong>achievements</strong> and a brand new <strong>leaderboard</strong>!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titan Revenge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2697890/Titan_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>[Unlock Equipment Sets for a Rapid Growth]</strong><br/>Class Advancement will offer you more equipment slots and equipment sets. Every equipment can be enhanced, polished, and strengthened further with Lucky Binding and Superb Promotion. Exclusive attributes and set appearances will also be available when all equipment of the set is collected.<br/><br/><strong>[Hundreds of Customization Options]</strong><br/>There are hundreds of beautiful skins of different styles in Titan Revenge. Show your personality by customizing your avatar and "dressing up" your character, pets, mounts, artifacts, and putting on the Hagios and the Necro Barrier! Be reborn to the amaze of all and awake your inner power!<br/><br/><strong>[Ideal Drop Rate for Valuables]</strong><br/>The drop rate of the Superb equipment in the game is fair for everyone. Titan Revenge distinguishes itself from other games by having a unique Boss reward mechanic: Equipment, skins for wings, pets and artifacts all have a good chance to drop in the battle. The more bosses you challenge, the more you get! In addition, you will be also rewarded with equipment and skins by participating in events and by completing the main quests, VIP quests in the early stage.<br/><br/><strong>[Recycle Repeated Equipment]</strong><br/>Repeated low-end equipment can be recycled for in-game currency in the Inventory. The repeated high-end equipment can be consumed to increase the success rate of the Superb Promotion for the equipment in use. In short, every equipment has a purpose. Challenge Bosses often to get more!<br/><br/><strong>[Ethereal System]</strong><br/>Transform yourself into an Angel or a Titan to unleash powerful skills. Both your damage and HP will be incredibly increased! Transforming at the right time can turn the tide of battle at a critical moment.<br/><br/><strong>[A Magical Social World]</strong><br/>You can build relationship with other players through multiple social systems: Destiny, Friends, and Alliance. In the game you are allowed to marry another player, or team up and assist others in battles. Get tired of solo gameplay? Start your journey in Titan Revenge!<br/><br/><strong>[Classic and Creative Gameplay]</strong><br/>This adventure is accompanied by an exciting story! Choose your class: Knight, Mage, or Archer, and hone your skills to earn yourself a place in this magical world. Archangel Sword, Special Ring, and the Dragonslayer gear can help you boost your BR significantly.<br/><br/><strong>[Thrilling Battles]</strong><br/>Take part in thrilling battles in Cross-server Arena, Imperial War, and Archangel War. There are multiple battle modes available, including 1v1, Guild battles, and Cross-server Faction battles. You can team up in real time and use the advantages of each class wisely to win, or fight solo to the top of the throne.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ep.家族</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2583920/Ep/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2583920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Gameplay:<br/>first-person exploration game that focuses on a family living in Japan who have encountered unfortunate events, with the daughter of the family as the protagonist.<br/><br/>Story:<br/>The family, consisting of a father, mother, and the daughter (the player character), has encountered a series of unfortunate events that have drastically changed them. As the player, it falls upon you to guide this altered family in what you believe to be the right direction.<br/><br/>Eerie Music:<br/>The in-game music and sound design intensify the player's sense of unease, further amplifying the fear factor.<br/><br/>Pursuit of Fear:<br/>[Ep. 家族] strives to immerse players in a chilling experience. Unique fear-inducing elements are strategically placed throughout the game, keeping players on their toes.<br/><br/>Player Choices:<br/>The story and ending of the game can be altered based on the choices players make. There are two different endings to uncover.<br/><br/>Setting:<br/>The game is set in Japan, offering players a unique cultural backdrop for the horror experience.<br/><br/>Streaming and Let's Plays:<br/>Players are encouraged to stream, record, and share their gameplay experiences of [Ep. 家族] with others.<br/><br/>Please note that [Ep. 家族] is designed to provide players with a gripping and unsettling horror experience. Player choices will shape the narrative and ultimately lead to one of two distinct endings. Are you prepared to confront the terrors that await in this Japanese household?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triadino</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1579270/Triadino/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1579270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1579270/extras/Triadino_Logo.gif?t=1703049476"><br/><br/>Triadino is a casual puzzle game inspired by Tetris and Rock-Paper-Scissors. This game is played with randomly generated triplets (triominos) of three different types of blocks: Rock, Paper and Scissors. The unique interactions between different block types upon placement make the game more interesting and challenging.<br/><br/>Like in Tetris, the triomino generated in each turn will fall to the bottom of the game board, and the player can move and rotate the triomino so that it can be placed in a particular position and orientation upon reaching existing blocks.<br/><br/>However unlike in Tetris, upon placement on existing blocks, additional operations will take place between triomino blocks and the blocks below them. Based on the block types, the triomino blocks may cancel out or replace the blocks below them, and after block cancellation, the remaining block(s) may further fall down.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1579270/extras/Triadino_Placement.gif?t=1703049476"><br/><br/>Triadino has three game modes: Casual, Regular and Challenging, plus two leveling up modes: Line Clearing and Full Clearing. These modes determine the falling speed of the triominos and the speed increment when the game levels up. They also determine the number of rows of initial blocks generated in the Full Clearing level up mode.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1579270/extras/Triadino_Solo.gif?t=1703049476"><br/><br/>Triadino can be played in either the single player (Solo) mode or the double player (Dual) mode. The Dual mode can be played by two players on the same computer with a shared screen, or on different computers within the same intranet. The Dual mode has two sub-modes: Parallel and Adversarial. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1579270/extras/Triadino_Dual.gif?t=1703049476"><br/><br/>Triadino supports two types of computer players: Easy and Hard. One can choose to play against a computer player, or let one computer player to play by itself, or let two computer players to play against each other just for fun.<br/><br/>Enjoy the game! Also the game provides a number of nicely animated backgrounds for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1579270/extras/Triadino_Animation_Plankton.gif?t=1703049476"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1579270/extras/Triadino_Animation_Ribbon.gif?t=1703049476"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1579270/extras/Triadino_Animation_Reflection.gif?t=1703049476"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stealth Blade</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2538160/Stealth_Blade/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2538160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Stealth Blade is a dark-style side-scrolling action game. The protagonist you play needs to pass numerous tests, avoid traps, and instantly kill the devil's minions to avenge his wife and save his son.<br/><br/>On the road to revenge, you need to continuously improve your skills, strengthen your attributes, and collect various props to help you kill enemies more efficiently.<h2 class="bb_tag">Use your katana to instantly kill all enemies in front of you</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2538160/extras/GIF.gif?t=1703044064"><h2 class="bb_tag">Beware of deadly traps, any contact will result in instant death</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2538160/extras/陷阱GIF.gif?t=1703044064"><h2 class="bb_tag">Kill the flying dragon to get extra rewards</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2538160/extras/护盾GIF.gif?t=1703044064"><h2 class="bb_tag">Strengthen yourself from multiple dimensions</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2538160/extras/技能展示.gif?t=1703044064"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phantom Vortex VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2705330/Phantom_Vortex_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2705330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2705330/extras/A_VR06.jpg?t=1703042797"><br/>Phantom Vortex VR is a hectic bullet hell filled with mayhem. Navigate the corridors of crafted levels and step into the other side of an ethereal world. Becoming a jiving phantom yourself.<br/>Features - Catch incoming projectiles and return them at your foes.<br/>Defeat a range of ghoulish adversaries with their own attack patterns.<br/>Face off against powerful bosses.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOCHI A GIRL</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2084740/MOCHI_A_GIRL/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2084740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2084740/extras/mochibura.gif?t=1703041249"><br/>Popular award-winning title!<br/>Japan Game Awards Under-18 Division Gold Prize<br/>Unity Inter High Grand Prize<br/>Xiamen International Animation Festival Game Art Award Grand Prize<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2084740/extras/stage1_movie.gif?t=1703041249"><br/>One button does everything from jumping to grappling with your trusty mochi whip in this exciting action game for all skill levels.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2084740/extras/stage6_movie.gif?t=1703041249"><br/>Torpedo through water, fire yourself like a cannonball, swing to dizzying heights, and more! Grab all the sushi and reach the goal to prove you’re the world’s best Mochi Girl!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conquest of Empires 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2542860/Conquest_of_Empires_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2542860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							[Game Bonuses]<br/><br/>The Early Access Test will open on December 20th. Enter the exchange code: COE888 in the game, and you can get 888 diamonds and 6 kinds of rare items. Join Conquest of Empires 2. Discover the charm of civilization, and enjoy the joy of conquest!<br/><br/>Royal Enlistment Order: Join the game and receive 28 powerful historical heroes, including Barbarossa, Louis IX, Alfred the Great, Queen of Sheba, Wu Zetian, Hannibal Barca, and Lancelot! Build an invincible army and conquer the world!<br/><br/>Building Upgrade Bonuses: Each time you upgrade a building, you will be rewarded with up to 3500 diamonds as well as various items, equipment, units, etc. to help you develop your empire!<br/><br/>Easy to Upgrade with Auto-Fight: 24 hours of automatic fight allows you to upgrade heroes and collect equipment easily, making your in-game adventures more relaxing and enjoyable!!<br/><br/>[Game Features]<br/><br/>Welcome to Conquest of Empires 2, an epic feast of strategy! This game is like an encyclopedia of ancient civilizations, where you will experience the rise and scramble of ancient civilizations.<br/><br/>In the game, you will become a city lord and choose one of the four great civilizations, namely China, Rome, Egypt or Persia, to start your own civilization. This game is not only a building simulation, but you also need to summon heroes and soldiers, skillfully combine all kinds of units and formations, and even fight against longer odds.<br/><br/>In addition, you can participate in a variety of missions, build houses, cultivate fields, operate forest farms, upgrade buildings and so on. Every time you complete a mission, you'll be rewarded with generous rewards. In Conquest of Empires 2, you will review the glory of history, fight with epic heroes and revive the glory of ancient cities. It is not only a numerical duel, but also the use of wisdom and strategy.<br/><br/>The game has no VIP privileges. We insist on fair competition, and focus on testing players' strategic intelligence and teamwork. We are committed to creating a user-friendly game, so that every player can easily enter the game, enjoy the glory of the ancient civilization, and feel the endless fun of conquest.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Got Crabs</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2695870/You_Got_Crabs/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2695870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You Got Crabs is a relaxing crab simulator that allows you to watch, and care for, crabs in different settings.<br>
<br>
Crabs<br>
Crabs are simple creatures. They require food and space to live, but not much else. They will roam around, eat plants or animals and breed with each other. Watch them grow and live their lives, or intervene with toys and new foods which can be found in crates that wash ashore.<br>
<br>
Evolution<br>
The crabs will evolve and their changes will affect their life cycles. The evolutionary processes are displayed by the color of the crab. A crab that has more red or orange will likely be able to handle heat better than a blue crab, for example. These traits are passed on to offspring, so they are able to adapt over time to changing environments. In the game, the player is able to modify the environments to force these changes.<br>
<br/>
Food<br/>
These particular crabs love to eat plants, particularly their specially formulated berries, but over time they may develop a taste for meat. If they do they will feast on the bodies of other dead crabs. If they never reach cannibalism, however, they may begin nibbling on the stalks that grow their special berries to gain extra nutrients. Be careful that they don't destroy the crop.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Pandas 熊猫在哪里</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2685220/Where_Pandas/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Search for 100 Pandas.<br/>A carefully hand drawn 4K scene filled with cute characters.<br/>The process is short and won't take up too much player time.<br/>You can choose your favorite dyeing for the convenience of color blind players.<br/>Extremely easy to achieve.<br/>Automatically save and read files.<br/>There is a local timer ranking.<br/>No punishment, easy and enjoyable.<br/>You can play games with family and friends on the same computer, suitable for all ages.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685220/extras/说明.jpg?t=1703071167"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire Guardian</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2690980/Fire_Guardian/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this great adventure, a resplendent being (Tolypeutes) acquires the power to face an army of mercenaries and rescue his brothers, reestablishing all sacred order.<br/>   The adventure takes place in the most varied settings to the sound of natural birds, insects, sea, winds, caves.<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Unlock combat animals (Pets) to help you.<br/></li><li>Change the shape of your body in ball mode and combat mode.<br/></li><li>Use your fists for close combat, and fire magic for ranged combat.<br/></li><li>Unlock: shields, weapons, pets. Improve your attributes: life, damage, shield time.<br/></li><li>Discover the secret passages.<br/></li><li>Adventure in forests, caves, cities, volcanic regions, industries, sewers, glaciers... to the sound of nature.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
