<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Subterrain: Mines of Titan</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1573100/Subterrain_Mines_of_Titan/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FERRSBJafXZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/extras/SUB-Discord-Banner.gif?t=1710261009"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/extras/SUB-Steam-banner-about-EN.png?t=1710261009"><br/><br/>After a massive meteor strikes the icy surface of Titan, nothing is left but a vast deposit of rare minerals. The TECC mining company rushes to establish a colony on Titan and successfully tap the riches, until the colony goes dark. It takes years to mount a salvage expedition to the far flung moon of Saturn, so make it count. Restart the flow of resources and figure out what happened to the first wave of colonists.<br/><br/>Stand between the sole survivors of Camp Huygens and total obliteration by Saturn's darkest mysteries. Every turn counts in the desperate struggle for survival, as Titan will not wait around - and neither should you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/extras/SUB-Steam-banner-titanic-EN.png?t=1710261009"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Titan is an unrelenting dynamic, persistent world. Every action and step advances time and brings Camp Huygens closer to collapse, unless someone intervenes.<br/></li><li> Help surviving colonists with their tasks, assign key jobs, harvest materials, and organize crafting stations to keep the doom at bay.<br/></li><li> Manage food and water intake, keep tabs on oxygen and energy levels, and treat any sustained injuries, all while penetrating the abandoned mining tunnels beneath the surface.<br/></li><li> Track the passage of time efficiently or it might turn out that the greatest threat to Camp Huygens isn't Titan or its monsters... but you!</li></ul> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/extras/SUB-Steam-banner-darkest-EN.png?t=1710261009"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Unearth the mysteries of Saturn's most famous moon and go deep beneath its surface to face off against its many horrors.<br/></li><li> Fight the monstrosities using intuitive, brisk turn-based combat. Do you make the fight close and personal, risking death as you go toe to toe? Or plink from afar, hoping that ammo won't run out at the wrong time?<br/></li><li> Harness the power of nanomachines to unleash devastating abilities against foes, but also sacrifice the ability to physically pummel monsters into submission?<br/></li><li> Gain experience and power alongside the celestial creatures underground. Evolve and adapt tactics, or perish in the darkness of Titan's mines!</li></ul> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/extras/SUB-Steam-banner-applied-EN.png?t=1710261009"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Craft an endless array of items thanks to a small handful of allies like weapons and elbow grease.<br/></li><li> Salvage what you can, break it down into materials, and produce tools like melee weapons, firearms, protective gear, explosives, and countless survival upgrades.<br/></li><li> Enhance yourself with medical supplies and continue research to develop even better versions.<br/></li><li> Survive long enough to unearth the terrible truth of what happened to the first wave of colonists or find a way to get off the doomed moon, no one said you get both...</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead by Daylight - All Things Wicked Chapter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2661270/Dead_by_Daylight__All_Things_Wicked_Chapter/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Main_Banner.gif?t=1710259123"><br/><br/>Dead by Daylight’s All Things Wicked delves into the depths of analog horror with <strong>new Killer, The Unknown</strong>, and <strong>new Survivor, Sable Ward</strong>. A new Map, <strong>Greenville Square</strong>, is available for all players. Purchasing this add-on unlocks 2 exclusive Cosmetics: <strong>The Unknown’s Garden Casual</strong> and <strong>Sable Ward’s Designer Corset</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Killer_Power.jpg?t=1710259123"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE UNKNOWN</h2>If you hear a soft voice crying out for help in the woods, stay the hell away. The true nature of The Unknown remains a mystery, barring one fatal certainty: to cross its path is to risk an unknowable fate.<br/><br/><strong>The Unknown’s Power: UVX (Unknown Venom X)</strong><br/><br/>Charge and launch a burst of UVX, which bounces once and creates a Blast Area upon impact. If they touch the Blast Area, they will become Weakened against your Power.   <br/>If a Survivor is Weakened, they will lose a Health State whenever they touch a Blast Area. Survivors can lose the Weakened status by successfully looking at The Unknown for a brief duration.<br/><br/><strong>Special Ability: Hallucinations</strong><br/><br/>During a Trial, The Unknown will intermittently create Hallucinations and leave them in its wake. The Unknown can highlight and teleport to any Hallucination, leaving behind a temporary Decoy version of itself. Survivors can Dispel Hallucinations, but only by staring at one while standing completely still. Weakened Survivors will take longer to Dispel a Hallucination, and any incomplete attempt will reveal their location through Killer Instinct. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Killer_Perks.jpg?t=1710259123"><br/><br/>The Unknown comes with <strong>3 new perks.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Unbound</h2>Unbound activates for a duration when a Survivor becomes injured. During this time, you’ll gain a brief speed boost whenever you Vault a Window.<h2 class="bb_tag">Unforeseen</h2>When you kick a Generator, your Terror Radius transfers to it for a duration. During this time, your Terror Radius increases and you become Undetectable.<h2 class="bb_tag">Undone</h2>Gain Tokens whenever a Survivor misses a Skill Check. When you damage a Generator, all Tokens will be consumed. For each Token consumed, the Generator loses 1% total progress and becomes blocked for 1 second.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Survivor_Perks.jpg?t=1710259123"><h2 class="bb_tag">SABLE WARD</h2>While some fear the darkness, Sable Ward embraces it. Fascinated by horror and drawn to all things wicked, Sable was among the few Survivors to willingly step into The Fog in search of her best friend Mikaela.<br/>Sable Ward comes with <strong>3 new perks.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Invocation: Weaving Spiders</h2>This Invocation can only be performed in the Basement and takes a considerable duration of time to complete. Survivors can see your Aura during the process and can join you, increasing the Invocation’s speed.  <br/>Once complete, all Survivors will gain a boost of Repair progress. On the other hand, you’ll be Injured and Broken for the remainder of the Trial.<h2 class="bb_tag">Strength in Shadows</h2>When in the basement, you can quickly heal without a Med-Kit. Afterward, the Killer’s Aura is briefly revealed.<h2 class="bb_tag">Wicked</h2>Gain the ability to successfully unhook yourself from Basement Hooks. When you successfully do so, the Killer’s Aura is briefly revealed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_New_Map.jpg?t=1710259123"><h2 class="bb_tag">NEW MAP: GREENVILLE SQUARE*</h2><br/>A slice of small-town Americana, long abandoned, long forgotten. Now, something wanders freely along the overgrown streets: a writhing creature responsible for a string of disappearances across the country.<br/>*This map is free for all players.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Exclusive_Item_Killer.jpg?t=1710259123"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXCLUSIVE CHAPTER KILLER ITEM: GARDEN CASUAL</h2>Her prize-winning peonies wilted and died without someone to care for them. The All Things Wicked Chapter includes an exclusive item for The Unknown, the <strong>Garden Casual Outfit</strong>, only available as part of the DLC. Please note that this item cannot be purchased separately.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Exclusive_Item_Survivor.jpg?t=1710259123"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXCLUSIVE CHAPTER SURVIVOR ITEM: DESIGNER CORSET </h2>Once she saw it in the store window, she knew she had a reason to save her money. The All Things Wicked Chapter includes an exclusive item for Sable, the <strong>Designer Corset</strong>, only available as part of the DLC. Please note that this item cannot be purchased separately.<br/><br/><br/><i>If you’re seeing this, your fate has been sealed.</i> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goblin Stone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1521970/Goblin_Stone/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FdF7NZJvSuA" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_Discord_00_Banner_616180.gif?t=1710259543"/></a><br/>Goblin Stone entrusts players with the fate of the last goblins to escape annihilation by cruel adventurers. To avoid extinction, they must build their numbers, venture back into the world, and put an end to the adventurers who hunt them. Embark on a heartwarming journey to rebuild a goblin lair and help them thrive in a turn-based roguelite where every decision counts.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_StoreGifs_5f.gif?t=1710259543"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_About_01_Bullets_Combat.png?t=1710259543"><br/>Craft the perfect goblin party by mixing classes, abilities, and genetics. Experience an innovative turn-based combat system, where the order of actions is determined by the strategic positioning of combatants.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_StoreGifs_1f.gif?t=1710259543"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_About_02_Bullets_Adventure.png?t=1710259543"><br/>Guide a merry party of goblins as they battle relentless adventurers, pompous elves, and surly dwarves. Dive into a world with nostalgic, storybook-inspired visuals, accompanied by an epic soundtrack composed by Hearthstone's Peter McConnell.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_StoreGifs_2f.gif?t=1710259543"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_About_03_Bullets_Colony.png?t=1710259543"><br/>Manage a thriving goblin colony and build your lair chamber by chamber, from the Barracks to the War Room. Carefully breed your favorite goblins, combining the finest genes and traits to cultivate a formidable lineage.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_StoreGifs_3f.gif?t=1710259543"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_About_04_Bullets_Choices.png?t=1710259543"><br/>Venture through procedurally generated adventures, where permadeath heightens the stakes. Difficult choices await as you decide which path to take and which goblins to sacrifice for survival.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_StoreGifs_4f.gif?t=1710259543"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_Infographic_Steam_EN_2.png?t=1710259543"><br/><br/>Receive exclusive news, updates, and perks by joining our active community on the <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FdF7NZJvSuA" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Goblin Stone Discord</a>.<br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FdF7NZJvSuA" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_Discord_00_Banner_616180.gif?t=1710259543"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contra: Operation Galuga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2235020/Contra_Operation_Galuga/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2235020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A new entry in the legendary Contra series is here! Contra: Operation Galuga is a thorough reimagining of the classic run-'n'-gun action game from the '80s, featuring modern graphics and sound, new stages, new enemies and bosses, new play mechanics, an updated weapons system, and explosive co-op combat for up to two players in Story Mode or four players in Arcade Mode!<br>
<br>
When the Red Falcon terrorist group takes over the Galuga Islands off the coast of New Zealand, elite Contra commandos Bill Rizer and Lance Bean springs into action, initiating an all-out war in which the fate of mankind hangs in the balance!<br>
<br>
Run, jump, and shoot your way through eight levels using a devastating arsenal - including the spread shot, laser, and homing missiles - now with stackable upgrades and awesome Overload abilities! The intense action is customizable with three difficulty settings plus a variety of additional challenge options. The true Contra legacy begins now!<br>
<br/>
Key Features:<br/>
•The original run-'n'-gun game is back, reimagined and more action-packed than ever!<br/>
•Attack aggressively across eight explosive stages! Infiltrate the jungle, ascend the waterfall, speed through an enemy base on a hovercycle, and more!<br/>
•Multiple playable characters with distinct abilities!<br/>
•Epic, screen-filling boss battles!<br/>
•New and fan-favorite weapons, now with stackable upgrades and incredible Overload abilities!<br/>
•Multiple difficulty options and a wealth of extra content						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload: Expansion Pass</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2689210/Persona_3_Reload_Expansion_Pass/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2689210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Dive deeper into the world of <i>Persona 3 Reload</i> with this expansion pass featuring new costumes, BGM, and an extended story content scenario “Episode Aigis -The Answer-”, offering over 30 hours of additional gameplay.<br/>Content will be released as follows:<br/><br/><strong>Wave 1 - <i>Persona 5 Royal</i> EX BGM Set and <i>Persona 4 Golden</i> EX BGM Set <br/>Release Date: March 2024</strong><br/>Unlock and listen to additional tracks from <i>Persona 5 Royal</i> and <i>Persona 4 Golden</i> while exploring and battling in dungeons in <i>Persona 3 Reload</i> and <i>Persona 3 Reload: Episode Aigis -The Answer-</i>.<br/><br/><strong>Wave 2 - Velvet Costume &amp; BGM Set <br/>Release Date: May 2024</strong><br/>Unlock Velvet Room themed costumes and BGM to further customize your dungeon experience in <i>Persona 3 Reload</i> and <i>Persona 3 Reload: Episode Aigis -The Answer-</i>. <br/><br/><strong>Wave 3 - New Expansive Story Scenario, “Episode Aigis -The Answer-” <br/>Release Date: September 2024</strong><br/>After unravelling the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fighting epic battles through Tartarus, and all the unforgettable events of <i>Persona 3 Reload</i>, the S.E.E.S. members find themselves trapped in a never-ending March 31st. Journey through the Abyss of Time as Aigis, undertake new challenges, and uncover the cause of this strange fate and the truth of what happened on that day... <br/><br/>Delve into this final chapter now with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, fresh animations and UI, and a rearranged soundtrack. <br/><br/>---<br/><br/><i>Persona 3 Reload: Persona 5 Royal</i> EX BGM Set Track List (8 total):<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Life Will Change<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Beneath the Mask<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Kichijoji 199X<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Gentle Madman<br/>- Dungeon BGM: I believe<br/>- Battle BGM: Keeper of Lust<br/>- Battle BGM: Blooming Villain<br/>- Battle BGM: Victory (Appears on battle results screen）<br/><br/><i>Victory</i> will automatically be applied as the battle result theme when you set one of the tracks in this pack as your battle BGM. It cannot be applied individually.<br/><br/><i>Persona 3 Reload: Persona 4 Golden</i> EX BGM Set Track List (8 total):<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Backside of the TV<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Game<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Junes Theme<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Heaven<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Long Way<br/>- Battle BGM: Revelations: Mitsuo<br/>- Battle BGM: The Almighty<br/>- Battle BGM: Results (Appears on battle results screen）<br/><br/><i>Results</i> will automatically be applied as the battle result theme when you set one of the tracks in this pack as your battle BGM. It cannot be applied individually.<br/><br/><i>Persona 3 Reload</i>: Velvet Costume &amp; BGM Set Contents and Track List (5 total):<br/>- Velvet Room themed costumes<br/>- Dungeon BGM / Battle BGM: Electronica In Velvet Room ("P4D" ver.)<br/>- Dungeon BGM / Battle BGM: Battle Hymn of the Soul (t.komine REMIX "AT 1st" P3D-EDIT ver.)<br/>- Dungeon BGM / Battle BGM: Battle Hymn of the Soul (Daisuke Asakura Remix)<br/>- Dungeon BGM / Battle BGM: Battle Hymn of the Soul -USH ver.-<br/>- Battle BGM: Dance Hymn of the Soul (Disco In Velvet Room) (Appears on battle results screen)<br/><br/><i>Dance Hymn of the Soul (Disco In Velvet Room)</i> will automatically be applied as the battle result theme when you set one of the tracks in this pack as your battle BGM. It cannot be applied individually.<br/><br/>To change your Costume, go to the Main Menu &gt; EQUIP &gt; Select character &gt; Select Outfit.<br/>To change your BGM, go to your Main Menu &gt; SYSTEM &gt; CONFIG &gt; Game System Settings and select Change Dungeon BGM or Change Battle BGM.<br/>You must own Persona 3 Reload with the latest patch downloaded to access expansion pass content. <br/>Some content in this product may overlap.<br/>Names and descriptions in this product are subject to change without notice. <br/>Scheduled release dates are subject to change.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebel Transmute</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1191660/Rebel_Transmute/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/Rebel_Transmute_Logo_Decorated_Steam.png?t=1710176486"><br/><br/>In this modern metroidvania you play as Moon Mikono, a space scrapper turned adventurer on a mission to uncover the true fate of her missing mother.<br/><br/>To accomplish this mission in your own, unique way you'll be swapping out game changing augments to suit your playstyle.  Aggressive and greedy?  Inquisitive and cautious?  Maybe you just want an army of friendly creatures!  With over 50 unique upgrades, Rebel Transmute allows you to play through a classic sci-fi adventure in YOUR style.<h2 class="bb_tag">CHALLENGING AND CUSTOMIZABLE COMBAT</h2>Use a variety of spells known as Bloodcasts, your trusty Foray-issued Blaster, and a variety of game changing Augments to take on a world of dangerous creatures and space travelers.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/16.gif?t=1710176486"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXPLORE AND MAP A VIBRANT SCI-FI WORLD</h2>The sprawling world of Rebel Transmute is full of stunning vistas: From vibrant greenery in the Overgrowth, to the fluorescent reefs of the Coral Fissure, to the sparkblood crystal-strewn Surface.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/09.gif?t=1710176486"><h2 class="bb_tag">Additional Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Encounter over <strong>80 unique enemies</strong> and over <strong>10 formidable bosses</strong>! From mutated worms and electrified beasts, to rogue AI's and gigantic bugs. All offering different and exciting challenges and interactions.<br/></li><li>Discover <strong>game-changing abilities</strong> hidden throughout the outpost.  Spin Bash, Wall Jump, and Void Dash your way across an interconnected network of tunnels, caverns, and research laboratories!<br/></li><li>Augment your playstyle with <strong>48 optional upgrades</strong> that can drastically change how you play the game.  Fight alongside a reprogrammed drone, twist your attacks into spiraling laser blasts, or even summon tentacles to block projectiles!<br/></li><li>Make use of a versatile mapping system to help track your progress.  Use custom markers, track your completion percentage, and find hidden terminals to uncover unexplored areas.<br/></li><li>Experience a <strong>personal and heartfelt story</strong>. As Moon searches for her mother she’ll also encounter various robot life, all with their own stories, personalities, and quests.<br/></li><li>A <strong>hand-painted pixel art</strong> aesthetic lends each and every character, enemy, and sector a personal touch.<br/></li><li>An immersive and atmospheric score, crafted to perfectly match every moment, from bombastic fights to solemn exploration.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchors Blockade Zone:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2819850/Anchors_Blockade_ZonePrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FPZHEvJTz65" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/dss.png?t=1709912394"/></a><br/><br/><strong>Difference between Prologue and Official Edition<br/>Prologue opens up a map</strong><br/><strong>Anchor: Blockade Zone game, is a collection of gun modification, exploring the map, death drop equipment of the Cthulhu theme 2D pixel style shooter. The game puts you in the role of an agent who enters a blockade zone to investigate with the aim of finding out the cause of the strange events in the blockade zone. Your character is trapped in the blockade and has to search for food, water and other supplies in order to survive, as well as completing quests to gather information and find the truth. In the process, don't be too surprised to encounter anything unnatural, whether it's going back in time or to the future. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/1y.png?t=1709912394"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/战斗.gif?t=1709912394"><br/><strong>Experience exhilarating shooting, fight sworn battles with hostile agents, Kraken monsters, and more, and beat the truth out of the world with the weapons in your hands! Poor for tactical penetration, rich for fire coverage, it's all up to you! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/2y.png?t=1709912394"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/改枪.gif?t=1709912394"><br/><strong>We strive to make you feel the thrill of 2d shooting, so that you can feel the real shooting experience.<br/>Up to hundreds of gun accessories, allowing you to freely remodel your exclusive weapon! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/3y.png?t=1709912394"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/仓库.gif?t=1709912394"><br/><strong>Recruit agents for your exploration operations and train them to grow into excellent agents to help you complete various missions and search various maps.<br/>Each exploration map is a repeated horizontal jump across the edge of life and death for agents, with different maps having different chances of resulting in an agent's outright death. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/4y.png?t=1709912394"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/搜索.gif?t=1709912394"><br/>Explore the map carefully and make sure your agent gets back to base safe and sound every time.<br/><strong>If an agent is unlucky enough to die or return to the city with serious injuries, the items he is carrying and searching for will be dropped with him. Only items placed in the safe will be retained. </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMERHOUSE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2533960/SUMMERHOUSE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2533960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2533960/extras/summerhouse_new_store_page.gif?t=1709984408"><br/><br/>SUMMERHOUSE is a small-scale building game and a love letter to the feeling of long lost summer afternoons.<br/><br/>Craft a neighbourhood of tiny, beautiful lived-in homes in a variety of settings: the sea, the city, or the mountains. While there are some little secrets to uncover, there are no rules, and you can’t win or lose. Just chill out, build to your heart’s content and soak up the atmosphere.<br/><br/>If relaxation and creation are your thing, this is a game for you :)<br/><br/><i>Please keep in mind that this is a small game with no goals or challenges, created by a single person🙂</i> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORE BLASTERS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/BORE_BLASTERS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/BLAST.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_blast_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Blast your way through rocks and dirt with your machinegun drill. Carve through the ground to uncover precious ores and defeat menacing foes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/LOOT.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_loot_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Uncover ancient relics and artefacts hidden in the deep. Amass a fortune in rare gems &amp; ores.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/UPGRADE.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_mortar_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Invest in powerful upgrades and unlock new abilities, turning your humble gyrocopter into a fearsome force to be reckoned with.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/DISCOVER.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_discover_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Explore a diverse range of biomes, from treacherous volcanic caverns to lush overgrown underground forests, each with its own unique challenges and rewards.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/FEATURES.png?t=1709907021"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Intense mining action with fast-paced blasting<br/></li><li> Constant progress - even failed runs aren't punishing<br/></li><li> Diverse biomes to explore<br/></li><li> Purchase upgrades to overpower your gyrocopter<br/></li><li> Navigate the overworld to unlock new mine shafts<br/></li><li> Collect and loot rare gems, ores, and artefacts to upgrade your gear and abilities<br/></li><li> Endless replayability with procedurally generated levels</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_drones_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/><br/>Drawing inspiration from mining games like Motherload and Galactic Mining Corp, Bore Blasters takes the genre to the next level with high octane action and fast paced gameplay. Fans of digging and collecting will find plenty to love, while the addition of deadly enemies and mysterious artefacts will keep even the most seasoned miners on their toes.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/WL_arrow.gif?t=1709907021"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_missiles_frame.gif?t=1709907021"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Realm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1330000/Stolen_Realm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/GreenDragon.gif?t=1709885067"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TURN-BASED STRATEGY MEETS ACTION RPG IN THIS DUNGEON CRAWLING LOOTER</strong></h2><br/><br/>Stolen Realm is a <strong>simultaneous turn-based tactical dungeon crawling looter with action RPG elements</strong> where you control up to <strong>6 heroes, solo or through online co-op</strong>, venturing forth in adventures set in a high-fantasy, low-poly world. <br/><br/>Stolen Realm features an <strong>innovative turn-based combat system</strong> where <strong>simultaneous turns</strong> allow every team to take their actions at once, creating quick combat encounters that blend the tactical depth of titles like Divinity: Original Sin with the thrill of a fast-paced action RPG. Every battle scales based on the number of players involved, so you can easily jump in and out of the game even in the same playthrough!<br/> <br/>With a <strong>highly customisable class system</strong>, Stolen Realm allows you to create traditional RPG classes or break the mold to forge a unique champion of your own as you draw from a pool of hundreds of possible skills. Make a spell-slinging assassin, a priest born of frost, or a shadow-infused knight. Further customize your build by earning and reforging <strong>loot that truly changes the way you play</strong>: wield Abbadon the Soul Crusher, a mythic mace that raises slain enemies as skeletal warriors to fight for you, or unsheath the Bloodletter, a cursed sword that grants additional power at the cost of your lifeblood. D&amp;D-like events where attribute-based rolls will have permanent effects on your character add yet another layer to building a character that is truly your own. Anything is possible in this title that keeps compelling choices at the forefront of your experience.  <br/><br/>Keeping the core appeal of RPGs at its forefront, Stolen Realm ensures you spend all your time, fighting, building your characters and making compelling choices that determine your immediate path or effect your character, rather than getting bogged down in side quests and other RPG-bloat.   After each battle, pick your path between story events, resource gathering, shops and treasure rooms, until you get to the final boss of each <strong>procedurally generated adventure.</strong> If you’re up to a challenge, crank the difficulty up with <strong>6 different difficulty levels</strong> – or pick <strong>Hardcore Mode with permadeath</strong>, where every battle can be the last!<br/><br/>Also features <strong>Roguelike Mode</strong>, a fast paced version of the game where you can mix and match builds that are simply not possible in the traditional campaign!<br/><br/>Carve a place in history with your sword and magic. Rise to honor and glory in the battlefield. <strong>Recover the Stolen Realm.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/CycloneKick.gif?t=1709885067"><h2 class="bb_tag">PRAISE FOR STOLEN REALM</h2><br/>“The tactical depth of Divinity: Original Sin” - GamesRadar+<br/><br/>“we’re losing our evenings to… Stolen Realm” - TheXboxHub<br/><br/>“A gorgeous looking game” - PC Gamer<br/><br/>“You can be a fire warrior. You can be a healing necromancer. You can do all sorts of weird s**t.” - <strong>Sacriel</strong><br/><br/>“What I like about this game is it’s straight to the point. You just go in, you’re building your character, you’re getting items…and you just fight. There’s no bulls**t.” - <strong>Shroud</strong><br/><br/>“It’s rad” - <strong>Sequisha</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/Dwarven_Warmachine.gif?t=1709885067"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>KEY FEATURES</strong></h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play solo or with friends in up to 6 player online co-op, allowing you and your friends to wreak havoc amongst your foes<br/></li><li>Experience thrilling and fast-paced turn-based battles thanks to a simultaneous team turn system<br/></li><li>Full story campaign, roguelike mode and streamer mode<br/></li><li>Use over 300 skills in 10 distinct skill trees allowing for complete and flexible character customization<br/></li><li>Navigate hex-based battlefields where positioning is key due to battle shrines with special effects, exploding barrels and movable crates<br/></li><li>Find and loot over 700 unique items, fully customizable with modifiers, as you explore a wonderful world full of magic, secrets and unexpected dangers<br/></li><li>Co-op focused design keeps gameplay fast paced and strategic for up to 6 players <br/></li><li>Easy drop-in, drop-out design and automatic scaling that allows you to join or drop out mid-quest <br/></li><li>D&amp;D-like attribute-based rolls in special events that have permanent character effects<br/></li><li>Fight against over 200 types of enemies in battles that will be different every time: thanks to the Enemy Modifications feature, every creature you face on the battlefield will be unique<br/></li><li>A world that changes on each expedition, from frosty peaks guarded by the elusive Blue Dragon to overgrown jungles where the rock giants roam. <br/></li><li>Pick your path between battles, choosing where to go between story events, resource gathering, shops, fights, and treasure rooms until you get to the final boss of each adventure<br/></li><li>6 different difficulty levels<br/></li><li>Choose between Normal Mode and Hardcore Mode with permadeath if you want a real challenge!</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE 2K24</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2315690/WWE_2K24/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2315690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							FORTY YEARS OF WRESTLEMANIA<br>
<br>
WrestleMania is the biggest event in sports entertainment, where Superstars become WWE Legends. Experience a gripping retelling of WrestleMania’s greatest moments in 2K Showcase of the Immortals, where you can relive a collection of some of the most unforgettable, career-defining matches.<br>
<br>
AN ICONIC ROSTER<br>
<br>
WWE 2K24 boasts a star-studded roster featuring WWE Legends like “Stone Cold” Steve Austin, Undertaker, and Andre the Giant, alongside current WWE Superstars like “The American Nightmare” Cody Rhodes, John Cena, Rhea Ripley, and Roman Reigns, whose larger-than-life entrances and signature moves are heightened by ultra-realistic graphics.<br>
<br>
NEW MATCH TYPES<br>
<br>
From Guest Referee to Casket, Gauntlet, and Ambulance matches, there are a bevy of new match types to experience in WWE 2K24, including support for multiple Superstars in Backstage Brawl.<br>
<br>
PROVE YOURSELF IN MyRISE<br>
<br>
Unleash your raw talent and become the undisputed champ in MyRISE, featuring two thrilling career arcs and original storylines chronicling your ascent to WWE stardom from the men's and women’s divisions.<br>
<br>
BUILD YOUR FACTION<br>
<br>
Assemble your favorite WWE Superstars and Legends in MyFACTION. Acquire cards, build a dominant faction, compete in online multiplayer and the all-new ranked quickplay. Plus, earn exciting promotional and final rank rewards as you climb the new seasonal leaderboard!<br>
<br>
CONTROL THE WWE UNIVERSE<br>
<br>
Develop feuds, weekly shows, and more in Universe mode, WWE 2K24’s ultimate sandbox, with expanded rivalry actions, all-new cutscenes, and support for double-title matches!<br>
<br>
CALL THE SHOTS IN MyGM<br>
<br>
Oversee the biggest brands and Superstars in sports entertainment as you challenge rival general managers for the top spot in MyGM. Explore more match types, more brands, and new general managers. Trade Superstars between brands, make executive decisions on contracts, and amp up the drama.<br/>
<br/>
**Online play including MyFACTION requires an internet connection and 2K Account. Terms apply.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duelists of Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1664200/Duelists_of_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/DoE_EVO_Trailer_-_steam_gif_short_30fps.gif?t=1710102934"><br/>Duelists of Eden is a card-grid-fighting game set after the events of One Step From Eden. Build your custom deck and battle online in real-time action! There are over 14 unique characters with strengths and weaknesses to encourage creative spell combinations and synergies. Will you combo slashes, fire, or even use bombs to eliminate your competition?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/SaffronWitch_steam_header-features.gif?t=1710102934"><h2 class="bb_tag">Deckbuilding</h2>Fight in a mix of strategy and real-time action! Create your own unique combination of spells to take down the competition. <br/>Save and edit an unlimited amount of decks in the editor!<h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic cardtridge and combo system</h2>Create combos on the fly, adapting the scenario and what spells you and your opponent have.<h2 class="bb_tag">Tutorial and training mode</h2>Learn the ropes in the tutorial mode and deep dive into the mechanics via training mode. <br/>Training mode includes hitboxes, character states, quick deck edits, speed modifiers, and more!<h2 class="bb_tag">Custom rollback netcode</h2>The game was completely rebuilt to support custom rollback netcode, for the smoothest experience possible.<h2 class="bb_tag">Replay mode</h2>Review your matches in replay mode!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/Selicy_OSFE_gif_steam.gif?t=1710102934"><br/><br/>Local multiplayer may require a controller.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals Zero Hour</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732960/Command__Conquer_Generals_Zero_Hour/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals Zero Hour brings you closer to the enemy than ever before. Engage opposing forces at hot spots around the globe as you match strategies and arsenals against the new masterminds of modern war.<br/><br/><strong>Arsenal.</strong> Unleash the next generation of 3D new units and 20 new upgrades including China's ECM Tank, GLA's BattleBus and the USA's Spectre Gunship.<br/><br/><strong>Missions.</strong> Take on 15 new missions and make tomorrow's headlines. Root out a splinter cell in Cairo, steal deadly toxins from a U.S. lab and more.<br/><br/><strong>Generals.</strong> Match strategies and arsenals against 9 enemy commanders with unpredictable personalities and tactics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Tiberian Sun™ and Firestorm™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229880/Command__Conquer_Tiberian_Sun_and_Firestorm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Second Tiberium War begins in this legendary sequel to the original Command &amp; Conquer. <br/><br/>With his forces stronger than ever, arch villain and leader of The Brotherhood of Nod - Kane - is pitched in an epic battle against the world's war machine - the Global Defense Initiative. Now you must orchestrate the fate of mankind.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on Dynamic Battlefields. Nature itself provides tactical opportunities - destroyable and deformable terrain, forest fires, treacherous ice fields and many more surprises that help or hinder your strategies.<br/></li><li>Exciting New Strategies and Units. Jump Jet Infantry, Hover Tanks, Tunneling APCs, Hunter Seekers, Laser Fences, Mechanized Battle Units and many more.<br/></li><li>The "Veterancy" Factor. Units can become faster and stronger as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>New Kinetic Battlefields. Flying shrapnel, shock waves and crashing debris are just a few of the exciting new technologies developed to enhance the in-game experience.<br/></li><li>The mood and attitude of the battlefield comes alive like never before - covert night missions, searchlights and new defenses intensify the thrill and excitement.</li></ul><br/>Then take the battle further in <strong>Firestorm, the official expansion pack for the game</strong>. Includes all-new campaign missions, cinematics, and units to decide the future of mankind.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Renegade™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229890/Command__Conquer_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer gets up close and personal in this classic First Person Shooter for one of the most iconic franchises.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wreak Havoc</strong> - Experience the Command &amp; Conquer universe on foot as Havoc, wise-cracking GDI Commando.<br/></li><li><strong>Make Your Own Rules</strong>  - Take on the evil Brotherhood of Nod using your own mix of brute force, stealth, and strategy.<br/></li><li><strong>Assault at Ground Level</strong>  - Dish out the damage in either first or third person.<br/></li><li><strong>Total Access</strong>  - Sneak inside and explore full-scale structures, like immense Tiberium Refineries and the ominous Hand of Nod.<br/></li><li><strong>Grind the Gears</strong>  - Beef up your arsenal by commandeering lethal vehicles, such as Nod Buggies, Flame Tanks, and Mammoth Tanks.<br/></li><li><strong>Weapons of Mass Destruction</strong>  - Choose from a multitude of weapons, including the Tiberium Auto Rifle, Chemical Sprayer, and the devasting Personal Ion Cannon.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potions: A Curious Tale</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/378690/Potions_A_Curious_Tale/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Add Potions: A Curious Tale to your wishlist!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/Wishlist_616.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/LunaCombatGif.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Use your wits to strategize conflict resolution that goes beyond pure combat-- you’ll have to think on your feet and act quickly to sidestep danger and trick, charm, and scare your opponents into dropping valuable resources. <br/><br/>As powerful as your potions are, you’ll find yourself up against monsters that can shrug off your most powerful attacks. Manage your resources carefully and use the environment and even other monsters to defeat your enemies, or you may find yourself with an empty satchel when you need your elixirs the most.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/SteamCraftingVideoFullPotTitleNX.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>On her path to potions mastery, Luna must gather rare ingredients even before she brews her first potion. While her grandmother and friends teach her basic skills and recipes, Luna must fill her vials through experimentation and discovery. <br/><br/>Explore the deep crafting system as you discover new ingredients across 7 biomes to craft over 100 unique potions with different element combinations. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/PuzzleGifTitle.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Solve devious puzzles and mysteries with your wits and your arsenal of mystical potions. With a little help from your grandmother (a powerful witch in her own right) and Helios, your cat familiar, you’ll overcome the challenges of these enchanted lands.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/StoryTitle.png?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Growing up is hard, and it’s even harder when you’re a witch! Encounter fairy tale and folklore characters as you guide Luna on her quest to become a potions master. With her sharp-tongued familiar at her side, Luna learns important coming-of-age lessons: Respect is earned, advice can be deceiving, and adults aren't always right.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FQS2SN55CC4" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/SteamHeaderDiscord616.png?t=1709876407"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/PetCatHeart.gif?t=1709876407"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Saboteur™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/24880/The_Saboteur/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/24880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Not all wars are fought on the open battlefield. Download The Saboteur to visit 1940s Nazi-occupied Paris, as you play tough Irish racecar mechanic Sean Devlin. Working with the French Resistance, Sean is out for revenge against ruthless Nazi Colonel Kurt Dierker, who executed Sean’s best friend.<br/><br/>This open-world action thriller takes you through the seedy streets of Paris as you seek to undermine the German authority and lead a rebellion. Fight across rooftops and through dangerous alleys, and operate a wide variety of vehicles as you navigate your terrain. You can even climb the Eiffel Tower or Notre Dame Cathedral for a sniping mission.<br/><br/>Use stealth and disguise to strike at the heart of the Nazi war machine by disabling trains, destroying bridges, and blowing up enemy facilities. As you work to remove the oppressive forces from parts of the city, the drab black-and-white palette gives way to bright colors, signifying that you’ve inspired the townspeople. The more you incite the people, the more they’ll aid you by intervening in fights or providing a quick getaway from pursuing Germans. The Saboteur presents a fresh take on World War II and features dramatic cinematic elements. The action and intrigue is yours to experience via download on the PC now.<br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>First Ever Open-World Paris</strong> — Climb the Eiffel Tour, snipe from Notre Dame Cathedral, and brawl on the Champs d’Elysee as you sabotage your enemies. Fight, climb, and prowl through the dark alleys, rooftops, burlesque houses, and seedy streets of the City of Lights — the ultimate playground for the Saboteur.<br/></li><li><strong>The Art of Sabotage</strong> — Being the Saboteur is all about attacking while staying unnoticed. Get your mission intel at underground clubs and cabarets. Eliminate your adversaries with stealth attacks, disguise, distractions, and explosives. Master a variety of weapons, automobiles, and skills to sabotage enemy operations. <br/></li><li><strong>The Will to Fight</strong> — An action-packed experience and thrilling storyline are made even more engaging by an innovative visual style, characters, and the new “Will to Fight” technology. Experience how the city reacts and changes around you as you free it from Nazi oppression. Only you can restore hope and grandeur to Paris.<br/></li><li><strong>French Resistance Strikes</strong> — Call for support from The Underground in the form of getaway cars, weapon deliveries, distractions, and much more.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 March Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2845260/100_March_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🌸🌹 WELCOME TO 100 MARCH CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌷🐈</h2><br/>Join the cutest adventure in the Lovely world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of romantic 8 march themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x200.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 March Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁 DLC List for this game 🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Extra.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867620/100_March_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867640/100_March_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x1.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_15" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavy Storm Shadow:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802380/Heavy_Storm_ShadowPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FwmfaDVPKSa" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/dss.png?t=1710177558"/></a><br/><br/><strong>Differences between the prologue and the full version<br/>The prologue opens up a character<br/>The prologue opens up a map</strong><br/><br/><strong>Unlock the true potential of your mech and witness its constant growth and upgrades! In deserts, ice and even satellites, kill thousands of swarms to strengthen your mech!<br/>At the end of each battle you will gain valuable resources to upgrade your mech's weapons and armor, unlocking new skills and powerful equipment.<br/>Through battles, you'll gain the bonds of your mech's pilots, forming modules in different directions to shape your unique fighting style.<br/>Grow and upgrade your mech in real time to make it more and more invincible and become the ultimate weapon against the swarm!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/1y.png?t=1710177558"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/1z.gif?t=1710177558"><br/><strong>Monsters are coming at you like wave after wave, and as your mech's guns move, the monsters explode into a fog of blood and fall in pieces, painting the earth in scarlet. Operate your mech to dodge attacks, kill through the siege, and find a way to survive among hundreds of enemies!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/2y.png?t=1710177558"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/2z.gif?t=1710177558"><br/><strong>Explore your own powerful combat combo by unlocking more and more powerful weapons and skills! Become stronger by killing and choosing, picking up resources, choosing the most suitable enhancements, and finally killing the terrifying bosses head-on!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/3y.png?t=1710177558"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/3Z.gif?t=1710177558"><br/><strong> offers a rich arsenal of multiple primary and secondary weapons, as well as numerous skills with unique features. These weapons and skills will provide endless possibilities for your battles. In the future, there will be even more powerful mechs waiting to be harnessed by you! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/4y.png?t=1710177558"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/4z.gif?t=1710177558"><br/><strong>The game already offers 3 challenging maps, each with unique enemy combinations and powerful bosses waiting to be challenged for a completely different leveling experience. As the game continues to update, you will meet more new maps and new modes of play to make your Meat Pigeon adventure even more colorful. </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sixty Four</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2659900/Sixty_Four/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F7YXd3tScqS" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/discord.png?t=1710217001"/></a><br/><br/>Created by a solo developer, Sixty Four is a clicker game that gradually becomes more idle with every machine you unlock, up to the the ultimate goal of full automation. Upgrade a factory in an extraordinary world. Progress to unlock new resources and machines, leading to new ways to expand and grow.<br/><br/><strong>❒ From Foundation to Complexity</strong><br/><br/>Begin your journey with a simple machine generating distinct cubes. Use combinations of cubes to unlock advanced machinery and new gameplay elements.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_3a_smaller.gif?t=1710217001"><br/><br/><strong>❒ An Evolving Factory Adventure</strong><br/><br/>Your factory is not just a collection of simple machines; it's a dynamic environment of challenges and strategy. Face new situations and discover opportunities with every innovative and abstract machine you encounter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_4a_smaller.gif?t=1710217001"><br/><strong>❒ A Fresh Mix of Gaming Mechanics</strong><br/><br/>Sixty Four combines simple yet engaging elements from idle, incremental, and strategy games. Pursue constant improvement and unravel the secrets behind messages from an unknown entity.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_5a_smaller.gif?t=1710217001"><br/><br/>Music by Jake Chudnow						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Thaumaturge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1684350/The_Thaumaturge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Thaumaturge_accolade_616x320_steam.png?t=1709742147"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/TT_claim_EN_small.png?t=1709742147"><br/><strong>The Thaumaturge is an isometric, story-rich RPG with a unique take on turn-based combat, character development features, and investigation mechanics</strong>, facing you with morally ambiguous choices – set in a world teeming with mysterious powers and strange ethereal beings called <strong>salutors</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/City_3-01.gif?t=1709742147"><br/><br/>The year is 1905. Warsaw lives under the yoke of imperial Russian tsardom. Its inhabitants constitute a diverse group of different ancestries, views, and beliefs with often conflicting interests: Russian soldiers, Jewish merchants, Polish townspeople, and more. Despite the circumstances, the city is a buzzing metropolis, where one can attend a breathtaking party with the high society, and later get robbed in one of the dark alleys of the Praga district. A city of great hopes and dreams on one hand and dark desires on the other.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Buka_2.gif?t=1709742147"><br/><br/>A <strong>thaumaturge</strong> bears both a gift and a burden at the same time. This parallel holds true for <strong>Wiktor Szulski</strong>, the game’s titular protagonist, who is drawn back to the tumultuous streets of 20th-century Warsaw by family matters. The gift of thaumaturgy is intertwined with family legacy, passed down through one's ancestors. This mystical inheritance significantly shapes Wiktor’s life journey tied around a pursuit of unearthly entities and their hosts. As only a thaumaturge can tame these ethereal entities - known to a select few as <strong>salutors</strong> - utilizing their mystical abilities to discover secrets hidden within the human soul and speak to the Darkness, no one understands quite like Wiktor how everyone suffers their own demons.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Wiktor_3-01.gif?t=1709742147"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Shape your story</strong> – as a full-fledged RPG, it allows you to alternate your choices and make you deal with the aftermath. <br/></li><li><strong>Develop your character</strong> – creating your own version of the thaumaturge will allow you to approach situations in different ways. <br/></li><li><strong>Experience unique turn-based combat</strong> and defeat your foes using human attacks and skills as well as psychic strikes delivered by salutors.<br/></li><li><strong>Influence and manipulate</strong> the temperaments of other characters to bend their will to your liking. <br/></li><li><strong>Tame the power of salutors</strong> – use the unique set of their skills to gain an advantage while exploring the world and when bringing your adversaries to their knees. <br/></li><li><strong>See the world that’s inevitably gone</strong> – explore the uncommon, heavily researched historic period of the early XX century Warsaw, where crime and luxury are often two sides of the same coin. Meet historical figures and learn about their involvement in the story. <br/></li><li><strong>Created in Unreal Engine 5</strong> to deliver a detailed &amp; beautifully crafted world.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeeperRL</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/329970/KeeperRL/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/Peek-2018-11-28-09-43.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL is an ambitious dungeon simulator with roguelike and RPG elements. Take the role of an evil wizard and study the methods of black magic. Equip your minions and explore the world, murder innocent villagers and burn their homes. Build your dungeon, lay traps and prepare for an assault of angry heroes. <br/><br/>When you control your minions the game changes into a classic roguelike, with turn-based and very tactical combat. You can also play as an adventurer and assault dungeons made by you or other players.<h2 class="bb_tag">Dungeon management </h2>You will dig deep into the mountain and build dozens of rooms, corridors and traps. Your minions will train and produce weapons and armor. Prisoners will be tortured. You will research new technologies like alchemy, beast mutation and sorcery.<h2 class="bb_tag">Z-levels</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341">Develop your base across multiple floors by digging down into the earth or building up. Build fantastic dungeon designs or elaborate castles and towers.<h2 class="bb_tag">Roguelike mechanics </h2>The world is simulated on a very detailed level. Creatures use equipment and consumable items. There are dozens of special items, spells, attributes and special attacks. You can cut off heads and limbs and blind or poison your enemies. If you're not careful with fire, you can burn an entire forest or even your own dungeon.<h2 class="bb_tag">Large, procedurally generated maps </h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-animated-gif-maker__2_.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL features a large, procedurally generated world. Explore dozens of locations, from small cottages and shops to major enemies dwelling in castles and dungeons. Uncover secrets, bring back great loot and prisoners back to your base in order to grow in power.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple playable factions</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/gif_keepers-ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>Play as a:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dark wizard researching black magic.<br/></li><li>White knight specialized in horses and angelic beings.<br/></li><li>Necromancer who crafts undead from the body parts of fallen enemies.<br/></li><li>Fragile colony of twelve dwarves.<br/></li><li>Goblin king searching for his lost wives.<br/></li><li>Collective of gnomes with a mechanized army.<br/></li><li>Lone adventurer focused on exploration.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Online map sharing </h2>KeeperRL offers the ability to download dungeons made by other players from Steam Workshop, and places them on your world map as enemies. See how others design their fortresses, fight with their minions, and steal their loot! After winning the game, you'll have the option to share your dungeon online as well.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Grindea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/269770/Secrets_of_Grindea/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/269770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Secrets of Grindea</i> is an old-school Action RPG with co-op support for up to 4 players. It is a tribute to and sometimes a parody of the old SNES games so many of us grew up with and loved! Journey through fantastical lands, and battle tons of different enemies and bosses in your quest for truth, friendship and, above all, finding the world's rarest treasures!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A rich world filled with 300+ unique, colorful characters and an engaging story to drive your journey forward.<br/></li><li>Co-op support for up to four players! Enjoy the entire storyline with your friends or call someone in to help with the more difficult challenges.<br/></li><li>Customization, customization, customization - design a character that represents you, then mix and match any of the 31 spells and skills across 9 different categories.<br/></li><li>30+ epic boss fights! Overgrown slimes, giant robots, mimics - we have it all!<br/></li><li>Side content - design your own home, fish, craft items, tame pets, partake in mini-games, grow plants - there’s plenty to keep you entertained when you want a break from the main story.</li></ul><br/>And last but not least:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Arcade Mode - Separate from Story Mode, the game includes a <strong>full roguelite</strong> version where you need to battle your way to the top on a single life, building a town of your own as you progress.  How far can you get?</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON BALL FighterZ</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/678950/DRAGON_BALL_FighterZ/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/extras/GIF_DBFZ_STEAM.png?t=1710262330"><br/><br/>DRAGON BALL FighterZ is born from what makes the DRAGON BALL series so loved and famous: endless spectacular fights with its all-powerful fighters.<br/><br/>Partnering with Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ maximizes high end Anime graphics and brings easy to learn but difficult to master fighting gameplay.<br/><br/>High-end Anime Graphics<br/>Using the power of the Unreal engine and the talented team at Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ is a visual tour-de-force.<br/><br/>3vs3 Tag/Support<br/>Build your dream team and sharpen your skills to master high-speed tag combinations.<br/><br/>Thrilling Online Features<br/>Ranked matches, interactive lobby, crazy 6-player Party Match... There is something for every taste!<br/><br/>Exclusive Story Mode<br/>Discover a never-seen-before scenario featuring Android 21, a brand new character whose creation was supervised by Akira Toriyama himself.<br/><br/>Spectacular Fights<br/>Experience aerial combos, destructible stages and famous scenes from the DRAGON BALL anime in 60FPS and 1080p resolution!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1709723687"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1709723687"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709723687"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709723687"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minami Lane</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678990/Minami_Lane/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Minami Lane is a small, wholesome management game set on a Japanese-inspired street. Create and manage your own street, make sure everyone is happy, and watch the villagers live their lives! Enjoy 2 to 4 hours of playtime, cute tanukis and lots of cats!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/Gameplay.png?t=1710273412"><br/><br/><i><strong>Build your street</strong></i><br/>Build homes to add villagers to your street, then improve their happiness by beautifying every inch and building a variety of shops &amp; attractions! These include ramen shops, boba cafes, bookstores and more, each with unique inventories and effects.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Building.gif?t=1710273412"><br/><br/><i><strong>Manage your shops</strong></i><br/>Attract customers with everything from floral bouquets to karaoke! Shops you create will need your careful guidance to offer the right products at the right prices. Lead them to success and make your neighborhood thrive.<br/><br/><i><strong>Watch your villagers live their lives</strong></i><br/>Once you start the day, you'll get to see each villager react to your street and offer helpful feedback on how to improve! Memorize their preferences and refine your street the following day.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Review.gif?t=1710273412"><br/><br/><i><strong>Reach your objectives</strong></i><br/>Complete missions to unlock new levels with more buildings, villager types, and other surprises.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/Features.png?t=1710273412"><br/><br/>What Minami Lane offers:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>2-4 hours of play time<br/></li><li>Create and customize your own adorable street<br/></li><li>Manage shops by adjusting their inventory, recipes, and prices<br/></li><li>Play strategically to complete each level's mission objectives<br/></li><li>Keep the streets clean by picking up trash<br/></li><li>Tanukis and cats!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Ramen.gif?t=1710273412"><br/><br/>What Minami Lane does not offer:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hardcore strategy<br/></li><li>Multiplayer<br/></li><li>Tons of missions<br/></li><li>New levels after release</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/GameModes.png?t=1710273412"><br/><br/>In Minami Lane's missions, you'll need to strategically plan each day and use random events to your advantage to complete multiple objectives. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Bike.gif?t=1710273412"><br/><br/>The sandbox mode focuses on creativity and relaxation, allowing you to immerse yourself in the peaceful, cozy world without the stress of objectives.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/DevTeam.png?t=1710273412"><br/><br/>Minami Lane is the collaborative effort of Dorian (Doot), Doriane (Blibloop) and Antoine (Zakku). Doot, a former data scientist turned game developer, brings light strategy and management gameplay, while Blibloop breathes life into the isometric world with her Studio Ghibli-inspired, hand-drawn designs. Zakku adds the finishing touches with joyful, wholesome music compositions and soundscape. We really hope you will enjoy this tiny game we made with love 💕<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678990/Minami_Lane/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678990/Minami_Lane/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR WARS™: Dark Forces Remaster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2292260/STAR_WARS_Dark_Forces_Remaster/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_8.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/><i>Star Wars</i>™: Dark Forces Remaster has been brought to life by the team at <strong>Nightdive Studios</strong>, fully remastered through its proprietary KEX engine, allowing the game to run on modern gaming devices at up to 4K resolution at 120FPS. New and returning players will enjoy <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces Remaster’s upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<br/><br/>The original 1995 <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces raised the bar for FPS games, offering players a significant degree of movement and interactivity, a large selection of items and power-ups, and engaging environments. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_10.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/>In the first <i>Star Wars</i> FPS video game, players assume the role of Kyle Katarn, a defector of the Galactic Empire turned mercenary for hire. Katarn joins the Rebel Alliance’s covert operations division tasked with infiltrating the Galactic Empire, where he discovers the secret Dark Trooper Project. The development of this powerful new series of Imperial battle droids and power-armored stormtroopers stands to strengthen the Empire’s grip on the galaxy unless Katarn and the Rebel Alliance intervene.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>All fourteen original levels, featuring <i>Star Wars</i>™ worlds and capital ships<br/></li><li>Use your ability to jump, duck, and crawl to solve puzzles and defeat enemies<br/></li><li>Your Personal Digital Assistant provides you with in game information such including map, inventory, and mission briefing<br/></li><li>Engaging first-person ground combat featuring ten weapons and twenty types of enemies<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS visuals<br/></li><li>Advanced 3D rendering enables updated lighting and atmospheric effects<br/></li><li>Modern gamepad support adds a new weapon wheel, and rumble<br/></li><li>Controller Support - vibration and gyro controls <br/></li><li>A variety of power-ups are made available to the player, including health, shields, weapons and ammunition<br/></li><li>For combat, the player may use fists, explosive landmines and thermal detonators, as well as blasters and other ranged weapons<br/></li><li>Includes immersive environmental puzzles and mazes </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_1.gif?t=1709278523"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709870080"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solium Infernum</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1893810/Solium_Infernum/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare yourself for Solium Infernum, the grand strategy game of politics, intrigue and betrayal, set in the ultimate arena of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingDarkSide2.gif?t=1710236812"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_IndulgeYourDarkSide_eng.png?t=1710236812"><br/>Satan's mysteriously vanished and Hell is in an uproar. Play as one of eight all-powerful and menacing Archfiends and indulge your Machiavellian dark side. Command legions, enlist champions, cast sinister rituals, and trick, rob, and insult your rivals to be crowned Hell’s new Dark Majesty.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingStrategy2.gif?t=1710236812"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_StrategyFromHell_eng.png?t=1710236812"><br/>Experience Solium Infernum's legendary devilish political machinations. Requiring nerves of steel and a true heart of darkness, every order you give will have lasting consequences. Get into the minds of your rivals, second-guessing their every move both on the map and on the floor of Hell’s parliament as you sling insults and demands in the only truly political strategy game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Eight playable Archfiends<br/></li><li>Eight single-player Chronicles<br/></li><li>Single-player Skirmish mode<br/></li><li>Revelations Tutorial Scenario<br/></li><li>Sessional and Asynchronous 2-6 player Multiplayer<br/></li><li>Dozens of Infernal Legions, including unique enormous Titans. <br/></li><li>Champion Praetors and dark Artifacts fit for any Archfiend!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingMulitplayer.gif?t=1710236812"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_InfernalMultiplayer_eng.png?t=1710236812"><br/>Play 2-6 player multiplayer games with your soon-to-be ex-friends in a single session of deceit and politics, or put your friendships to the test in quick daily bursts with Solium Infernum’s infamous asynchronous multiplayer for a truly harrowing scheme-in-your-sleep experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/Heading_DarkArt2.gif?t=1710236812"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_DivineMadness_eng.png?t=1710236812"><br/>If you love dark art, you’re in the right place. Brimming with striking visions of Hell unlike anything you’ve seen before, Solium Infernum is an infernal feast for the eyes with multitudes of individual dark paintings to enjoy. Every item of the game is accompanied by mind-blasting artwork, a feat declaring Solium Infernum a winner of the 2022 Game Makers Sketchbook.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingRessurect.gif?t=1710236812"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_CultClassic_eng.png?t=1710236812"><br/>Originally inspired by Milton’s epic poem, Paradise Lost, League of Geeks’ (known for seminal digital board game Armello) sophomore title is a re-imagining and modernisation of Vic Davis’ critically acclaimed cult-classic of the same name, hailed as a masterpiece of strategy game design. <br/><br/>Once again, prepare to lose yourself within ‘the cold glory of a difficult decision’ as we resurrect Solium Infernum from the depths of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/label_praise.png?t=1710236812"><br/>Note: The following quotes refer to the original Solium Infernum (2009) by Vic Davis.<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum is a political wargame set in hell… The game is now finished, and none of the friends survived. By which I mean, we all hate each other now.”</i> <br/>- Rock Paper Shotgun<br/><br/><i>“It’s a game about playing other people, in both senses of the word…. This is game design based on psychology as much as rules.” </i><br/>- Quarter to Three<br/><br/><i>“More than any game I've played in years, Solium Infernum nails the sensation of staring at a screen and losing yourself in the cold glory of a difficult decision.”</i><br/>- Game Developer (formerly Gamasutra)<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum kicked my knees out from under me ... this game took my past experience with strategy games and threw it, like a pro basketball player, into a bin eighty feet away.”</i><br/>- Eurogamer<br/><br/><i>“One of the best games of the year.”</i><br/>— Three Moves Ahead<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_toReign.png?t=1710236812"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calendar Notess</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2845970/Calendar_Notess/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Calendar Notess: Transform Your Daily Plans into Art</h2>"Calendar Notess" turns calendar management into art. Taking notes on days, adding tags, tracking completion statuses, adding special icons to the calendar, visualizing all this information with graphs, and the ability to export to PDF... All these features offer an experience that goes beyond just organizing your daily life.<h2 class="bb_tag">Main Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li><strong>Tagging and Status Tracking:</strong> Add tags to your notes and mark your tasks as 'Done' to easily manage and track all your tasks.<br/> </li><li><strong>Customizable Icons:</strong> Add special icons to your days to personalize your calendar. Quickly recognize important days and tasks with visual cues.<br/> </li><li><strong>Advanced Graphing:</strong> Visualize your notes and tags with various graphs. Easily analyze your progress and efficiency.<br/> </li><li><strong>PDF Export:</strong> Export your calendar and notes to PDF. Save and share your plans outside the digital world.</li></ul>How Does It Make a Difference?<br/>"Calendar Notess" is not just a calendar app, but also a tool that enriches your daily life. It contains all the details that will make your day more efficient, whether in your personal or professional life. It maximizes time management by keeping your events, meetings, tasks, and special moments together.<br/>Who Is It For?<br/>It's ideal for people of all ages and professions. Students, professionals, managers, home administrators, and more... If you want to manage your time effectively, visualize your plans, and enjoy every moment, "Calendar Notess" is the right choice for you.<br/><strong>Get Started!</strong><br/>Managing your time and organizing your life has never been this easy and enjoyable. Transform your plans into art with "Calendar Notess" and live every day with maximum efficiency. Download now and discover the innovative face of calendar management!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProtectHeart</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2791010/ProtectHeart/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							ProtectHeart is a strategy and defense game. Your objective is to protect the heart from various enemies, from turtles to fighter jets. You'll get experience points for defeating each enemy, once you have enough points you'll be given an upgrade opportunity that will last for the rest of the game! You need to pick carefully, it could be the difference between surviving and failing.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Forged Wedding</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2656650/My_Forged_Wedding/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a Steam version of a hit visual novel game released on the mobile reader app Love 365: Find Your Story by Voltage Inc. It is a collection of romantic, richly illustrated interactive stories with the following premise:<br/><br/>On a whim, the heroine ends up in a fake marriage to a man she's just met. The two move in together and play at wedded bliss, but spending each day together brings them inevitably closer. What was once just pretend starts to feel real... <br/>Enjoy the will-they-won't-they excitement of newlywed life that begins with a lie in My Forged Wedding!<br/><br/>An opening movie and adventure feature have been added to the Steam release, so even players that have previously read the app version will discover more things to enjoy.<br/><br/><strong>The Story:</strong><br/>"Marry me... Only a month would do."<br/><br/>Due to a twist of fate, you're now pretending to be the wife of a man you've just met. At first, you're against the idea of this fake marriage, but as the days go on and you get to know one another, your mutual attraction deepens...<br/><br/><strong>Characters:</strong><br/>Yamato Kougami  "Physics teacher"<br/>Takamasa Saeki  "Author"<br/>Ren Shibasaki     "Scientist"<br/>Takao Maruyama "Lawyer"<br/>Yuta Kajima        "Comedian"<br/><br/><br/><strong>Contents:</strong><br/>Includes "Main Stories" in the App "Love 365: Find Your Story."<br/>Follows Yamato, Saeki, Ren, and Takao's stories up to "Honeymoon: Epilogue."<br/>Stories for Yuta are included up until "Wedding Bells: Epilogue."						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ElbmarKs</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1856830/ElbmarKs/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1856830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>After surviving more than 3000 years of dissension, fighting, and self-destruction finally we learned to leave together with mother nature and each other, but now mankind needs to face a new, never seen, powerful, external enemy.<br/><br/>Nobody knows where they came from but we realized quickly we have to fight to survive.<br/><br/>A small talented scout team gave their life to localize the base of the alien intruders, scientists working day and night created an enhanced version of our probably biggest invention of all time, a teleport that can send the brave human fighters right inside the enemy base.<br/><br/>But the crux is just coming right now, our heroes must search and acquire all the possible information about the enemy base to hopefully be able to destroy it ...</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1856830/extras/Cover_base.png?t=1710283245"><br/><br/>During the game, you must, destroy lurking enemies, or just avoid or take over them, find and use hidden aids, destroy, deactivate, and avoid different kinds of gates, get through enemy waves, and be patient, accurate, and quick when it's needed, test your memory in the labyrinths.<br/>Do not forget to collect the missing pieces of the enemy base blueprint on each level to get to the next one and be able to unlock new spaceships!<br/><br/>You can select from 3 Difficulty levels, Practice, Normal, and Classic. <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> In Practice difficulty mode you have checkpoints saved to continue from a given part of a level, and 5 lives to complete each and every level<br/></li><li> In Normal difficulty mode you have 3 lives to complete each and every level<br/></li><li> In Classic difficulty mode you only have 3 lives to complete the whole game</li></ul><br/>The game now has a Leaderboard too, but only Normal, and Classic mode results are participating, sorry ;)<h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Spoiler Alert! </u></h2>The game has a physics-based movement system so your space-ship moves with a bit of inertia, it could take a while to get familiar with it, figure out how to avoid or take over e.g. the enemy missiles, but do not give up, it is worth the effort I promise ;)<br/>Precision and accuracy are also key to getting through the levels and you will need stamina too as in Normal Difficulty mode you only have 3 lives to solve a single level, and in the good old Classic mode only 3 to finish the whole game!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multicrash!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2792820/Multicrash/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2792820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">What is Multicrash!</h2>Multicrash! is a simple retro-arcade-survival game where the goal is to get as many points as possible. Manage up to four roads, swapping the ship between two lanes on each road to avoid obstacles, pick up coins for points, or spawn another road. Each round starts off easy, but the speed of the game accelerates over time until surviving on just one road becomes almost unmanageable. However, there are ways to keep the round alive even after reaching max speed. Both spawning new roads and crashing will reset the game speed (yes, crashing can be good!) but remember, more roads = more points: Obviously having more roads means more coins spawn, but each coin is also worth the number of roads alive. This means that with four roads up, (4x coins spawn) x (4x coin value) = (16x efficiency!). The round ends when the last remaining road crashes. See how you compare by competing with others on the global leaderboard.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAT &amp; ONION</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781210/CAT__ONION/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781210/extras/heading9.gif?t=1710271480"><br/>A warm and whimsical cat adventure where you climb, talk, fly and smack your way to places where no cat has ever gone before!<br/><br/>Go on a short yet cosmic journey packed with curious characters, imaginative environments and good vibes.​<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781210/extras/square616_2.gif?t=1710271480"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781210/extras/features.gif?t=1710271480"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>You play as a cat!<br/></li><li>Talk, find items and use your abilities to go where no cat has ever gone before!<br/></li><li>Meet a cast of entertaining characters<br/></li><li>No combat, unless you count smacking stuff with a baseball bat<br/></li><li>An imaginative world<br/></li><li>Takes 30-60 minutes to finish: You'll experience a lot in a short time!<br/></li><li>A jazzy soundtrack<br/></li><li>Secret cat things for curious cats<br/></li><li>Made by one person<br/></li><li>Enjoy chunky pixelart, with a grand total of 8 colors!<br/></li><li>Cat</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781210/extras/seeyou4.gif?t=1710271480"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subterrain: Mines of Titan</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1573100/Subterrain_Mines_of_Titan/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FERRSBJafXZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/extras/SUB-Discord-Banner.gif?t=1710261009"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/extras/SUB-Steam-banner-about-EN.png?t=1710261009"><br/><br/>After a massive meteor strikes the icy surface of Titan, nothing is left but a vast deposit of rare minerals. The TECC mining company rushes to establish a colony on Titan and successfully tap the riches, until the colony goes dark. It takes years to mount a salvage expedition to the far flung moon of Saturn, so make it count. Restart the flow of resources and figure out what happened to the first wave of colonists.<br/><br/>Stand between the sole survivors of Camp Huygens and total obliteration by Saturn's darkest mysteries. Every turn counts in the desperate struggle for survival, as Titan will not wait around - and neither should you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/extras/SUB-Steam-banner-titanic-EN.png?t=1710261009"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Titan is an unrelenting dynamic, persistent world. Every action and step advances time and brings Camp Huygens closer to collapse, unless someone intervenes.<br/></li><li> Help surviving colonists with their tasks, assign key jobs, harvest materials, and organize crafting stations to keep the doom at bay.<br/></li><li> Manage food and water intake, keep tabs on oxygen and energy levels, and treat any sustained injuries, all while penetrating the abandoned mining tunnels beneath the surface.<br/></li><li> Track the passage of time efficiently or it might turn out that the greatest threat to Camp Huygens isn't Titan or its monsters... but you!</li></ul> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/extras/SUB-Steam-banner-darkest-EN.png?t=1710261009"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Unearth the mysteries of Saturn's most famous moon and go deep beneath its surface to face off against its many horrors.<br/></li><li> Fight the monstrosities using intuitive, brisk turn-based combat. Do you make the fight close and personal, risking death as you go toe to toe? Or plink from afar, hoping that ammo won't run out at the wrong time?<br/></li><li> Harness the power of nanomachines to unleash devastating abilities against foes, but also sacrifice the ability to physically pummel monsters into submission?<br/></li><li> Gain experience and power alongside the celestial creatures underground. Evolve and adapt tactics, or perish in the darkness of Titan's mines!</li></ul> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/extras/SUB-Steam-banner-applied-EN.png?t=1710261009"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Craft an endless array of items thanks to a small handful of allies like weapons and elbow grease.<br/></li><li> Salvage what you can, break it down into materials, and produce tools like melee weapons, firearms, protective gear, explosives, and countless survival upgrades.<br/></li><li> Enhance yourself with medical supplies and continue research to develop even better versions.<br/></li><li> Survive long enough to unearth the terrible truth of what happened to the first wave of colonists or find a way to get off the doomed moon, no one said you get both...</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Love Lost</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1873120/No_Love_Lost/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1873120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1873120/extras/Looter-and-player-fight-616x230-_256-colors_-gif-with-title.gif?t=1710265988"><br/><br/><strong>Choose your crew and shuttle down to your battleground:</strong> In this exhilarating third-person, action-adventure, a carnivorous alien planet with a vicious bite awaits your arrival! There’s only one reason to risk your life on Drosera – the lucrative resource called Nectar. Pick 1 of 2 crews to join and get ready to raid! <br/><br/>In 15-minute sessions, race through a vibrant planet with over 4 lush biomes on state-of-the-art hoverboards. Compete in quests to garner your team more Nectar and dodge perilous dangers deep within Drosera. When night falls and the real monsters come out, get back on your extraction ship stat or be left behind to become one with the planet forever!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1873120/extras/Raptor-chase-616x230-_256-colors_-with-title.gif?t=1710265988"><br/><br/><strong>Claw your way to the top: </strong>Choose your gear wisely! With a wide array of both melee and ranged weapons, as well as traps and gadgets, the chance to bring your team to victory is never out of reach…or certain fate.  <br/><br/><strong>Harvest smart or risk it all: </strong>Only those who make it on the extraction ship will leave with their Nectar, so optimize your tactics, rally your crew and use ANY means necessary to get your nectar onboard! <br/><br/><strong>Death is NOT the end:</strong> Our respawn system keeps you and your friends together in the action for the entire raid! Revive fallen teammates and plot your revenge to steal that Nectar back!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1873120/extras/whatdoesntkillyou.gif?t=1710265988"><br/><br/><strong>What kind of Raider will you be? </strong>For every day that you survive, gain perks to strengthen your resolve for the next round! Mix and match builds to get the perfect perk combination but beware! Getting stranded on Drosera means losing your perks until your next successful run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1873120/extras/Horizongif2.gif?t=1710265988"><br/><br/><strong>Discover all the planet has to offer: </strong>Drosera is a world full of mystery and much of it has yet to be revealed! Keep your eye open for continuous updates (such as new biomes, characters and gameplay additions,) being added to the world!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>FEATURES: </strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore a dangerous planet rich with sweet, sweet Nectar in 15-minute sessions!<br/></li><li>Race through DROSERA with top-of-the-line hoverboards and hoverbikes.<br/></li><li>Take part in competitive questing alongside your team and your enemies!<br/></li><li>Experience simultaneous PvP and PvE! Go head-to-head against the other crews and take on Droserian wildlife for bigger rewards!<br/></li><li>Trade in your nectar for fancy hoverboard and weapon skins, express yourself with extra emotes and more!<br/></li><li>Build your perks after every successful extraction to dominate the Raider ranks!<br/></li><li>Experience a new adventure in every game with procedurally generated quest chains!</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goblin Stone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1521970/Goblin_Stone/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FdF7NZJvSuA" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_Discord_00_Banner_616180.gif?t=1710259543"/></a><br/>Goblin Stone entrusts players with the fate of the last goblins to escape annihilation by cruel adventurers. To avoid extinction, they must build their numbers, venture back into the world, and put an end to the adventurers who hunt them. Embark on a heartwarming journey to rebuild a goblin lair and help them thrive in a turn-based roguelite where every decision counts.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_StoreGifs_5f.gif?t=1710259543"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_About_01_Bullets_Combat.png?t=1710259543"><br/>Craft the perfect goblin party by mixing classes, abilities, and genetics. Experience an innovative turn-based combat system, where the order of actions is determined by the strategic positioning of combatants.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_StoreGifs_1f.gif?t=1710259543"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_About_02_Bullets_Adventure.png?t=1710259543"><br/>Guide a merry party of goblins as they battle relentless adventurers, pompous elves, and surly dwarves. Dive into a world with nostalgic, storybook-inspired visuals, accompanied by an epic soundtrack composed by Hearthstone's Peter McConnell.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_StoreGifs_2f.gif?t=1710259543"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_About_03_Bullets_Colony.png?t=1710259543"><br/>Manage a thriving goblin colony and build your lair chamber by chamber, from the Barracks to the War Room. Carefully breed your favorite goblins, combining the finest genes and traits to cultivate a formidable lineage.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_StoreGifs_3f.gif?t=1710259543"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_About_04_Bullets_Choices.png?t=1710259543"><br/>Venture through procedurally generated adventures, where permadeath heightens the stakes. Difficult choices await as you decide which path to take and which goblins to sacrifice for survival.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_StoreGifs_4f.gif?t=1710259543"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_Infographic_Steam_EN_2.png?t=1710259543"><br/><br/>Receive exclusive news, updates, and perks by joining our active community on the <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FdF7NZJvSuA" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Goblin Stone Discord</a>.<br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FdF7NZJvSuA" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_Discord_00_Banner_616180.gif?t=1710259543"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left Behind</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2854130/Left_Behind/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854130/extras/Left_Behind_gif_1_Compressed.gif?t=1710257891"><br/><br/><strong>LEFT BEHIND</strong> Is a proudly pinoy-made realistic psychological horror game where you take on the role of a real estate agent with a client looking to sell you a property. Before finalizing the transaction, you decide to personally inspect the property. However, instead of a straightforward and quick interaction with the client, you find yourself thrust into a deeply unsettling and frightening situation.<br/><br/>This game requires the use of a microphone for certain parts of the gameplay. With your microphone, you can speak and hear your voice in real-time within the game, with effects that vary depending on your in-game location.<br/><br/>For instance, when you're inside a building, your voice will echo. However, when you're out in the open field, your voice will sound normal.<br/><br/><strong>Key Feature</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Immersive gameplay<br/></li><li>Immersive flashlight<br/></li><li>Hyper-realistic graphics<br/></li><li>Real-time voice recognition<br/></li><li> Surrounding-based voice recognition<br/></li><li>Rich Storyline<br/></li><li>Fear Inducing Atmosphere</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Always 1-1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2843820/Always_11/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2843820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Loop through the same level and spot the differences that may or may not occur.</strong><br/><br/><i>You start the game at Level 1-1, but for some reason the game just won't let you finish 1-1.<br/>Instead it will start to loop inifinitely. But you can make it stop!<br/>At each loop, there is a chance that something in the level has changed.<br/><br/>Find the change and enter the red pipe. If you think nothing has changed, simply continue to let the level loop.<br/>Each correct decision will lead you one step closer to clear level 1-1.<br/>However, if you make a wrong decision or if you couldn't find the change, you will need to start from zero again.<br/><br/>Choose the correct way consecutivley 10x, to clear level 1-1.</i><br/><br/><br/><br/>Changes occur randomly and in random order, so you can clear the game multiple times, but seeing different changes.<br/><br/>Features:<br/>Horror Anomalities - replaces few changes with a spooky version<br/>Inifinity Health - enemies can not defeat you<br/>99 Lives - start the game with 99 lives<br/>?????? - clear the game once to unlock it						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against Great Darkness Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2464480/Against_Great_Darkness_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2464480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2302150/Against_Great_Darkness/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2302150/Against_Great_Darkness/</a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2464480/extras/BrickByBrick.gif?t=1710253000"><br/>Against Great Darkness Prologue is a brick-breaker, bullet hell, roguelite. Choose your pagan deity and break free from the clutches of Lucifer. Juggle your disks to defeat your enemies as you progress through the circles of hell and confront relentless demonic bosses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2464480/extras/UniqueLoot.gif?t=1710253000"><br/>In each run, acquire powerful relics that will assist you in your escape. Juggle the disks to unleash the power they hold and discover the synergies that will truly set you free.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2464480/extras/MysteryEvents.png?t=1710253000"><br/>Choose between acquiring motes of light, purchasing items in the shop, receiving a much-needed heal, or risking it all with unique mystery events that can either reward or hinder your ascent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2464480/extras/MetaProgression.gif?t=1710253000"><br/>You may have gambled on a risky juggle that put you in harm's way and ended your run. Don't fret; the Radiant Shards you collect during your attempts can be used to empower your next run.<br/><br/><strong>FEATURES:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>1 circle of hell to explore.<br/></li><li>3 pagans to choose from.<br/></li><li>2 Distinct demonic bosses.<br/></li><li>Each attempt out of hell is unique.<br/></li><li>Make choices over unique events to gain powerful relics.<br/></li><li>100+ Items offer unique modifiers based on gameplay.<br/></li><li>Curses that really alter the way you play.<br/></li><li>Unlock new items on each run.<br/></li><li>Increase your chances by spending Radiant Shards gained on every run.<br/></li><li>Ascend through 9 progressively harder levels of difficulty.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passing By - A Tailwind Journey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2085440/Passing_By__A_Tailwind_Journey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Set in a beautiful and whimsical world of floating isles and a never-ceasing west wind, Passing By - A Tailwind Journey allows you to embark on a memorable voyage as Curly, a young balloonist, who is tasked with delivering a mysterious letter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085440/extras/PBY_Launch_GIF.gif?t=1710259717"><br/><br/>In this innovative genre hybrid of 2D puzzle platformer, survival game and adventure, you can explore the world at your own leisure, traveling from island to island by balloon ship and solving various puzzles while having to manage your resources in order to survive. An exciting adventure full of wholesome encounters and meaningful experiences awaits you!<br/><br/>Are you prepared to make the long trip through the clouds towards an unknown destination?<br/><br/><i>"The journey is its own reward. May your burner always warm you and the west wind ever favor you!"</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085440/extras/Item_Icons_1.png?t=1710259717"><h2 class="bb_tag">KEY FEATURES</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore carefully crafted levels across a large variety of colorful biomes.<br/></li><li>Meet quirky island inhabitants and make memorable friendships with fellow travelers.<br/></li><li>Solve each island's unique puzzles and find ancient secrets.<br/></li><li>Customize your balloon ship to your liking using a wide range of designs and attachments.<br/></li><li>Discover whimsical details presented in a beautiful 2D low-poly art style.<br/></li><li>Experience a fully dynamic, atmospheric score.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085440/extras/Item_Icons_2.png?t=1710259717"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMPYRE: Earls of the Deep Earth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2649500/EMPYRE_Earls_of_the_Deep_Earth/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2649500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2649500/extras/e3_logo_plate_500x.png?t=1710248834"><br/><strong><u>Overview</u></strong><br/><br/>You think the year is 1899, but you seem to have lost your memory. You can confirm you’re on a ship, and you've been told that you're heading for Shanghai. Whatever the truth may be, the only thing you have left is a name: Elias. Who is he? Why is he important? and what does he have to do with your missing past? The only way to find answers is to venture forth, exploring an exotic and unfamiliar land.<br/><br/>EMPYRE: Earls of the Deep Earth is a classic isometric tactical RPG with a story-driven campaign. Taking place before the Great Flood that changed the EMPYRE world, your journey takes you through the land of China at the end of the 19th century. The adventure ahead places you in a new setting where a Neo-Victorian renaissance with science fiction/fantasy twists is taking place! <br/><br/>On your journey, you will visit many strange villages encounter many peculiar characters, and explore mysterious underground locations. Your allies and enemies are intent on guiding you toward an unknown goal. Only time will tell if you have the bravery and ingenuity to survive the search for answers in the final EMPYRE adventure: Earls of the Deep Earth.<br/><br/><strong><u>Features</u></strong><br/><br/>- Explore a surreal new landscape with vivid locales and a colorful cast of characters.<br/>- Experience new ways to wage combat with an all new armory of 19th century Chinese weaponry.<br/>- Test your wits against improved enemy AI in battles that will challenge you at every turn!<br/>- Experiment with Ancient Chinese medicines						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DINO MERCS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1827640/DINO_MERCS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1827640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							DINO MERCS is an arcade-style roguelite deckbuilding game where you play as a veteran member of Dark Solar Defense, a shadowy private military corporation run by dinosaur mercenaries. The democratic government of the planet Velraterra has fallen to the fascist forces, and you've been hired to scavenge and compete with rival mercenary groups. To survive, you will go on operations, engage in fierce combat, and defend your forward operating base from attackers.<br/><br/>FEATURES:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <i>Strategic Deckbuilding:</i> In order to survive and complete your mission, craft a powerful deck from a growing collection of cards.  <br/></li><li> <i>Multiple Playable Characters:</i> Try out different cards and ways of playing by playing as one of three unique playable characters, with more to come! <br/></li><li> <i>Fight Enemy Mercs:</i> Fight 15+ different enemy dinosaur mercenaries, including Merc Killers, elite enemies that will test your limits. <br/></li><li> <i>High Score Chaser:</i> The game's infinite nature and arcade style of play allows for ever-escalating levels of power and challenge.<br/></li><li> <i>Missions:</i> Want a shorter, more focused play session? Missions are for you! Go on a mission and complete the objective while building a powerful deck and fighting enemy mercs. </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Games Challenge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2673590/Winter_Games_Challenge/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Faster, farther, higher! </h2><br/>Fly like an eagle, perform spectacular dramatic half-pipe stunts and race down the ice track or across the slopes. Take on sporting challenges in eight action-packed winter sports disciplines. Play alone against the AI or together with up to three friends and experience thrilling competitions packed full of fun: Set the record and win the trophy!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>5 tournaments with varying levels of difficulty<br/></li><li>Arrange your own sports event<br/></li><li>Local multiplayer mode for up to 4 athletes <br/></li><li></li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">8 cool winter sports:</h2>• Freestyle skiing<br/>• Snowboard<br/>• Curling<br/>• Giant slalom<br/>• Alpine skiing<br/>• Ski jumping<br/>• Luge<br/>• Bobsleigh						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrath of the Roothless</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827490/Wrath_of_the_Roothless/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							When Jacob, a disheveled war veteran, gets startled by a massive quake and accompanying roar of destruction he fears the worst.<br/>He hurries over to his home and sees it beyond wrecked, someone threw down an entire wall on top of his house!<br/>This is the final straw, he grabs the things closest to him, a Drumstick and a Trashcan Lid, and vows his revenge.<br/><br/>Now Ruthless and Roofless, whoever did this shall know his Wrath!<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/>Wrath of the Roothless is a randomly generated action roguelike, follow Jacob and punch through hordes of enemies, unleashing magical chicken powers along the way. Collect wrath from your slain enemies and improve your ability to brawl. Every level features a chance to earn a favor of the gods, these can further change your gameplay experience.<br/><br/><strong>About Wrath of the Roothless</strong><br/>Wrath of the Roothless is a game about revenge, and dispensing it to monstrous enemies. Raking up crystalized wrath and scoring on the Rock of Remembrance. Currently the game features 1 playable environment type for runs, and 1 boss monster. <br/><br/><br/><i>No plans are present to further develop the game, other than fixing critical bugs.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divine Journey 2: The Five Books of Moses</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2828150/Divine_Journey_2_The_Five_Books_of_Moses/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2828150/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"The Five Books of Moses" serves as a compelling sequel to the acclaimed Divine Journey: The Life of Jesus. In this immersive game, players embark on a profound exploration of the foundational stories from the Bible across multiple chapters. Dive into the epic narratives of these ancient texts, experiencing the miracles, laws, and divine guidance that laid the groundwork for a nation. Engage with 13 unique types of minigames, each designed to enhance your understanding of these ancient tales.<br>
As you progress, encounter carefully selected quotes from the Bible, adding a spiritual layer to the gaming experience. Whether you're deciphering ancient texts, uncovering hidden symbolism, or solving interactive puzzles, the biblical quotes offer reflections on the profound themes explored in the game. <br>
"The Five Books of Moses" transcends traditional gaming, providing a contemplative experience that encourages players to connect with the timeless wisdom embedded in these sacred scriptures. Immerse yourself in the sacred narratives in a journey through the Bible's foundational books.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Of Pharaohs</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1515920/Tomb_Of_Pharaohs/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1515920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Collect keys to unlock the "Pharaohs Tomb" and fight his remains to pass the level!  Dodge traps, scorpions and mummies in a procedurally generated maze with an infinite amount of levels.  Collect coins to unlock characters, upgrade them and increase rewards!  How deep into the tomb you can go?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warped Continuity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2761290/Warped_Continuity/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Warped Continuity is a puzzle platform game based on the Indie game Continuity, but it includes the ability to reverse gravity, create a block, and remove blocks in some levels.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contra: Operation Galuga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2235020/Contra_Operation_Galuga/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2235020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A new entry in the legendary Contra series is here! Contra: Operation Galuga is a thorough reimagining of the classic run-'n'-gun action game from the '80s, featuring modern graphics and sound, new stages, new enemies and bosses, new play mechanics, an updated weapons system, and explosive co-op combat for up to two players in Story Mode or four players in Arcade Mode!<br>
<br>
When the Red Falcon terrorist group takes over the Galuga Islands off the coast of New Zealand, elite Contra commandos Bill Rizer and Lance Bean springs into action, initiating an all-out war in which the fate of mankind hangs in the balance!<br>
<br>
Run, jump, and shoot your way through eight levels using a devastating arsenal - including the spread shot, laser, and homing missiles - now with stackable upgrades and awesome Overload abilities! The intense action is customizable with three difficulty settings plus a variety of additional challenge options. The true Contra legacy begins now!<br>
<br/>
Key Features:<br/>
•The original run-'n'-gun game is back, reimagined and more action-packed than ever!<br/>
•Attack aggressively across eight explosive stages! Infiltrate the jungle, ascend the waterfall, speed through an enemy base on a hovercycle, and more!<br/>
•Multiple playable characters with distinct abilities!<br/>
•Epic, screen-filling boss battles!<br/>
•New and fan-favorite weapons, now with stackable upgrades and incredible Overload abilities!<br/>
•Multiple difficulty options and a wealth of extra content						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The witch and the bottle of concepts</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2489670/The_witch_and_the_bottle_of_concepts/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2489670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The witch's mage is to pick up the broom and hit hard!</strong><br/><br/>A fantasy pixel-art Metroidvania game. With your reliable companion, discover the island and break the 4th mirror, find the truth under the meta mask!<br/><br/>Villains invade the island, and the only witch on the island has lost her memory and magic power?<br/>You'll wield your broom to swat baddies hard, and the collector in your broom will charge up your partner to cast speciality spells.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2489670/extras/未命名.gif?t=1710225027"><br/><br/>In our fantasy pixel world, you can:<br/>Explore the entire small island with your elf companion at a seamless map, cross fields of wheat and snow, climb the library and magic tower.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2489670/extras/未命名1.gif?t=1710225027"><br/><br/>Hit your enemies and Charge the magic power on your broom: <br/>Will you use a sword or throwing knives? Magic balls are also good! Hundreds of abilities and combinations for you to build!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2489670/extras/IMG_202310176993_600x359.png?t=1710225027"><br/><br/>Together with the charming residents of the island, search for the secrets of the deserted island and uncover the truth behind the demon king!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2489670/extras/Sprite-0005.png?t=1710225027"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Trick: Double Blind</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2254710/Death_Trick_Double_Blind/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254710/extras/Header-2.gif?t=1710225911"><br/><br/>Come one, come all to Morgan’s Traveling Circus, the greatest show in America! Or it was, until its star, Hattie, disappeared. <br/><br/>Take a step back in time to the middle of the mid 20th century, as a magician and a private eye tackle the case of the missing magician. Marvel at lush pulp art visuals and an atmospheric soundtrack that harkens back to the golden days of the traveling circus! But never forget, there’s a murderous mystery afoot.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254710/extras/MainStage_crazyborder_retime_1.gif?t=1710225911"><br/>Take control of two protagonists tackling the case from different perspectives: one a fellow magician and colleague of the victim, and the other a private eye grappling with a bout of amnesia. Use their unique skills and expertise to befriend and interrogate a huge cast of characters, investigate various locations, and hunt down contradictions in a winding narrative filled with twists, turns, and treachery sure to shock and delight would-be detectives and circus fans alike.<h2 class="bb_tag">Turns &amp; Action Points:</h2> With only limited actions one can take before passing time, plan carefully about which clues to pursue and which locations to investigate.<h2 class="bb_tag">Twin Perspectives:</h2> Alternate between a magician and a private eye: two different characters, with access to different information., and put the pieces together to see the bigger picture! <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254710/extras/2Perspective_retime.gif?t=1710225911"><h2 class="bb_tag">Unique "Contradiction" Mechanic:</h2> Gather evidence in your collection before combining conflicting reports to create a "contradiction," then challenge the deceptions of those who would deceive a master investigator!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254710/extras/Contradiction-2.gif?t=1710225911"><br/><br/>🕵️‍♂️ <strong>8</strong> fully animated characters with their own goals, histories, and motives. <br/>🎪 <strong>10</strong> gorgeous locations to investigate and revisit.<br/>🎨 <strong>50+</strong> set of CGs and <strong>300+</strong> panels of comics to bring the circus to life <br/>🔠 A sprawling and non-linear narrative to engross and enchant <br/>🎭 Different unlockable endings for each major character.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254710/extras/Tarot-card-2.gif?t=1710225911"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2254710/Death_Trick_Double_Blind/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2254710/Death_Trick_Double_Blind/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimal Escape</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2782420/Minimal_Escape/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Fantasy, fairy tale-like, puzzle adventure game<br>
Simple gameplay with difficult puzzles.<br>
Experience a fairy tale fantasy in a puzzle adventure game.<br>
Minimal Escape is a story about a small fairy in a fantasy world.<br>
Is the dark world you travel simply a little nightmare, or our future to come?<br>
Traverse and purify the polluted world and try to restore its former beauty.<br>
<br>
Main Features<br/>
•A mix of arcade, adventure, and puzzle<br/>
•Incorporates the laws of physics<br/>
•24 alluring and addicting stages<br/>
•Advanced puzzles that require all of your brainpower<br/>
•Exquisite 3D animation created with the Unity engine<br/>
•Offers a dreamlike, surreal experience with its highly immersive visuals and audio<br/>
•Diverse and original level designs<br/>
<br/>
How to play<br/>
•Solve complicated puzzles, and escape and survive against all sorts of obstacles<br/>
•Find hidden elements, explore paths, and collect stars<br/>
•Simple controls with directional and jump buttons that require a little bit of luck<br/>
<br/>
Minimal Escape is a top quality indie/arcade/adventure mobile game.<br/>
Listen to the echoes of the environment.<br/>
The world's fateful secrets lie before you.<br/>
Play this beautiful odyssey now!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saving Mrs. Hinako</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626240/Saving_Mrs_Hinako/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>"Whoa... You're Kiichi, aren't ya?!"</i><br/>My next-door neighbor is none other than Hinako, the older girl who I used to know back during my childhood. All the memories from my childhood come flooding back to me. It's just as nostalgic as it is surprising.<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A heartfelt visual novel<br/></li><li>Japanese voice acting</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">STORY</h2><br/>When Kiichi moves into a new apartment after transferring from a technical school to a university, his next-door neighbor happens to be Hinako, a former delinquent once feared by many back in their hometown.<br/><br/>Seeing Hinako is still as beautiful and cool as when they were younger digs up long-buried memories, rekindling Kiichi’s forgotten crush. However, there is one poignant difference this time around—Hinako is now a married mom!<h2 class="bb_tag">CHARACTER</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626240/extras/chara01_en.png?t=1710205238"><br/><strong>Hinako Kurose</strong><br/><i>Voice: Kazuha</i><br/>Hinako’s tumultuous journey into delinquency sprouted from cracks in her strained relationship with her father. In her late teens, she entered into a dubious relationship with her current husband and eventually married him.<br/><br/>With her unapologetically wild demeanor, she wields a tongue that could cut glass. However, beneath this rough exterior is a whole lot of heart—which tends to land her in her fair share of overly friendly situations...<br/><br/>Due to her challenging upbringing, she dreams of building a joyful and happy home.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2839310/Evader/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2839310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Move white square with the arrow keys on your keyboard to dodge red squares.<br>
<br>
This is a game used to test market for those who like challenges and easy gameplay.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scribble</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2826650/Scribble/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2826650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Feel like a real designer and follow this strange but friendly character in this 2D, monochromatic adventure.<br>
<br>
In a fun game with fluid movement and simple, responsive controls.<br>
<br>
Venture between vertical and horizontal platforms, avoiding traps and cliffs.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exanimum: The Silent Call</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2601030/Exanimum_The_Silent_Call/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2601030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Exanimum: The Silent Call - It is a first-person indie psychological horror game.<br/><br/>The terrifying and bizzare events that happened to Jason and his daughter Jessica on the road to Greenfield town are dragging them into this eerie adventure, leading them into an unknown world. As Jason and Jessica venture deeper into the depths of the forest, an unsettling silence envelops their surroundings, the birds cease their songs, the fog thickens, and the rain intensifies. However, fear is silently approaching with every step they take, relentlessly pursuing them.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2601030/extras/ETSC.gif?t=1710179723"><br/><br/>Creepy Atmosphere: The game immerses players in a creepy atmosphere by drawing them into dark areas with realistic sound effects and graphics.<br/><br/>Psychological Tension: Players experience tension-filled moments in a journey filled with terrifying secrets and threats.<br/><br/>Fear could be approaching at any moment, providing players with constant suspense.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebel Transmute</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1191660/Rebel_Transmute/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/Rebel_Transmute_Logo_Decorated_Steam.png?t=1710176486"><br/><br/>In this modern metroidvania you play as Moon Mikono, a space scrapper turned adventurer on a mission to uncover the true fate of her missing mother.<br/><br/>To accomplish this mission in your own, unique way you'll be swapping out game changing augments to suit your playstyle.  Aggressive and greedy?  Inquisitive and cautious?  Maybe you just want an army of friendly creatures!  With over 50 unique upgrades, Rebel Transmute allows you to play through a classic sci-fi adventure in YOUR style.<h2 class="bb_tag">CHALLENGING AND CUSTOMIZABLE COMBAT</h2>Use a variety of spells known as Bloodcasts, your trusty Foray-issued Blaster, and a variety of game changing Augments to take on a world of dangerous creatures and space travelers.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/16.gif?t=1710176486"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXPLORE AND MAP A VIBRANT SCI-FI WORLD</h2>The sprawling world of Rebel Transmute is full of stunning vistas: From vibrant greenery in the Overgrowth, to the fluorescent reefs of the Coral Fissure, to the sparkblood crystal-strewn Surface.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/09.gif?t=1710176486"><h2 class="bb_tag">Additional Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Encounter over <strong>80 unique enemies</strong> and over <strong>10 formidable bosses</strong>! From mutated worms and electrified beasts, to rogue AI's and gigantic bugs. All offering different and exciting challenges and interactions.<br/></li><li>Discover <strong>game-changing abilities</strong> hidden throughout the outpost.  Spin Bash, Wall Jump, and Void Dash your way across an interconnected network of tunnels, caverns, and research laboratories!<br/></li><li>Augment your playstyle with <strong>48 optional upgrades</strong> that can drastically change how you play the game.  Fight alongside a reprogrammed drone, twist your attacks into spiraling laser blasts, or even summon tentacles to block projectiles!<br/></li><li>Make use of a versatile mapping system to help track your progress.  Use custom markers, track your completion percentage, and find hidden terminals to uncover unexplored areas.<br/></li><li>Experience a <strong>personal and heartfelt story</strong>. As Moon searches for her mother she’ll also encounter various robot life, all with their own stories, personalities, and quests.<br/></li><li>A <strong>hand-painted pixel art</strong> aesthetic lends each and every character, enemy, and sector a personal touch.<br/></li><li>An immersive and atmospheric score, crafted to perfectly match every moment, from bombastic fights to solemn exploration.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project 13: Taxidermy Trails</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2492740/Project_13_Taxidermy_Trails/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2492740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Project 13: Taxidermy Trails, a Walking Simulator set in a mesmerizing Taxidermy Museum. In this immersive experience, you assume the role of an kidnapped Probant forced to find a way to escape. Complete all 13 Walks to get out of this Nightmare.<br>
<br>
Your mission is clear: report any anomalies you encounter during your walks. But beware, a single misstep means starting over. Only by consistently reporting accurately will lead to the real Exit.<br>
Key Features:<br>
<br>
Repeating Museum Corridor: Explore a hauntingly repetitive environment, where each step could lead to discovery or deception amidst the eerie displays of taxidermy.<br>
<br/>
Over 35 Anomalies: Uncover the secrets hidden within the museum as you encounter over 35 unique anomalies. Stay very vigilant, as every detail holds significance.<br/>
<br/>
Confirmation After Each Walk: After each walk, confirm whether you experienced any anomalies. Your precision determines your progress.<br/>
<br/>
Escape on the 13th Walk: Success lies in your ability to navigate the corridors and accurately report anomalies. Reach the 13th walk unscathed, and you may find the exit.<br/>
<br/>
Variable Duration: The duration of your expedition is unpredictable, ranging from 40 minutes to "a lot longer." Sharpen your senses and hone your observation skills to expedite your journey.<br/>
<br/>
Embark on this surreal adventure where reality blurs, and your choices shape your destiny. Are you prepared to unravel the mysteries of Project 13: Taxidermy Trails and overcome the challenges that lie ahead? The museum corridors await – enter if you dare						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EnGaCho Dreamy Butterfly</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2810380/EnGaCho_Dreamy_Butterfly/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"EnGaCho" is an arcade-style  side-scrolling action game where you advance while defeating enemies and earning money.<br/>The main character "EnGaCho'' goes on a journey to defeat the evil nouveau riche and help the people who are suffering from poverty...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810380/extras/Dotto.png?t=1710173857"><h2 class="bb_tag">When you are in trouble, money will solve the problem!</h2>EnGaCho's journey will be tough. You should use the money you earn to power up EnGaCho.<br/>It is up to the player to decide whether to be aggressive or focus on durability.<h2 class="bb_tag">100 stages in total!</h2>However, that doesn't mean you have to clear everything. There are many warp zones within the stages.<br/>You can attack the final boss using the shortest route, or you can work hard to earn a score. Again, it's up to the player.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810380/extras/Dotto2.png?t=1710173857"><h2 class="bb_tag">tips</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Don't miss the power-up items scattered throughout the stage.<br/></li><li>Once you cleared a stage, you can play it as much as you like in Practice mode.<br/></li><li>If you save money instead of spending it, you can get more money and score.<br/></li><li>Also check out the SHOP on the title scene.<br/></li><li>Boss battles should be fought with proper countermeasures.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810380/extras/Dotto3.png?t=1710173857"><br/><br/>Make full use of all options and grab glory!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARCH ALL - MOUSES</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2853610/SEARCH_ALL__MOUSES/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2853610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">SEARCH ALL - MOUSES</h2> is a hidden object game in which you need to find all the mice in a large location. The mice will be located in a variety of places, from the most prominent to barely noticeable places. The entire game location looks lively because of the animation elements. Find all the mice! Don't let them go unnoticed :)<br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/>- Animation elements on location;<br/>- 100 mice to find;<br/>- Pleasant soundtrack;<br/>- The gameplay can be interrupted at any time, and the game will automatically save the result;<br/>- Implemented hints! If you find it difficult to find an item, use the hint!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True Backrooms</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1085680/True_Backrooms/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1085680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The most accurate depiction of the backrooms.</strong><br/><br/>Wander an ever growing maze in this horror themed walking simulator. Try to escape before you succumb to madness or before any monsters notice you. You might not be alone. Game length varies wildly dependent on the player, but most can expect a 20-40 minute horror experience.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/>Cool retro graphics.<br/>4:3 aspect ratio.<br/>General controller support.<br/>Unique Scares.<br/>A huge labyrinthine plane of existence.<br/><br/>Too many games miss the mark when it comes to recreating the backrooms. It should be about getting lost, losing hope, and going insane from the monotony. So I have created it. Can you reach the end of the backrooms?<br/><br/><strong>Warning: This game is designed to make you experience insanity, player discretion is advised, and the game contains some flashing lights.</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Empire</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1449550/Chinese_Empire/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1813230/Wild_West_Builder/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1813230/Wild_West_Builder/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/addtowishlist_gif.gif?t=1710168458"><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FC5KpZ9AEex" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/discord.png?t=1710168458"/></a><br/><br/>Become the Chinese emperor and build your own, great empire! Put more developed buildings up using accessible raw materials. Plan carefully each path and buildings arrangement. Build your own great empire and make new history!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/1.png?t=1710168458"><br/><strong>BUILDING</strong><br/>The key to creating an economically strong empire is the skillful placement of individual buildings. Plan the location of each of them well and you will certainly use their potential effectively. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/2.png?t=1710168458"><br/><strong>CROPS</strong><br/>For centuries, cultivation in China has been an extremely important part of the economy. Make the best of what the local areas have to offer!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/3.png?t=1710168458"><br/><strong>DEVELOPMENT</strong><br/>Starting from a small village, expand your empire to colossal dimensions! Over time, build new buildings available, all the time taking care of not only economic development, but also cultural development.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/5.png?t=1710168458"><br/><strong>DYNAMIC LIGHTING</strong><br/>The entire production has been dressed in a realistic graphic design to reflect the charms of the lands in which we will be building our empire as much as possible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/4.png?t=1710168458"><br/><strong>ROAD SYSTEM</strong><br/>Thanks to a well-planned network of roads, residents will move faster, which will increase the efficiency of your economy and help keep your empire in order.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats of the Ming Dynasty</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2854690/Cats_of_the_Ming_Dynasty/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to "The Cats of the Ming Dynasty," a delightful game of finding cats. Set against the backdrop of "Along the River During the Qingming Festival," a vibrant genre painting by Qiu Ying, a Ming Dynasty Chinese painter, the game incorporates 600 hand-drawn cats, creating interesting interactions between the cats and historical scenes and characters.<br/><br/>-----Game Features-----<br/><br/>- Relax and enjoy ancient artworks.<br/>- 6 different scenic scenarios.<br/>- 600 adorable hand-drawn cats.<br/>- Comforting and relaxing music.<br/>- Cute cat sound effects.<br/>- Clicking on the game name on the cover allows you to view the complete "Along the River During the Qingming Festival."<br/>- 100 carefully crafted achievement icons.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854690/extras/1.png?t=1710166609">.<br/><br/>------------------------						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piece Link</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2690960/Piece_Link/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Drag and Connect the Pieces!</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690960/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif.gif?t=1710165404"><br/><br/>Piece Link is a puzzle game that involves arranging blocks of various shapes to fill a playing field. The main objective of the game is to fit the blocks into a designated square so that all the blocks are used and there are no empty spaces. This requires strategic placement of the differently shaped pieces into a grid, aiming to form a complete square without any holes. The game is designed to be both entertaining and educational, challenging players' problem-solving skills and spatial reasoning.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
