<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>20 Small Mazes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2570630/20_Small_Mazes/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2570630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a puzzle game with twenty small mazes. If you solve the mazes, you beat the game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>It's about 1-2 hours long, maybe.<br/></li><li>You need a keyboard and mouse to play it. One person played through the whole game on the Steam Deck, but I tried it and think it's better on PC.<br/></li><li> A few puzzles require knowledge of English. No puzzle requires sound or audio to solve it. No puzzle requires being able to recognize different colors.</li></ul> <br/>I hope you enjoy it. <br/> 						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irotoridori No Sekai HD - The Colorful World</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2591380/Irotoridori_No_Sekai_HD__The_Colorful_World/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Irotoridori No Sekai - The Colorful World is a Japanese-style visual novel produced by FAVORITE, a Japanese developer of romance visual novels.</h2></strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591380/extras/01.gif?t=1708127277"><br/><br/><strong><u>Story:</u></strong><br/><br/><i>Our story follows Kanoue Yuuma, an amnesiac boy with a special power, and Nikaidou Shinku, a translucent girl only visible to Yuuma who gave him that power. With it, he can heal any and all wounds.<br/>But it comes at the cost of the memories he's made. <br/>He lives a simple life: going to school and being scolded by his childhood friend, Kisaragi Mio, by day, and working with his master, Natsume Suzu, in the evenings.<br/>However, whenever he falls asleep, he always sees the same dream... a white world, feathers falling, and a girl calling out for him to save her.<br/>The student dormitory his master resides in has a special door in the basement, which connects their world to a myriad of different parallel ones. He travels from world to world, searching for one that resembles the scenery he sees in his dreams, but to no avail.<br/><br/>Then, one night, as he's out at night strolling around town, he spots a girl jumping from the lighthouse. <br/>Yuuma rushes over and heals her using his power, but after coming to, the girl claims to know him and his power, and asks him much like the voice in his dreams:<br/><br/><strong>"Please save me, Kanoue Yuuma."</strong></i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591380/extras/1.png?t=1708127277"><br/><strong><u>Nikaidou Shinku:</u> </strong><br/><br/>The translucent sorceress who gave Yuuma his special power.<br/>A calm, rational girl who rarely shows her emotions. She exudes an air of maturity in stark contrast to her youthful appearance.<br/>She currently sticks by Yuuma's side to achieve a certain goal--that is, to get him to experience love.<br/>"Love. Romantic feelings. I want you to experience the one thing I was never able to."<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591380/extras/2.png?t=1708127277"><br/><strong><u>Minami Kana:</u></strong><br/><br/>A strange, unknown girl who fell from the sky one night.<br/>After Yuuma managed to save her, she claimed to have known him and exchanged a certain "promise" with him many years ago, which he has no recollection of.<br/>Eventually, she comes to live alongside him in the dormitory, taking it upon herself to perform the duties of a maid.<br/>While she's able to take care of household chores, her cooking is abysmal, and she seems to be gravely lacking in the common sense department.<br/>"Please, help me, Mister Sorcerer. I'm really in quite the predicament right now!"<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591380/extras/3.png?t=1708127277"><br/><strong><u>Kisaragi Mio:</u></strong><br/><br/>Yuuma's childhood friend, who's in his class at school.<br/>Due to their longstanding friendship, teachers and other classmates often come to her for all matters concerning Yuuma, the habitual skipper, which slightly peeves her.<br/>She's noticed Yuuma getting chummy with a lot of girls who (she thinks) are cuter than her, which has secretly been a source of stress for her.<br/>Her cooking skills are excellent, as are her domestic skills in general.<br/>"That's what I like about you. You're sincere."<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591380/extras/4.png?t=1708127277"><br/><strong><u>Shikishima Kyou:</u></strong><br/><br/>A looney girl with an imaginative mind who never leaves her room in Arashiyama Hall and loves spouting off her delusions of grandeur.<br/>She has a very laid-back demeanor, and despite being a slight airhead, doesn't hold her punches when it comes to criticism.<br/>Due to being a social outcast who lives day in and day out playing and watching nothing but games and anime, she never sees the light of the sun, and accordingly, her skin is fair and white.<br/>Being a night owl, she always seems sleepy, but ever since meeting Yuuma, she's been leaving her room more and more.<br/>She also seems to possess a mysterious power...<br/>"Are you my brother?"<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591380/extras/5.png?t=1708127277"><br/><strong><u>Toumine Tsukasa: </u></strong><br/><br/>A new resident at the dorm who always seems to be running to and fro, busy as a bee.<br/>She's a grade below Yuuma at school, and to pay for her tuition and living expenses, she works until late at night at the local bathhouse.<br/>She's honest to a fault and hard-working, but also very stubborn. Once something gets into her head, it can be hard to convince her otherwise.<br/>She also has a habit of tripping over nothing, although that isn't to say she's clumsy in general.<br/>She can handle household chores with ease and excels in particular at doing menial tasks.<br/>"The local baker man is a god incarnate!"						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caribbean Legend</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2230980/Caribbean_Legend/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i><strong>Based on Sea Dogs series and inspired by Sid Meier's Pirates!</strong></i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/Wishlist_Follow_ENG.gif?t=1708054173"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/История_EN.gif?t=1708054173"><br/><br/>Welcome to the Caribbean in 1654 AD, a place teeming with opportunities and mysteries. Assume the role of Charles de Maure, a young French noble who embarked on a journey to the New World to assist his brother. What initially appeared to be a simple family matter quickly evolves into a lifelong adventure.<br/>Immerse yourself in the tale of a noble brat who rises to become the most influential figure in the Caribbean. <strong>Riches, titles, power, and romance – the ultimate booty awaits, and it's up to you to seize it all.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/steamchar.jpg?t=1708054173"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Embark on a 200-hour-long journey.<br/></li><li>Undertake hundreds of quests.<br/></li><li>Freeplay, rush through the story, or combine both - you're the Captain, and your ship will sail where you command.<br/></li><li>Experience a historical narrative with a touch of mystique.<br/></li><li>Explore romantic interests and companions.<br/></li><li>Choose from various career options, from general-governor to pirate baron.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/Мир_EN.gif?t=1708054173"><br/><br/>The Caribbean Sea – a realm of dozens of islands and cities, a grand archipelago shrouded in mystery and secrets. From the summits of Indian pyramids to the ocean depths, unique rewards, quests, and curiosities await. <strong>This open world is your sandbox, you are free to explore it and shape your legend as you see fit. </strong>Your decisions determine where to go, what to do, and who to take with you. Subdue the New World or it will destroy you!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Discover dozens of islands and settlements.<br/></li><li>Build your very own colony.<br/></li><li>Explore caves, pyramids, jungles, Indian tribes, and lost cities.<br/></li><li>Visit taverns, brothels, shipyards, churches, forts, and many other points of interest.<br/></li><li>Engage in treasure hunting and gambling.<br/></li><li>Experience dynamic weather and the serene turquoise sea.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/Море_EN.gif?t=1708054173"><br/><br/><strong>Owning a warship is a privilege, a symbol of status and luxury. </strong>You are among the very few who can afford such grandeur. Begin your journey with a simple sloop and work your way up to commanding a ship of the line or even a fleet of these formidable vessels, ready to plunder cities at your whim. No one will stand in your way. Tired from leading massive armadas and the responsibility? Take command of a fast Frigate or Corvette and just free roam the Caribbean. In moments of tranquility at sea, relish the stunning views, embrace the sense of exploration, or navigate in the heart of a storm.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/valciria3_копия.png?t=1708054173"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Command dozens of ships representing the glory of the Age of Sail.<br/></li><li>Customize, paint, upgrade, and repair your vessel.<br/></li><li>Engage in unforgiving yet enjoyable naval combat.<br/></li><li>Experience intense boarding action, from the upper deck to the captain's cabin.<br/></li><li>Collect unique vessels to rule the seas.<br/></li><li>Manage booty distribution, morale, and the threat of mutinies.<br/></li><li>Assemble a formidable team of officers.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/боевка_EN.gif?t=1708054173"><br/><br/>Captains are most vulnerable when they set foot on land. Surviving naval combat can be challenging, but at least you won't die alone – your crew will stand with you till the very end. Land battles are different: dishonest, ruthless and risky for you and those who you hold dear. <strong>Bring your companions with you, poison your weapons, study the terrain, craft deadly items, and confront thugs, soldiers, pirates, and rivals head-on.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/face_201_копия.png?t=1708054173"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tailor your character's build – become a heavy swordsman, a nimble rogue, a master sharpshooter, or a silver-tongued diplomat.<br/></li><li>Equip yourself and your companions with a wide array of swords, axes, rapiers, armor, muskets, and pistols.<br/></li><li>Craft amulets, ammo, potions, and always be prepared for battle.<br/></li><li>Seek out challenges – the more you fight, the stronger both you and your character become.<br/></li><li>Command military operations from raiding to sieges.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708005696"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708005696"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smalland: Survive the Wilds</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/768200/Smalland_Survive_the_Wilds/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>"Before the time of the giants, we lived freely under the Sun and Moon. Centuries have passed, but those stories of the surface world have been passed down through the generations. Now the giants are gone, and you, Vanguard, must venture out into the wilds once more, on an urgent mission. Be brave, and do not falter…"</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/TreeLookingup.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the vast “Land of the Small" </h2>Traverse lake sized puddles, scale skyscraper sized trees, scramble through cavernous cracks in roads, as you experience a huge open world from a new perspective. Explore dense forests, hazardous swamps and strange ruins left over from the time before. Uncover lore and knowledge from hidden NPCs scattered throughout the world and learn to survive in this vast wilderness. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Land_of_Small.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Tame and ride creatures</h2>Uncover recipes that will let you tame and ride an array of critters. Leap huge distances on the back of a Grasshopper, zoom around on a Damselfly, scurry from place-to-place on a Spider. This world and its inhabitants are yours to conquer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Mounts.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive together</h2>Play alongside friends with support for up to 10 players in multiplayer. Explore together, fight together, build together and survive the wilds as a team.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Together.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build encampments on the ground or amongst the trees</h2>Scavenge or refine resources to build your encampment with multiple material tiers, from leaves and twigs to sturdy stone. Pick your favourite spot in the world and build, or scale vast trees and claim your own settlement at the top.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Housing.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Craft powerful armour sets</h2>Collect powerful armours that provide you with resistances and abilities and mix them up to personalise your appearance. Glide through the skies in winged armour, swing from tree to tree with the grappling hook and many more. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Armors.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive the Wilds</h2>Most of the creatures you encounter will see you as lower on the food chain – Ants, Cockroaches, Beetles, Wasps, and Spiders all view you as a potential meal. Weather conditions and seasons are in constant flux so if you want to survive for another day, preparation is key.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Survive_the_Wilds.gif?t=1708077077"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Rock Galactic: Survivor - Supporter Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2782850/Deep_Rock_Galactic_Survivor__Supporter_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							If you simply can't get enough of Deep Rock Galactic: Survivor then the Supporter Pack is for you. Your support fuels further development of the game, and gives you this small satchel of exclusive in-game goods as a nice bonus:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A prestigious golden skin for all four dwarf classes!<br/></li><li>A fancy supporter badge on the main menu game logo<br/></li><li>Our heartfelt and eternal thanks and gratitude &lt;3</li></ul><strong><u>Important note</u></strong>: By buying this DLC you are first and foremost showing your support for the game and for Funday (developers) and Ghost Ship (publishers). The bling-bling in the list above is really just icing on the cake!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider I-III Remastered Starring Lara Croft</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2478970/Tomb_Raider_IIII_Remastered_Starring_Lara_Croft/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2478970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover Lara Croft’s Original Adventures, Lovingly Restored</h2> <br/>Play the Original Three Tomb Raider Adventures: For the first time ever, play the complete experience with all expansions and secret levels on modern platforms in this definitive collection.<h2 class="bb_tag">Included Game Titles</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tomb Raider I + Unfinished Business<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider II + Golden Mask<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider III + The Lost Artifact</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><strong>Solve Ancient Mysteries</strong>: Uncover treasures of the ancient world by solving puzzles and unraveling mysteries lost to the ravages of time.<br/><br/><strong>Globe-trotting Adventure</strong>: Follow Lara Croft around the world and face off against deadly foes and dangerous myths.<br/><br/><strong>Lovingly Restored</strong>: Experience the classics boasting upgraded graphics, with the option to switch to the original polygon look at any time.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arzette: The Jewel of Faramore</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1924780/Arzette_The_Jewel_of_Faramore/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924780/extras/intro_gif.gif?t=1708026324"><br/><br/>After ten years of peace...the evil Daimur has returned! Princess Arzette is the Kingdom of Faramore’s only hope to restore harmony to the land!<br/><br/>In this brand new interactive action adventure game, you control the resourceful princess Arzette. Travel through multiple breathtaking locations filled with scum, villainy and secrets, speak with the locals to uncover mysteries and objectives, and take on the evil Daimur as <strong>Arzette: The Jewel of Faramore</strong> brings you the best interactive gaming experience since the invention of the CD-ROM!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924780/extras/mortar_gif.gif?t=1708026324"><br/><br/><strong>Featuring:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hand painted backgrounds and incredible sprite art.<br/></li><li>Fully voice-acted cartoon cinematics with a colorful cast of characters.<br/></li><li>A sprawling world with diverse locations and many secrets.<br/></li><li>Acquire powerful items and abilities by exploring and helping those in need.<br/></li><li>Veteran dev team including artist Rob Dunlavey, Digital Foundry's John Linneman and Audi Sorlie, voice talent Jeffrey Rath and Bonnie Jean Wilbur, and award winning composer Jake "Button Masher" Silverman.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islands of Insight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2071500/Islands_of_Insight/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Islands of Insight: a sublime shared-world puzzle game set in a fantasy realm of ancient wonders and natural beauty. Brimming with mysterious puzzles to solve, secrets to uncover, and vibrant landscapes to explore, this peaceful world of floating islands is the perfect place to unwind. Embark on a puzzle adventure of your choice, all at your own pace.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_1-Title-Journey_EN.png?t=1708109878">‎‎‏‏‎<br/>Play as a Seeker on a peaceful journey rich in exploration and puzzle-solving. Embark on the Path of Discovery and let your curiosity guide you through a breathtaking open world where the answer is always in sight.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_Gifs_Journey_HD.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_2-Title-Puzzles_EN.png?t=1708109878"><br/>Seek out and solve an unparalleled collection of over 10,000 puzzles divided across 24 puzzle types. Every corner of the world holds a new eureka moment for you to discover. From enigmas of perspective to logic problems, environmental challenges and more, the puzzles you’ll encounter vary in difficulty and have been crafted by some of the best minds in puzzle design to create an engaging experience for both newcomers and seasoned puzzle fans.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_Gifs_Puzzles_HD.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_3-Title-Exploration_EN.png?t=1708109878"><br/>Freely explore the main island’s expansive open world where most of the puzzles and secrets are found. Wander the vibrant landscapes and architecture of its 5 distinct biomes or spread your wings to glide above them. Navigate the environment’s verticality and take your game to new heights. Unlock puzzle types and new areas in the campaign by completing 20+ Enclaves housing curated puzzle challenges. Go where you want. Solve what you want. The only path here is the one you make.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/3.IOI_Steam_Gif_Exploration___Discovery_2.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_5-Title-Experience_EN.png?t=1708109878"><br/>Customize your character. Increase your puzzle masteries to level them up while earning sparks to unlock new abilities. Complete daily quests. Seamlessly interact with other players in our shared world to gain or offer a bit of guidance, or choose to figure things out entirely on your own. With puzzles that refresh over time, a new discovery awaits with every visit to the islands.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/4.IOI_Steam_Gif_An_Evergreen_Experience_2.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/>Age restrictions may apply to access this game.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2436570/DRAGON_QUEST_BUILDERS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/Toybox_Announce_Build.gif?t=1707862917"><br/>The first title in the BUILDERS series, DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS, is bringing its handy crafting features to Steam!<br/>Gather, craft and build to defeat defeat the evil Dragonlord and restore Alefgard to it's former glory!<br/>In a world made out of blocks, everything that you see can be materials used to create! Farm ingredients, craft various items and build your base to unite the people roaming the ruins. From buildings to entire towns, you have the freedom to make your village your very own.<h2 class="bb_tag">■ Story</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/Toybox_Announce_Lightning.gif?t=1707862917"><br/>BUILDERS is set in the realm of Alefgard, the setting for the first ever DRAGON QUEST game.<br/>The world of Alefgard has been plunged into darkness, its light stolen by the evil Dragonlord, and this story begins with the appearance of a young hero with a mysterious ability to build things... And so the stage is set for an epic tale in which the dark world of Alefgard is returned to life with the power of creation!<h2 class="bb_tag">■ The first DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS title, helpful crafting features include:</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/intextbanner_3.png?t=1707862917"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Place blocks remotely, or destroy blocks with ease, with just a single click of the mouse!<br/></li><li> Now Includes a helpful Undo feature, which allows you to put things back to how they were before!<br/></li><li> Now Featuring Big Bash, a useful feature introduced in DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS 2 that allows you to break all objects in a particular area in one go!<br/></li><li> Terra Incognita, BUILDERS’ free build stage, the stackable block height is doubled!<br/></li><li> Includes fun side content, like collecting figurines of NPCs and monsters, or gathering pixels and exchanging them for a variety of handy items!<br/></li><li> Use Build Cards to share buildings with other players and bring their buildings to life on your island!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">■ Includes all DLC from previous versions of DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/intextbanner_4.png?t=1707862917"><br/>The Steam version of DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS includes all of the DLC from past versions including the free build mode, Terra Incognita: Magic Carpet, Boss Monster Model Set, Astronomy Set and Pixel Ring.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/Toybox_Announce_Stack.gif?t=1707862917"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultros</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2386310/Ultros/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You wake up stranded, after seemingly crashing your ship on The Sarcophagus — a giant, space-drifting, cosmic uterus holding an ancient demonic being known as ULTROS. Trapped in the eternal loop of a black hole, you will have to explore The Sarcophagus and meet its inhabitants to understand the part you play. <br/><br/>Are you the gruesome breaker of this cycle, or can you become a link from destruction to rebirth? <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat1.png?t=1708088745"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat1.gif?t=1708088745"><br/>ULTROS is set in a multifaceted realm - a vast alien landscape teeming with life. Grounded in science fiction, ULTROS comes wrapped in an eccentric art style and a mystical soundtrack from the visionary El Huervo, renowned for his work on Hotline Miami. ULTROS explores meta-themes of mental health, life, death, and karmic cycles through deep lore and environmental storytelling.       <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat2.png?t=1708088745"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat2.gif?t=1708088745"><br/>Experience brutal, intimate, close-quarter combat with cosmic lifeforms, driven by a sense of urgency – where precision is paramount and every cut of your blade counts. Yet this intense combat is juxtaposed with cultivating the greenery and tending to plant life in The Sarcophagus, providing precious moments of contemplation and peace. In turn, this grants deeper access to obscured paths.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat3.png?t=1708088745"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat3.gif?t=1708088745"><br/>The rich world of ULTROS holds many secrets for those curious enough — and fearless enough — to seek them out. A unique loop-based mechanic will allow you to start over at key moments in the story, providing opportunities to unfold such secrets, unlock different areas of the world and new abilities on a branching skill tree. Experiment with and master your own specific fighting style as you explore the world of ULTROS. Each loop brings you closer to the truth...						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Will:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802530/Space_WillPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 10 in the prologue, 59 in the official version<br/>Galaxy: 2 in the prologue, 6 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><strong>Sixty basic cores, hundreds of base station equipment, and thousands of chips, you can freely cooperate and shoot through the dual-angle joystick operation in a survival Roguelike game! Explore the sci-fi space and build your strongest battleship!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Step 1: Choose a "core" as your basic role<br/>Step 2: Choose a "crew" as your initial weapon<br/>Step 3: Select a galaxy for exploration</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game will continuously collect new "units" or "chips" during the exploration process<br/>Using "crew" can expand weapons and enhance combat effectiveness for your warship<br/>Using "chips" can enhance various abilities of your warship</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Each "core" or "unit" has a maximum of 4 interfaces. When the interfaces are used up, you cannot equip more parts, but you can also infinitely increase the number of your interfaces!<br/>Each "crew" can use the right mouse button to rotate and adjust the optimal angle for combat</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game features dual joystick shooting, with the keyboard moving and the mouse aiming at the enemy. Of course, there are many weapons that can automatically attack or be placed in the scene as traps for use~</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_TITLE_FULLSCREEN.gif?t=1708080818"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_1.png?t=1708080818"><br/> <br/>In New Eden, 1695, communities of settlers are plagued by a dreadful curse. As Banishers, step into their lives, investigate the source of evil, unravel chilling mysteries, explore diverse landscapes, and interact with unforgettable characters whose fate lies in your hands.<br/><br/>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden is an all-new title crafted by renowned studio DON'T NOD, known for their acclaimed titles such as Life is Strange and Vampyr. Immerse yourself in an intimate narrative Action-RPG, taking you on an exhilarating journey between life, death, love and sacrifices.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_2.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_FANTASY.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Play as a couple of Banishers, Red and Antea, experienced spirit hunters entrusted with the daunting task of dispelling a malevolent curse through powerful rituals. Protect the living from the threat of lingering ghosts and specters, and become a beacon of hope in a world consumed by darkness.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_3.png?t=1708080818"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_NARATION_LOVE.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Experience a heart-wrenching love story between Antea Duarte and Red mac Raith. When Antea is killed and turned into a spirit, you find yourself facing a choice. Will you uphold your oath and ascend her soul, or will you sacrifice the living in the hope of bringing her back? Your decisions will shape the fate of New Eden’s inhabitants - may they be living or dead, and determine the end of your journey.<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>BLAME</strong> the living and sacrifice their lives, holding them responsible for their actions<br/></li><li><strong>BANISH</strong> souls of the departed, condemning them to eternal suffering<br/></li><li><strong>ASCEND</strong> souls, liberating them from eternal sorrow and granting them serenity</li></ul><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_4.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_COMBAT.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Banishers are specialized in combat against undead creatures, such as specters or ghosts. Combine Red's physical arsenal with Antea's supernatural powers in a dynamic combat system. Find your own style by mixing weapon attacks and spiritual abilities. Powerful synergies will lead you to defeat New Eden’s most dangerous enemies and bosses.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_6.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_SKILL.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Unleash the full power of the Banishers by unlocking new gear and supernatural abilities. By exploring New Eden, you will find ancient artifacts, trinkets and valuable resources to enhance your equipment in preparation of future fights. In addition to your arsenal, progress in Antea’s skill trees to upgrade her devastating spectral powers and unseal new combos.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_5.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_EXPLORATION.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Investigate haunting cases in a mystical world full of dark secrets. Discover New Eden, a North America settlement marked by terrible stories and secrets of its tormented inhabitants. Understanding each resident’s motivations will be essential to guide your decisions throughout the game.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_7.png?t=1708080818"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Ninja Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_9" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🥋🐾 WELCOME TO 100 NINJA CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🗡️</h2>🗡️Join the cutest adventure in the Ninja world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of ninja themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game.<br/>😊Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x200.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Ninja Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Extra.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816000/100_Ninja_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815980/100_Ninja_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Artbook.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x1.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_10" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_11" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III - BlackCell (Season 2)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731840/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III__BlackCell_Season_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Get Call of Duty® Points* and in-game content for Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III and Call of Duty®: Warzone™.<br>
<br>
Offering includes:<br>
<br/>
- Battle Pass for Season 2<br/>
- 20 Battle Token Tier Skips<br/>
<br/>
Exclusive BlackCell Sector on the Battle Map:<br/>
<br/>
- 1100 Call of Duty® Points<br/>
- BlackCell Operator<br/>
- Assault Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Battle Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Finishing Move<br/>
<br/>
- BlackCell Bonus Topper with 11 additional reactive Operator skin alternatives and 6 Weapon Blueprints with Tracers.<br/>
<br/>
Activision may update, replace, or remove this in-game content at any time.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1708019001"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal Richards (formerly of Echos)</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1708019001"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about the future of Sheepy, limited edition merch and more.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXIT KUN</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781370/EXIT_KUN/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a game of finding differences and observing. Our game challenges players to carefully observe and spot the distinctions that lead them to the elusive "Exit KUN."<br>
<br>
Game Overview:<br>
<br>
You find yourself trapped in an enigmatic underground labyrinth, and your only goal is to reach "Exit KUN." The journey demands keen observation of your surroundings. Every detail matters, and anomalies could be your key to progress.<br>
<br>
How to Play:<br>
<br/>
Observe Carefully: Scrutinize your surroundings to uncover anomalies that may guide your way or pose a threat.<br/>
Turn Back if Needed: If anomalies are detected, swift decision-making is crucial. Turn back immediately to avoid unforeseen consequences.<br/>
Forward Momentum: Should your observation reveal no anomalies, press forward. <br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Developer Notes:<br/>
This game is inspired by Exit 8. You are free to create, upload, and monetize videos and any other content featuring Game on platforms such as YouTube, Twitch, and other video-sharing websites. The characters, places, and elements involved in the game are fictitious. Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, or events is purely coincidental.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soak &amp; Splash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2051500/Soak__Splash/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2051500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the Soak &amp; Splash! Get ready to sweat, socialize, and have a blast with your friends in this unique game that combines the best of traditional sauna culture with modern party fun.<br>
<br>
First, step into the steamy sauna and feel the heat and humidity envelop your body.<br>
<br>
Once everyone is inside, it's time to start the fun. You can start by whisking each other with broom.<br>
<br>
Feeling competitive? You can also fight with other players with sauna equipment. Or you can simply relax and enjoy the company of your friends, chatting, singing, or telling jokes.<br>
<br/>
Finally, when you've had enough of the sauna, you can cool off in the nearby pool or shower.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, this game is all about having fun, bonding with your friends, and experiencing the unique benefits of sauna culture. So why wait? Download game and get ready to sweat, laugh, and enjoy life to the fullest!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/315210/Suicide_Squad_Kill_the_Justice_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Rocksteady Studios, the creators of the Batman: Arkham series, Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is a genre-defying third-person action shooter where the ultimate band of misfits must do the impossible to save the world: Kill the Justice League.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/SSKTJL_Intro.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Join the newly “recruited” members of Amanda Waller’s infamous Task Force X (aka the Suicide Squad), Harley Quinn, Deadshot, Captain Boomerang and King Shark, as they set out on an impossible mission to Kill the Justice League. Drop into an expansive and dynamic open-world Metropolis ravaged by Brainiac’s invasion and terrorized by the heroes who once protected it. <br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/Traversal_2.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Each Squad member brings their own traversal mechanics to help them navigate a sprawling and battle-torn Metropolis, combining free-roaming exploration and combat verticality for an unforgettable experience. Players are free to experiment with a variety of different play styles to unleash maximum damage on their enemies. Whether in single player or online with up to three of your friends, players can take on this suicide mission their own way.<br/><br/>Post-launch, players can expect a continuously evolving Metropolis with free new playable villains, environments, weapons, in-game events, and more, all included with purchase of the base game.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788630/Nothing_Together/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play together. Maybe.<br/><br/>Just do Nothing as the timer goes up and climb the leaderboards. If you do Something, you lose.<br/><br/>Play in <strong>Together </strong>mode, where up to 20 players unite to do Nothing, or compete with other players in <strong>Battle Royale</strong> to find out who's the best at doing Nothing!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161700/Persona_3_Reload/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a transfer student thrust into an unexpected fate when entering the hour "hidden" between one day and the next. Awaken an incredible power and chase the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fight for your friends, and leave a mark on their memories forever. <br/><br/>Persona 3 Reload is a captivating reimagining of the genre-defining RPG, reborn for the modern era.<br/><br/>Key Features: <br/>- Experience the pivotal game of the Persona series faithfully remade with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, and signature stylish UI. <br/><br/>-Fully immerse yourself in an emotional, gripping journey with new scenes, character interactions, and additional voiceover.<br/><br/>- Choose how to meaningfully spend each day through various activities, from exploring the Port Island to forging genuine bonds with beloved characters.<br/><br/>- Build and command your optimal team to take down otherworldly Shadows and climb closer to the truth.<br/><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Deluxe Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook: Filled with 64 pages of character art, concept art, backgrounds and other illustrations from the game!<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack: Listen to newly arranged tracks from the original Persona 3 plus all-new tracks from Persona 3 Reload, presented by the Atlus sound team for a total of 60 new songs.</li></ul><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Premium Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack<br/></li><li>Persona 3 Reload DLC Pack:  P5R Phantom Thieves Costume Set, P5R Shujin Academy Costume Set, P5R Persona Set 1, P5R Persona Set 2 , P5R BGM Set, P4G Yasogami High Costume Set, P4G Persona Set</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLCARD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1201540/HELLCARD/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Hellcard</strong> is a <strong>cooperative roguelike deckbuilder</strong> that can be played in both <strong>Singleplayer </strong>and <strong>Multiplayer </strong>modes. The game takes place in the paper dungeons known from Book of Demons, and its main mechanics revolve around deckbuilding and fast-paced tactical card battles. <br/><br/>If you are excited about <strong>HELLCARD</strong>, be sure to <strong>wishlist </strong>the game on Steam. Otherwise, consider wishlisting anyway - who knows, we might surprise you yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif5_600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/>What makes <strong>HELLCARD</strong> unique and different from other deck-building games is that <strong>monster placement actually matters</strong> and can be used to your advantage.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif4_600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>HELLCARD</strong> supports <strong>co-op battles</strong> with up to three heroes facing the Archdemon's hordes. In <strong>singleplayer mode</strong>, you can descend into the dungeons solo or recruit computer-controlled companions. In <strong>multiplayer mode</strong>, your friends or strangers can help you battle the hordes of hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif1-2-3-600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/r2g_logo_fixed.png?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>Return 2 Games</strong> is a series of unique mid-core games inspired by the golden days of PC gaming. Each R2G title is a tribute to a single hit game from the '90s: a reimagining of a single universal story for a brand-new audience, using modern means and innovative, often vastly simplified gameplay mechanics.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/pillars.png?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>HELLCARD</strong> was first envisioned as a new game mode inside the Book of Demons universe, but we soon realized that its design is huge and that it should be executed as a stand-alone spin-off game. If you want to learn more about Return 2 Games or support us in the development of the series, visit the <strong>Supporter Pack</strong> store page. On release, <strong>HELLCARD </strong>will be a part of it.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/706770/Return_2_Games_Supporters_Pack/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/706770/Return_2_Games_Supporters_Pack/</a><br/><strong>Book of Demons</strong>, the first part in the series is already here, be sure to check it out as it includes a free demo. <br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/449960/Book_of_Demons/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/449960/Book_of_Demons/</a><br/>Also, be sure to check out <strong>Book of Aliens</strong>, the second book in the series and a tribute to MicroProse’ UFO: Enemy Unknown that’s also in the works:<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1196230/Book_of_Aliens/" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1196230/Book_of_Aliens/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1131620/Dominion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Expand a small kingdom to a mighty Dominion!  <br/><br/>Play the Spiel des Jahres winning boardgame beloved by millions around the world. This is the officially licensed implementation.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Reigning.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Discover the game that defined a genre, Dominion was first to popularize deck-building and remains a staple of tabletop. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/GrowYourKingdom.png?t=1707010484">Collect as many Victory Points as you can by building a powerful deck. Your deck starts out a small sad set of Estates and Coppers, but you hope that by the end of the game it will be brimming with Gold, Provinces, and the inhabitants and structures of your kingdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/BuildEngine.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Choose wisely among the 10 cards available in the tableau to create the strongest combos to dominate your opponent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CollectAllExpansions.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Make your games more exciting with additional cards and rules from up to 15 expansions including the recent Plunder expansion! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/NearInfiniteVariety.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Over one hundred thirty-two septillion possible Kingdom combinations, 500+ cards, 15 and counting expansions, and ongoing promo packs make Dominion one of the most extensive and replayable boardgames in the hobby. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CompeteComputer.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Sharpen your skills with solitaire style solo play against a robust AI, with four levels of difficulty. Our innovative AI learns through self-play. Earn Achievements and win in Recommended Sets against each AI level. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/PlayWithFriends.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Join up to 6 players online through your device or pass and play among your friends. Play ranked or unranked matchmaking, with realtime and asynchronous modes. Set up a private table for a family game, challenge a stranger in the lobby, or invite a friend!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Daily.png?t=1707010484"><br/>A daily ritual to relax with over a cup of coffee. Try the Daily Dominion, a free puzzle level available to players around the world. Practice your strategy to keep up a winning streak and climb the leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CrossPlatform.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Play from any supported device, whenever you want, after verifying your email in-game. Join games with opponents on platforms other than your own to enjoy the largest possible multiplayer pool and speedy matchmaking. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/JoinCommunity.png?t=1707010484"><br/>With an active Discord and online community, make new friends or challenge new people to a game. Export and share kingdoms and game summaries to compare strategies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/FreeToPlay.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Download the game that started it all for free! The base set of Dominion is available at no charge. Try the rotation of expansion cards in the Daily at no cost once per day. Jump into a lobby game with expansions enabled to try before you buy. Only the host needs to own the expansions.    <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Intro.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Learn the ropes in this easy to pick-up, hard to master title. Play one of the most highly regarded strategy tabletop games of all time through our simple tutorial.  The core loop is easy to follow, but offers a wealth of strategy to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>1-6 player</strong> support<br/></li><li><strong>500 </strong> plus <strong>cards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Solo play</strong> against four AI difficulties<br/></li><li><strong>Async </strong>&amp; <strong>real-time</strong> multiplayer<br/></li><li><strong>Ranked</strong> &amp; <strong>unranked</strong> matchmaking<br/></li><li><strong>Lobby</strong> &amp; <strong>Private game</strong> tables<br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform multiplayer</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform purchases</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Daily challenge</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Challenging AI</strong> that learns through self-play<br/></li><li><strong>Recommended Sets</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Customize</strong>, save &amp; share <strong>Kingdoms</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Achievements</strong>, <strong>Stats </strong>&amp; <strong>Leaderboards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Pass &amp; Play</strong> mode<br/></li><li>Automated <strong>score-keeping</strong> &amp; hints<br/></li><li><strong>Smart-play</strong> options to streamline gameplay<br/></li><li><strong>Jumbo mode</strong> for readability on phones<br/></li><li><strong>Turbo mode</strong> to zoom through games quickly<br/></li><li><strong>Tutorial</strong> &amp; <strong>Rules</strong><br/></li><li><strong>4 languages</strong>: English, Japanese, German, French<br/></li><li><strong>15 expansions</strong> plus three promo packs </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Awards for the Boardgame</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Awards.png?t=1707010484"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/881020/Granblue_Fantasy_Relink/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/881020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Story<br/>
Granblue Fantasy takes place in the Sky Realm, a world where myriad islands float in a great blue expanse. Take your role as captain of a skyfaring crew, joined by a scrappy little dragon named Vyrn and a young girl with mysterious powers named Lyria. Together you sail with a colorful cast of crewmates, including kings and misfits alike, for Estalucia, a fabled island beyond the end of the skies.<br/>
<br/>
In the Zegagrande Skydom, islands are guarded by powerful creatures known as primal beasts and winds carry tales of a secretive organization known as the Church of Avia. Unveil a web of intrigue reaching far beyond the borders of Zegagrande and engage in a battle for the fate of the Sky Realm itself.<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay<br/>
Engage in real-time combat with a party of four in this character action RPG—choose from a diverse roster of skyfarers, each with their own unique weapons, skills, and combat styles. Teamwork makes the dream work with party-based mechanics such as Link Attacks and Chain Bursts to help you crush foes in spectacular fashion. Tackle quests solo or with the help of others for up to 4-player co-op and take down treacherous foes to score rare loot to further enhance your gear. Every enemy and party formation has its own strengths and weaknesses—the key to victory lies in working out how these pieces fit together.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced combat not your thing? Assist modes can provide accessibility for gamers of all skill levels. Toggle on Full Assist to have all actions performed automatically during battle!<br/>
<br/>
The Sky Realm is rich in lore and history. Browse Lyria's journal at any point during the game to access a trove of writings on the world's peoples, places, and more. In addition to the wealth of side quests available, Fate Episodes allow you to delve into the backstories of each member of your crew!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlazBlue Entropy Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2273430/BlazBlue_Entropy_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/原创声明-英语.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗EN_.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>Charismatic character designs with unique aesthetic styles and dramatic animations create a flamboyant, awesome combat experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快的动作连招EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快动作连招.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>Smooth controls, infinite possibilities of combos, and realistic combat feedback. This is the roguelite game with the best action experience yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超多角色豪华制作EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/全员图618x346.jpg?t=1707811616"><br/>Ten playable characters with vibrant personalities, unique combat styles, and immersive voice-acting.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式自由定制EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式，自由定制en.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>There are hundreds of moves for you to build around, plus countless elemental effects and legacy skills passed between characters. The possibilities are infinite. Time to make the best fighter of your own!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/抉择拯救世界EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/GIF-抉择拯救世界EN.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>In the future where the world has been plunged into chaos, people enter a cyberspace called ACE, seeking their last chance to resolve the crisis.<br/>If you are the only person in this world who knows the truth, how will you react?<br/>The ending is also the beginning. Your decision will decide humanity's future.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2772560/Supermarket_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This Prologue is a limited version of the full game to stop waiting and jump into running your supermarket already. Don't forget to wishlist the full game to continue your most fun supermarket experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Design your store, optimizing for efficiency and aesthetics. Determine where products are displayed, manage your aisles, and ensure a smooth shopping experience for your customers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Order stock using an in-game computer and anticipate the arrival of your next delivery. Unpack goods, organize them in your storage room and display them on shelves, fridges, and freezers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Read product barcodes, handle cash and credit card transactions, and ensure customers leave satisfied with their shopping and checkout experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier_Raw.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Navigate the complexities of a real-time market. Buy products when prices dip and determine the best-selling prices to balance customer satisfaction with profit margins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><br/>Wishlist the full game "Supermarket Simulator" where every decision matters. Will you rise to the occasion, transforming a modest establishment into a retail powerhouse, all while balancing customer satisfaction, finances, and mafia expectations?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Lily - Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2220360/Paper_Lily__Chapter_1/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Something terrible has happened. You can’t bear to think about it - but you can’t live like this anymore. You stopped attending school, you haven’t left your house in months, you have no reason to get out of bed anymore. There are no choices left.<br/><br/>No choice except... that strange golden letter.<br/><br/>It’s time to get your life back together. <br/><br/>One last try.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/divider.png?t=1706724298"><br/><br/>Paper Lily is a story-driven, psychological horror RPG where each puzzle has multiple solutions and outcomes. <strong>There is always another way.</strong><br/>Follow Lacie's story as you explore a dangerous hidden world, solve puzzles in multiple different ways, and face strange enemies. The game is playable in about 4 hours and contains multiple endings depending on your actions.<br/><br/>Paper Lily - Chapter 1 is the continuation to the prologue, <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1698960" rel="" target="_blank">Project Kat</a>, but it can also  be enjoyed without having played it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/lacie_sai_walk.gif?t=1706724298"><h2 class="bb_tag">Out of Context Features</h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple ways of solving puzzles!<br/></li><li>Touch grass, and trees<br/></li><li>Minigames where you press buttons and push boxes around<br/></li><li>Call your mother<br/></li><li>Harmless Snack™<br/></li><li>Various things made of paper<br/></li><li>Bunnies (or whatever those things are)<br/></li><li>Demons<br/></li><li>Fast demons<br/></li><li>Social anxiety simulation<br/></li><li>Table salt<br/></li><li>...Is that Kat? Nah, probably not<br/></li><li>Bathroom etiquette<br/></li><li>Death</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2072450/Like_a_Dragon_Infinite_Wealth/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/Accolades_616.png?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>EPIC EMOTIONAL DRAMA</strong><br/>Two larger-than-life heroes brought together by the hand of fate, or perhaps something more sinister…<br/><br/>Ichiban Kasuga, an unstoppable underdog who’s no stranger to crawling up from rock bottom, and Kazuma Kiryu, a broken man facing down his last days.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/2_Epic_Emotional_Drama.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>BEST-IN-CLASS RPG ACTION</strong><br/>Experience one-of-a-kind combat with dynamic, fast-paced RPG battles where the battlefield becomes your weapon, and anything goes. Adapt your party’s skills to the situation with outlandish jobs and customizations to strategically subdue enemies with over-the-top moves. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/3_Best_In_Class_RPG_Action.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>INFINITE ADVENTURE</strong><br/>Live it up in Japan and explore all that Hawaii has to offer in an adventure so big it spans the Pacific. Unforgettable moments await at every step of the journey with a unique mix of quests and activities to enjoy at your leisure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/4_Infinite_Adventure.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Deluxe Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Ultimate Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/>- Assorted Outfit Bundle: Customize your party's look with outfits &amp; swimwear<br/>- Sujimon &amp; Resort Bundle: Get legendary Sujimon, resort guests and special boosters<br/>- Yakuza CD Collection Set: Increase your in-game playlist with classic karaoke tracks						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNDER NIGHT IN-BIRTH II Sys:Celes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2076010/UNDER_NIGHT_INBIRTH_II_SysCeles/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Sys:Celes sinks towards ruination.<br/>For the Immortalize, the collapse of all that is, looms on the horizon.<br/>The curtain rises on the final chapter of the Hollow Night. Catastrophe beckons...<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store1b.gif?t=1707122865"><br/><br/>Experience the Dramatic Stylish 2D Fighting Action in the latest entry of the UNDER NIGHT IN-BIRTH series!<br/><br/>The first numbered sequel in the series!<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Choose from a roster of 24 total characters, with renewed visuals!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store2.jpg?t=1707122865"><br/>3 new characters join the battle: Moonlight Dancer "Twin Barrel Beauty" Kaguya, Indomitable Rampart "Steel Guardian" Tsurugi, and Endless Entity "Eternal Re-Birth" Kuon.<br/>You won’t be able to take your eyes off the intense battles between these 24 fighters with the highly detailed HD pixel art graphics!<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Simple inputs make it easy to jump into the fray!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store3.gif?t=1707122865"><br/>New to fighting games? Not a problem – simple inputs mean even beginners can pull off moves with a single button!<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Now supporting rollback netcode for an improved online experience!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store4.jpg?t=1707122865"><br/>With the addition of Casual Matches, it’s easier than ever before to dive in and enjoy online battles.<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Introducing new moves and game mechanics!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store5.gif?t=1707122865"><br/>All characters now boast new moves, such as Hyde’s Blaring Outrage and Linne’s Soaring Dragon.<br/>The new game mechanics Creeping Edge and Celestial Vorpal open up additional depth to gameplay.<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ The final chapter! A new tale of the Hollow Night…</h2>Sever the cycle. An end to the endless.<br/>May the tale of these countless Nights be concluded, on this eve, the moment of destiny.<br/>A long-awaited continuation to the tale of the Hollow Night unfolds!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summon Masters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2100140/Summon_Masters/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2100140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a card and board game with the following features:<br>
<br>
Deck Building: Players can build their own decks to battle with. Depending on different strategies and opponents, players can choose different cards to counter.<br>
<br>
Tactical Gameplay: The game uses a 3x10 chessboard, and players can freely place cards to fight. Players need to develop tactics and arrange card positions and usage order within limited space.<br>
<br>
Different Professions: Players can choose freely from four professions - swordsman, mage, monk, and archer. Each profession has different characteristics and skills, and players can choose according to their preferences and tactical needs.<br/>
<br/>
Competitive Battles: Players can battle with other players after building their decks, and it is fun to fight with other people. Through battles with other players, players can improve their strength and tactical skills.<br/>
<br/>
Team Dungeons: In addition to fighting against other players, players can also team up with others to challenge high-difficulty dungeons. Players need to defeat powerful bosses through cooperation and strategy to get more rewards and cards.<br/>
<br/>
Special Challenges: Players can participate in special rules challenges and use their intelligence to defeat other players. These special rules make the game more interesting and challenging, and players need to constantly think and try new strategies.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced: Each game is fast-paced (within 5 minutes), and can be played in short fragments of time. The fast pace of the game allows players to enjoy the game in a short time, while also being able to play at any time and anywhere.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2248950/TransSiberian_Railway_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take the helm of a classic Russian locomotive, discover the raw beauty and wildness of Siberia and try to survive on the longest railway line in the world. This is the Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator. A game for real adventurers!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/drinking1.gif?t=1707824452"><br/><br/>Complete the tutorial and the first kilometers of the route for free.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/explosion_gif.gif?t=1707824452"><br/><br/>The Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator offers amazing rail and survival challenges on real Russian dangerous routes. Feel what it is like to put your hands at the helm of a powerful freight locomotive and explore the untouched natural landscape that is sure to delight you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/shooting_gif.gif?t=1707824452"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Prologue features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Detailed simulation of driving a VL10 locomotive - the locomotive control is slightly simplified.<br/></li><li> Locomotive repair system - Manage and replace locomotive parts that are constantly wearing out.<br/></li><li> Train traffic simulation - Follow rail signs and signals to avoid derailment or damage to a part of the locomotive.<br/></li><li> Work system - Earn by completing transport orders. <br/></li><li> Game modes (Survival) and (Simulator). It is recommended to play in the (Survival) mode. This is the leading game mode that is constantly being developed. <br/>For players who are not interested in survival mechanics, a simple Simulator mode is available. <br/></li><li> Mafia system - Complete missions for the mafia to earn extra money.<br/></li><li> Survival system with statistics of hunger, thirst, alcohol, hangover, disease and hypothermia - Eat and drink to avoid death. <br/>Keep the right temperature so you don't freeze.<br/></li><li> Shooting system - Use your weapons for hunting and self-defense.<br/></li><li> Purchase and sales system - Buy various items, food, tools, weapons and ammunition.<br/></li><li> Locomotive inspection mode - Inspect the condition of locomotive parts and replace them in time to avoid damage.<br/></li><li> Dynamic weather system with day and night cycle - Survive extreme weather conditions.<br/></li><li> Route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Novosibirsk-Main) - scale 1:1. Buy the full version with the route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Krasnoyarsk).<br/></li><li> Police system - A corrupt militia watches over your movements.<br/></li><li> Much more to discover.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paradise Angel</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2627340/Paradise_Angel/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2627340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2627340/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1708146016"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2627340/extras/Paradise_Angel_Description_1_EN.png?t=1708146016"><br/>The Holy Grail, a divine artifact that the land of Erodrad was blessed with, has gone missing. With the Grail gone, Power will flow out of control, and Erodrad's future will grow bleak. God commands the angel Elu to descend from heaven and seek the Grail. Her journey begins in Benedicta Town...<br/><br/>Can Elu find the Holy Grail in time, or will the world fall to ruin as Power overflows? Who is behind the disappearance of the Holy Grail?<br/><br/>Only you can see Elu's story through to the end!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2627340/extras/Paradise_Angel_Description_2_EN.png?t=1708146016"><br/>Explore God's miniature garden in search of the Holy Grail. Be careful, though! The enemies in areas of interest are corrupted by overflowing Power, making them incredibly violent. Use Elu's miracles to protect yourself in this exploration-based RPG!<br/><br/>The mayor of Benedicta Town and the parish priest will help you along in your journey. The mayor has many leads and avenues for investigation and will help you every step of the way. The priest isn't so nice.<br/><br/>Your actions during Elu's journey and the amount of Power she absorbs will lead you to different endings. Try your best to find them all!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2627340/extras/Paradise_Angel_Description_3_EN.png?t=1708146016"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2627340/extras/Paradise_Angel_Description_01_EN.png?t=1708146016"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2627340/extras/Paradise_Angel_Description_02_EN.png?t=1708146016"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2627340/extras/Paradise_Angel_Description_4_EN.png?t=1708146016"><br/><strong>Exploration-based RPG</strong><br/>The land of Erodrad is vast and has plenty to see—though that makes finding the Holy Grail a difficult task indeed. Every area you take on has a unique vibe and different enemies to face.<br/><br/><strong>Quests</strong><br/>While waiting for the mayor to gather new leads on the whereabouts of the Holy Grail, you can help the citizens of Benedicta Town—for a reward, of course! There's plenty of people in need of help and plenty to see...<br/><br/><strong>Class System</strong><br/>As you level up, you may be upgraded to a new class. Each class has its own advantages, but keep an eye on your Power Gauge! There are some classes that can only be obtained at a certain level of Power...						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dangerous Arena</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2651760/Dangerous_Arena/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The arena is not a place for the weak. In this game, you have to win in the arenas by placing your warriors.<br/>The soldiers fight on their own; your task is to place the soldiers correctly in the arena.<br/>Choose wisely who will fight. Some units attack from afar but have little health, some fight close but are vulnerable to exploding units.<br/>Some slow down enemies, and some can take many attacks before dying. Forward to victory, general!<br/><br/>-Dynamic gameplay<br/>-Dangerous enemies<br/>-Interesting gameplay</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flowball</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2330770/Flowball/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Flowball is an incredibly challenging platformer where the goal is to get the ball to the finish platform for each level. There are 19 levels in total and in order to complete the game and get added to the high-scores, you need to beat all of the levels back to back in the same session.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraalOnline Era</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2358050/GraalOnline_Era/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the world of GraalOnline Era, a modern 2D action MMO RPG. Purchase weapons and work with a gang to compete in activities such as special events, base capturing and PvP battles in the Spar Complex, or start your own gang and chart your own path! There are a ton of unique weapons available. Melee weapons for close quarters or take out your enemies from long range with guns!<br>
Complete quests to access other items to boost your arsenal. Character customization is a staple of GraalOnline! There are thousands of hats and outfits with the option to upload your own graphics to the game, which makes the customization options endless! Player houses and gang houses offer further customization options, with stores across the map providing a wide variety of ideas and unique furniture items. Seasonal changes bring various updates, including unique themed shops, season-appropriate methods for making money, and unique changes to the map.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
<br>
Create your Gangster<br>
There are infinite Free ways to customize your character when you start playing, options to upload your pixel art to create endless customization possibilities and to show off your style. <br/>
<br/>
House customization, with countless shops in-game that sell thousands of unique pieces of furniture to customize your house the way you want.<br/>
<br/>
Massive Open World PVP<br/>
Battle against thousands of players in real-time on GraalOnline Era, Whether it be 1 v 1 sparring matches or 5 v 5 gang spar matches, or maybe you join your friends and play Laser Tag, defend against waves of enemies in Plasma Corp, or join in a Battle Royale! Or even take part in a Gang War with gangs of up to 25 players to claim Gang Bases or battle players across the giant map! <br/>
<br/>
Collect<br/>
GraalOnline Era is updated regularly with various hats, weapons, items and furniture to collect! <br/>
<br/>
Jobs<br/>
There is something for everyone to do to gain currency in GraalOnline Era. Make pizzas at Speedy Pizza, dig up shells at one of the beautiful beaches around the game, collect mushrooms and garbage across the massive map, and many more!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sins OV Cigar</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626410/Sins_OV_Cigar/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Extreme melee/gun combat with a focus on player aggressiveness and risk/reward mechanics. Features agile movement and brutal melee combat<br>
<br>
Richad Cigar, quadrillionaire and head of the Cigar corporation, has been dealt a military invasion by a rival splinter company organized by a former friend, Tony Robusto. Cigar seeks to capture Robusto himself. In thousands of years, not one normal or healthy person has set foot in this continent dominated by corrupt business.<br>
<br>
Also known as Sins Of Cigar.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Eerie Surroundings</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2772300/The_Eerie_Surroundings/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trying to find the exit but you are stuck in a loop. To find the exit, observe your surroundings and get familiar with it. On floor 0 you will be presented with an area to study the layout of objects. The timer will start once you are ready to play. The correct decision will move you up a floor and the incorrect decision will reset you back to the beginning. Observation is key.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, choose the elevator that states no anomalies otherwise choose the elevator that states confirm anomalies.<br/><br/>The Eerie Surroundings as it states is set in a eerie theme and is a short game. Currently there are 3 levels. 2 levels are locked but can be unlocked providing you beat the timer challenge.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15 - 120 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">Replay Ability</h2>Once you have beat the timer challenge for a level you can go back on that level and try to beat your new best time.<br/><br/>You have permission to create, upload, and monetize videos and any other content featuring Game on platforms such as YouTube, Twitch, and other video-sharing websites.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neon Tail</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1126270/Neon_Tail/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1126270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1126270/extras/itchio_20190213.gif?t=1708128544"><br/><strong>Save your city from alien invasion!</strong><br/>You are a rising SFS Pro star, who acquired mysterious powers from a powerful being.<br/>Use your agility and wits to stop the invasion of aliens!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1126270/extras/Explore_BluePulse_city.png?t=1708128544"><br/><strong>Explore BluePulse city!</strong><br/>Take small jobs, go shopping, relax in restaurants and cafes, and earn fame and fortune by becoming a Skate for Street Pro star player!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1126270/extras/Roller_Skating_Physics.jpg?t=1708128544"><br/><strong>Roller Skating Physics!</strong><br/>Master the new roller skating physics and become so precise no crazy jumps will resist you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1126270/extras/Meet_colorful_and_interesting_people.png?t=1708128544"><br/><strong>Meet colorful and interesting people!</strong><br/>The world of Neon Tail is filled with interesting people, time to make many friends!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1126270/extras/Take_care_of_your_camera_Drone.png?t=1708128544"><br/><strong>Take care of your camera Drone</strong><br/>Visit Drone shops to upgrade or install extensible modules on your camera drone Modulo. Scanners, Maps, HUD, Photographs, Flashlights, Codex, etc...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1126270/extras/power.jpg?t=1708128544"><br/><strong>Learn about mysterious powers!</strong><br/>An incredible adventure awaits you, as you discover strange super powers that you will need to master to protect the city from an Alien invasion!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1126270/extras/Save_Bluepulse_City.jpg?t=1708128544"><br/><strong>Save Bluepulse City!</strong><br/>Use your agility, dexterity, wits, reputation, friendships, and super powers to save your city from disaster!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dodge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2794300/Dodge/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2794300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dodge is a game about dodging hazards with your mouse for as long as you can, while you gather score to unlock the next stages.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They Dug Too Deep</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2462100/They_Dug_Too_Deep/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2462100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Dwarves have long mined the mountain they live in. Ever down, ever for greater wealth. Dangers have always been present, from fungal spores that zombify dwarves, to clans of angry feral goblins.  The giant spiders and cave crawlers were dangerous, but manageable.  But now…now the Dwarves have released something.  But what else would you expect, since… They Dug Too Deep.<br/><br/>-Take control of the dwarf who said, “Not I” the slowest and explore what was released in the depths of the mines.<br/><br/>-Fight goblins, spiders, zombies, rogue automatons,  &amp; then deal with the forces of hell that your dwarven delving unleashed.  Plus what is lurking... beneath.<br/><br/>-Use various dwarven contraptions to stem the endless tide.  From Crystal scatter guns, to crank action lightning guns, hydraulic morning stars, gas powered goblin skewerers, and even a handful of -shudder- elven spells.<br/><br/>-Emblazon yourself with powerful runes to empower your dwarven blood!<br/><br/>-How deep can you get?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2462100/extras/tDtDBanner2.5.png?t=1708117563"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Hour Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684030/Happy_Hour_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Happy Hour Hero is a cartoony, flow-state bartending game that boasts:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Four core modes - Happy Hour, Easy Casual, Normal Casual, and Hardcore!<br/></li><li>Two minigames - Dart Attack and Bowling!<br/></li><li>Seven drinks to master and a full bar to keep stocked!<br/></li><li>Four leaderboards to climb!<br/></li><li>Options for all playstyles - seated, standing, and roomscale. Smooth motion, snap turning, and teleportation!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684030/extras/Postcard_eng.png?t=1708116104"><br/>We’ve not had a lot of luck hiring competent bar staff, but I have a feeling you’re the right one for the job. Keep the beer stocked, the spirits flowing, and the customers merry. Oh, and if you mess up, it’s coming out of your paycheck. It gets pretty busy, so just stay on your toes and don’t get mixed up. Alright? Welcome to the team.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684030/extras/TripleGif_aspect__6_.gif?t=1708116104"><br/><strong>Test your spirits!</strong><br/><br/>If your shift goes well, you might just earn a spot on the global leaderboards. Fancy yourself a pro-mixer? Join the highballers in hardcore mode.<br/><br/><strong>On-the-job training!</strong><br/><br/>Not feeling competitive? Play in casual mode and serve customers who couldn’t care less!<br/><br/><strong>Customers getting you down?</strong><br/><br/>Take part in teambuilding activities and compete with your colleagues - score high in darts or smash bottles in the bowling alley - drinks on the loser!<br/><br/><strong>Get your hands dirty!</strong><br/><br/>We built this bar from the ground up for VR, so you'd better make it a success!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardcore Cottagecore</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2753330/Hardcore_Cottagecore/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2753330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2753330/extras/hccc-variety.gif?t=1708116031"><br/><br/>Mushroom meadow is being devastated by hundreds of drones who want to build another Amazon warehouse! It’s time for these fungi to fight back with wild auto-firing cottagecore abilities like spinning embrodery hoops and mason jar molotov cocktails! Choose your mushroom, go it solo or team up with your best bud, survive the horde and win back your turf! Get ready for a small co-op or solo dive into mushroom mayhem!<br/><strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2753330/extras/hccc-char-select.gif?t=1708116031"><br/>Features</img></strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>  Numerous unique and powerful abilities to destroy robots with<br/></li><li>  Cute cottagecore aesthetic<br/></li><li>  Quests to complete in each area<br/></li><li>  Play singleplayer or local 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>  Unlockable characters<br/></li><li>  Multiple areas<br/></li><li>  Full controller support or even play 2 players on a single keyboard</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2753330/extras/hccc-hoops-for-gif.gif?t=1708116031"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2753330/extras/hccc-molotov.gif?t=1708116031"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RC Revolution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2347040/RC_Revolution/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2347040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Experience the Thrill of RC Revolution!</h2>Welcome to the exhilarating world of radio-controlled car racing, where unforgettable moments of intense immersion await you! The game seamlessly combines strategy, skill, and speed to offer an experience that stands as a timeless classic in the realm of competitive racing.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2347040/extras/01_Text_L_Strip._Build.Race_1.gif?t=1708110306"><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer Mayhem and Cooperative Gameplay</h2>Dive into the heart-pounding multiplayer mayhem with a wide array of competitive and cooperative modes. Race against your friends or team up with them to share victory, whether it's on a split screen or online. Each race presents an opportunity to push your limits and climb the ranks in our rewarding progression system!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2347040/extras/02_text_R_you_ride_you_rules.gif?t=1708110306"><h2 class="bb_tag">Variety of Cars, Tracks, and Customization Options</h2>Choose from a diverse collection of cars and tracks, each with its own unique challenges and characteristics! Customize your car to suit your racing style and witness firsthand how it affects your performance on the track.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2347040/extras/03_Text_LCollect_car.gif?t=1708110306"><h2 class="bb_tag">Easy to Pick Up, Difficult to Master</h2>Our game strikes the perfect balance between accessibility and challenge! With realistic and aesthetic physics, a variety of gameplay options, and a relentless focus on fun, we cater to both casual gamers and seasoned veterans. Enjoy exhilarating drifts, power slides, overtaking maneuvers, crashes, and collisions as you hone your skills on the track!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2347040/extras/04_Text_R_Giant_world.gif?t=1708110306"><h2 class="bb_tag">Replayability with a Creative Track Builder</h2>The fun doesn’t stop at just racing! Unleash your creativity with our intuitive and customizable track builder. Design your own tracks, complete with clever obstacles and hazards. Set up your own championship events using our championship editor, adding to the replayability and competitive spirit of the game.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2347040/extras/05_Text_L_drive_into_1.gif?t=1708110306"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBSCURIA</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2756780/OBSCURIA/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2756780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>WELCOME TO OBSCURIA</strong>The large cruise ship Nocturne has been evacuated due to a shipwreck, everyone has been evacuated except one person, Captain Blackhood.<br/>Since he gave the order to evacuate he has not been seen again, your mission as an agent is to find him alive, or dead, but to find him, in addition an invasion of ghosts has invaded the cruise ship.<br/>Genre: Horror, Exploration, Scare, Tension<br/>Price: Free to play<br/>In OBSCURIA, you will embark on a terrifying experience aboard the "Nocturne", a state-of-the-art cruise ship that hides dark secrets. Armed only with a flashlight, your bravery will be tested as you explore dark hallways and solve puzzles to reveal the truth behind an ancient curse.<br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2756780/extras/Diseño_sin_título__22_.png?t=1708110019"><br/>The ship, desolate and silent, immerses you in an atmosphere of mystery and danger. You must face The Consuming Shadow, a terrifying entity that patrols the dark areas. Avoiding direct encounters and hiding will become crucial for your survival.<br/><br/>Sudden scares, creepy apparitions and challenging puzzles will keep you guessing throughout the journey. Discover the dark history of the "Nocturne" through scattered notes and diaries, revealing the tragedy that has left the ship in a state of abandonment.<br/>The great cruise ship of 2023 has suffered a<br/>unexpected evacuation, Captain Blackwood ordered<br/>to the entire crew that the ship was evacuated, this<br/>Because the Nocturne fell under the curse of the Nightmare, a<br/>old cruise ship from the same company that had a shipwreck in 1993<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2756780/extras/Diseño_sin_título__23_.png?t=1708110019"><br/>OBSCURIA offers an immersive and terrifying experience, at no cost. Will you dare to brave the wrath of the eternal sea aboard the "Nocturne"?<br/>Enter to discover the mysteries and find the secrets<br/>from Captain Blackhood.<br/>With your flashlight and your rescue equipment you will be the only one who<br/>can enter into this experience of terror, so why<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2756780/extras/Diseño_sin_título__24_.png?t=1708110019"><br/>Waiting to play OBSCURIA, <strong>NOW AVAILABLE FOR FREE ON STEAM.</strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gregg: Tower Defence</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2655130/Gregg_Tower_Defence/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2655130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Gregg: Tower Defence</strong> is a captivating pixel art tower defense game that puts your strategic prowess to the test. Take on the role of Gregg, a resourceful little builder, and face a relentless onslaught of slimes in epic battles. Here are some of the key features:<br/><br/><strong>Six Unique Towers:</strong> Craft and upgrade six different tower types, each with its own distinctive abilities and strategic advantages. Mix and match to create the ultimate defense.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2655130/extras/TOWER.png?t=1708106431"><br/><br/><strong>Resource Gathering:</strong> Explore the world to collect 5 different resources, the building blocks of your tower defense strategy. Each resource is vital for crafting your towers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2655130/extras/RESOURCE.png?t=1708106431"><br/><br/><strong>Day and Night Cycle:</strong> Survive the day by harvesting essential materials, and then prepare for the night when waves of slimes attack your base. Adapt to the changing conditions to stay one step ahead.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2655130/extras/DAYNIGHT.png?t=1708106431"><br/><br/><strong>Upgrade System:</strong> Improve your towers as you advance, with five tiers available for each tower, allowing them to adapt to the ever-growing threat posed by advancing enemy waves.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2655130/extras/UPGRADE.png?t=1708106431"><br/><br/><strong>Gold and Gear:</strong> Earn gold by defeating slimes, and use it to bolster your arsenal. Upgrade your axe for resource gathering, improve your speed, and expand your base to accommodate more towers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2655130/extras/GOLD.png?t=1708106431"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Small Mazes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2570630/20_Small_Mazes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2570630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a puzzle game with twenty small mazes. If you solve the mazes, you beat the game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>It's about 1-2 hours long, maybe.<br/></li><li>You need a keyboard and mouse to play it. One person played through the whole game on the Steam Deck, but I tried it and think it's better on PC.<br/></li><li> A few puzzles require knowledge of English. No puzzle requires sound or audio to solve it. No puzzle requires being able to recognize different colors.</li></ul> <br/>I hope you enjoy it. <br/> 						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irotoridori No Sekai HD - The Colorful World</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2591380/Irotoridori_No_Sekai_HD__The_Colorful_World/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Irotoridori No Sekai - The Colorful World is a Japanese-style visual novel produced by FAVORITE, a Japanese developer of romance visual novels.</h2></strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591380/extras/01.gif?t=1708127277"><br/><br/><strong><u>Story:</u></strong><br/><br/><i>Our story follows Kanoue Yuuma, an amnesiac boy with a special power, and Nikaidou Shinku, a translucent girl only visible to Yuuma who gave him that power. With it, he can heal any and all wounds.<br/>But it comes at the cost of the memories he's made. <br/>He lives a simple life: going to school and being scolded by his childhood friend, Kisaragi Mio, by day, and working with his master, Natsume Suzu, in the evenings.<br/>However, whenever he falls asleep, he always sees the same dream... a white world, feathers falling, and a girl calling out for him to save her.<br/>The student dormitory his master resides in has a special door in the basement, which connects their world to a myriad of different parallel ones. He travels from world to world, searching for one that resembles the scenery he sees in his dreams, but to no avail.<br/><br/>Then, one night, as he's out at night strolling around town, he spots a girl jumping from the lighthouse. <br/>Yuuma rushes over and heals her using his power, but after coming to, the girl claims to know him and his power, and asks him much like the voice in his dreams:<br/><br/><strong>"Please save me, Kanoue Yuuma."</strong></i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591380/extras/1.png?t=1708127277"><br/><strong><u>Nikaidou Shinku:</u> </strong><br/><br/>The translucent sorceress who gave Yuuma his special power.<br/>A calm, rational girl who rarely shows her emotions. She exudes an air of maturity in stark contrast to her youthful appearance.<br/>She currently sticks by Yuuma's side to achieve a certain goal--that is, to get him to experience love.<br/>"Love. Romantic feelings. I want you to experience the one thing I was never able to."<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591380/extras/2.png?t=1708127277"><br/><strong><u>Minami Kana:</u></strong><br/><br/>A strange, unknown girl who fell from the sky one night.<br/>After Yuuma managed to save her, she claimed to have known him and exchanged a certain "promise" with him many years ago, which he has no recollection of.<br/>Eventually, she comes to live alongside him in the dormitory, taking it upon herself to perform the duties of a maid.<br/>While she's able to take care of household chores, her cooking is abysmal, and she seems to be gravely lacking in the common sense department.<br/>"Please, help me, Mister Sorcerer. I'm really in quite the predicament right now!"<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591380/extras/3.png?t=1708127277"><br/><strong><u>Kisaragi Mio:</u></strong><br/><br/>Yuuma's childhood friend, who's in his class at school.<br/>Due to their longstanding friendship, teachers and other classmates often come to her for all matters concerning Yuuma, the habitual skipper, which slightly peeves her.<br/>She's noticed Yuuma getting chummy with a lot of girls who (she thinks) are cuter than her, which has secretly been a source of stress for her.<br/>Her cooking skills are excellent, as are her domestic skills in general.<br/>"That's what I like about you. You're sincere."<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591380/extras/4.png?t=1708127277"><br/><strong><u>Shikishima Kyou:</u></strong><br/><br/>A looney girl with an imaginative mind who never leaves her room in Arashiyama Hall and loves spouting off her delusions of grandeur.<br/>She has a very laid-back demeanor, and despite being a slight airhead, doesn't hold her punches when it comes to criticism.<br/>Due to being a social outcast who lives day in and day out playing and watching nothing but games and anime, she never sees the light of the sun, and accordingly, her skin is fair and white.<br/>Being a night owl, she always seems sleepy, but ever since meeting Yuuma, she's been leaving her room more and more.<br/>She also seems to possess a mysterious power...<br/>"Are you my brother?"<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591380/extras/5.png?t=1708127277"><br/><strong><u>Toumine Tsukasa: </u></strong><br/><br/>A new resident at the dorm who always seems to be running to and fro, busy as a bee.<br/>She's a grade below Yuuma at school, and to pay for her tuition and living expenses, she works until late at night at the local bathhouse.<br/>She's honest to a fault and hard-working, but also very stubborn. Once something gets into her head, it can be hard to convince her otherwise.<br/>She also has a habit of tripping over nothing, although that isn't to say she's clumsy in general.<br/>She can handle household chores with ease and excels in particular at doing menial tasks.<br/>"The local baker man is a god incarnate!"						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of Nowhere</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2218620/Out_of_Nowhere/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2218620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Be in control of a dog in an adventure action horror game. Set in a fantasy medieval open world full of mysteries where aliens took over and there is no one left to help you. Explore the different areas of the map to find out how to defeat them.<br>
<br>
Out of Nowhere is developed by one passionate brazilian who wants to create a short but unforgettable experience for everyone.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOGUN</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2010160/SHOGUN/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2010160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2010160/extras/STOREGIF.gif?t=1708103696"><br/><br/>Your last objective: KILL<br/>An endless horde of Démons flood in as you struggle to survive. Too angry to die, Shogun raises hell.<br/><br/>SHOGUN is an arcade style shooter that emphasizes running and gunning to stay alive. Rip through waves of increasingly difficult enemies hell-bent on your doom by shooting, looting, and eluding a bullet hell of cartoonish horror. Refuse death, explode with burning rage and tear asunder!!!<br/><br/>Inspired by the games that founded the fps genre, SHOGUN was created to give homage to the demon slaying experience in a bite sized form.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEAMRUSH</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2647100/STEAMRUSH/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Fast-Paced Melee Combat:</h2>Engage in intense melee combat that keeps your heart racing. Quick reflexes and expertly timed slashes, parries, jumps and dodges are essential as you face challenging foes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647100/extras/ScrapKnightCombat.gif?t=1708105918"><h2 class="bb_tag">Strategic Parrying:</h2>Master the art of parrying to gain the upper hand in battles. Perfecting this skill is your ticket to success in STEAMRUSH's combat system.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647100/extras/ScrapKnightParry.gif?t=1708105918"><h2 class="bb_tag">Diverse Boss Fights:</h2>Battle formidable bosses, each with their own unique combat mechanics. Adapt your approach and come up with winning strategies to defeat these challenging adversaries.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647100/extras/AutomaCombat.gif?t=1708105918"><h2 class="bb_tag">Discover the Story:</h2>Explore the city and find collectibles that shed light on Haze's mysterious narrative. These hidden gems provide insight into the city's secrets and add depth to your gaming experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647100/extras/CollectiblePickUp.gif?t=1708105918"><br/><br/>STEAMRUSH promises an exciting blend of action, strategy, and storytelling, all within the intriguing backdrop of Haze. Will you complete your mission to uncover the city's mysteries and conquer its dangerous inhabitants?<h2 class="bb_tag">Steamrush is part of the Big Ones, an initiative of AIV - Accademia Italiana Videogiochi aimed at adding a production experience to the teaching carried out in the various courses, from the creation of the game concept to commercial publishing.<br/>The objective of the Big Ones is to give students the opportunity to collaborate with colleagues from other courses in the development of a video game project in which everyone can put the skills acquired during the lessons to the test and at the same time perfect their soft skills.</h2> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Up Hike</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2767280/Up_Hike/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an exhilarating ascent in <strong>Up Hike</strong>, the  platformer game that challenges your skills and precision! In this thrilling 2D adventure, your goal is simple yet daunting: reach the summit. Brace yourself for a journey filled with heart-pounding jumps, strategic wall bounces, and the ever-present risk of a dizzying fall.<br/><br/><strong>Up Hike </strong>is a maze of precarious platforms, each jump demanding your utmost attention and timing. Your every move counts and as you go up the challenge will intensifie.<br/><br/><strong><br/>Game Mechanics:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong> Challenging Platformer:</strong> The only way to reach the end of your hike is to jump, but be carefull the <i>higher you go the harder you fall</i>.<br/><br/></li><li> <strong>Strategic Wall Jumping</strong>: Use the walls to your advantage to bounce and reach higher in a sequence of consecutive jumps<br/><br/></li><li> <strong>The longer you hold the jump, the further you will go:</strong> You will need a lot of practice to master it<br/><br/></li><li><strong> Dynamic Landscapes: </strong>Explore a variety of environments as you climb, each with its own set of challenges. From forests to icy peaks, adapt to new obstacles and keep climbing.<br/><br/>Will you rise to the challenge and reach the summit in <strong>Up Hike</strong>?<strong><u> The ascent begins now!</u></strong></li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Stories: The Legend of Toymakers Collector's Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2834890/Christmas_Stories_The_Legend_of_Toymakers_Collectors_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2834890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Elephant Games</strong> returns with the jolliest sequel, <i>Christmas Stories: The Legend of Toymakers</i>!<br/><br/>Welcome to the magical land of the Christmas elves! Young Fizzy is finally old enough to build toys in Santa's workshop, and he's gifted with a magic hammer passed down in his family through generations! He can't wait to get to work, but a mishap unleashes a pair of diabolical dolls bent on freezing the shop and destroying the Christmas spirit! You'll have to thwart these dastardly dollies and take back Christmas on your very first day of work! Don't be fooled by the adorable characters and yuletide atmosphere. This story is not for the faint of heart! Solve challenging puzzles, locate cleverly hidden objects, and save Christmas in this wild story full of Christmas cheer!<br/><br/>This is a special Collector's Edition release full of exclusive extras you won’t find in the standard version. The Collector’s Edition includes:<br/><br/>•	Easily navigate the magical world of the elves with the handy strategy guide!<br/>•	Download and keep beautiful wallpapers to immerse yourself in magic!<br/>•	Bring the adventure home with the exclusive music player!<br/>•	Continue the breathtaking story in the exclusive bonus chapter!<br/><br/>This is a Hidden Object Puzzle Adventure game, meaning a specific genre of story-driven, point &amp; click adventures. Throughout the game, players are tasked to find a list of objects hidden within a particular scene, and to occasionally complete various mini-games/puzzles.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash Cow DX</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2225830/Cash_Cow_DX/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2225830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2225830/extras/cash_cow_dx_logo_animated_580x208.gif?t=1708102695"><br/><strong>Holy cow, it's all about the moooney!</strong><br/><br/>Embark on an udderly jolly adventure to rescue Cash Cow's riches from the grasp of those sneaky Pig Pockets and reclaim what's rightfully hers! Get ready for a blast from the past with an 80s inspired arcade experience released 40 years late...<br/><br/><br/><strong>Cash Cow DX features…</strong><br/><br/>- 5 multi-screen levels, bonus stages and secrets<br/>- player speed selection: normal or turbo<br/>- arcade, speedrun and marathon modes<br/>- worldwide leaderboards<br/>- delightful chiptunes by Vincent Verger aka Tuï<br/><br/><strong>Tough as nails and no continues: are you ready?</strong> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abyssal Frontier</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2762560/Abyssal_Frontier/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2762560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>!!!THIS GAME HAS BODY HORROR,GORE AND TRYPOPHOBIA WARNING!!!</strong><br/>You're just a normal Captain, trying to finish your cargo run and earn some well-deserved shore leave. <br/>Your crew is solid, even if you have a newbie onboard. You've done this dozens of times. <br/><br/><i>Oh? A new toy to play with.</i><br/><br/>All you have to do is visit this last outpost, and you'll be done for a good, long, while. <br/>One more jump. <br/>One more Sale.<br/><br/><i>We'll see about that.</i><br/><br/>After all, this is just a normal run...<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Voice Acting</strong><br/><br/></li><li><strong>Handdrawn Backgrounds and Art</strong><br/><br/></li><li><strong>Amazing Soundtrack</strong> by the talented Keno Nifty!<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Time Loop Mechanics</strong><br/><br/></li><li><strong>Multiple Endings</strong> <br/><br/></li><li><strong>A Dating Sim Mode?</strong>Of course not. That would be silly</li></ul><br/>Loosely inspired by Junji Ito's "Hellstar Remina" and games from the Zero Escape Series, this game immerses you in a nightmare where an eldritch planet hungers for your very essence. Will you succumb to the insidious influence of the eldritch planet, or can you find a way to break free from the cyclical nightmare?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead Alone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2541400/Dead_Alone/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2541400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dead Alone is an intense <strong>first-person survival shooter</strong> set in a dangerous apocalyptic cityscape. In this desolate landscape, your <strong>precision in shooting and meticulous resource management</strong> will be the key to survival.<br/><br/>In Dead Alone, players can choose between two gripping game modes: <strong>Survival and Horde</strong>. In the Survival mode, they navigate a <strong>fully open world</strong>, making crucial decisions on where to go, which enemies to confront, and how to manage gear and fatigue while scavenging for valuable loot. Alternatively, the Horde mode offers a more <strong>linear progression through sectors</strong>, challenging players to face waves of enemies and strategically upgrade their gear through a shop. <br/><br/>In each mode, players must wield their gathered resources and equipment to battle an <strong>endless onslaught of increasingly relentless foes</strong>. Prepare for an experience where precision, resourcefulness, and survival instincts will be put to the ultimate test in this <strong>unforgiving</strong> post-apocalyptic city.<h2 class="bb_tag">EXPLORATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2541400/extras/environmentHalfSpeed.gif?t=1708099271"><br/>In Dead Alone, embark on the exploration of a small open world with<strong> vibrant and stylized urban environments</strong>. <br/><br/>The landscape offers a mix of dilapidated buildings, ruined streets, and crumbling infrastructure, all of which have succumbed to the ravages of time and disaster. Nature has started to reclaim its territory, with overgrown vegetation breaking through the concrete, adding an eerie and haunting charm to the surroundings. <br/><br/>On the other hand, there are pockets of the city where remnants of human settlements still exist. You may stumble upon abandoned shelters, once inhabited by survivors like yourself. Exploring these areas may reward you with valuable resources, ammunition, or even new powerful weapons to bolster your chances of survival.<h2 class="bb_tag">COMBAT</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2541400/extras/CombatHalfSpeed.gif?t=1708099271"><br/>In Dead Alone, combat is a constant battle against <strong>hordes of zombies with diverse classes</strong>. <br/><br/>As you advance through the game, the intensity of combat escalates, with increasingly powerful and specialized zombies appearing. Surviving these encounters demands smart utilization of your gear, projectiles, and resources. Your weapons choices, will be critical in taking down the undead menace effectively. <br/><br/>To prevail against your ennemies you’ll also need to adapt and develop your combat skills, employing precise aim, resourceful tactics, and efficient use of your surroundings.<h2 class="bb_tag">GEAR</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2541400/extras/gearHalfSpeed.gif?t=1708099271"><br/>In Dead Alone, the<strong> gear plays a vital role</strong> in your survival journey. <br/>Explore the open world and discover an array of weapons with varying rarities, each impacting their effectiveness. Special weapons are also hidden throughout the game, waiting to be discovered as you progress. These rare finds can be true game-changers, granting you a significant advantage.<br/><br/>Managing your health and ammunition is crucial, as you can quickly find yourself overwhelmed if you run out of supplies during intense battles. Strategic use of healing items, upgrades and crafting resources can be the difference between life and death.<br/><br/>The diverse range of gear options in Dead Alone ensures that your choices matter. You must decide which weapons to wield, how to upgrade them, which items to craft, and how to use healing resources effectively.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FY4EVCbZMtQ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2541400/extras/DiscordBanner.jpg?t=1708099271"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">ABOUT ME</h2>Hey, I’m Nerwy ! I’m a solo game dev and I started working on this game more than 3 years ago as a side project, it has been a long rocky road to get here but i’m very proud of being able to show this project finally near completion ! If you think you could enjoy this game, any wishlist would help me a lot !						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overmorrow</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1658970/Overmorrow/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1658970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Overmorrow has a gameplay focus on unguided exploration and big-picture puzzle solving. With a distinctive visual style and a peculiar, mysterious metanarrative, this game is sure to give you a unique indie experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1658970/extras/GIF_Seagulls.gif?t=1708099255"><br/><br/>In Overmorrow, the more Runes you discover, the more actions you can perform in a single day, and the deeper you may explore the mysterious island. There is no time limit, so be sure to fully enjoy the tranquil spaces in this fixed camera 2D game, where every screen contains unique art and curious secrets.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1658970/extras/GIF_Blossom.gif?t=1708099255"><br/><br/>When your Runes have been exhausted, resting will replenish them, but also progress the day count and narrative. After 30 in-game days, your save is deleted. However, in Overmorrow, things are rarely as they seem on the surface, and that is just one more step to discovering the game's many mysteries.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1658970/extras/GIF_Forest.gif?t=1708099255"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2786830/Epstein/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2786830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Epstein<br/><br/>Type: Survival / Adventure<br/><br/>Description:<br/>In Epstein Island, players prepare for a mysterious and dangerous survival and exploration journey on an island! They uncover dark secrets and have perilous missions. By defeating various creatures on Epstein Island, reach the Mini Bosses. There will be 3 Mini Bosses on the island, each located in different regions and dropping different items. The first Mini Boss is Clintin, the second Mini Boss is Havking, and the third Mini Boss is Minwell.<br/><br/>After defeating these individuals and gaining strength, you need to defeat the final Boss, Jefry, who rules over the island. However, be careful and improve your base with your friends on the island and launch attacks. Find the magic elements in the hidden areas of the island and use them! MJ's found within the island will assist you; seek their help instead of trying to harm them, as they will be your allies!<br/><br/>Features:<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2786830/extras/Adsız_tasarım__57_.png?t=1708099230"><br/>Build and Upgrade Your Base:<br/><br/>Strengthen yourself on the island by building your own base. Enhance your home and character with new weapons and mechanics you learn, becoming even stronger!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2786830/extras/Adsız_tasarım__58_.png?t=1708099230"><br/>Fish, Breed Animals, and Produce Meat. Survive!:<br/><br/>As you develop yourself on the island, your character will get hungry. You can fish by making a rod and using worms from the soil as bait with a shovel. Build a farm for pigs and chickens, feeding them with their favorite fruits to produce meat. Be careful! Don't forget to cook the meats.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2786830/extras/Adsız_tasarım__59_.png?t=1708099230"><br/>Find the Temple's Code and Defeat the Boss!<br/><br/><br/>Experience realistic survival in a mysterious and dangerous island environment.<br/>Engage in a dark and immersive storyline filled with mysteries for players to explore.<br/>Combat challenges with morbiders and other formidable foes.<br/>Form strategic alliances and interactions with other survivors.<br/>A dynamic game world where your decisions significantly impact the storyline.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telmari</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2468110/Telmari/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2468110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Telmari save her Sunflowers on her journey to the Demon Tree, on this precision platformer with your catastic companion. Face over 100 hand-crafted levels where your skill and patience will be tested as you explore the world of Agra.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2468110/extras/Todas_4.png?t=1708098671"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Mechanics</h2>Our main game mechanic will be the plunge bow. It will have two primary uses.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>    Once attached to a surface it will work as a propelling object for our heroine Telmari. This will allow her to jump faster and higher than usual.<br/></li><li>    It can be used to avoid enemies by assisting Telmari to jump/fly over the enemies she encounters on her journey. After all, Telmari wouldn't damage a fly.</li></ul><br/>While the mechanic is simple and easy to understand, it gives the player multiple ways to approach a level.  <br/><br/>Levels are designed to make it harder for Telmari to take shortcuts. So bouncing on arrows will often propel you into more dangerous areas—this way we cater to two different groups of players.<br/><br/> The more skilled players can attempt to beat the level as fast as possible using the varied and complicated combos (The more arrows you bounce onto the faster you will go). In contrast, casual players can enjoy a safer play style taking the longer but easier paths.<br/><br/>Some enemies in the game move much faster than Telmari or obstruct the path. For such encounters, it will be vital to master the arrow to outmaneuver them.<br/><br/>Thanks!<br/>I hope you enjoyed out little game. Keep a look out for our future endeavors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2468110/extras/Fin_01.png?t=1708098671"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vtuber Animator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2810100/Vtuber_Animator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"> <h2 class="bb_tag"> <strong> What can Vtuber Animator do? </strong></h2></h2>Vtuber Animator is a VRM model animation player that can synchronize animations in real-time to live streaming software via the OSC protocol.<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Featured</strong></h2></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Support *.vrm model</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Support *.vmd and mixamo fbx animations</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Support *.vpd poses</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Animations can be switched using hotkeys</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"> <h2 class="bb_tag"> <strong> How to use? </strong></h2></h2>In <strong>Vtuber Animator</strong>:<br/>Press "Model+" then select your model through the file picker<br/>Enter ip and a port and press "Connect"<br/>Press "Import" in "Motion List",then select your motion through the file picker<br/>Press "Play" button<br/><br/>In <strong>VSeeFace</strong>:<br/>Enable the "OSC/VMC Receiver (Disable Tracking)" option in VSeeFace, and input the same port as entered in Vtuber Animator. <br/>Optionally toggle "Apply VSeeFace Tracking" and any other toggles underneath it if you only want to perform partial poses.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood Engine</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2702760/Blood_Engine/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2702760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2702760/extras/BloodEngineSeeThruSmall.png?t=1708096036"><br/>In the year 2058, the world is on the brink of collapse due to overpopulation and dwindling resources. In a covert mining and research facility, tucked away in an undisclosed location, a ground-breaking discovery unfolded, a metallic bacteria capable of melding seamlessly with both organic matter and metals.<br/><br/>Driven by the desperation of governments and militaries, they experimented with combining the metallic bacteria with human DNA. Creating the ultimate soldier, the Blood Engine. However, the experimental bacteria proved unpredictable, mutating uncontrollably and giving rise to an epidemic of mindless biomechanical cyborgs known as The Red Swarm.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2702760/extras/BloodEngineSwarm.gif?t=1708096036"><br/><br/>Embark on an adrenaline-fueled journey as a Blood Engine soldier, activated by a science engineer, moments before he was killed. The player awakens to find themselves trapped in a military mining and research facility, now infested with The Red Swarm. The entire complex is encased in an impenetrable electrified dome sealing you, survivors, and the Red Swarm within.<br/><br/>Navigate the treacherous terrain of the infected complex, battling through hordes of biomechanical adversaries, rescuing survivors, and restoring power and control. The fate of the world hangs in the balance as you strive to eliminate the threat before it spills beyond the confines of the facility.<br/><br/>Blood Engine immerses you in an intense and challenging third-person open-world experience, delivering thrills and suspense as you race against time to thwart a global catastrophe. Will you emerge victorious against the relentless Red Swarm, or succumb to the biomechanical onslaught? The fate of humanity rests in your hands.<br/><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2702760/extras/BiohackStudioSmall.png?t=1708096036"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Maze Dream: the puzzle journey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2397880/A_Maze_Dream_the_puzzle_journey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2397880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Maze Dream is a mix of a maze and puzzles. In this game, you control a sheep prince with the power of the cloud and your objective is to reach the end of the level and jump over the fence.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2397880/extras/jump-the-fence.gif?t=1708094757"><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">JUMP THE FENCE</h2></strong><br/>Your objective is to reach the end of each maze and jump over the fence to move on to the next level.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2397880/extras/mistakes.gif?t=1708094757"><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">LEARN FROM YOUR MISTAKES</h2></strong><br/>To err is human, I say sheep... learn from your mistakes and play it again, without life points in the dream world.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2397880/extras/manage.gif?t=1708094757"><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">MANAGE YOUR POWER CARDS</h2></strong><br/>Use your powers to cross the maze, relax and think a little before acting as your resources are limited.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2397880/extras/environment.gif?t=1708094757"><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">USE THE ENVIRONMENT</h2></strong><br/>Study and analyze the terrain and how you interact with it, this could be the solution to the puzzle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2397880/extras/secrets.png?t=1708094757"><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">UNLOCK SECRETS</h2></strong><br/>In some levels you will find secrets, a magic letter or a key without a lock, collect what you can to unlock new experiences.<h2 class="bb_tag">Use all your cards to beat the maze</h2> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Hour And A Straight Line</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2712630/One_Hour_And_A_Straight_Line/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Go to the end of the "line", you have all the time you need. If you want a challenge try to make it in less than an hour and compete for the leaderboard.<br/><br/>One Hour And A Straight Line (OHSL) is a mix between Parkour and FPS games with a little musical twist and a relaxed vibe.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712630/extras/gif2steampageV2.gif?t=1708093603"><h2 class="bb_tag">On this little linear journey you will have:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Wall Riding as the main movement mechanic. You will be wall riding/climbing 95% of the time. With an unique setup allowing complete control of your movements while wall riding.<br/><br/></li><li>Musical Guns instead of normal guns. Shoot to the beat of melodies.<br/><br/></li><li>Platform building: Farm blocks with your musical guns, then place and wallride on them to avoid gaps or obstacles and maximize your speed.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712630/extras/gif1steampageV2.gif?t=1708093603"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wonderway</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2372220/Wonderway/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2372220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Wonderway is a puzzle game where the direction of gravity can be changed. Everything in this game interacts with gravity. You can change the position of items by arrows and portals, utilize cores of energy doors to create passages or blocks, use arrow-shifters to control the direction of arrows, and even separate the gravity of character from the space. Explore many more mechanics and get to the goal by moving and manipulating every items in the levels.<br>
<br>
The game has over 170 hand-crafted puzzles which experiment with the game's mechanics in a multitude of ways. Each puzzle contains at least one new idea, which showcases the wonder of the way to the goal. Hope you enjoy exploring and solving these puzzles.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meteora's Mystic Merge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2751810/Meteoras_Mystic_Merge/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2751810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Meteora's Mystic Merge is a puzzle game based on the famous Suika game. Instead of fruits it uses a variety of vtubers as assets. Meteora's Mystic Merge features currently only a new game mode with a playable character (namely Meteora) who has a special ability, and a classic mode coming soon which plays a lot like the original though with some changes.<br/><br/>This game is similar to the cult game "2048" as well as "Suika Game" which is a switch exclusive.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay:</h2>Combine two of the same character/object to get to the next one.<br/>Try to get to the final Meteora without exceeding the glass or throwing any objects outside of it.<br/>On the right side you can see a little graph which explains the progression levels.<br/>Though the first ones seem rather easy, getting to the final Meteora is challenging to say the least<h2 class="bb_tag">Maybe you will get her:</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2751810/extras/11_normal.png?t=1708108110"><h2 class="bb_tag">Credits:</h2>Art by Rune<br/>Gravity++ by Excelsus						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camping Vlog Simulator 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2665380/Camping_Vlog_Simulator_2024/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2665380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Step into the serene beauty of nature with "Camping Vlog Simulator"! </h2><br/>Immerse yourself in the great outdoors and experience the tranquility of camping in stunning virtual landscapes. Witness breathtaking sunsets and pitch your tent under starry skies: This game lets you live the life of a digital nature enthusiast. Record your camping adventures and share them with the world as you embark on a realistic camping experience. With stunning graphics and captivating gameplay, it's time to escape into the wilderness from the comfort of your own home. Start your adventure today and ignite your passion for the great outdoors!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features: </h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Expansive virtual camping environments to explore.<br/></li><li>Realistic day-night cycles and dynamic weather.<br/></li><li>A variety of camping equipment and gear to use.<br/></li><li>Campfire cooking and food preparation mechanics.<br/></li><li>Immersive soundscapes to enhance the camping experience.<br/></li><li>A progression system to unlock new equipment.<br/></li><li>In-game tips and tutorials for novice campers.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Journey to Santa</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815100/Christmas_Journey_to_Santa/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2815100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Christmas Journey to Santa is a relaxing platformer game about a snowman who dreams of meeting Santa Claus on Christmas Eve. He sets off on a long journey to fulfill his wish. Traveling around the world, he meets obstacles on his way, collects magic red coins to present to Santa. A magical atmosphere and positive emotions await children and adults in the game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enkindle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2809110/Enkindle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2809110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A relaxing and wholesome "clear-up" cooking game. Match 3 objects to cook them in the pan. Don't let the pan get too full. Clear all the objects, clear your mind.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2809110/extras/Clear_your_mind_1.gif?t=1708091931"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Match 3 objects to cook them in the pan<br/></li><li>Don't let the pan get too full<br/></li><li>Clear all the objects to pass the level<br/></li><li>Perfect game for those that get satisfaction from clearing up clutter or hearing the sound of food sizzling. </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2809110/extras/Relaxing_sounds_and_effects_2.gif?t=1708091931"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Relaxing sounds that help you relax<br/></li><li> If you like the sound of food sizzling, this game is perfect for you.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2809110/extras/Lots_of_levels.gif?t=1708091931"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Lots of unique level variations<br/></li><li> Randomly generated levels for unlimited relaxation.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2809110/extras/Phsyics_items_1.gif?t=1708091931"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Over 200+ unique items<br/></li><li> Physics-based items</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2809110/extras/Controls.gif?t=1708091931"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Just tap on an item<br/></li><li> Simple satisfying gameplay</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Relaxing music and effects.<br/></li><li> No timers, play at your own pace.<br/></li><li> Over 200+ physics items.<br/></li><li> Lots of unique level variations.<br/></li><li> Quick levels. Levels range from 30 seconds up to 5 minutes.<br/></li><li> Intuitive controls, just tap the item.<br/></li><li> Helps you relax and de-stress.<br/></li><li> Easy to pick up and play. Fun for all ages.<br/></li><li> Various gameplay, graphics, and performance settings.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
