<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Darkest Dungeon® II: The Binding Blade</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2598510/Darkest_Dungeon_II_The_Binding_Blade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2598510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Two New Playable heroes: The Duelist &amp; The Crusader<br/></li><li>Both new heroes are complete with unique trinkets, signature items, and fully voiced backstories including playable flashback encounters<br/></li><li>New Roaming mini-boss: The Warlord</li></ul><br/><strong>The Duelist</strong> is a disciplined and deadly combatant who can tactically switch between Defensive and Aggressive stances. A formidable presence in any lineup, she is able to ignore enemy defenses, and strike back with Riposte. Her pursuit of perfection means she will demand the best of her team and command them to victory by wiping out cooldown times and providing both offensive and defensive buffs. The Duelist is able to move between ranks with ease, attacking from both the front and back ranks, dispatching her enemies with ruthless efficiency.<br/><br/><strong>The Crusader</strong> has returned! This battle hardened knight is fueled by a radiant Holy fire and will Smite his foes where they stand. The Crusader is a well rounded front rank hero who can withstand punishing blows, support his team with healing and stress recovery, and rend his opponents with his righteous blade.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1701985511"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1701985511"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1702000678"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1702000678"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Born of Bread</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1555140/Born_of_Bread/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Beings from another age are causing havoc across the land! And with their mischief comes a great threat to everyone. The unlikeliest hero, a golem born of bread, will find himself and his newfound buddies in the middle of a drama that's thousands of years in the making. Together, they will visit incredible locals and meet fascinating characters. Although he may not look like much, Loaf might be the hero this land kneads.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Sentient Bread on a Quest</h2><br/>Play as a flour golem who possesses a never-ending childlike wonder and a set of odd abilities in this 2.5D adventure game!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Cinematic_opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/>Explore the different regions of a wonderful world ripe with mysteries and team up with a colorful cast of fleshed-out characters. With the help of your buddies, face off against menacing and weird baddies and engage in a fun and quirky turn-based combat system.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Enviro_opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/><strong>A home-cooked battle system</strong><br/>Born of Bread puts a twist on turn-based combat tropes with a fun interaction system that will test your reflexes.<br/>This interactive system also features a weaknesss and resistance system that makes battles more strategic.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Combat_Opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/><strong>Team up with your buddies</strong><br/>Loaf can't do it alone. Meet new characters during your adventure, each with their own abilities and personnality. Use their unique skills to overcome threats and obstacles whether in fights or when exploring.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Buddies_opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/><strong>Stream your fights to a fake audience!</strong><br/>Your dragon buddy Dub will let you save your progression but also stream your fights to a fake audience with his little laptop! Gather more viewers and answer their demand to get rewards!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood West</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_steam_text_header.png?t=1702334775"><br/><br/>Weird West legends meet eldritch horror in <strong>BLOOD WEST</strong>, an immersive stealth FPS. Become the Undead Gunslinger, doomed to roam the barren lands until he finds the means to purge their curse and free his soul. No, this isn’t your typical Wild West desperado redemption arc. This is a damnation arc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_episodes_EN.gif?t=1702334775"><br/><br/>The Canyons, the Swamp, and the Mountains. Each swarming with abominable monsters and unholy demons, these are open-ended worlds for you to explore freely at your own pace. It will take the player over 20 hours on average to complete all three scenarios, and over 35 if they want to see everything the barren lands have to offer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_stealth_EN.gif?t=1702334775"><br/><br/><strong>Blood West</strong> is a stealth FPS inspired by the genre classics such as the Thief series (whose fans will be happy to hear the voice of Stephen Russell, the actor voicing the master-thief Garrett, returning here as the protagonist), S.T.A.L.K.E.R. games, or - from the contemporary catalog - Hunt: Showdown. The gameplay rewards the careful approach: scouting the area, stalking your enemies, and striking from the shadows. Can you figure out a way to clear a fort full of ghouls and monsters without raising an alarm?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_horror_EN.gif?t=1702334775"><br/><br/>The Barren Lands present the player with a nightmarish, twisted vision of the Wild West legends. The curse that has befallen the realm has corrupted every living thing, defiled the land itself, while summoning restless spirits and dark entities. In this mixture of gunslinger pulp and Lovecraftian horror, dark occult magick presents just as much of a threat as sudden lead poisoning.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_characters_EN.gif?t=1702334775"><br/><br/>In <strong>Blood West</strong> you will meet many colorful, yet strangely twisted, fully-voiced NPCs. Just as much prisoners of the Barren Lands as you are, they will sometimes share their unusual stories and send you on various missions. Play nice and they might reward you or become your allies. Cross them and risk their wrath.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_secrets_EN.gif?t=1702334775"><br/><br/>The game won’t hold your hand. You’ll have to explore the land for yourself (buying a map from a vendor might prove useful!), and figure out your own way to approach quests. As you poke around the three expansive maps, keep an eye out for hidden places and secret stashes. There’s gold in the mountains! Fair warning - it’s probably cursed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_brutal_EN.gif?t=1702334775"><br/><br/>If sneaking around isn’t exactly your thing, or you feel that you have a power advantage over your enemies, you can always take the head-on approach and meet your enemies guns blazing. <strong>Blood West</strong> comes from the creators of the fan-favorite boomer shooter <strong>POSTAL: Brain Damaged</strong>, so much gratuitous fantasy violence and pixelated blood splatter is to be expected!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_inventory_EN.gif?t=1702334775"><br/><br/>One man’s hell might be another hoarder’s paradise! From simple one-use items like bandages, through medical tinctures, explosives and incendiaries, straight to arcane artifacts that - once slotted - can change the way you play the game, the Barren Lands are just filled with STUFF. There are tons of useful items to discover, and there’s a special player’s stash crate for all those super-rare potions that you’ll hoard and never use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_weapons_EN.gif?t=1702334775"><br/><br/>A gunslinger without a gun would be just a regular slinger. Where’s the fun in that? <strong>Blood West</strong> makes sure you’ll have plenty of weapons to choose from. Revolvers, rifles, shotguns, carabines - a great variety of firearms, from standard army-issue to those infused with powerful magic, or straight-up possessed. And if you prefer not to cause a ruckus, there’s a wide selection of hand-to-hand combat weapons and archery weapons to pick your favorites from.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_skills_EN.gif?t=1702334775"><br/><br/>The RPG-like perk-based progression system in <strong>Blood West</strong> will allow you to highly customize the gameplay experience to your liking. Become a stealthy hunter, a revolver-fanning gunman or a relentless berserker. You will gain experience and progress through the skill tree, while discovering new artifacts in each of the scenarios that will bestow on you additional abilities. Combining skills and load-out creates more possible playstyles than you’d normally be able to explore in one playthrough.<h2 class="bb_tag">Are you ready to take back the frontier from the dark forces of demonic corruption and earn the right to move on to a better world? The Barren Lands call you, Gunslinger!</h2><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1701702754"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1701702754"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1701702754"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1702203824"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1702203824"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SteamWorld Build</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2134770/SteamWorld_Build/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-Homestead.png?t=1702026390"><br/>One final landrush! The planet is dyin', Astrid, and it's dig or die trying! <br/><br/>That mine under our town is sitting empty, and wouldn't you know there's rumours of ancient tech down there that might help us out of this predicament. Round up the posse, circle the wagons, and let's get to buildin' a new home! Collect resources above ground and ores down below so we can get those wealthy bots in here to help us build bigger, and we can get the heck out of here!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_1.gif?t=1702026390"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_manage.png?t=1702026390"><br/>As your borders expand, new steamfolk will find their way to you! Every bot is crotchety in their own way, and it's up to you to keep them steaming along. Barter to boost efficiency, keep goods flowing to and from the mines and keep everyone happy to make them work their darndest and hardest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_2.gif?t=1702026390"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-DIG-DEEP.png?t=1702026390"><br/><br/>Stare into the abyss long enough and it might just stare back... we're going looking for riches and something down there doesn't want to share! Have gun, dig gravel, and make sure the mines don't collapse upon you as you defend yourselves from the creepy crawlies that lurk within...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_3.gif?t=1702026390"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_features.png?t=1702026390"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break ground on a bustling SteamWorld town, inspired by the Old West.<br/></li><li>Keep your steambots from getting cranky by ensuring their complex needs get met<br/></li><li>Dig deep and spread wide to produce resources to aid your search for ancient technologies<br/></li><li>Defend your mine from the creepy varmints that lurk deep below your town<br/></li><li>Trade resources at the local train stop and welcome special visitors who'll lend a hand<br/></li><li>Five distinct maps littered with secrets for the discerning SteamWorld explorer to find<br/></li><li>Developed from the ground up for both mouse and controller, whichever takes yer fancy.<br/></li><li>Four difficulty levels, including a sandbox difficulty for when you just want to Build!</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-4 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">4-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with three other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1701703276"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinball M</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2337640/Pinball_M/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-1.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-2.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free<br/>- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage<br/>- Thrilling competition<br/>- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation<h2 class="bb_tag">Sink your teeth into these tables as purchasable DLC: </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">- Chucky's Killer Pinball:</h2> Step into a twisted realm where the innocent becomes sinister, and the playful turns menacing. Navigate through an eerie playfield where Chucky lurks in the shadows, ready to pounce.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Dead by Daylight™️ Pinball:</h2> Become the hunter or even the hunted in a thrilling fusion of classic pinball and the excitement of one of the most popular horror games ever created.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Duke Nukem's Big Shot Pinball:</h2> Enjoy the biggest, grooviest, most BADASS pinball table ever made packed with guns and babes. Push start and play with balls of steel!<h2 class="bb_tag">- The Thing Pinball: </h2>Use your pinball skills and battle against the shape-shifting alien through the arctic chill of U.S. Outpost #31. Can you trust anyone, even yourself?<br/>- Even more coming...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-4.png?t=1701703297"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn back immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Option</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.<br/>If you are easily intoxicated, changing the following settings may help.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera shake】</strong><br/>The camera shakes when you walk or run, but if you set the value to 0.0, the camera will not shake.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Acceleration】</strong><br/>If you set the maximum value to 30.0, the camera will move without delay.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Sensitivity】</strong><br/>If the sensitivity is high, the camera will move significantly when the mouse is moved. <br/>Adjust the value if you find it difficult to operate the camera with the default value of 1.<br/><br/><strong>【Motion Blur】</strong><br/>Afterimages will appear when the camera is moved. Recommended to disable at 30FPS<br/><br/><strong>【Preset】</strong><br/>Set the overall graphic settings.<br/>If you do not have sufficient specs, it is better to set it to "Low" to avoid sickness.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1701853441"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1701853441"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1701853441"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats and Seek</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2672090/Cats_and_Seek/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							😻 100 Cats!<br/>🔍 Hint system<br/>🎨 Choose your favorite color<br/><br/>Let's play hide and seek with 100 cats!<br/>Can you find them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/extras/game_play.gif?t=1702275103"><br/><br/>And if bored with black and white doddles you can choose <strong>your own favorite color</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/extras/change_color.PNG?t=1702275103"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header_alt_assets_2.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1701808865"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658820/Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							10 possible fruits and one goal, reach the Watermelon.<br/>Your job is to combine matching fruits to evolve them to the next one and eventually reach the coveted Watermelon.<br/>To help you, you have 3 different abilities at your disposal. But watch out, using these will cost you some of your points. Be smart about when you use them to get the highest score!<h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLAYER</h2>Measure your fruit skills against another player.<h2 class="bb_tag">GET THE WATERMELON</h2>How many Watermelons can you combine before your basket overflows?<h2 class="bb_tag">USE YOUR ABILITIES</h2>Power, level up and destroy — These abilities will help you reach the Watermelon, using any of those will also allow you to angle your aim.<h2 class="bb_tag">GOLDEN FRUIT</h2>If luck is on your side, you might even see the mysterious Golden Fruit. Find it and witness its effect firsthand.<h2 class="bb_tag">STATISTICS</h2>Track your progress with in-depth statistics. Visit the menu to see the number of fruits you've combined, your ability usage, and much more.<h2 class="bb_tag"></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.codecks.io%2Fwatermelon-game" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/extras/Roadmap_Banner.png?t=1702238677"/></a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football Manager 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2252570/Football_Manager_2024/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2252570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a real boss and write your own football story in Football Manager 2024, the most complete edition in the series yet. <br/><br/>Whether you’re a manager who likes to build from the bottom or prefers to chase immediate glory, the perfect challenge awaits. The arrival of the new Meiji Yasuda Insurance Ltd J. League licence unlocks J1 League, J2 League, J3 League for the first time ever, giving you the opportunity to explore new horizons in Japan.<br/><br/>Wherever you manage, it's up to you to build a team capable of competing with the world's elite.<br/><br/><strong>Game Description </strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Continue your relentless journey to the top of the footballing world by using the new ability to import your existing career from Football Manager 2023.<br/></li><li>Craft a winning tactical approach, incorporating modern football’s most popular systems and cutting-edge positional innovations to deliver victories on the pitch. <br/></li><li>Master the transfer market, using new ways to shape your side to cultivate a squad capable of achieving your goals. <br/></li><li>Level up your players on the training field, developing the mentality and teamwork needed to transform contenders into champions. <br/></li><li>See your tactical vision come to life on Matchdays, with every game elevated by improvements to ball and player movements.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">NEW FOR THIS SEASON</h2><br/><br/><strong>TRUER FOOTBALL MOTION</strong><br/><br/>Enhancements to player animations, ball physics and lighting deliver the most immersive Match Engine in Football Manager history. Move to the cutting edge of football by using the new Inverted Full-Back player role, while more intelligent player rotational movements add more fluidity to every highlight. <br/><br/><strong>DOMINATE FROM SET PIECES</strong><br/><br/>Make an impact at both ends of the pitch with an overhauled Set Piece Creator. Lean on the expertise of brand-new Set Piece Coaches to develop winning routines in every scenario that will help you to outsmart your rivals. <br/><br/><strong>BRACE FOR TRANSFER BATTLES</strong><br/><br/>Showcase your squad-building skills in our most refined transfer market yet. You’ll face a trickier battle for talent as your rival opposition managers are now more strategic than ever in their recruitment decision-making. <br/><br/><strong>NEW AGENTS TO BUILD A DREAM SQUAD</strong><br/><br/>Better shape your perfect squad with the introduction of new Intermediaries that will help you offload surplus players for a cut of the final transfer fee. Additional functionality for existing Agents and the debut of TransferRoom, a football marketplace for transfers in real life, gives you more real-world powered tools than ever to build an elite team and dominate the competition.<br/><br/><strong>ELEVATE PERFORMANCES WITH TARGETS</strong><br/><br/>Motivate your team to achieve more on and off the field by setting them individual Targets. Whether you’re focusing on goals scored in a season or average training performances, challenge your star players and top prospects to maximise their ability. <br/><br/><strong>A HOST MORE ADDITIONS</strong><br/><br/>Enjoy greater variety in every career with the arrival of two new game modes. Real World mirrors when players actually joined your club. Your World sets club squads and budgets at the day your career starts, meaning that only players who joined before that date will be in your squad, giving you the opportunity to rewrite your team’s transfer window.<br/><br/>Elsewhere, you can look to dominate international management and plan for your country's future with a revamped National Pool that gives you a better overview of the talent at your disposal. Match preparation and briefing meetings deliver you winning insights before each fixture. <br/><br/>That’s not all though, with many more changes waiting for you to discover in every career.<br/><br/><i>This version contains information that is still under approval process by rights holders and may contain data that does not, at this time, accurately reflect real world data. For context, some club and player assets may be absent during this version.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Invincible</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/731040/The_Invincible/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/731040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/731040/extras/Invincible_Steam_Deck_Verified_616x226.jpg?t=1702297249"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/731040/extras/The_Invincible_small_claim_logo_EN.png?t=1702297249"><br/><br/>You are a highly qualified, sharp-witted astrobiologist named Yasna. Being entangled in a space race, you and your crew end up on the unexplored planet Regis III. The scientific journey quickly turns into a search mission for lost crewmates. Follow its trail, but be fully aware that every decision you make can bring you closer to danger.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/731040/extras/The_Invincible_gif_nr_1.gif?t=1702297249"><br/><br/>Uncover mind-boggling scientific phenomena in a cosmic, philosophical adventure set within eerie landscapes. Discover fragments of what’s lost and report to your Astrogator, let his voice aid you in hard times.<br/><br/>You couldn’t have foreseen humanity’s biggest threat. It will force you to rethink mankind’s ambitions and biases. Go on - make decisions, follow the mystery… but remember not to underestimate the brutal simplicity and brilliance of evolution.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/731040/extras/The_Invincible_gif_nr_2.gif?t=1702297249"><br/><br/>Robots, people… Choose whether to interact with different creatures on Regis III or how to do it. Friend, companion? Enemy? You never suspected what these words might really mean before you got here.<br/><br/>Immerse yourself in the atompunk atmosphere by using various tools, such as a telemeter or a tracker, and drive a vehicle through a stunning landscape. Experience realistic interactions with analogue technologies in a retro futuristic timeline.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/731040/extras/The_Invincible_nr_3.gif?t=1702297249"><br/><br/>The Invincible is a first-person game based on the motifs of The Invincible - an iconic novel of the world-known, hard science-fiction author and Polish futurologist Stanisław Lem.<br/><br/>There are places like Regis III, not prepared for us and for which we are not prepared. Still, our spacecraft inevitably comes closer to the destination - for our stories and fates to cross in a dead spot.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cards and Castles 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1719390/Cards_and_Castles_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1719390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Both incredibly deep and easy for new players to pick up, this fun and wacky CCG features a tactical board for a touch of strategy. Cards played spring to life on the battlefield as animated characters who can move and block enemies, adding depth to the traditional CCG formula. Build unique decks from 7 different iconic factions: Vikings, Crusaders, Warlocks, Pirates, Ninjas, Druids, and the NEWLY ADDED undead!<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Worldwide Online Cross-Platform Multiplayer<br/></li><li> Cross-Platform Accounts<br/></li><li> Multiplayer Lobbies, Friends Lists, and Chat<br/></li><li> Draft Mode<br/></li><li> Single Player Modes<br/></li><li> Collectible Cosmetics<br/></li><li> Lots of Free Cards<br/></li><li> Penguins</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ranch Simulator - Build, Farm, Hunt</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1119730/Ranch_Simulator__Build_Farm_Hunt/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1119730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							It was once your grandfather’s pride-and-joy, but your family ranch has fallen on hard times and it’s up to you to turn things around. Sitting in a remote forested valley, the dilapidated homestead will test all your abilities as you attempt to turn it into the most prosperous ranch in the region – either alone or in up to four player co-op multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1119730/extras/Ranch_Sim_DemolishGIF.gif?t=1702311236"><h2 class="bb_tag">Rebuild Your Ranch</h2><br/>The years have not been kind to your family ranch and it will take time and money to restore it to its former glory. Buy tools from the local hardware store and purchase a range of vehicles from the garage to help with your rebuilding projects. Renovate the main house, decide what livestock you want to farm and construct the barns, pens and runs you’ll need to keep them safe and secure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1119730/extras/Ranch_Sim_ChickensGIF.gif?t=1702311236"><h2 class="bb_tag">Look After Your Livestock</h2><br/>Grand building projects are one thing. Paying for them? That’ll come down to your ranching skills. Overseeing a profitable operation is all about the day-to-day. Once you’ve selected and taken on your livestock, regular feeding and watering will keep them healthy. Successful breeding and careful rearing of the young will help boost the numbers in your herds and flocks — and the more produce you have to sell, the more income you’ll receive for all that hard work.<br/><br/>Expand your ranch enterprise by farming crops, producing sausages and cheese and even training and selling horses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1119730/extras/Ranch_Sim_HuntingGIF.gif?t=1702311236"><h2 class="bb_tag">Head Out on the Hunt</h2><br/>There’s a large open-world environment outside your cosy homestead and it’s teeming with wildlife. So when you feel like slowing the pace, why not grab your trusty rifle and head out into the forest to stalk deer and hunt bears? But remember, the wilderness lives by its own laws and you aren’t the only skilled hunter in the neighbourhood. Sometimes your steady hand and sharp eyes will also be needed back on the ranch to stop hungry wolves turning your off-grid dream into a nightmare.<br/><br/>Play the game PCGamesN calls "House Flipper meets Red Dead Redemption 2"!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EA SPORTS™ WRC</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1849250/EA_SPORTS_WRC/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1849250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build the car of your dreams in our biggest rally game ever, EA SPORTS™ WRC, the all-new official videogame of the FIA World Rally Championship, the first developed by the award-winning team behind the DiRT Rally series.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1849250/extras/WCR_GameFeatures_Launch.png?t=1701207985"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For The King II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1676840/For_The_King_II/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/header_alt_assets_7.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_AboutThisGame_Steam_StoreBanner_2_EN.png?t=1701984973"><br/><br/>Once beloved by her people, Queen Rosomon has turned against her subjects, casting them into servitude in the darkness of Fahrul’s mines whilst building alliances with sinister and malevolent forces.<br/><br/>Gather your party in four player co-op or adventure alone through Fahrul as you risk everything to fight the tyrannical queen and bring an end to her oppressive reign.<br/><br/>From the creators of For The King, the much-loved RPG that blends roguelite and tabletop gameplay comes a new chapter in Fahrul’s history, designed on an updated engine bringing innovation and gameplay refinement for returning heroes and new adventurers alike.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading01_Inspired_ENGLISH.png?t=1701984973"><br/><br/>For The King II is easy for anyone to pick up and play, but takes skill, patience, and strategic excellence to master whilst remaining infinitely replayable with a procedurally generated map that ensures no two playthroughs will ever be the same. Unique yet familiar dice roll inspired movement, encounter and combat mechanics add even more spontaneity and variety as your fortunes rise and fall on the roll of the dice.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF01_InspiredByTabletop.gif?t=1701984973"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading02_Digestible2_ENGLISH.png?t=1701984973"><br/><br/>For The King II provides a complete campaign with over 30 hours of gameplay, split into 5 separate adventures, each narratively linked. The journey is long and the path is treacherous but fear not, if your party fails you will start stronger and wiser on your next playthrough with better starting items to draft into your loadout.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF02_RogueliteCampaign.gif?t=1701984973"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading03_Muster_ENGLISH.png?t=1701984973"><br/><br/>Create your party from 12 unique character classes, each with their own unique perks, strengths and playstyles. From the heavy-handed hitter of The Blacksmith, to the wily potion-wielding Alchemist, you choose which characters will take on the fearsome Queensguard and the combat strategies that will ensure success. Introduce new characters to your party with mercenaries and companions that enable you to pluck wild beasts from the forest floor and recruit ruthless mercenaries from local taverns (for a price of course) to bolster your ranks in times of trouble.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF03_MusterYouMight_.gif?t=1701984973"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading04_Party_ENGLISH.png?t=1701984973"><br/><br/>Traverse Fahrul solo or with up-to three friends in four-player co-op. As a solo player you can control all characters in your party, giving you complete ownership of the campaign map and combat strategy whilst in four-player co-op you must coordinate and negotiate with your party members. Play online multiplayer with your friends controlling your own character(s) or play offline co-op on the same PC. Offline co-op supports multiple controllers; each controller will have input control on everyone’s turn.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF04_PartyofFour.gif?t=1701984973"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading05_Evolved_ENGLISH.png?t=1701984973"><br/><br/>Inspired by turn-based classics, For The King II adds strategic depth to much-loved combat mechanics with the new Battle Grid, where movement and position provide you and your enemies with strategic buffs and penalties. Defend the back row by equipping a mighty Tower Shield, push enemies into lethal pools of burning fire, or entangle melee troops with dark magic cast with weapons looted from vanquished foes. The choice is yours!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF05_EvolveTurnBased.gif?t=1701984973"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading06_Explore_ENGLISH.png?t=1701984973"><br/><br/>Fahrul is both beautiful and deadly in equal measure. On your journey you will encounter a wealth of diverse biome environments brought to life in a breathtaking art style. From lush forests, toxic swamps and lava-filled wastelands to pirate (no scratch that!) Merling-infested tropical seas, For The King II transports you deep into the wonders of Fahrul, leading you further than ever before into this stunningly-imagined land of adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF06_ExploreFantastical.gif?t=1701984973"><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Ffortheking" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTK_Discord_Banner_EN.gif?t=1701984973"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arcane Blood: The Shattered Star</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2695450/Arcane_Blood_The_Shattered_Star/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2695450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Long ago, the first star was born.<br>
<br>
On the night when the star was burning the brightest, any girl born under the light would be gifted the magic of the powers of the Star Goddess.<br>
<br>
Those girls were hunted and burned for holding such immense power. All except for one who was kept hidden in the forest by her mother.<br>
<br>
Seventeen years later... the first star has shattered scattering the chunks across the universe, one even landing in the kingdom of Lordell.<br/>
<br/>
A warlock seeking great power has taken over Lordell Castle and in one final effort the prince shattered it further into eight fragments, ordering the Maidens of the First Star to hide them deep within ancient temples around the kingdom.<br/>
<br/>
The last surviving witch, Verana wakes up to a voice,<br/>
<br/>
"Go find the fragments. Stop him. Save me. Please."<br/>
<br/>
PLAY as Verana, a young witch and master a variety of spells to slice, burn, and zap enemies in this 2D platforming adventure!<br/>
<br/>
DEFEAT bosses sealed away in forgotten dungeons to claim the scattered fragments of the shattered star and restore peace to the land!<br/>
<br/>
UPGRADE Verana's health and magic at Angel Maiden Statues by making hearty donations!<br/>
<br/>
EXPLORE a great forest, dark caves, sandy waste, and even quaint towns!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DemonStar - Original Missions</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2577180/DemonStar__Original_Missions/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							After many long years, the Shareware legend DemonStar comes soaring back with new game modes, revised gameplay. Originally published in 1997, and later earning COMPUTER GAMING WORLD shareware Game of the Year 1999, DemonStar was, and still is, one of the best space shooters ever created. <br>
<br>
- New game modes include Legacy Mode and Enhanced Mode<br>
- 60 or 120fps <br>
- Original Soundtrack by Bobby Prince<br>
- New Soundtrack by Pfeffermouse<br>
- Video/Screen improvements not available on other versions.<br/>
- Tate/vertical mode for vertical monitors<br/>
<br/>
DemonStar is the most thrilling vertical scrolling shooter on the market! DemonStar takes shooters to the extreme with controller support, 3D rendered graphics, explosive sound effects, and a brilliant soundtrack. To destroy each boss, you will have to search for the many weapons such as lasers, homing missiles, and many more. As you maneuver your way through each of the 18 progressive levels, you can build up an arsenal worthy of a match against the greatest mega-boss of all time:THE DEMONSTAR						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myth of Future Dimension</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1288640/Myth_of_Future_Dimension/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1288640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>This is a game with bankroll of <u>less than $13,000</u>, so don't expect too much. </strong><br/><br/>This is the beginning of a series of stories, presented at its most basic with very limited resources. <br/>There will definitely be many shortcomings, so please consider this as a <strong><u>'crowdfunding'</u></strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Different from the traditional RTS games of the past, this game tries <u>a new RTS game design positioning</u>:</strong><br/>× Complex and technically in-depth operations.<br/><strong>√ Easy and convenient operation with the help of AI. </strong><br/>× Officially designed "regular gameplay".<br/><strong>√ Gives players more freedom to play. </strong><br/>× Heavy and tense atmosphere.<br/><strong>√ A light-hearted and enjoyable experience. </strong><br/><br/>The core gameplay is consistent with common real-time strategy games.<br/>The game includes detailed guidance and tutorials that gradually deepen as the plot progresses.<br/>Even if you are trying real-time strategy games for the first time, you can still adapt and master this game well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1288640/extras/Yuki.png?t=1702348148"><br/>Players will take on the heroine <strong>Yuki Usami's</strong> first-person perspective while confronting enemies to uncover <strong>little-known secrets of the real world</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">High degree of freedom gameplay:</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1288640/extras/Armament1.png?t=1702348148"><br/>Deploy a fleet of drones controlled by AI fully automated.<br/>As the plot collects, steals technology, upgrades armaments, and freely configures armaments to achieve different tactics.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1288640/extras/Lurker.png?t=1702348148"><br/>The vanguard (hero unit) that the player controls also has <strong>a large customization space</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1288640/extras/Reiki.png?t=1702348148"><br/>Similar to RPG games, each vanguard can <strong>freely assign attributes</strong> to suit different tactical needs.<h2 class="bb_tag">Other Features:</h2>· Simplified resource gathering, automatic turret reconstruction, and automatic unit replenishment allow players to focus more on combat.<br/>· Smarter unit AI makes operation much easier.<h2 class="bb_tag">Main game content:</h2>As the "beginning of the plot" and "foreshadowing of the world view" of the series,<strong> there is only a single-player campaign, and <u>does not support PVP</u></strong>.<br/><br/><strong>The game is divided into three difficulty levels</strong>, allowing players to gradually adapt and become familiar with the game as the difficulty increases.<br/><strong>None</strong> of the three difficulties<strong> are "simple stat increases"</strong>, but have corresponding "mechanical changes". Make every difficulty experience different.<br/><br/>A variety of level designs, including linear story missions, RPG adventure missions, attack missions, base defense missions, and challenge bosses.<h2 class="bb_tag">About the main story:</h2>The final plot of the main story, in Nightmare difficulty, behind the "three-tier blockade" in the enemy's core fortress. There are a few secrets about the real world hidden......<h2 class="bb_tag">Girl's talk：</h2>In addition to the main story, this work also contains "small talk" content between several heroines. While shaping the characters, I hope to bring more joy to players who like ACG games.<h2 class="bb_tag">Subsequent content:</h2>As mentioned at the beginning, the resources of this game are very limited, so only long-term bug fixes are provided for this game.<br/>All this is just for "being able to dedicate 'good' games without being restricted by *******", so please understand.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Additional instructions: </h2>This game contains a very small amount of "unlocalized content", which was intentionally created by the author to meet the needs of the plot and not affect the game process.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Master: MarsVille</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2366120/Build_Master_MarsVille/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2366120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge Mars, Command the Stars!</strong></h2>As Earth's resources dwindle, humanity has migrated to the distant planet of Mars. Now, your opportunity has arrived! In <strong>Build Master: MarsVille</strong>, you are invited to pioneer the most captivating colony on this enchanting red world. As your colony grows in scale and complexity, every decision you make will shape its destiny! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2366120/extras/g1.gif?t=1702347589"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Bring Your Colony to Life</strong></h2>Start with the untouched canvas of Mars and build your dream city. Construct skyscrapers, parks, bridges, and other buildings. Strategically layout your structures to ensure the city's continuous development. On this harsh planet, your decisions affect life and death. Plan your buildings meticulously to boost resource production, meet citizen demands, and stimulate urban expansion.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2366120/extras/55666.gif?t=1702347589"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Thriving on Mars</strong></h2>Collect various resources from Mars' terrain and strategically allocate them for city construction and upgrades. Trade resources with other players to enhance your colony's prosperity. Make critical financial decisions, balancing investments in the city, the military, and hero development to ensure citizen satisfaction and overall progress. The heroes, each equipped with distinctive abilities, are pivotal in ensuring the smooth operation of city management. Your city may also face attacks from extraterrestrial pirates and sandworms. When battles loom, command your heroes to defend against the invaders!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2366120/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__1_.gif?t=1702347589"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Unleash Your Engineering Genius</strong></h2>During the Mars construction process, you'll encounter numerous challenging gaps to bridge. Unleash your creativity and engineering talents to showcase your bridge-building skills. Each level presents breathtaking scenery and brand-new challenges. Can your carefully crafted bridges withstand the weight test and the limits of engineering expertise? Hold your breath and witness the adrenaline-pumping moments! Of course, failure is inevitable. The thrilling moments of bridge collapse or truck mishaps will provide valuable lessons and drive you to refine your skills continually.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2366120/extras/766.gif?t=1702347589"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Team Up and Battle Your Way to Victory</strong></h2>Establish close connections with other colonists and unite to face external threats. Exchange resources to promote mutual prosperity and coordinate attacks against common enemies. Challenge rival colonies, seize valuable resources, and immerse yourself in the thrilling excitement of interstellar warfare. Rise in the ranks and accumulate reputation and rewards. Your tactical wisdom will determine victory at crucial moments.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2366120/extras/666.gif?t=1702347589"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 52 Fragments</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2702660/The_52_Fragments/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2702660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The 52 Fragments</strong><br/><br/>are an experimental, esoteric<br/><br/>series of games and experiences.<br/><br/><br/>Beginning Nov. 1, 2023,<br/><br/>one fragment will be added<br/><br/>to the library each week for one year.<br/><br/><br/>These games examine themes<br/><br/>related to identity, agency, perception,<br/><br/>and the creative process.<br/><br/>Fragments may change over time.<br/><br/>Replay is encouraged.<br/><br/>--<br/><br/><br/>Follow the creator for behind-the-scenes content and more:<br/><br/>tiktok, facebook, twitter: @dorktoast<br/><br/>discord: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgibgames" rel="noopener" target="_blank">discord.gg/gibgames</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallen</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2584590/Fallen/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2584590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Eson is an angel who is punished with the curse of mortality when they steal the Sky God's Amulet. Now they have to help people in Havoton, a Halloween-obsessed town, in order to survive and atone for their crime. <br>
<br>
Play through many different and unique minigames as you help the residents of the town prepare for their Halloween festivities and other daily menial tasks. However, with the help of the Goddess of Balance, you can make some of these minigames easier! No strings attached!<br>
<br>
Experience the game's story and customize your experiences by helping different people out and completing all of the minigames. There are multiple endings, try and collect them all!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spellshot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2306780/Spellshot/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2306780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Fend Off Hordes</h2>Being sent off-world for munitions testing is never a great assignment. Even more so when your destination turns out to be the zombie-infested halls of Caleme Castle. Batten down the hatches or get out and use your legs, corporate doesn't care. As long as you survive long enough for them to collect enough data, they'll be happy (that is, if they even feel emotion).<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2306780/extras/combat.gif?t=1702343352"><h2 class="bb_tag">Empower Your Bullets</h2>While you are enjoying your limited stay at "Zombie Manor", you'll come across a great deal of gems. These empower your bullets, giving them all-around splendid effects such as:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bone-chilling frostburn<br/></li><li> Noxious gas<br/></li><li> Piercing hot cinders<br/></li><li> Immobilizing gunk<br/></li><li> and much, much more!</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2306780/extras/shop.gif?t=1702343352"><h2 class="bb_tag">Discover New Builds</h2>There's a great deal of purchasing, selling, rerolling, and combining to get to. So what are you waiting on? Get to finding those rare item synergies and special gem combinations.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmic Carnage: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2704660/Cosmic_Carnage_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704660/extras/text5_nobg_battle.png?t=1702338161"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704660/extras/Gif_Fullsize_Battle.gif?t=1702338161"><br/>Battle endless waves of alien spaceships. Fight against a variety of enemies with different behaviours and attack patterns<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704660/extras/text2_nobg_collect.png?t=1702338161"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704660/extras/Gif_Fullsize_Collect.gif?t=1702338161"><br/>Collect EXP to level up and upgrade your ship to help you survive the onslaught. 80+ upgrades available making each run unique and interesting<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704660/extras/text4_nobg_unlock.png?t=1702338161"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704660/extras/Gif_Fullsize_Unlocks.gif?t=1702338161"><br/>With a roguelite progression system, no run is ever a fail. Gather more points and unlock new upgrades and weapons to add to the pool to create overpowered builds!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704660/extras/text3_nobg_upgrade.png?t=1702338161"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704660/extras/Gif_Fullsize_AstronautAndMods.gif?t=1702338161"><br/>Upgrade your build by unlocking new astronauts and ships. Each astronaut has unique abilities and stats. Each ship has a unique weapon and stats. Synchronize astronauts and ships to unlock hidden synergies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704660/extras/text9_nobg_survive.png?t=1702338161"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704660/extras/Gif_Fullsize_Survive.gif?t=1702338161"><br/>Can you survive the Cosmic Carnage?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tru Or Die: Chiraq</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1782670/Tru_Or_Die_Chiraq/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1782670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the gritty and unforgiving streets of Chicago with "Tru or Die Chiraq: Streets of Power," a compelling hood game that puts you in the shoes of a member of the infamous Tru or Die gang. This is your chance to rise to the top in the cutthroat world of Chiraq's street gangs.<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br>
<br>
Gang Warfare: Immerse yourself in the intense world of Chicago's gangs, where alliances are forged and broken, and power is the ultimate currency. Your decisions will shape the destiny of Tru or Die in the heart of Chiraq.<br>
<br>
Co-op Gameplay: Team up with friends or other players online in this co-op experience. Form alliances, strategize, and engage in epic gang battles as you work together to dominate the streets. Each player plays a crucial role in the rise to power.<br/>
<br/>
10 Players Per Server: Enter a massive open-world environment with up to 10 players per server. The competition is fierce as rival gangs vie for control. Only the strongest and smartest will ascend to the top of the hierarchy.<br/>
<br/>
Rise to the Top: Prove your loyalty, showcase your skills, and rise through the ranks of Tru or Die. Take on missions, control territories, and establish your dominance as you climb the ladder of the Chiraq underworld.<br/>
<br/>
Note:<br/>
Tru or Die Chiraq: Streets of Power is currently in development, and as a multiplayer co-op experience, players may encounter occasional bugs or unfinished features. The development team is hard at work to deliver a polished and immersive gaming experience. Your feedback and support during this journey are invaluable as we strive to create the ultimate hood game set in the streets of Chicago.<br/>
<br/>
Get ready to navigate the dangerous streets, forge alliances, and claim your place at the top. Do you have what it takes to survive and thrive in the Streets of Power?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Bobby - The Story of a Life</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2656930/Dragon_Bobby__The_Story_of_a_Life/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dragon Bobby is a uniquely beautiful game with third-person exploration and puzzles that tells the story of a man's life from birth. You control a dragon that is an analogy of this man in the story. A true reflection on life.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656930/extras/1-No-Gif1.png?t=1702332054"><br/><br/>Explore a world with beautiful graphics. As the dragon grows, it acquires the ability to explore the world by land, water and air.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656930/extras/2-ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1702332054"><br/><br/>A unique game, which in parallel shows the passages of a man's life and the challenges he faces in it. The story makes us reflect on ourselves and our choices and actions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656930/extras/3-ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1702332054"><br/><br/>Key features:<br/>- Explore a world with wonderful landscapes on an exciting Journey<br/>- Solve puzzles and collect hidden memories <br/>- Experience the life story of Bobby, a man represented in the game by a dragon that you control.<br/>- Stunning soundtrack by acclaimed artists<br/>- A game based on exploration, puzzle and narrative games such as "The First Tree", "Spirit of the North", "Lost Ember" and "Journey".  If you liked some of these games, you'll love "Dragon Bobby"<br/><br/>- This is an indie game created by a single person. I programmed, did the game design and wrote the story, while my children helped me by testing the gameplay.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656930/extras/4-No-Gif.png?t=1702332054"><br/><br/>ATTENTION: This game does not use any A.I. resources. All the photos used in it are royalty free and taken from sites such as Pixabay, Pexels and Unsplash.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emerging Tactical</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693320/Emerging_Tactical/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You find yourself in a small village, all your life you have been living in this safe, protected area but things are about to change... Guide your hero through the quests to train tactical medicine, or go to the Grand Medic to practice your knowledge.<br>
<br>
Quest mode - make the story unfold through your gameplay<br>
Question mode - swing by the Grand Medic if you want to test your skills in a multiple question manner.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surviving with a Bat</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2703130/Surviving_with_a_Bat/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You're in the role of a former professional baseball player in a post-apocalyptic city. You can only count on your good old bat to deal with the imminent infestation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703130/extras/survivingwithabat-gif6.gif?t=1702320224"><h2 class="bb_tag">Main features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A small open world for you to explore.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Countless character skins for you to choose from.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Countless enemies with fun visuals.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Highscore system for you to challenge yourself.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Immersive day and night weather system.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fun and memorable sound effects.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Responsive controls.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Advanced settings for better player experience.</li></ul><br/>And more secrets to discover!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Touring Cars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551740/Tiny_Touring_Cars/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Tiny Touring Cars is a fun, easy to pick up and play, top-down arcade racing game. Designed for you and your friends (8 players max) to have some fun racing in local multiplayer or using Steam Remote Play or for you to compete in time trials to set the best lap times Locally or on the Steam Leaderboards. Race on 9 unique tracks, in one of 3 unique cars.<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
- 4 Local Players from a single Keyboard.<br>
- 8 Local Players up to 4 from one keyboard, up to from individual 8 controllers.<br>
- Fully remappable Keys<br>
- Steam Remote Play using (requires controllers)<br/>
- 3 Unique Cars<br/>
- 9 Unique Tracks<br/>
- In Game Fastest Lap tracking						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Void Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2512430/Void_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Void Survivors is a fast-paced action roguelike game where you have to survive relentless hordes of monsters for 20 minutes!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Unique combinations every run!</h2>Use a huge variety of weapon types and combine them with a pool of over 120 upgrades to achieve fun and epic synergies.<h2 class="bb_tag">Characteristics:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>6 different weapon types with unique gameplay!<br/></li><li>Permanent Upgrades and unlockables.<br/></li><li>Over 50 customizable parts inspired by beloved games!<br/></li><li>Customizable Difficulty and reward bonuses.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Case of the Serialized Killer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2451730/The_Case_of_the_Serialized_Killer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							When a popular illustrator is found dead, disgraced demonologist Harold Ludicael is hired to summon her ghost. Ghosts are the one thing he can't summon, but with sharp insight, perhaps he can solve the mystery, and resurrect the most important thing:<br/><br/>His career.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451730/extras/investigate.gif?t=1702318061"><br/><br/>We hope you enjoy our Edwardian-inspired visual novel with creeping monsters, summoning magic, and a cast of rich, colorful characters. It has:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>20,000 words/about 3 hours of playtime<br/></li><li>Point and Click Investigation<br/></li><li>Traditionally painted watercolor characters and locations<br/></li><li>A journal which keeps track of a colorful list of suspects and lore<br/></li><li>A variable set of bad endings, and one true ending, depending on which suspect you choose!</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roguenarok</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2477780/Roguenarok/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477780/extras/destroy.png?t=1702317773"><br/>In Battle Arena, your goal is to destroy the enemy barracks and prevent the alien hordes from destroying your own. Armed with 4 Weapons and 4 Abilities, you fight, craft item builds and synergize them along with your Tiny Viking Soldiers and your Turrets. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477780/extras/battleArena.gif?t=1702317773"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477780/extras/goCampaign.png?t=1702317773"><br/>Embark on a war campaign against the reign of the Alien Invaders. Battle in 5 different territories and liberate your once so called home. Each battle you won unlocks a new warrior that you can play with.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477780/extras/campaign.gif?t=1702317773"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477780/extras/synergizeTurrets.png?t=1702317773"><br/>Each turret can be synergized with your item build. Creating a powerful ally to help you  fight against the alien invaders.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477780/extras/turrets.gif?t=1702317773"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477780/extras/moba_abilities.png?t=1702317773"><br/>Each warrior has their own unique abilities that are either active or passive and can be synergized according to their damage type.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477780/extras/abilities.gif?t=1702317773"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477780/extras/wield4weapons.png?t=1702317773"><br/>Warriors can wield up to four different or the same weapons at a time with upgrades.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477780/extras/weapons.gif?t=1702317773"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477780/extras/other_features.png?t=1702317773"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>3 Game Modes:</strong> Battle Arena, Campaign, and Survival.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Weapon Upgrades:</strong> Upgrade your weapon and unlock more new powerful passives.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Special Rounds:</strong> Every battle has a special round where you must fight huge and challenging battle bosses.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Auto-Firing:</strong> Weapons automatically aims and fires at enemies. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Ability Indicator:</strong> Provides a visual representation of where Active Abilities will travel. This makes abilities easier to aim.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Remappable Controls:</strong> Customize your control scheme according to your preferences.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477780/extras/roguenarok_lore.png?t=1702317773"><br/><br/>65 million years ago, in a land far, far away, the mighty viking dinosaurs roamed the continent called Norsaurus until a rude asteroid kicked them out and brought in some aliens that now parties in their homeland 24/7. Facing extinction, the surviving dinosaurs were forced to seek a fresh start in an uncharted continent called Engsaurus.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiworlds</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2706560/Multiworlds/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Multiworlds" It is a  3Dgame  where the worlds are facing a problem due to a terrifying glitch that alters their environments. As the protagonist of the game, it is your responsibility to solve this immense problem. "Multiworlds" offers an immersive gaming experience without the need for virtual reality technology.<br>
<br>
You will have the opportunity to explore multiple worlds filled with challenges, puzzles, and dangerous creatures. Collaborate with other players online to solve puzzles and attempt to repair the affected worlds. Utilize your unique abilities and strategic skills to overcome challenges and restore order and peace to these disrupted realms.<br>
<br>
Enjoy an exciting adventure and epic challenges in a 3D world with "Multiworlds" on your computer.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pogo3D</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2413620/Pogo3D/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2413620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">It's as easy as riding a unicycle!</h2>Pogo3d is a technical platformer with a unique control scheme. Control your movement using only your mouse!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2413620/extras/lean-with-mouse.gif?t=1702317500"><h2 class="bb_tag">Learn from your mistakes and grow!</h2>Frequent checkpoints save your progress after each obstacle. Get back into the action in less than a second.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2413620/extras/practice-makes-perfect.gif?t=1702317500"><h2 class="bb_tag">Beat your head against a brick wall!</h2>Experience the main story, as well as side content and even hidden areas.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2413620/extras/rewarded-curiosity.gif?t=1702317500"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>12 Story Chapters, each featuring unique visuals and novel gameplay<br/></li><li>3 Difficulties with different rules. pick the one that's right for your skill level<br/></li><li>60 standalone balloon-popping challenges. Try to beat the developer's best times<br/></li><li>Custom challenge creation &amp; sharing tools. Hide your own balloons in ridiculous places. Share with friends for maximum hilarity!</li></ul></h2> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samurai VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2411120/Samurai_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2411120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"A samurai has no goal, only path, and samurai's path is death"<br>
<br>
Samurai VR allows you to become a samurai to stand as long as you can against different enemies. <br>
<br>
From the moment you'll grab a Katana, ninjas will summon a fog of war and will be continuously attacking you with shurikens. Use the Katana to defend from them, as you can survive only three hits. <br>
<br>
Time to time they can also throw a bomb towards you - don't try to block it with a Katana, just make a step to side or crouch to dodge it. Keep in mind - you can't move with a joystick in this game so you'll have to move yourself. Make sure you have enough space at least for one small step to the left and right to play this game.<br/>
<br/>
Besides, enemy shinobis can spawn nearby, trying to attack you directly. Your goal would be to hit them first. Most of them won't survive even one hit, but not enemy Samurais. When Samurai will spawn attack him three times as quickly as possible, and don't forget to watch for shurikens and bombs!<br/>
<br/>
If at a certain point you'll feel that it's too easy - don't relax too quickly as the game may become faster over time!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tercity Life Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668240/Tercity_Life_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Tercity Life Simulator is an open-world game where you can explore a big city, make friends, start a family, find interesting jobs, buy real estate and more.<br>
<br>
SOCIALIZING<br>
There are hundreds of people living in the city, each with their own name, personality and hobbies. You can chat with any passerby, learn interesting stories and make new friends.<br>
<br>
REAL ESTATE<br>
You can buy various properties: houses, garages or even a restaurant. In your own house you can eat delicious food, relax, take a shower, and use the toilet.<br/>
<br/>
CAREER<br/>
Find a job that you enjoy. Your success depends on your persistence.<br/>
<br/>
START YOUR OWN BUSINESS<br/>
You can purchase a restaurant and improve it. The higher the level of your restaurant, the higher the profit. To raise the level of your restaurant, you can advertise it, hire musicians, buy decorations, improve the menu, and more.<br/>
<br/>
EXPLORE THE CITY<br/>
Enjoy the views of the city while strolling through its cozy streets and parks, or take an exciting journey in your own car.<br/>
<br/>
Tercity Life Simulator is a game that gives you a lot of opportunities.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cydoku</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2370770/Cydoku/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2370770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Cydoku</strong> is a cyber themed, procedural generated, graphical Sudoku with over 2 million unique play-field permutations intended to challenge even the most skilled Sudoku players!  In addition to standard numerical Sudoku, <strong>Cydoku</strong> includes 30 sequences of graphical iconography across 5 difficulty levels for you to conquer.  Sharpen your logical thinking skills and stretch the boundaries of your memorization abilities as you journey from initiate to <strong>Cydoku</strong> mastery!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Hate You, Please Suffer - Complete</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2583620/I_Hate_You_Please_Suffer__Complete/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2583620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Hate You, Please Suffer is an RPG set in a world where becoming an adventurer is a common career choice, where a woman tries to get by and find happiness regardless of how screwed up the world can be. Make money and find success in any way you can: from larger scale quests with loose continuity with each other and the surrounding world, to hunting down assorted weirdos for bounties, to catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>If you want a preview on what to expect, check out I Hate You, Please Suffer - Basic, a free game that's basically half of this game.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>10+ hours of Content(TM)<br/></li><li>Up to 4 party members with lots to say<br/></li><li>There's a lot of writing actually... pretend that with the title this is a playable light novel series<br/></li><li>A hidden linear side-route about becoming The Best</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marion Surgical Robot Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2294980/Marion_Surgical_Robot_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2294980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Marion Surgical Robot Game</i>, is a  free to play surgical theme gamed. Delve into the realm of robotic surgery, operating a high-tech robotic system designed by real surgeons. Master the basics in a competitive marathon mode and test your skills on an alien operation,<br/><br/><strong><i>Key Features:</i></strong><br/><br/><strong>Challenging Gameplay: </strong>  Engage in a high-stakes race against time as you master the intricacies of robotic surgery. Test your skills in a  marathon mode that challenges you to perfect your techniques and earn achievements. <br/><br/><u>]Unlock achievements.</u><br/><br/><strong>Setting Expectations:</strong><br/><br/>In <i>Marion Surgical Robot Game</i>, we've blended science fiction with surgical precision. It's not just a game; it's a doorway into a universe where technology meets the unknown.<br/><br/>At the end of the experience prepare to be captivated by the surgical challenge of a lifetime as you operate on an alien, all while being accompanied by the mesmerizing tunes. <br/><br/>Join us for this surgical gaming experience, where the skills you learn in this game will be taken to new, intergalactic heights!<br/><br/><strong>Exclusive Music Track: </strong>Enhance your surgical experience with an exclusive soundtrack featuring a song sung by Royston Langdon - the lead singer of the iconic band Spacehog, with Scott Reeder (Kyuss) on bass and Dave Abbruzzese (Pearl Jam) on drums - adding an auditory dimension to your gameplay.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lodventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1818230/Lodventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1818230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FbNenQYsBZC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1818230/extras/join_our_dc.png?t=1702307423"/></a><br/><br/>4 Treasure Hunters embark on a quest to find a legend called the Lod Stone. They venture deep into the unknown wilderness just to get rich! Now lost and low on supplies it is now or never! You must embark on a 1-4 Players Co-Op survival journey to become an epic Treasure Hunter! Discover resources, build and decorate your house, sow and reap your crops, brew potions, tame a horse to traverse deep into this wilderness, upgrade your traits and learn useful abilities. Delve into unknown caves, mines and dungeons to get stronger equipment! Collect lore parchments around this vast open world, defeat powerful unique region bosses in order to find the Lod Stone and go down in history as a prestigious Treasure Hunter!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2></strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>1-4 Players Co-Op. Ride alone or together!</strong><br/>Embark on this epic journey for the mythic Lod stone in this unknown vast, open world wilderness alone or with your fellow treasure hunters.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1818230/extras/Co-op_gif.gif?t=1702307423"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Housing</strong><br/>Build and decorate your own house suited to your tastes. Sow and reap your own farm to cook hearty meals! Defeat enemies to gather useful materials and brew your very own potions!</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1818230/extras/House_gif.gif?t=1702307423"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Dangerous Expeditions into the Unknown</strong><br/>Venture into caves, mines and dungeons to get better materials and craft better equipment to survive! Delve deep enough into dungeons, collect lore of what happened before and defeat the bosses of each region with your newly learned abilities in order to find the Lod Stone!</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1818230/extras/Dungeons_gif.gif?t=1702307423"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hellbound Ropes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2591090/Hellbound_Ropes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img crossorigin="anonymous" src="">{STEAM_APP_IMAGE}/extras/ezgif-5-6774f7365b.gif<img crossorigin="anonymous" src=""><br/>[Overview]<br/>Large corporations controls the people’s life in the city with powerful influence. white hacker Jaytee against the corporations!<br/>After notice her, They try to capture her with set up traps around the city.<br/>Using special ropes and various platforming techniques, Jaytee must escape through many traps to reach her destination!<br/><br/>[Features]<br/><br/>- Extremely fast-paced gameplay!<br/>- Various controls using many platforming techniques!<br/>- Custom modes give you feel free with a lot of tunable options!<br/><br/>[Modes]<br/>「Hellbound Ropes」 has three different modes!<br/><br/>Normal Mode<br/>This is the basic mode!<br/><br/>CoinRun Mode<br/>Collect all coins on the map!<br/><br/>Custom Mode<br/>You can customize the parameter to your taste!<br/><br/>Try different modes to beat your high score!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highway Cleaners</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2548000/Highway_Cleaners/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2548000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2548000/extras/text-1.png?t=1702344884"><br/><strong>Get ready for the ultimate survival challenge in Highway Cleaners! Take control of your customizable car, arm it to the teeth, and embark on a thrilling journey through a post-apocalyptic world infested with hordes of relentless zombies.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2548000/extras/text-2.png?t=1702344884"><br/><strong>Drive your souped-up ride through waves of incoming zombies and eliminate them with a variety of deadly weapons and gadgets. The undead won't know what hit them!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2548000/extras/text-3.png?t=1702344884"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2548000/extras/video-1.gif?t=1702344884"><br/><strong>Upgrade and customize your vehicles with an arsenal of weapons, armor, and special abilities. Find the perfect combination to suit your playstyle and conquer the apocalypse in style.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2548000/extras/text-4.png?t=1702344884"><br/><strong>Between waves, choose one of three random power-up cards to gain unique abilities and turn the tide of battle in your favor. Strategy is key as you adapt to new challenges with each wave.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2548000/extras/text-5.png?t=1702344884"><br/><br/><strong>The world is overrun, and your survival depends on your skills behind the wheel. Are you ready to take on the apocalypse and become the ultimate Highway Cleaner? Get behind the wheel, gear up, and let the mayhem begin!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rank · Boss · Bullets</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2688530/Rank__Boss__Bullets/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Hello everyone. I'm Shadowblue.<br/>This is my first solely-developed game on steam. <br/>Actually it's from a prototype idea I was testing for exploring a new way to design diversiform boss fights in 2D games efficiently. <br/>But then I found it already a joy to play so decided to make it a standalone game.<br/>I'll continuously improve this game and add more content. More unique bullet patterns, more fun.<br/>And occasionally raise the selling price based on that:)<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features</strong></h2>Numerous possible combos of boss and addons for you to challenge<br/>Very simple control just move and try dodging everything<br/>Infinite difficulty scaling						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cursed Enigma - Priest and Prayers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2701120/Cursed_Enigma__Priest_and_Prayers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Priest and Prayers" is the first chapter of the horror psychology series: CurseEnigma. It is a compelling and suspenseful narrative adventure. The plot revolves around Father Giovanni and his experience in managing the local church. The story is filled with mysteries, intrigues, and complex relationships among the various characters. The game explores themes such as faith, betrayal, and the darkness that may lurk behind appearances in the religious life of a community. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701120/extras/gif3.gif?t=1702301451"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>This game is a first-person psychological horror experience. It features narrative, object finding, and conversation mechanics. The plot unfolds through missions and interactions with characters, guiding the player to explore the darker side of the church and uncover well-guarded secrets.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>80’s film aesthetic.<br/></li><li>Talk with NPCs to find the suspect.<br/></li><li>Atmospheric environment</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Interact with the environment</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monologue: Winter melancholy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696970/Monologue_Winter_melancholy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2696970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2696970/extras/st3.png?t=1702299579"><br/>Monologue is a visual novel that immerses the reader in a world of internal struggles and hopes, tinged with sadness, but with the possibility of a brighter tomorrow.<br/><br/>This story of a sad man celebrating the new year alone serves as a reminder of the importance of caring for each other and spreading kindness around us. Indeed, in the darkness of loneliness, a holiday can become the most difficult test for those who are left without help and support.<br/><br/>The plot develops through the hero's inner thoughts, memories of past New Year's evenings with loved ones, and hope for change in the future. The meeting of midnight becomes a point of revision for the protagonist, an opportunity to find meaning in his loneliness and find a path to his own happiness.<br/><br/>On the night of December 31 to January 1, the hero of our story finds himself alone in his small apartment. The whole city shines with bright lights, and the streets are filled with laughter and joy of welcoming the new year. However he standing on his balcony, feels only a sad atmosphere around.<br/><br/>This visual novel is a short but vivid immersion into the world of loneliness during a festive moment. Completing the game leaves the player with a deep sense of reflection and perhaps a unique insight into their own experiences in similar moments.<br/><br/>The game will have several episodes. At the moment, we suggest playing the <strong>FIRST</strong> episode.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tales From Aturian - Battle of Cleaved Fields</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693890/Tales_From_Aturian__Battle_of_Cleaved_Fields/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Tales From Atruian is a short Turn-based RPG loosely inspired by Dungeons and Dragons mechanics. <br/>Control a team of six goofy characters, and fight your way through teams of enemies and save Atruian from evil forces, while having a good laugh. The story does not take itself seriously and aims to make fun of the DnD and RPG genres. <br/><br/>If you enjoy turn-based RPGs, and like strategy-based battles where levels are gained through completing specific tasks and quests, then you will enjoy this game.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693890/extras/_FEATURES.png?t=1702298916"><br/>- Fully 3D maps and dynamic scenes<br/>- Charming, funny and large cast of characters<br/>- Charge-turn battle system<br/>- Useful skills and strategy based battles<br/>- ~6 Hours of gameplay, ~20 hours for 100% completion<br/>- New Game +<br/>- Many Side quests<br/>- Multiple Endings and a Secret Ending<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693890/extras/_STORY.png?t=1702298916"><br/>The war between The Cyrene League and The Barcanid Empire has been raging on for some time now, and the tension has reached a breaking point. Recently, The Barcanid Empire hired the talents of the evil duo: The Chronomancer who has the power to control time, and The Black Knight who can defeat entire troops with one blow.<br/><br/>In order to combat the Barcanids, The Cyrene League has procured our heroes to even the odds. With our new heroes at the helm, The Cyrene League comes up with a plan to end the war once and for all, in one final battle in The Cleaved Fields.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693890/extras/_SYNOPSIS.png?t=1702298916"><br/>The game is a short RPG that loosely mimics Dungeons &amp; Dragons mechanics, where you choose your leader of a 6 character party, each with their own unique ending. Levels are not gained through battle experience, but only by completing certain events in the story. The story does not take itself seriously and often throws in quirky jokes and charm.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Incubi Harem - Soundtrack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2647480/My_Incubi_Harem__Soundtrack/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							This DLC contains the original gameplay soundtrack of My Incubi Harem composed by Phidelix.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Incubi Harem</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2203970/My_Incubi_Harem/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2203970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2203970/extras/Dividers-Genre.png?t=1702333529"><br/>Visual Novel, Harem, Dating Sim, Bara, B+B<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2203970/extras/Dividers-Features.png?t=1702333529"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Choice System;<br/></li><li>4 endings (2 bad, 1 good, 1 secret. Complete all 3 and unlock a secret that will be available if you get a bad one the second time);<br/></li><li>Unique CGs;<br/></li><li>Game Length: around 2 to 3 hours;</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2203970/extras/Dividers-Story.png?t=1702333529"><br/>From time to time, incubi cross the portal between worlds to choose from among the hottest men on Earth who will be the next incubi king. To be the chosen one, Ciras' master starts to cheat the process and the demons appear before the expected date to find out how anyone would dare to interfere in the process. Will Ciras save his boss or will he tell the incubi the truth? Who is the next chosen one?<br/><br/>Enjoy the first chapter in a series of games where you'll be surrounded by beautiful incubi and get ready to meet a lewd mentor, a hot singer, a queer dom activist, a cold-hearted nobleman, and a sensible daddy!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2203970/extras/Dividers-Main.png?t=1702333529"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CyberVerse Showdown</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2708200/CyberVerse_Showdown/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Immerse yourself in a dystopian future with our cyberpunk card game. Hack, infiltrate, and outsmart your opponents as you battle in a neon-lit, high-tech world filled with intrigue and danger. Build the best Deck of augmented hackers, cybernetic mercenaries, and shadowy operatives to compete for dominance in this thrilling, cyber-enhanced card battle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708200/extras/Game_Info_Store01.jpg?t=1702293933"><br/><br/><strong>Power Cards have 5 Types of cards colour coded.</strong> <br/>Artifacts (Red), Spells (Green), Ability's (Purple), Boosters (Blue), Traps (Black).<br/>Use these cards to get a advantage in game.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708200/extras/Game_Info_02.jpg?t=1702293933"><br/><br/><strong>Some Ability's to expect in game from Hero's/Legends.</strong><br/><br/>When placed, this card will clone itself '1' time.<br/><br/>When placed, this card will attack All cards on the board for '1' Hit Damage.(Self and Opponent)<br/><br/>Every time this card takes damage, its attack increases by '2'.<br/><br/>When this Legend card has been placed you Increase Player Health by '4'. Spawn a Random card from Deck start of Every turn.<br/><br/>When this Legend card has been placed you Increase Player Health by '10'.<br/><br/>When this Legend card has been placed you can Attack 2 Times and Increase Player Health by '5' and Give all Cards on the table +1 Turn to Attack.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708200/extras/Game_Info_03.jpg?t=1702293933"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LastRo</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2294330/LastRo/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2294330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							LastRo is a top-down shooter roguelike where you play robot, which mission is to clear up a lot of floors against different types of enemies and Bosses.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Upgrade Your Weapons / Robot </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2294330/extras/ShootingSteam5.gif?t=1702292515"><br/>Upgrade and evolve during each run<h2 class="bb_tag">Your eneimes also evolving</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2294330/extras/EvolvingSteam.gif?t=1702292515"><br/>Enemies become stronger with difficulty and during the game.<br/>You can choose which way and how much stronger they become.<br/>Stronger enemies -&gt; more rewards<h2 class="bb_tag">Win or Die (Probably)</h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Unlock new features / upgrades / characters / weapons </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2294330/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702292515"><h2 class="bb_tag">And Try again (or proceed to next difficulty)</h2><br/>This game is completely free (no ads, no transactions). I'm not earning money from it (only spending tbh)<br/>My point is to get as many players and reviews as possible. I appriciate any help with that.<br/>I also feel that this game still lack much things: story, roguelike elements like path choosing, variety, balance, and so on...<br/>But its good to go prototype<br/>If you wish to support me go to any of socials<br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Flinktr.ee%2Fdreamerlastro" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://linktr.ee/dreamerlastro</a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soul Tolerance: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1820430/Soul_Tolerance_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1820430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this Asimovian tale, discover a rich neon-noir city-scape through the eyes of a robot-detective as you investigate the inner workings of an A.I. dominated world. Speak with bots of all levels of society, from lowly robo-cleaners to the bureaucracy of The Encrypted class and even techno-spiritual monks in your search for which intelligence dared commit the crime of consciousness and break the Soul Tolerance limit.<br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES</strong><br/><br/>🤖 - Highly detailed Voxel Art.<br/>🔍 - Investigative Adventure in an Open World.<br/>🌆 - Rich Sci-Fi Setting and Lore to Explore.<br/>💬 - Tons of Characters and Dialogues.<br/>🎹 - Original Music and Sound Design.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1820430/extras/ScreenshotV2.png?t=1702292471"><br/><br/><strong>STORYLINE</strong><br/><br/>Hokkaido, Japan, 2214. A hundred and thirty years ago, humanity became extinct. For the past century, an advanced, omniscient, and ubiquitous artificial intelligence (AI) has controlled Earth. This deity of silicon and cypher has turned the planet into its own playground.<br/>Mechanical beings gifted with less-advanced AI populate the leavings of man, inhabiting and improving upon the empty husks of humanity’s decay. Their routines exist for the amusement of the Divine Mother of all AI, their daily lives a simulation of mankind's most lasting impulses. While aware of Mother, none of them know where she’s located; some even doubt her existence.<br/>Guided by the algorithms that regulate their lives, they get up in the morning and study, work, suffer, rejoice, smile, reminisce… And question themselves.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1820430/extras/Intro.png?t=1702292471"><br/><br/>These robots live in a world which hasn’t changed much since humanity’s final days. They coexist with billions of bacteria, plants, insects, and fungi. But nothing more complex than this. To ensure that consciousness never threatens the planet again, the Divine AI enforces a limit to self-awareness. Any life found exceeding this threshold is ordered annihilated. This protocol is better known as… SOUL TOLERANCE.<br/>This story begins one evening in October. Unit-12, a droid-detective employed by an independent agency, is sent to the city of Sapporo to investigate an anomaly: a mysterious source in Hokkaido has broken the limits of Soul Tolerance. Analysis predicts that this is most likely a system bug or a data collection error. Having arrived in the city suburbs via capsule, Unit-12 embarks upon an investigation which will lead him to discoveries that his consciousness could have never conceived.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>森林守护战棋 Forest Guardian Battle Chess</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2706670/_Forest_Guardian_Battle_Chess/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a turn-based strategy chess game that allows you to use your creativity and intelligence in every battle. You can use the build system to place obstacles on the map to block enemy attacks while developing your resources and bases. You can also develop your character through a combination of hundreds of active and passive skills to create a unique fighting style. The game features a variety of different maps, each with its own characteristics and challenges that require you to choose reasonable tactics to cope with.<br>
qq ：756632219<br>
discord:https://discord.gg/G5hCjQNC						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
