<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Milo and the Christmas Gift</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2716140/Milo_and_the_Christmas_Gift/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							After his adventure in Milo and the Magpies, Milo is looking forward to spending a cosy Christmas at home. But a Christmas gift is about to upset his holiday celebrations, especially when said gift disappears after a little misunderstanding! Can you help Milo bring home the lost Gift and save Christmas for Marleen… and himself?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_playing_1.gif?t=1703496663"> <br/><br/>Milo and the Christmas Gift is a free-to-play short and atmospheric point-and-click adventure game created by artist Johan Scherft. The game is a spin-off story following the events in Milo and the Magpies. The game has 5 chapters and a gameplay time of around 30 minutes!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/>■ Relaxing yet stimulating game-play<br/>Join Milo in his home and revisit some of the neighbouring gardens, but this time in a wintery Christmas wonderland! Interact with the festive environment and solve small point-and-click / hidden-object puzzles.<br/><br/>■ Captivating artistic atmosphere<br/>Each hand-painted, interior and snowy garden Milo has to search through has its unique personality, reflecting that of Milo’s owners and next-door neighbours respectively.<br/><br/>■ Atmospheric soundtrack<br/>Each chapter has its own festive theme song composed by Victor Butzelaar.<br/><br/>■ Average playtime: 15-30 minutes<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_snow_1.gif?t=1703496663"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few Nights More: Genesis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713070/Few_Nights_More_Genesis/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Please note: This is a free prologue and it includes act 1, and only 1 playable character and blood school is playable, The maximum heritage gained is limited to 50, and the maximum difficulty can be set to 2. As well only one castle will be available. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Blood3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Conquer castles and claim your birthright!</strong><br/> <br/>The fight to reclaim your place in this world begins. Rebuild lost ruins, make them stronger and defend them against your enemies. After you regain your strength, move on to conquer more territories and eventually claim your birthright.<br/><br/>Few Nights More offers the unique fusing of castle management and turn based rogue-like combat. Fight against humanity, the undisputed masters of this world in your absence. Choose between eight different Vampire Lords, each with their own ambition and history. Find your trinkets, skills and perks along your way. Design your very own castle by placing the right rooms, adding decors that directly contribute to your army and your Vampire Lord. Conquer more castles so your influence and power grow, until you claim your birthright.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Ferocity3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Core Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Design your castle by adding new Rooms, Traps and Minions. Stack up on some buffs with shiny decors to get ready for the invasion screen to defend it to the end of every night!<br/> <br/></li><li> Choose among 7 different Vampire Lords with unique History, Gameplay and Abilities.<br/> <br/></li><li> Master 1 out of 3 Disciplines each time you play, each with 60 unique skills.<br/> <br/></li><li> Acquire new random skills, perks and trinkets to survive the nights.<br/> <br/></li><li> Excel in either being a Prestigious Vampire, a Seductive one, or master a Terrifying presence against your enemies.<br/><br/></li><li> Test the builds you made against a variety of Hunters, Veterans and Unique Bosses in an action packed turn based combat system.<br/> <br/></li><li> Endure three acts across 12 difficulty levels, striving to survive and progress. Accumulate Heritage Points to enhance your lord's starting stats, skills, and unlock new castles and talents unique to each lord.<br/><br/></li><li> Engage in the boundless challenge of Infinity Mode, where you can continuously test your limits without relying on a castle. Each night, you will be presented with three options to advance, growing stronger as you push yourself to see how far you can go.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703868247"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1702674942"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1703493452"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1703493452"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1703186631"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1703318086"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1703318086"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1702747783"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobalt Core</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2179850/Cobalt_Core/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_1.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>Cobalt Core is a sci-fi roguelike deckbuilder with a unique single-axis combat system that will throw you for a loop. Many loops! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_2.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>Give orders to your crew by playing cards: Will you <strong>raise shields</strong> to protect your ship, <strong>dodge</strong> incoming missiles and cannon fire to avoid damage outright, or <strong>strike</strong> preemptively to disable your enemy’s weapons? Outmaneuver your foes to stay just ahead of impending calamity, and reach the Cobalt Core!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/characters.png?t=1703278835"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fresh new spin on tactics –</strong>  dodge attacks and target weak points in this unique single-axis take on tactics combat. Outwit the enemy in a high stakes game of cat and mouse!<br/></li><li><strong>Customize your deck –</strong> hundreds of cards and split upgrade paths means no two runs will be the same. Find that perfect combo that brings your deck from powerful to overpowered.<br/></li><li><strong>Get to know your crew –</strong> each character comes with a completely unique playstyle and their own personal story. Bring 3 along, mix and match their decks, and see how these little goobers get along with each other.<br/></li><li><strong>Tons of replayability –</strong>  hundreds of different character+ship combinations before you even hit “start run”. Crank up the difficulty and really test your skills!<br/></li><li><strong>Get in the groove –</strong> featuring 90+ minutes of catchy and electrifying original music by <i>Minecraft</i> composer Aaron Cherof!<br/></li><li><strong>Forward momentum –</strong> untangle a narrative and unlock more playstyles as you go. Is there any escape from this time loop?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/grandma_cookies.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>By the makers of <i>Sunshine Heavy Industries</i>, recipient of IGF's <strong>Honorable Mention for Excellence in Design 2022</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658820/Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							10 possible fruits and one goal, reach the Watermelon.<br/>Your job is to combine matching fruits to evolve them to the next one and eventually reach the coveted Watermelon.<br/>To help you, you have 3 different abilities at your disposal. But watch out, using these will cost you some of your points. Be smart about when you use them to get the highest score!<h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLAYER</h2>Measure your fruit skills against another player.<h2 class="bb_tag">GET THE WATERMELON</h2>How many Watermelons can you combine before your basket overflows?<h2 class="bb_tag">USE YOUR ABILITIES</h2>Power, level up and destroy — These abilities will help you reach the Watermelon, using any of those will also allow you to angle your aim.<h2 class="bb_tag">GOLDEN FRUIT</h2>If luck is on your side, you might even see the mysterious Golden Fruit. Find it and witness its effect firsthand.<h2 class="bb_tag">STATISTICS</h2>Track your progress with in-depth statistics. Visit the menu to see the number of fruits you've combined, your ability usage, and much more.<h2 class="bb_tag"></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.codecks.io%2Fwatermelon-game" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/extras/Roadmap_Banner.png?t=1702238677"/></a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EA SPORTS™ WRC</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1849250/EA_SPORTS_WRC/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1849250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build the car of your dreams in our biggest rally game ever, EA SPORTS™ WRC, the all-new official videogame of the FIA World Rally Championship, the first developed by the award-winning team behind the DiRT Rally series.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1849250/extras/WCR_GameFeatures_PostLaunch.jpg?t=1702998175"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For The King II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1676840/For_The_King_II/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/header_alt_assets_7.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_AboutThisGame_Steam_StoreBanner_2_EN.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Once beloved by her people, Queen Rosomon has turned against her subjects, casting them into servitude in the darkness of Fahrul’s mines whilst building alliances with sinister and malevolent forces.<br/><br/>Gather your party in four player co-op or adventure alone through Fahrul as you risk everything to fight the tyrannical queen and bring an end to her oppressive reign.<br/><br/>From the creators of For The King, the much-loved RPG that blends roguelite and tabletop gameplay comes a new chapter in Fahrul’s history, designed on an updated engine bringing innovation and gameplay refinement for returning heroes and new adventurers alike.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading01_Inspired_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>For The King II is easy for anyone to pick up and play, but takes skill, patience, and strategic excellence to master whilst remaining infinitely replayable with a procedurally generated map that ensures no two playthroughs will ever be the same. Unique yet familiar dice roll inspired movement, encounter and combat mechanics add even more spontaneity and variety as your fortunes rise and fall on the roll of the dice.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF01_InspiredByTabletop.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading02_Digestible2_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>For The King II provides a complete campaign with over 30 hours of gameplay, split into 5 separate adventures, each narratively linked. The journey is long and the path is treacherous but fear not, if your party fails you will start stronger and wiser on your next playthrough with better starting items to draft into your loadout.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF02_RogueliteCampaign.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading03_Muster_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Create your party from 12 unique character classes, each with their own unique perks, strengths and playstyles. From the heavy-handed hitter of The Blacksmith, to the wily potion-wielding Alchemist, you choose which characters will take on the fearsome Queensguard and the combat strategies that will ensure success. Introduce new characters to your party with mercenaries and companions that enable you to pluck wild beasts from the forest floor and recruit ruthless mercenaries from local taverns (for a price of course) to bolster your ranks in times of trouble.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF03_MusterYouMight_.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading04_Party_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Traverse Fahrul solo or with up-to three friends in four-player co-op. As a solo player you can control all characters in your party, giving you complete ownership of the campaign map and combat strategy whilst in four-player co-op you must coordinate and negotiate with your party members. Play online multiplayer with your friends controlling your own character(s) or play offline co-op on the same PC. Offline co-op supports multiple controllers; each controller will have input control on everyone’s turn.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF04_PartyofFour.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading05_Evolved_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Inspired by turn-based classics, For The King II adds strategic depth to much-loved combat mechanics with the new Battle Grid, where movement and position provide you and your enemies with strategic buffs and penalties. Defend the back row by equipping a mighty Tower Shield, push enemies into lethal pools of burning fire, or entangle melee troops with dark magic cast with weapons looted from vanquished foes. The choice is yours!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF05_EvolveTurnBased.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading06_Explore_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Fahrul is both beautiful and deadly in equal measure. On your journey you will encounter a wealth of diverse biome environments brought to life in a breathtaking art style. From lush forests, toxic swamps and lava-filled wastelands to pirate (no scratch that!) Merling-infested tropical seas, For The King II transports you deep into the wonders of Fahrul, leading you further than ever before into this stunningly-imagined land of adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF06_ExploreFantastical.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Ffortheking" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTK_Discord_Banner_EN.gif?t=1703284946"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoboCop: Rogue City</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1681430/RoboCop_Rogue_City/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FGzNdTVQAs6" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/ROBOCOP_ROGUE_CITY_BANNER_DISCORD_615x195px_EN.jpg?t=1701074570"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif01_EN.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif02_EN.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Description_Banner01_EN.png?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif03_EN.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Description_Banner02_EN.png?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif04_EN_V1.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Description_Banner03_EN.png?t=1701074570"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Talos Principle 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/835960/The_Talos_Principle_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/835960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/835960/extras/Talos2_reviews.jpg?t=1703182380"><br/><br/>Born into a new world where biological humanity is extinct but human culture lives on in a city of robots, you find yourself swept up in a mind-bending adventure involving a mysterious megastructure hiding enormous powers.<br/><br/>The more you discover, the more you will be confronted with questions about the nature of the cosmos and the purpose of civilization. The broken promise of a better tomorrow, the fear of repeating humankind’s mistakes, faith in reason or renouncing humanity altogether - the choices you make and the sides you take will determine the course of events.<h2 class="bb_tag">A New Generation of Puzzles</h2>Solve a wide array of puzzles with varying difficulty levels, including clever metapuzzles and highly challenging Gold puzzles. Finish the game without solving every puzzle, or pursue the rewards of complete mastery. A variety of new abilities, such as gravity manipulation and mind transference, join the established mechanics of the original Talos Principle, creating a fresh but familiar experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Philosophical Odyssey</h2>Take the next step forward in the story of The Talos Principle in a thought-provoking, character-driven interactive story with multiple endings penned by returning writers Jonas Kyratzes (The Eternal Cylinder, Clash: Artifacts of Chaos) and Tom Jubert (The Swapper, Subnautica), joined by Verena Kyratzes (The Hand of Merlin, Serious Sam 4).<h2 class="bb_tag">Brave New World</h2>Explore more than a dozen all-new environments, from a city on the brink of a paradigm shift to the varied landscapes of a mysterious island that holds the keys to the future. Take a break from puzzle-solving to discover long-buried secrets and strands of forgotten history.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Melodies of Creation</h2>Immerse yourself in the rich, bittersweet world of The Talos Principle with a stunning soundtrack by master composer Damjan Mravunac (Serious Sam, The Talos Principle), with a guest appearance by Chris Christodoulou (Risk of Rain 1 and 2).						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Time at Sandrock</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1084600/My_Time_at_Sandrock/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>My Time at Sandrock</strong>-Just like My Time at Portia, My Time at Sandrock takes place in a wholesome post-apocalyptic world 330 years after the Day of Calamity destroyed most modern technologies.<br/><br/>After accepting a job offer to become Sandrock’s newest Builder, you’ll arrive in the wild and rugged city-state, where it’s up to you and your trusty tools to restore the community to its former glory. Gather resources to build machines, befriend locals, and defend Sandrock from monsters — all while saving the town from economic ruin!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/Build_your_workshop.png?t=1704082179"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/build_workshop-min.gif?t=1704082179"><br/><br/>Transform a run-down workshop into a well-oiled production facility! Use an intricate set of machines to process materials and produce parts of huge structures before assembling them piece by piece to help Sandrock flourish.<br/><br/>Create hundreds of unique items at the worktable to decorate your homestead, give gifts to Sandrock’s residents, or assist with community requests.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/Explore_the_open_world.png?t=1704082179"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/explore-min.gif?t=1704082179"><br/><br/>Explore vast deserts surrounding the city-state of Sandrock. Dive into ruins to dig for Old World relics, seek our materials in hard-to-reach locations, or spend time relaxing in Sandrock with your neighbors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/Extensive_story___NPCs.png?t=1704082179"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/npc-min.gif?t=1704082179"><br/><br/>Experience a detailed story complete with hundreds of sidequests and over 30 all-new characters. Spend time getting to know Sandrock’s residents, uncovering backstories, and making meaningful connections along the way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/New_combat.png?t=1704082179"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/combat-min.gif?t=1704082179"><br/>Quickly shift between melee combat and third-person shooting mechanics in dynamic action battles.Use the new weapons and defense break mechanic to your tactical advantage, or boost your stats to simply smash through battles! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/MINI_GAMES.png?t=1704082179"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/mini_games-min.gif?t=1704082179"><br/>A diversity of mini-games allow you and local Sandrock residents to stay entertained in the desert town.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/Multiplayer_EN.png?t=1704082179"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/multiplayer-min.gif?t=1704082179"><br/>Explore, build, and battle with up to 4 players. Together, shape the dynamic town, construct towering structures, engage in battles, share romantic moments, and dive into mini-games. Every move counts, earning points and unlocking new dimensions for your evolving character. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/And_more.png?t=1704082179"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Use your workshop’s profits to turn the empty prairie into farmable land;<br/></li><li>Grow crops for extra cash or transform them into delicious dishes;<br/></li><li>Attend festivals with Sandrock’s residents;<br/></li><li>Find secrets and much more!</li></ul><br/>Both <strong>Portians </strong>and <strong>brand-new Builders </strong> who have never set foot in Portia will find a fun new world with lots to explore at their own pace, along with divergent NPC stories to enhance replayability. Experienced Builders will find everything you enjoyed about <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/666140/My_Time_At_Portia/" rel="" target="_blank"> My Time at Portia </a> and more, and you will feel right at home in the delightful life-sim RPG that is My Time at Sandrock.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FdZAQjFp" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/Steam_DiscordJoin_banner_Sandrock_003_1_.jpg?t=1704082179"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-night</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1993820/Tnight/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In one of the remote cities, there are benefits for young families to move. The newly minted family decided to try their luck and moved there in the hope of their happiness. They did not even anticipate what conditions would need to be fulfilled in order to stay in this city and whether it was possible to fulfill these conditions in essence<br/>About the game<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993820/extras/MonsterReady.gif?t=1704176002"><br/>The game contains the best qualities so that the player does not get bored for a second<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li></li></ul> Full immersion in the atmosphere of the laura game<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li></li></ul> Plot insertion video<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li></li></ul> variety of puzzles<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993820/extras/Ready.gif?t=1704176002"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li></li></ul> A bunch of monsters with different mechanics<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li></li></ul> Acquaintance and communication with the characters and much more awaits you in the game T-Night.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KO Chaos</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2727550/KO_Chaos/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2727550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							- Overview -<br>
"Attack! Wait I mean roll! No, no attack!" KO Chaos is a game trying to minimize the Soul's combat formula. You must roll, attack, and find a dance with bosses to find their openings. You may select from a catalog of heroes that are tasked with defeating a boss of your choosing. With each character you choose, there will be a rating on how they affect the difficulty. Depending on how cowardly you are, this will affect your play style.<br>
<br>
- Story - <br>
After three hundred years of wars breaking out across the realm of Burlock, many heroes have fallen. The lands were left with nothing but despair and color completely faded. Later on, the heroes are left wandering their realms, lifeless husks of their former selves. Someone knew it couldn't be long before these husks<br>
could be used as weapons. So a soldier named Henward was tasked with putting an end to these husks. Only time will tell what could be done.<br>
<br/>
- Gameplay -<br/>
You can choose from a catalog of heroes and bosses to fight in whichever order you see fit. You can use this to practice and better understand the mechanics of the game. Right now there are only 6 bosses and 2 heroes to choose from.<br/>
<br/>
*fair warning game is really difficult*						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AquaRevive - VR Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658980/AquaRevive__VR_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Immerse yourself in the groundbreaking VR experience of "AquaRevive". Combat algal bloom pollution in a visually stunning underwater world, restoring the ecosystem's health. Dive into an unforgettable journey of environmental restoration and make a difference in the fight against algal bloom pollution.<br>
<br>
The story begins as you step into the dome, where the walls come alive with luminous targets representing algal blooms. Your mission is to use the dynamic chemical spheres to destroy these algal targets and save the ecosystem from their devastating impact.<br>
<br>
As the game progresses, waves of targets emerge, testing your speed and precision. You must swiftly strike the spheres, aiming accurately to shatter the targets one by one within a limited time frame, clearing them out. Get ready for this environmental journey and become the hero who defends against the invasion of algal blooms!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PvPillman</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2739120/PvPillman/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A short-run time game for preferably 5 players (I did not set a max number of players). Everyone will hunt the host player while the host tries to collect every pellet on the screen. The host is also going to play a top-down version of the game while everyone else is playing from a third person viewpoint. The host gains health from eating the other players, but also losses health when getting eaten by players. <br>
<br>
Doesn't seem to work for everyone, I had to mess around with UPNP settings on my router to let the game run normally.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escape from Blackwood</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2718500/Escape_from_Blackwood/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2718500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game simulates an escape room in a fantasy castle. The player starts in a closed dungeon and must try to escape as quickly as possible. To do this, the player can inspect, drag, throw, and interpret objects to obtain new clues to solve new puzzles.<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
<br>
Free 3D movement<br>
Many objects to inspect, drag, and throw<br>
Numerous complex puzzles<br/>
Single-player<br/>
Room 1: Tutorial room to learn mechanics.<br/>
Room 2: The castle						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shipwrecked 64</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2160220/Shipwrecked_64/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2160220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><u>Excerpt from the back of the original Shipwrecked Box:</u></strong><br/><br/>	“BUCKY AND HIS FRIENDS NEED YOUR HELP!<br/>After a sudden crash during a routine fishing trip, Bucky ends up on a mysterious island, where his friends appear to be apprehended by a pack of wolves for disturbing the peace. Embark on a puzzle-based adventure, as Bucky wanders the vast island of Nulla Terra, helping his friends work off the damages, fix your boat, and get back home!”<br/><br/><strong><u>What is this?</u> </strong><br/><br/><i>Shipwrecked</i> (Or <i>Shipwrecked 64</i> as the internet has dubbed it) was an old game originating from the late 90’s, commissioned by the (at-the-time) beloved Broadside Animation Studio, developed by a relatively unknown game studio, Cogware Games. <br/><br/>The game had a very mysterious nature surrounding its launch, as it was only available from August 13th 1997, to August 17th, 1997, receiving little promotion from Cogware, and none from Broadside. This downloadable version of the game is the closest one can get to playing the original copy of the game. We at the SWRC (Shipwrecked Recovery Crew) were lucky enough to get our hands on an original cartridge, dump it, and convert a lot of the code to new software. With help from two of the original developers, we were able to make this game accessible to everyone. <br/><br/><strong><u>Disclaimer: </u></strong><br/><br/>	Shipwrecked 64, while portraying itself as an authentic product, is in fact a work of fiction. Some scenes in the game are graphic and violent in nature. Shipwrecked 64 is what people may refer to as an ARG, and will require out-of-the-box thinking, but also travelling outside of the game for answers. It can be very complex at times, and is intended as a community effort of sorts. Forum posts, or even playing in calls with others, taking notes, and other methods are the best way to proceed forward.<br/><br/><strong><u>Features:</u></strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Two Modes, a 2023 mode and 1997 mode. A fixed, safer version of the game, and the unstable and somewhat disturbing version that was pulled from store shelves. <br/></li><li>A game with multiple layers, endings, and many areas to explore.<br/></li><li>A strange, surreal, and dark story that jumps from our world to the game’s world. <br/></li><li>Exploration is a key aspect of cracking the case. Dig deeper and deeper into the rabbit hole of Cogware Games. <br/></li><li>Controlled Decay, which will slowly break every level of the game depending on the actions of the player. </li></ul><br/><strong><u>Join us, and help us decipher what this game is trying to tell us. </u></strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fairway Club</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2579540/The_Fairway_Club/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2579540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Grab your clubs and get to The Fairway Club now! We offer a relaxing golfing experience for any type of golfer. Hit one of our courses, located all around the world, in the morning, evening or night! You can take your boat to Forest Islands for a secluded and quiet round of golf, or why not travel into the mountains over at Western Peaks to play surrounded by nature as far as your eyes can see? Not your cup of tea? How about the pink fields of Blossom Meadow, where the giant blossom willow trees keep you relaxed throughout your game!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2579540/extras/ezgif.com-crop.gif?t=1704133752"><br/><br/>Explore the courses and play at your own pace! We offer each player state of the art carts to travel around with, or if that's not your cup of 'tee' then you can have a walk around instead.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2579540/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__2_.gif?t=1704133752"><br/><br/>We offer unlimited access to the courses and also access to the TFC tournament, a regular golf competition held at our courses where you can win money &amp; level up your player! You can earn fans and take your game to the next level with your new sponsored gear!<br/><br/>Fancy some practice before that? Try out our state of the art driving range with global leader boards and regular competitions to see who the best fairway club member is! Rack up points through our timed mode and earn prizes (or just beat your friends!). If this isn't for you, how about the endless mode where you can chill out, get to know your clubs and hit targets for as long as you desire.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2579540/extras/ezgif.com-crop__1_.gif?t=1704133752"><br/><br/>You can also hit the putting greens to get used to reading the greens and avoiding any 3 puts when it matters!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2579540/extras/ezgif.com-crop__2_.gif?t=1704133752"><br/><br/>Customise your character to put yourself in the game! On top of the sponsored items you can unlock new clubs and balls with the money you earn throughout these various game modes (or even as prizes for finishing at the top!). Progress your career, earn more fans and become the best!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2579540/extras/ezgif.com-crop__3_.gif?t=1704133752"><br/><br/>But most of all, come to the Fairway Club and relax, as the one thing we can promise is a truly relaxing experience!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream Island: A Skyward Journey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2723980/Dream_Island_A_Skyward_Journey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to <strong>Dream Island: A Skyward Journey!</strong> My name's Peter Hart and I've made a game all about <i>climbing</i>, <i>crying </i>and <i>retrying</i>! <br/><br/>Embark on an adventure where every jump, dodge and prayer counts!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/>• Encounter:<strong> Lions</strong>, <strong>Turrets</strong>, <strong>Hammers</strong>, <strong>Jump-Pads</strong>, <strong>Falling Platforms</strong> and <strong>Slow Motion</strong>! <br/>• Hone precision moves as you listen to <strong>14 origional soundtracks</strong>. <br/>• Test your mental fortitude with over <strong>190 voiced lines</strong> for success and failure. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723980/extras/Gif4.gif?t=1704124088"><br/><br/><strong>Explore Two Maps:</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723980/extras/2maps.2Small.png?t=1704124088"><br/><br/>•<strong> Dream Island</strong>: A laid back challenge for the everyday gamer.<br/><br/>• <strong>Pain Island</strong>: A remix of Dream Island with increased enemies, shifted platforms and amplified intensity!<br/><br/>Dream Island—<i>where falling is your first step to success.</i> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Trek</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693810/Galaxy_Trek/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Remember the days when games were simple to learn and really fun to play? Experience pure joy as you blow up your enemies in real-time with phasers and torpedoes. Watch those enemy ships blow to pieces and their bits fly across your screen. Check the view screen for the status of your Starbases, open up the Galaxy Map and see if enemies are nearby, spend some time jumping to different sectors and explore anomalies, or just jump to the unknown. Each time you jump to a new sector the game will auto save (provided there are no enemies in the sector) so you can re-play should something go wrong.<br>
<br>
Galaxy Trek lets you choose between seven levels of difficulty but the game play does not change.  The enemies will not be any stronger and your ship won’t be any weaker, so what you learn at lower levels you can continue to use at the higher levels. <br>
<br>
Galaxy Trek was designed to let you focus on the fun, without worrying about the details. As long as your hull remains intact, everything will function. Starbases are not necessary to obtain victory, but they are needed to repair your hull, so you might want to keep one around.  <br>
<br>
Galaxy Trek is the game for anyone who is looking for that fun and uncomplicated gaming experience. It’s a real-time strategy game, perfectly combined with a bit of Sci-Fi and a lot of exciting action. Featuring fun graphics, high-quality music, great sound effects, and easy-to-learn controls, it is a game that will keep you hooked for hours with no two games ever being the same.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spider Inferno</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2677620/Spider_Inferno/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Game mission:<br>
<br>
The main destination is the planet “Earth One”. After a failed laboratory experiment, most of the planet's humanity was overrun by spiders. What remains is a laboratory with our world-famous, genius Professor Dr. MS-SI.<br>
<br>
Initially, the mission objective is set by the command center in such a way that the professor must be rescued and freed at all costs using resources.<br>
It later turns out that our esteemed professor is possessed by spiders and is obviously starting to mutate and cannot be stopped. The mission objective is changed so that the professor must be eliminated. Now they come into play Commander!<br>
<br/>
1. Prevent the spiders from spreading further.<br/>
2. Fight back all the spiders.<br/>
3. Secure the lab.<br/>
4. Save the professor.<br/>
5. Destroy the professor.<br/>
<br/>
Commander, priority is to destroy the spiders and the professor.<br/>
<br/>
The game takes place in the year 2317. The global world government has tried to cover up the nuclear contamination and denies any form of alien spiders. Failure is not accepted. The government expects a takeover from all enemy hands and the complete eradication of all enemy forces. This is the only way to achieve a new population of humanity. To this end, initial arrangements were made to resettle the chosen people.<br/>
The government will soon start sending secret messages and transmitting the coded tickets for a new life on the planet “Earth One”. We regret to inform Commander that a ticket costs 1 million Global, we expect tumultuous conditions and expect a victory announcement shortly. A place on “Earth One” has been secured for you, but only if you achieve the mission objective!<br/>
<br/>
The new planet “Earth One” must be freed from the alien spiders and the professor, otherwise there is a risk of destruction and global collapse.<br/>
<br/>
That's why we make them -------------- Commander the savior of humanity!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arcane Fighters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2621460/Arcane_Fighters/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2621460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the world of Arcane Fighters, where nostalgia meets fun and competitiveness. It's a blast from the past that captures the spirit of sharing a keyboard with friends, all while relishing the joy of local multiplayer gaming.<br>
<br>
Arcane Fighters is a thrilling 2D platform Player vs. Player (PvP) experience, where you can engage in magical battles against your friends, employing cunning strategies and, of course, MAGIC! Dive into the world of arcane warfare and choose from a wide array of unique spells, crafting your ultimate strategy to outwit and outmaneuver your opponents. Please note that the game is still in its early access phase, so stay tuned for more exciting updates and content!<br>
<br>
It isn't just a game; it's a time machine to those memorable moments when laughter filled the room and the competition was fierce. In an era dominated by online play, Arcane Fighters harks back to the days when gathering around a single screen was the pinnacle of gaming excitement.<br>
<br>
Rediscover the thrill of shared controllers, the camaraderie of local play, and the joy of friendly rivalry with up to three friends. It's your chance to create new memories while treasuring the old ones.<br>
<br/>
Arcane Fighters: More than a game, it's a celebration of the past and a doorway to the future.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Technician's Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2472390/A_Technicians_Nightmare/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2472390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>A Technician's Nightmare</strong><br/>It is the story of an air conditioner technician who was hired to repair air conditioners in an area far from the city. And on that day, the owner of the house was busy so he was not at home. What's strange is that in addition to air conditioning repair work. The owner asked for help in catching rats in the house and bringing them back to her. which she will add bonus money Although it seemed strange, they decided to take the job because they needed the money. <br/>Without knowing that something unusual had happened in this house...<br/><br/>The player must successfully complete the mission, during which there will be strange events occurring in the house. Their main objective is to survive and make it back safely.<br/><br/><br/><strong>Game Features</strong><br/>- Single player and Coop (1-4 Player) <br/>- Game Session<br/>- Quest (Repair, Catch, Find item)<br/>- Quick time event (On repair or Escape Alert)<br/>- Light System<br/>- Sneak<br/>- Random Anormaly Event<br/>- Ghost AI (It will chase when it hears a sound.)<br/>- Note Story<br/>- 2 Map (House and Farm)<br/>- Text Chat (Font Support: EN, CN, KR, JP, TH)						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surmountable</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2744000/Surmountable/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Your ship is shot down while engaged in a space battle. You land on an unknown planet. With your battleship damaged and no way of contacting your mother ship, you must survive on the planet until you find a way back home.<br>
<br>
In Surmountable, you will need to collect resources, fight off local predators, and discover the civilization that used to inhabit the planet. Prepare to explore and be challenged in this semi-open-world game of survival. Play as a male-looking or female-looking character.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanatophobia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2566310/Thanatophobia/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2566310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Thanatophobia</strong> is a survival game in a horrific atmosphere, playable solo or in cooperation with a minimum of 2 players and a maximum of 4 players. Escape unscathed, don't get caught, there won't be a second chance.<br/><br/>You land in a strange place inhabited by a mad killer, your goal is to get out alive, use clues.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2566310/extras/TheSchool__1_.png?t=1704113987"><br/><br/>Each time you start a game you will be in a different place, with a different objective, you will also have a random character with its associated skill.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Example:</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2566310/extras/Capture_d_écran__143_-removebg-preview.png?t=1704113987"><br/><strong>Jody </strong>can run continuously, the stamina bar never runs out.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2566310/extras/Capture_d_écran__142_-removebg-preview.png?t=1704113987"><br/><strong>Adam </strong>has the ability to throw cups in order to pull the killer in a specific direction. It has 7 cups that recharge after 35 seconds.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2566310/extras/Capture_d_écran__141_-removebg-preview.png?t=1704113987"><br/><strong>Brian </strong>throws rocks at the killer, stunning him for 5 seconds. It has 7 stones which will recharge after 35 seconds.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2566310/extras/Capture_d_écran__144_-removebg-preview.png?t=1704113987"><br/><strong>Josh </strong>can slow down time with his composure for 10 seconds, after this time he will only be usable after 15 seconds.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Regular new arrivals</strong></h2><br/>The game can be updated regularly, adding new content such as characters with their associated skills, as well as maps and a new objective. Good luck!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2566310/extras/skullhead.png?t=1704113987"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hire Me!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2725770/Hire_Me/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dream Big, Apply Recklessly!<br/><br/>Welcome to the whimsical, wacky and slightly weird world of <strong>AllJobs Agency</strong>, where 'All' is not just a catchy prefix. Choose <i>any</i> job you want — or even make one up — and brace yourself for <i>the most relentless job interview of your life.</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Do you have what it takes to land your dream job?</h2><br/>Answer a series of (often too) personal questions asked by the agency's ruthless and brutally honest job agent, who is like if Ricky Gervais and a lie detector had a love child. He will do anything to throw you off guard. Especially when you want to <i>become </i>one. Prepare for an interview that dives into your deepest fears, favorite pizza toppings and why you think capes should make a comeback in office attire.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Choose the job you want or make one up: whether you want to become an astronaut or an underwater basket weaving consultant, you're in charge of your career.<br/></li><li>Answer both serious and not-so-serious questions to see if you're fit for the job.<br/></li><li>Subject yourself to mockery, roastings, ridicule, condescension and even disapproving glances from our demanding interviewer.<br/></li><li>Pixel art. Or 'stupid blocky graphics' as my son calls it.<br/></li><li>Short experience (around 30 minutes).<br/></li><li>No Interview is the same!</li></ul><br/>So iron your 8-bit tie, slap on a smile thicker than a pixelated pancake and charm the binary socks off the AllJobs Agency!<br/><br/>Tap that download button and catapult yourself into occupational stardom. It's time to fake it 'til you make it in the jazzy job jungle!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Thai Boyfriend</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2701560/My_Thai_Boyfriend/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is an LVG, a GALGAME, a visual novel, a funny and hilarious game. It's a story about love choices of a Thai Ladyboy. He fell in love with both man and woman, it's so hard for him to make the choice. In the meantime, his boyfriend also fell in love with him and his girlfriend as well, so it's also very hard for him to make the choice too. So, various bizarre plot twists will unfold, providing players with a truly shocking and unique experience in this game. It's based on real story happened in Pattaya Thailand. This game is developed by an open source engine, all scripts, pictures, videos, music are not encrypted in any way.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701560/extras/GifAboutTheGame.gif?t=1704100725"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find Room 96</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732640/Find_Room_96/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trying to find room 96 but you are stuck in a loop. To find room 96, observe your surroundings and get familiar with it. On floor 0 you will be presented with an area to study the layout of objects. The timer will start once you are ready to play. The correct decision will move you up a floor and the incorrect decision will reset you back to the beginning. Observation is key.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, choose the elevator that states no anomalies otherwise choose the elevator that states confirm anomalies.<br/><br/>Find Room 96 is a short game. Currently there are 3 levels. 2 levels are locked but can be unlocked providing you beat the timer challenge.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15 - 120 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">Replay Ability</h2>Once you have beat the timer challenge for a level you can go back on that level and try to beat your new best time.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XiJiang Shipyard</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2690180/XiJiang_Shipyard/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Xijiang Shipyard" is a construction game with a realistic style that focuses on free creation.<br>
It has many features to serve creation: various shapes of geometry, rich realistic materials, realistic plants, various skills to accelerate construction, independent editor, carving details, 3D printing interface, bringing virtuality into reality, model interface, and world into other virtual worlds.						</br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extraordinary: Immortal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667780/Extraordinary_Immortal/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Karena opened the letter and picked up a cup of coffee)<br>
<br>
... I was born in April E102, in the Ewutanxi tribe of the Eqha grassland ...<br>
... I saw you in the temple when I was 14 years old when I was first cursed, but you are not the ancient person from 700 years ago...<br>
...When I woke up again, it was already the winter of E825...<br>
... Assuming that our meeting in the temple did not happen, then the future must not be the current future...<br>
<br>
"Extraordinary: Immortal" is the sequel to "Extraordinary: Soul", a point-and-click puzzle game created by TeatimeWorkshop<br>
<br>
Game features:<br>
The operation and gameplay of the game are simple. Even if you have never played point-and-click puzzle games, you can easily get started.<br>
The story in the game is accompanied by colorful picture book style, which will make you unable to put it down.<br/>
Follow Karena and Moe to experience a case investigation that spans time and space						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Legend of Ogorets #4: Warren</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2703030/The_Legend_of_Ogorets_4_Warren/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are aboard a ship headed straight for the center of the galaxy. The Legend of Ogorets is a series featuring mature, action-packed, character-driven adventures in post-apocalyptic settings. Your choices matter. #4 is the adventure of Warren, an energetic mercenary, embarks upon an epic journey to find the perfect place to plant her telescope at night. Average read time: 40-50 minutes. Some readers may find this content disturbing.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zamakan</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2228100/Zamakan/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2228100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An exciting endless runner game with an Egyptian theme.<br>
Players take on the role of a space ship, representing an alternative reality where the ancient Egyptian civilization advanced to space travel. <br>
The objective of the game is to travel as far as possible through an asteroid field without crashing into any obstacles. <br>
The game's unique feature is the visualized time-space grid, where objects of different masses can bend the fabric of time-space. <br>
Therefore, players need to maneuver their space ship through this challenging environment, using their skills and quick reflexes to avoid colliding with asteroids. <br>
With its intriguing premise, visually stunning graphics, and engaging gameplay, this game is sure to provide hours of endless fun and excitement for players of all ages.						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TVS Sample Box</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2710260/TVS_Sample_Box/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2710260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							TVS Sample Box is a Sample HUB App that offers Trash Vomit Studios Mini-Games, Concepts and an information HUB for Trash Vomit Studios indie video games.<br>
<br>
Each Mini-Game included is a standalone Mini-Version Sample of Trash Vomit Studios larger products. <br>
<br>
This App is meant to serve as a Free introduction to Trash Vomit Studios developer's indie video games to demonstrate the feel, game play, artistic approach and differentiated style that Trash Vomit Studios video games have to offer.<br>
<br>
-The Knowledge of Hermit: Premonition *Mini-Game   (A fraction sample of the Full Game that can be found on Steam.)<br/>
-Crazy Brain: High Score Attack *Mini-Game  (A fraction sample of the Full Game that can be found on Steam.)<br/>
-The Pain: Nightmare Run *Mini-Game   (A prototype sample of a concept game currently in development.)<br/>
-Victim World Map Tour  (An interactive tour of the Map which makes up both Victim &amp; Happy Mask which are both found on Steam.)<br/>
-Trash Vomit Studios Video Game Descriptive Pages (Pages which describe each of Trash Vomit Studios released Video Games)<br/>
-Concept Extras <br/>
-Developer &amp; Development Information Pages<br/>
<br/>
*This application will be updated and expanded with New Free content from time to time.  <br/>
Such as New Mini-Games and expanded content and information.<br/>
<br/>
*This app can also serve as a test run for the other Trash Vomit Studios Apps.<br/>
If your PC can run this App, your PC can run all Trash Vomit Studios games at the same level.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire Racing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2695250/Fire_Racing/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2695250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Real Racing game.<br>
6 tracks. A racing game with day, night, and seasons.<br>
A game where you can run on various roads with various obstacles and natural scenery.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamster Hunter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2726490/Hamster_Hunter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Hamster Hunter is a short horror hunting game, with a small story attached.<br>
In this game you will have access to buying different contraptions to put the Hamsters through, like guillotines, microwaves and more.<br>
<br>
You are playing as a student heading home for an annual family reunion, once you arrive you notice you family is missing, you then embark on a search to find out what happened to them. Along the way you get this HATE for Hamsters that then turns into a hunt. You then hunt and torture them in the name of revenge for your family.<br>
<br>
In Hamster Hunter you will &amp; can.<br>
You can buy and build different contraptions to place around the map.<br>
You can tranquilize hamster and do various things with them.<br/>
You will embark on a story to find your missing family.<br/>
You can lure Hamsters in with bait.<br/>
You can freely explore the map looking for blueprints.<br/>
You can make meat patties from the Hamsters and sell it.<br/>
Etc.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Really Dog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2670890/Really_Dog/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2670890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							There are 7 types of dogs, each with unique skills and symbolic meanings.<br/>You can feel the joy of harvesting monsters, very decompression.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2670890/extras/shop2e.png?t=1704128618"><br/><br/>The basic gameplay is a bit like whack-a-mole, easy to understand.<br/>In DLC, we provide Paku Mode, Mini Mode, and the Endless Level. We recommend it to players who enjoy challenges.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2670890/extras/shop1e.png?t=1704128618"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tead</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2145700/Tead/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2145700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Tead is a murder mystery visual novel game inspired by Danganronpa, Phoenix Wright and others. <br>
<br>
12 strangers wake up in a room. They're told one of them is secretly the Game Master, and they must try to kill the Game Master. But if one of them murders someone who's not the Game Master, the murderer will be killed unless they can convince others they were not the murderer. The others must figure out who the murderer is or they will all die. <br>
<br>
Collect evidence, make arguments, and identify the murderer, but don't lose sight of the ultimate goal of eliminating the Game Master. Many will die along the way, but remember: Their Endings Are Deserved.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CandyVenture: Rebaked</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2723610/CandyVenture_Rebaked/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The good old <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/987800/CandyVenture/" rel="" target="_blank">CandyVenture</a> is finally back on Steam</strong>! We have carefully re-baked the whole game, taking care of its old values, but in a modern guise! Unlocked framerate, controller support, improved level design, new effects and much more!<br/><br/><strong>The story:</strong><br/>Candyland was a peaceful place on earth, a place where all the candy is made. The inhabitants of the village are hard workers, they've dedicated their lives to make candy. But there's someone in space who wants to start his own candy business. His name is CHUYGOK382XZ, but everyone calls him Micron. He lives on the Moon, he built his own factory, but... Their only raw material is cheese! (Because everyone knows, the Moon is made from cheese). Sadly, no one bought his cheese-candies. One night he came up with an evil plan. He will invade CandyLand with his army and takes all the candy with himself to the Moon! At night he sent his army to the Earth... CandyLand is in a big trouble now.<br/><br/>And this, where the story begins...<br/><br/>Bogyi and his friends count on you! Stole the candies back from Micron and save CandyLand!<br/><br/><strong>Game features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>4 playable characters!<br/></li><li>16 levels and exciting boss fights!<br/></li><li>Perk system!<br/></li><li>Cozy 2D retro graphics and sound!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Karina Katana</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731530/Karina_Katana/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Karina Katana is a classic 2D-style action adventure in a world divided into individual levels with 8 exciting biomes.<br>
<br>
You level up your skills to traverse the different worlds and fight 8 different types of enemies.<br>
Every opponent has different strengths and weaknesses. You need to recognize these and use them against them.<br>
<br>
Each enemy drops different items when you defeat them.<br>
Collect your opponents' items and use them to improve your weapons and skills in the shop.<br/>
<br/>
Find new weapons in the newly unlocked biomes and unlock new skins by playing.<br/>
<br/>
Each level also has a timer with which you can see your speed so you can be faster next time.<br/>
You can also get up to 3 badges for different challenges for each level.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evasion from cluster 42</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2521460/Evasion_from_cluster_42/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2521460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Evasion from Cluster 42, an arcade spaceshooter for 1 or 2 players with 3D GFX and a Background Story. There are lots of different levels in totally different environments.<br>
<br>
The game has some unique features:<br>
- Play every level from top down view or from side view. You'll get a different view and a different experience that way for each level!<br>
- You can decide if enemies appear and behave in a random way or completly linear always the same.<br>
- There is also a retro shader if you want the game to look like in the 90s but better<br>
- You can totally change and build your ship your style there are about 30 different ship parts for a unique look and abilities, and extra modules and weapons. You can also rotate your weapons and tell the ship how to use it's energy...<br>
- 1 or 2 players (alone or local coop with shared screen)<br>
- There are daily and weekly quests and also trophies<br/>
- There are hiscores  global and local, per Game Mode and for each level<br/>
- There is also a Arcade / Survive Game-Mode<br/>
- Rogue-like elements in the game, play certain levels multiple times to farm resources and improve your spaceship if the game gets to hard in some later levels						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electron Flux</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2143660/Electron_Flux/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Electron Flux is a Rogue-Lite tower defense game that challenges players to make strategic, adaptive decisions  about how they focus research, place towers, manage resources, and adapt their strategy on each play-through to rebuff the advances of waves of enemies from destroying their circuit! Each play-through features procedurally generated towers for the player to place with different shot patterns, range, damage, and abilities! Players choose which towers to research and upgrade during each play-through, decisions which could mean the difference between passing your class, or turning in a smoldering husk for your final project! Place your towers strategically on your circuit board, because procedurally generated waves of bugs have come to destroy your hard work!<br>
<br>
All towers and enemies are rendered in hand-crafted, isometric, vaporwave pixel-art style! The towers and enemies also emit detailed video effects from particles being blown off of them to arcs of chain lightning! Blast and relax to Electron Flux’s midi-inspired original score and handcrafted sound effects!						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>027</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2706960/027/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i><strong>CAUTION</strong>: this game is not for the faint of heart</i><br/><br/>027 is a first-person survival horror game.<br/><br/>Wander and investigate the empty town that once was home to your old best friend; Chris Williams. Uncover untold mysteries behind Chris' disappearance, or flee from the monstrosities the run-aways left behind.<br/><br/><strong>Environment</strong><br/>027 is set inside an abandoned town with many places within to explore. Whether it be out in the streets, in the house, the mall, or in their twisted, maze-like counterparts, terror will be inevitable.<br/><br/><strong>Storyline</strong><br/>You are a friend of Chris', hoping to find out what happened to him, and if he's still alive. You check every corner of the town, but you find more than just clues are lurking around in your friend's hometown.<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/>Solve puzzles to progress into the game and discover it's deeper meaning.<br/><br/>Survive as you encounter things you'd never expect. With no way to defend yourself, you only have one choice: run. <br/><br/>Utilize the resources given to you, and all will be closer to well.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet X16</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2727770/Planet_X16/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2727770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>NOTE:</strong> If you are using Proton you may need to <a href="https://help.steampowered.com/en/faqs/view/7D01-D2DD-D75E-2955" rel="" target="_blank">set the launch options</a> to:<br/>PROTON_USE_WINED3D=1 %command%<h2 class="bb_tag">General Control of the Game</h2>SHIFT+L: <strong>Load Game</strong><br/>SHIFT+S: <strong>Save Game</strong><br/>Ctrl+C / Pause Key:       <strong>Pause Game/Exit Level</strong><br/>Left Click:                      <strong>Select Unit or Building</strong><br/>SHIFT+Left Click:           <strong>Select Multiple Units</strong><br/>Double Left Click:          <strong>Select all similar units in view</strong><br/>Right Click on Map:       <strong>Tell unit(s) to go there.</strong><br/>Right Click on Enemy:   <strong>Tell unit(s) to attack unit or building</strong><br/>Escape:                          <strong>Abort whatever unit/building is doing</strong><br/>A:                                   <strong>Attack unit, building, or terrain</strong><br/>Left Click Mini-map:      <strong>Change view area to that part of map</strong><br/>Right Click Mini-Map:    <strong>Send selected unit(s) to that area</strong><br/>Mouse at Screen Edge:  <strong>Scroll Viewing Area</strong><br/>Cursor Keys:                   <strong>Scroll Viewing Area</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">First Priorities</h2>You have between 9 and 10 minutes before the enemy will <br/>    attack.  Use that time to start harvesting resources and<br/>    building up defenses.<br/><br/>Minerals - You will need to build a smelter (Hotkey T) near <br/>    where you see rocks and crystals.  Use the builder to pick <br/>    up minerals and drop them along sides of the smelter <br/>    building.  The smelter will automatically pick them up and <br/>    process them as it needs. <br/><br/>    Start with the crystals first, as they are the highest <br/>    value resources.  When those run out, you can process the <br/>    rocks, starting from the largest to the smallest.<br/><br/>Solar Power - You will first need to build a power station <br/>    (hotkey A) somewhere on the map.  Once it is finished, you <br/>    can build up to 8 solar panels around the power station.  <br/>    If you need more than 8 panels (which you probably will) <br/>    then build an additional power station.<br/><br/>Gas Refinery - Build the refinery (hotkey G) on top of <br/>    volcanos.  The more volcanoes you tap, the more gas you'll <br/>    have available.<h2 class="bb_tag">Setup Defenses</h2>    You can move rocks or build walls to fortify the areas <br/>    most vulnerable to attack.  Then build sentry tanks at the<br/>    factory and move then a few spaces behind your wall, as <br/>    they have a very long firing range.  Be sure to set them <br/>    to sentry mode (hotkey S).  If they aren't spinning, then <br/>    they aren't going to defend!<h2 class="bb_tag">Build A Radar Station</h2>    This game does not employ a fog of war, and you can always<br/>    see anything in the main view area.  However, if you want to<br/>    be able to see both player and enemy mobile units live on <br/>    the mini-map, a radar station must be present. Player units<br/>    show up in white, while Protoid units are yellow.<h2 class="bb_tag">Balance Of Units</h2>    Obviously not all units are equal.  Some are slow, some are<br/>    fast.  Some are cheap, and some are expensive.  A small<br/>    group of heavy tanks, for example, could decimate your <br/>    opponent's base. However, they are expensive, take a long<br/>    time to build, and they are slow to move.  On the flip side<br/>    of that, ATVs are cheap and fast, but not very powerful.<br/><br/>    In time, you will learn which units are best suited for<br/>    different strategies.<h2 class="bb_tag">Missile Silo</h2>    Missiles can devestate your opponents base easily.  But be<br/>    warned, they are expensive and slow to build.  You must<br/>    also build a new missile for each launch.<br/><br/>    The coordinate system used is based on how many spaces <br/>    relative to the silo the target is.  So, if you have more <br/>    than one missile silo, the coordinates will not be the same<br/>    for each one.  Also the coordinates are shown in hexa-<br/>    decimal.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Protoids</h2>    It is good to know your enemy.  The Protoids will typically<br/>    not attack your base until their army has reached a certain<br/>    size.  However, they will always rush to defend the base if<br/>    you attack them.<br/><br/>    They aren't too bright when it comes to navigating the map<br/>    to attack your base.  However, their tanks will blast<br/>    through terrain objects that are in the way, or even build<br/>    bridges over water, thus allowing the rest of the units<br/>    a path to your base.  <br/><br/>    Protoids do rebuild their base if pieces of it are<br/>    destroyed.  So don't wait too long after a partially<br/>    sucessful attack, or you may have to start all over again.<h2 class="bb_tag">Difficulty Levels</h2>    There are three difficulty levels: easy, normal, and hard.<br/>    There are numerous things that change with each level. Some<br/>    things are small, such as the ratio of tanks vs soldiers<br/>    that are built.  Also the number of sentry pods that the <br/>    Protoids build varies.  It is as little as 4 pods per base<br/>    in easy mode, to 12 pods in hard mode.  <br/><br/>    In easy mode, the protoids will not even build a factory, <br/>    hence no tanks will be made. And with no tanks, the Protoids<br/>    will not cross water or create paths through forest or<br/>    rocks.  <br/><br/>    In hard mode, the Protoids will build two bases at the<br/>    start of the game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runic Survivor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2116920/Runic_Survivor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2116920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2116920/extras/GifSequence_1.gif?t=1704054128"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive the Onslaught!</h2>Fight through hordes of monster to break the seals and defeat the guardians before it is too late!<h2 class="bb_tag">Craft Custom Spells!</h2>In this game you do not unlock weapons or skills as you progress, instead, you unlock powerful arcane Runes.<br/><br/>Runes can be used to craft spells on the fly and can be changed and modified to your hearts content! <br/><br/>Craft a spell shooting fiery bolts that split off into massive explosion every time they light an enemy on fire. Or an aura that knocks any enemy that approaches you back, at least until the hordes of enemies overwhelm you. The only limit is your creativity... and your mana.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2116920/extras/GifSequence.gif?t=1704054128"><h2 class="bb_tag">Unlock new equipment!</h2>With every death you get stronger, earning gold that can be used to purchase passive abilities and bonuses to increase your chances next time.. And when you get a hang of it, increase the difficulty and face even stronger foes!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2116920/extras/GifSequence_2.gif?t=1704054128"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterpact</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2061750/Counterpact/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2061750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Counterpact is a 2D platform-shooter that pits two teams against each other, or a solo player against the tough, radiant forces the Gilded Spire has to offer.<br/><br/><strong><u>7 Unique Characters</u></strong><br/>Each playable character comes with their own set of mechanics. If you enjoy glass cannon gameplay, try Shiniko the Reaper, who can output some serious damage despite her low health and close-ranged attacks; use her Dash to maneuver around (or through) enemies. Prefer to take a beefier approach? Try SYS.TR the Bulwark, who can use channel the damage she receives into powerful auras using her Rerouted Power.<br/><br/><strong><u>Different Weapons to Try</u></strong><br/>Don't like how a character plays by default? Maybe the current situation calls for something different? Perhaps you're just looking for to spice up their gameplay? Each character has a variety of alternate weapons to choose from, some of which even change their role, all while keeping their core mechanics intact. New weapons will be added over time as well.<br/><br/><strong><u>Over 200 Cosmetics to Collect</u></strong><br/>By simply playing the game (no microtransactions are involved), you can earn Eclipsium which can be used to purchase new weapons and cosmetics. Cosmetic items include different outfits for characters, little pets that follow you, chairs that you can sit on, emotes to taunt with, and more. Having a hard time getting what you want? Don't worry, you can even trade items with other players.<br/><br/><strong><u>Enter the Gilded Spire</u></strong><br/>If you want a solo experience, the Gilded Spire awaits you. Fight through four floors of bulky enemies and traps for a chance to earn riches. If you really want to challenge yourself and reap great rewards, try conquering the Gilded Spire on the Blinding difficulty. After that, you can truly test yourself with Gilded Gauntlets.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Hero After the Fall</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2374410/My_Hero_After_the_Fall/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2374410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In a war known as the "Fall of the Heavenly God," the source of divine power, the Well of Magic, was destroyed. This led to the disappearance of the Heavenly God's power that had been guarding the continent, and the once-sealed Gate of the Void was reopened, allowing countless demons to pour into the land. The only hope now rests with the young hero chosen by the Guardians. He must gather the remaining Divine Power Crystals, rebuild the Well of Magic, seal the Gate of the Void, and save this continent plunged into despair.<br/>This is a pixel tower defense game that combines light Rogue and grass cutting!Select your hero and place your hero at the designated construction point on the map to block the enemy!<h2 class="bb_tag"> 30+heroes for you to choose from! </h2>There are a total of 30+heroes for you to choose from, and the number is still increasing! Each hero has 2-3 unique skills to learn and upgrade, and combinations of different heroes can have unexpected effects!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2374410/extras/P3-export.png?t=1704080152"><h2 class="bb_tag"> 150+random blessings </h2>150+random blessings! As the battle deepens, blessings will become more powerful!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2374410/extras/P1-export.png?t=1704080152"><h2 class="bb_tag"> Talent and props </h2>Three mainstream talents for you to choose from, with different hero lineups or genres to produce unexpected effects! Each hero has his own powerful props hidden in the level!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2374410/extras/P2-export.png?t=1704080152"><h2 class="bb_tag"> A total of 78 maps in 10+ series </h2>Many maps are rich in game content while also containing story elements!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2374410/extras/P4.png?t=1704080152"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feedback and Concerns</h2>This indie game was developed by DAYA alone. DAYA can be contacted or feedback can be provided through the following methods:<br/>QQ Group：658408243<br/>Discord: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F5GxCXQwsep" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Click here</a><br/>BILIBILI: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspace.bilibili.com%2F510842503%3Fspm_id_from%3D333.1007.0.0" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Click here</a><br/><a href="mailto:Email：1789258932@qq.com">Email：1789258932@qq.com</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2374410/extras/DAYA_Icon2-export.png?t=1704080152"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoshi_no_Natchan</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733640/Hoshi_no_Natchan/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2733640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> Even if you don't play games often,<br/>You might be able to see the ending an hour after you pick up this game.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Introduction</h2>"Hoshi_no_Natchan" is a retro style pixel art 2D action game.<br/>This game was created so that even people who are not very good at games can experience the fun of clearing the game.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Wow you went ahead!<br/></li><li>You jump well!<br/></li><li> You are great at collecting stars!<br/></li><li> It's cool when you fight the enemy!<br/></li><li> It's cute even if you make a mistake!<br/></li><li> Even if you get game over, you keep trying and don't give up!<br/></li><li>Let's hope you reach the goal! </li></ul>I would be happy if you could think, "Games are fun!" through this game.<h2 class="bb_tag">What kind of game is it? </h2>It is a 2D action game that mainly uses the <strong>control key</strong>, <strong>jump button</strong> and <strong>attack button</strong>.<br/>Aim for the goal star and move forward through the four stages.<br/>There will also be enemies that will block Hoshi_no_Natchan's path.<br/>Defeat them by stepping on them or attacking them.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Features? </h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Flick away</li></ul>If you defeat an enemy with an attack, you can send the enemy flying.<br/>It often happens that the enemy you bounce back hits another enemy...<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Energy Dash</li></ul>Defeating enemies will increase your dash energy.<br/>Having dash energy will make you dash faster for a short time.<h2 class="bb_tag">FOR SUPER PLAYERS</h2>If you are confident in your ability, try reducing vitality, stock, and time from the options.<br/>This game is easy to clear, so you can play with a high score (or low score) or aim for a clear time.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
