<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>The Walking Dead: Destinies</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2192790/The_Walking_Dead_Destinies/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2192790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Begin your journey as Rick Grimes, waking alone in a hospital surrounded by the dead. Assemble allies and fight your way through the walker apocalypse across iconic locations from The Walking Dead, including Atlanta, the Greene family farm, the prison, and Woodbury. In crucial choice-driven moments, you’ll forever shape the destiny of your team of characters from the series. Heroes and villains, living and dead – it’s up to you to decide whether to stay the course of history or forge your own path through the world of AMC’s The Walking Dead.<br>
<br>
• Shatter Fate: Alter the story of AMC’s The Walking Dead by weaving your own path through the series’ events. Save the villain, kill the hero… and live with the consequences.<br>
<br>
• Slash, Bash, and Shoot the Undead: Slay hordes of walkers in third-person action with a variety of melee and ranged weapons, including bats, katanas, revolvers, shotguns, and crossbows.<br>
<br/>
• Play as 13 Iconic Characters: Assemble your roster from from AMC’s The Walking Dead, including Rick, Shane, Michonne, Carol, Daryl, and more.          <br/>
<br/>
• Survive the Apocalypse: Manage limited resources, scavenge for weapons and ammo, and maximize your party’s abilities to stay alive.<br/>
<br/>
• Experience the Tension: Defend your camp, rescue survivors, and fight through stealth and all-out combat. Get one last chance at survival in a “broken state” before the zombie threat overwhelms you.						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SteamWorld Build</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2134770/SteamWorld_Build/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-Homestead.png?t=1701453785"><br/>One final landrush! The planet is dyin', Astrid, and it's dig or die trying! <br/><br/>That mine under our town is sitting empty, and wouldn't you know there's rumours of ancient tech down there that might help us out of this predicament. Round up the posse, circle the wagons, and let's get to buildin' a new home! Collect resources above ground and ores down below so we can get those wealthy bots in here to help us build bigger, and we can get the heck out of here!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_1.gif?t=1701453785"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_manage.png?t=1701453785"><br/>As your borders expand, new steamfolk will find their way to you! Every bot is crotchety in their own way, and it's up to you to keep them steaming along. Barter to boost efficiency, keep goods flowing to and from the mines and keep everyone happy to make them work their darndest and hardest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_2.gif?t=1701453785"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-DIG-DEEP.png?t=1701453785"><br/><br/>Stare into the abyss long enough and it might just stare back... we're going looking for riches and something down there doesn't want to share! Have gun, dig gravel, and make sure the mines don't collapse upon you as you defend yourselves from the creepy crawlies that lurk within...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_3.gif?t=1701453785"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_features.png?t=1701453785"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break ground on a bustling SteamWorld town, inspired by the Old West.<br/></li><li>Keep your steambots from getting cranky by ensuring their complex needs get met<br/></li><li>Dig deep and spread wide to produce resources to aid your search for ancient technologies<br/></li><li>Defend your mine from the creepy varmints that lurk deep below your town<br/></li><li>Trade resources at the local train stop and welcome special visitors who'll lend a hand<br/></li><li>Five distinct maps littered with secrets for the discerning SteamWorld explorer to find<br/></li><li>Developed from the ground up for both mouse and controller, whichever takes yer fancy.<br/></li><li>Four difficulty levels, including a sandbox difficulty for when you just want to Build!</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HoloParade</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2647230/HoloParade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">A lively parade with hololive VTubers and mascot characters!</h2><br/>"HoloParade" is a fan game of hololive and the first title to serve as a test case for "holo Indie". Collect, nurture, and enjoy watching your favorite characters! It's a 2D tower defense game that offers depth, strategy, and can also be enjoyed casually.<br/><br/>What is "holo Indie"?:<br/>It is a general term for a game brand for derivative work games, produced using the "game creator support program" with the aim of co-creating with fans and creators of hololive Production around the world.<h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 1: Simple Yet Deep, Lively Battles</h2>The basic system is a classic 2D tower defense game where you summon characters from your base and march them forward to destroy the enemy's base to win. While the controls are simple, the gameplay is profoundly deep. With over 65 characters, each possessing a variety of abilities like ally healing support and self-destruct attacks, skillful combination and flexible formation are key to enjoying the game.<br/><br/>Additionally, there's an element inspired by parades called the 'Symphony Effect,' where various effects are activated based on the musical instruments played by the characters in march. This adds further strategic depth to the formation of your parade squad and the order of their summoning.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Battle.gif?t=1701417555"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 2: Comprehensive Development Elements</h2>In addition to leveling up and limit breaking, there is a 'Skill' system that allows you to add special abilities not available through regular development. Since you can add up to three types of skills to each character and select them carefully, you can enjoy a unique development process! Furthermore, since you can reset levels and get a full refund of the coins spent, it allows for more freedom in restructuring formations and character development.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Skill_ENG.gif?t=1701417555"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 3: No Gacha Purchases, No Stamina System</h2>The scout gacha, which allows you to acquire characters, can be used by consuming tickets obtained within the game, with no additional purchases required. Also, as there is no stamina system, you are not bound by time and can play as much as you like, whenever you like.<br/><br/>Moreover, the scout gacha allows you to choose from two randomly selected character candidates, enabling players to make selections based on their strategy or preference rather than leaving it entirely to chance.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Gacha_ENG.gif?t=1701417555"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 4: Take a Break with Various Talents and Mini-Games in the Office</h2>When you return to the office, the home screen, you'll be greeted by newly recorded voice lines from Harusaki Nodoka, a staff member of hololive. In the office, talents from hololive may also make appearances, and you might witness some unexpected interactions.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Home_ENG.png?t=1701417555"><br/><br/>Additionally, mini-games with entirely different gameplay from the main story are implemented. These games allow you to collect coins necessary for character strengthening. At the initial release, a mini-game titled "Hurry Up! Miko-Chi!" is available, where Sakura Miko (a VTuber affiliated with hololive) who overslept, dashes at full speed towards her destination while avoiding obstacles. More mini-games are planned to be added in future updates.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/RunMikoti.gif?t=1701417555"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Truck Simulator - Kansas</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2298430/American_Truck_Simulator__Kansas/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2298430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Introducing Kansas! A U.S State that is home to a truly authentic cowboy culture and miles of land littered with wildflowers. Located in the Midwest of the USA, Kansas is known for its native grasslands, streams, abundant blue skies, and green grassland vistas. <br/><br/>Once considered to be the country’s agricultural heartland, "The Sunflower State" has managed to attract many large businesses and develop in other industrial areas due to its central location and convenient infrastructure for logistics operations. But, as the nickname suggests, nature is certainly doing very well to keep up with technological progress, as the state parks and vast prairies offer unique views with a marvelous atmosphere that will leave every trucker passing by with something to remember.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Deliver to 14 explorable cities including Kansas City, Wichita, or Topeka<br/></li><li>See several landmarks unique to Kansas such as the historic Dodge City, Monument Rocks, and Mount Sunflower<br/></li><li>Become a trucker transporting goods for Kansas' key industries - Salt Mine, Food Factory, Car Factory, Building Material Factory, and Battery Factory<br/></li><li>Deliver cargo to Aerosystem, playing a key role in Wichita's aerospace industry<br/></li><li>Visit Hutchinson and admire the world's largest silos<br/></li><li>Play a crucial role in one of America's largest agricultural states. Transport goods that sustain Kansas' farming legacy<br/></li><li>Enjoy trucking through several scenic towns (settlements)<br/></li><li>Drive through expansive prairies, providing unforgettable views</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Truck Simulator - Farm Machinery</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2638630/American_Truck_Simulator__Farm_Machinery/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Saddle up drivers, because the Farm Machinery DLC for American Truck Simulator has arrived! Transport everything from trusty tractors to forage harvesters across scenic virtual highways and roads. <br/><br/>Featuring 2 in-game brands, Owl &amp; Greenler, you'll be able to deliver a variety of unique cargoes on Lowboy, Dropdeck or Flatbed trailers to a number of agriculture-related industries large and small across the country.<br/><br/>This DLC includes:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Sprayer <br/></li><li>Crawler Tractor <br/></li><li>Forage Harvester <br/></li><li>Fertilizer Spreader <br/></li><li>Grain Trailer<br/></li><li>Autonomous Tractor <br/></li><li>Hay Baler <br/></li><li>Seeding Unit <br/></li><li>Disc Harrow</li></ul><br/>Naturally, we couldn't let you go driving without some themed cabin accessories for your cabin either! <br/><br/>Cabin Accessories<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Lunch Kit<br/></li><li>Scarecrow <br/></li><li>Straw Hat <br/></li><li>Stuffed Autonomous Tractor <br/></li><li>Harvester Toy </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turok 3: Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1996770/Turok_3_Shadow_of_Oblivion_Remastered/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/raptor_jumps.gif?t=1701367237"><br/><br/><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> is a faithful restoration of the classic first-person shooter originally released in 2000 for the Nintendo 64, upgraded through Nightdive Studios’ proprietary KEX Engine for play on modern gaming devices with up to a 4K resolution at 120FPS. <br/><br/>It joins Nightdive Studios and Universal Games popular Turok and Turok 2: Seeds of Evil remasters, capping off the trilogy. <i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> features upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<h2 class="bb_tag">FINISH THE HUNT</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/sniper_one_eye.gif?t=1701367237"><br/><br/><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> is the first title from Nightdive Studios to be remastered using the latest version KEX engine, which utilizes an improved renderer to achieve a higher tier of visual fidelity across 3D models, textures, and graphical effects.<h2 class="bb_tag"><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> Key Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A remastered version of the 2000 classic, available for the first time since its Nintendo 64 release<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS performance<br/></li><li>Advanced rendering features, including anti-aliasing, bloom, ambient occlusion, dynamic shadows, and motion blur	<br/></li><li>Remastered environment art, character models, and updated weapon models<br/></li><li>Brand new Achievements</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/robot.gif?t=1701367237"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinball M</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2337640/Pinball_M/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-1.png?t=1701438722"><br/><br/>The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-2.png?t=1701438722"><br/><br/>- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free<br/>- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage<br/>- Thrilling competition<br/>- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation<h2 class="bb_tag">Sink your teeth into these tables as purchasable DLC: </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">- Chucky's Killer Pinball:</h2> Step into a twisted realm where the innocent becomes sinister, and the playful turns menacing. Navigate through an eerie playfield where Chucky lurks in the shadows, ready to pounce.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Dead by Daylight™️ Pinball:</h2> Become the hunter or even the hunted in a thrilling fusion of classic pinball and the excitement of one of the most popular horror games ever created.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Duke Nukem's Big Shot Pinball:</h2> Enjoy the biggest, grooviest, most BADASS pinball table ever made packed with guns and babes. Push start and play with balls of steel!<h2 class="bb_tag">- The Thing Pinball: </h2>Use your pinball skills and battle against the shape-shifting alien through the arctic chill of U.S. Outpost #31. Can you trust anyone, even yourself?<br/>- Even more coming...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-4.png?t=1701438722"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truck &amp; Logistics Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/873840/Truck__Logistics_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Load, drive, and deliver through a huge open world with up to 24 players in cross-platform multiplayer. Join your friends in exciting heavy transport convoys. Jump into the driver's seat of more than 30 unique vehicles and carry out complex loading tasks to deliver a variety of cargo.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Load.gif?t=1701358833"><br/><br/><strong>Load pallets, containers, vehicles &amp; more!</strong><br/>Each mission is unique and comes with its own challenges. Start up your business by loading pallets into vans with a forklift. Then work your way up to loading heavy containers with telescopic handlers onto trailers. Maneuver vehicles such as cars, forklifts, skid-steers, wheel-loaders and more onto your trailers. Hundreds of unique and challenging missions and deliveries await you! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Drive.gif?t=1701358833"><br/><br/><strong>Drive cars, vans, trucks &amp; more!</strong><br/>Drive and customize over 30 unique vehicles. From minivans to heavy trucks, each vehicle has its own detailed interior and realistic driving physics. Vehicles can be damaged, causing axles to bend and making driving difficult. Refuel and repair at service stations to get back on the road in full swing. Make each vehicle your own by customizing it to your liking. Stick to the traffic rules or risk getting fined in random police traffic controls and radar speed cameras. Push your driving skills to the limit in many diverse and challenging missions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Deliver.gif?t=1701358833"><br/><br/><strong>Deliver in an open world with up to 24 friends!</strong><br/>Enjoy the ultimate delivery experience in co-op multiplayer. Join your friends, make convoys, earn money and expand your companies together. Escort other players safely to their destinations using specialized convoy equipment. Explore a vast 28 km² open world, from bustling cities to tranquil rural areas. Explore and uncover hidden secrets scattered across the map. Get ready for a journey into a dynamic and completely open world where the deliveries never end!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 30 unique vehicles with realistic interiors<br/></li><li>Huge 28km² open world (no hidden walls!)<br/></li><li>Cross-platform multiplayer with up to 24 players<br/></li><li>Escort convoys in co-op multiplayer missions<br/></li><li>Full day / night cycle<br/></li><li>Hundreds of different challenging missions<br/></li><li>Realistic driving physics and damage system<br/></li><li>Vehicle customization<br/></li><li>Random police traffic controls &amp; speed cameras</li></ul><br/>Start your company today! Join our community below, see you on the road!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FPCjxFjs" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Discord_2023.gif?t=1701358833"/></a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEVI</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2230650/TEVI/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FZ9KrdFvNRK" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/JoinUsOnDC.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Action-Packed_Combo_System.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/戰鬥動圖.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>The protagonist Tevi is nimble and agile, wielding both her trusty dagger and an oversized wrench for dishing out melee damage in style. Alongside her, companions Celia and Sable manifest as two floating orbitars, ready to unleash a variety of ranged offensive and supportive magic in battle. Adapt your combat style to suit any situation and bring down foes with flashy, dazzling combos!<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Thrilling_Boss_Battles.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Boss.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Every boss fight is a unique challenge requiring different strategies to tackle, all while you dodge their attacks and look for openings to counter-attack. <br/>As bosses change phases, their attack and bullet patterns become increasingly challenging, and they can even unleash devastating ultimates. Continual offense can submit bosses into a vulnerable BREAK state, during which you can deal massive bursts of damage.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Myriad_Abilities,_Equipment,_and_Exploration.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/badge.jpg?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Scattered across the the expansive world, there are over 300 different items and pieces of equipment waiting to be discovered. These items can enhance your abilities or introduce new ones, allowing you to find more methods of navigating the world and finding secrets. A cornucopia of equippable sigils can be freely configured to create builds tailored to your preferences and playstyle.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/A_Rich,_Expansive_Fantasy_World.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/場景6.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Dive into the vibrant world of Az, in which you will discover various towns, regions, peoples, histories, and civilizations, each with their own tale to tell. Along the way, you'll meet a large cast of strange and colorful characters. As their tales unfold and intertwine, you'll be drawn into a tale full of adventure, friendship, mysteries, and danger... <br/><br/>Get ready to embark on an unforgettable adventure, writing your own epic journey alongside Tevi!<br/><br/><a href="https://youtu.be/psxior_WswQ" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/角色介紹.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tevi（VA: Lynn）<br/></li><li>Celia（VA: Yoko Hikasa）<br/></li><li>Sable（VA: Natsumi Fujiwara）<br/></li><li>Zema（VA: Tomokazu Sugita）<br/></li><li>Vena（VA: Rie Kugimiya）</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call to Arms - Gates of Hell: Liberation</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2447590/Call_to_Arms__Gates_of_Hell_Liberation/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<strong>“Soldiers, Sailors, and Airmen of the Allied Expeditionary Force: you are about to embark upon the Great Crusade!”<br/>This DLC introduces the western front action in 1944, featuring the US faction, as well as German western front content.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/01Sherman.gif?t=1701279518"><br/><br/>Be among the first to scale the Atlantic wall and fight your way through the Bocage. <br/>Be the spearhead that breaks the stalemate in the battle of the Bulge. <br/>Re-live the rush to the Rhine bridge, on the road into the heart of Germany!<br/><br/>Or, fight for the Wehrmacht and be the one that leads the counterattacks, the one that stops the breakout. In other words; be the one that defends “Fortress Europe” facing all the classic dilemmas that come with it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/02Beach.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Single Player</h2>The single player campaigns focus on four legendary western front units: the “Liberation” campaign has the 2nd Rangers and the 3rd Armored Division on the US side. Beside 6 single player missions, this DLC also offers 4 skirmishes for the US faction, which are part of the campaign storyline.<br/>In all of the missions, you will find yourself in intense battles on iconic battlegrounds, recreated to the last detail; get a taste of the bitter fighting against fanatical opposition, liberating western Europe step by hellish step. The action will be intense and the immersion will be up there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/03Nebel.gif?t=1701279518"><br/><br/>The German campaign,  “Festung Europa”, has the 3rd Fallschirmjäger division and 116th Panzer division on the German side in 6 intense and compelling missions.<br/>Be the one that commands the Wehrmacht forces on the western front from Normandy to the last battles in the Ruhr pocket. In the German campaign you will enjoy a lot of new content as well! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/04Maps.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer</h2>“Liberation” adds the USA to multiplayer with 20 brand new western front MP maps, and all of the new weapons, vehicles and tanks; it also adds a new German late war doctrine.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/05Mist.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Conquest</h2>For conquest, 25 western front maps are included. These, like other maps, use the unique set of assets we have created to immerse you in the western front atmosphere. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/06wespe.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Visuals</h2>Liberation pushes the boundary of the visuals of the Gates of Hell universe to a new standard, with hundreds of highly detailed environment models, improved destruction for buildings and beautiful environments. To ensure the historical accuracy of our content, we have collaborated with WW2 Armor in Florida, who provided us with vast amounts of valuable documentation and knowledge.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/07Logo.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Content</h2>The Liberation DLC contains:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>10 US single player missions, including 4 US skirmishes<br/></li><li>6 German single player missions<br/></li><li>150+  new US and German vehicles, cannon, ships, aircraft and tanks<br/></li><li>50 new small arms<br/></li><li>500+ new humanskins<br/></li><li>20 new MP maps<br/></li><li>25 new DCG (Conquest) maps<br/></li><li>500+ new editor assets for the western European theater.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MULLER-POWELL PRINCIPLE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2155770/THE_MULLERPOWELL_PRINCIPLE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FeY9JWyTaAm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_discord.png?t=1701271403"/></a><br/><br/>It is a sci-fi story that takes place in the near future. You are Harry Herman, an employee of Delta Laboratories who researches interdimensional traveling. You had been participating in a project that was supposed to benefit all humanity, but something went wrong. Through the gameplay, you will solve various physics-based puzzles using an energy-manipulating weapon, travel across space and time to explore surrealistic universes and find out the dark truth about this project and your connection to it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_gameplay.png?t=1701271403"><br/>Solve various puzzles and trick enemies using physics interactions and your special tool - the Portable Energy Manipulator. <br/><br/><strong>PHYSICS PUZZLES &amp; INTERACTIVE ENVIRONMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/gameplay_physics.gif?t=1701271403"><br/><br/>Many objects in the game can be picked up, brought somewhere, or manipulated in other ways. Whether it's a computer terminal, a box you can carry, or a simple mug on a table. Explore various interactive environments to find clues and return to the riddle with a solution, which in some cases may be several. Nothing was made for you to solve, there's no cube dispenser or an obvious exit door at the end. It's all for you to figure out.<br/><br/><strong>PORTABLE ENERGY MANIPULATOR</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/gif_photongun.gif?t=1701271403"><br/><br/>The device you carry throughout the game can absorb different energy types from the environment and use them to perform various tasks.<br/><br/>Absorbing energy from a particular source will give the gun its’ properties. The heat energy from fire and radiators will melt glass, security cameras can be blinded by a beam of light, and for powering generators, you can take hazardous radiation from toxic puddles scattered across Delta Labs facilities. And of course, you will make an encounter with the quantum entanglement energy - the mysterious power capable of opening rifts between worlds. <br/><br/>Apart from solving environmental puzzles, your device can also be used against various creatures you'll meet in parallel dimensions. Most of the time you can't defeat your enemies; instead, you can use the Manipulator to outsmart or suspend them. Some enemies can be frozen in place using the force field energy, while others are sensitive to light and can be distracted by shooting a beam at it in the distance. You will require more advanced strategies and combining various energy types to pass them.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_story.png?t=1701271403"><br/>You find yourself in one of Delta Labs' off-world research facilities in an unknown dimension that looks more like a crashing-down laboratory. Your old friends Eugene and Alex try to connect with you shortly, and with their help, you start a journey through various dimensions. You will learn different physics interactions and meet unusual creatures on your way home. Along this, you have to unveil the mysteries of this project and your past. <br/><br/>Experience a non-linear story where your choice always matters. Can you get to the bottom of this, or just try to escape? Who to listen? Who to trust? Which side will you take? And will you finally “break the Principle”? That depends entirely on you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_setting.png?t=1701271403"><br/>Make your way back to Earth through mysterious parallel dimensions littered with puzzles and secrets, uncover mysterious connections between the worlds you visit, and reveal the dark truth about Delta Labs and your involvement with them. Dare to explore?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_features.png?t=1701271403"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Solve various physics-based puzzles<br/></li><li>Unique gameplay mechanics that involve an energy-manipulating weapon <br/></li><li>A mix of sci-fi with surreal and esoteric themes makes the game setting a unique design. Most of the time you'll spend in bizarre alien dimensions<br/></li><li>Deeply thought-out story and lore. Each location and each character in the game has its own story revealed through various notes, environmental narratives, and characters' conversations.<br/></li><li>The game features multiple endings that can be achieved through different choices </li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn around immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Other</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destiny 2: Season of the Wish Silver Bundle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2218002/Destiny_2_Season_of_the_Wish_Silver_Bundle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2218002/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Purchase the Season of the Wish Silver Bundle and receive the 'Brave Explorer' Legendary Emote along with 1700 Silver (1,000 + 700 bonus Silver) which you can use to purchase Season of the Wish, cosmetics, and more! <br>
<br>
Visit the Seasons tab in-game to use your Silver and buy Season of the Wish.<br>
<br>
To unlock your new Emote, visit the Special Deliveries Terminal in the Tower.<br/>
<br/>
One-time purchase only available during Season of the Wish. Silver is an in-game currency used at the Eververse store.<br/>
<br/>
Season of the Wish not included with purchase.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1701359196"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1701359196"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1701359196"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retro Commander</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/338820/Retro_Commander/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/338820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/338820/extras/icon_and_text_v05_-_600x195px.png?t=1700862195"><br/>Retro Commander is a <strong>post-apocalyptic</strong> real-time strategy wargame (RTS). Take command and fight it out in a world where a cataclysmic timeline has transpired on Mother Earth. Wage wars solo, against the AI, or take on your gaming comrades and friends in cross-platform multiplayer matches. Form teams and clans and fight co-op style with the AI and other players for ultimate victory.<br/><br/>As opposed to other real-time strategy game, Retro Commander tries to focus on both, a fun <strong>single player</strong> and a thrilling <strong>multiplayer</strong> experience. The game strives to be easy to learn with a modern user interface. Single player comes with skirmish matches against the AI as well as a comic-based <strong>story campaign</strong>. Multiplayer can be played cross-platform and includes a ranking and rating system.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u>Post-Apocalyptic</u>: Real-time strategy (RTS) played in a post-apocalyptic timeline on Mother Earth. The environment includes day-night cycles, rain, snow, wind and solar flare activity.<br/></li><li><u>Story Campaign</u>: Deep campaign and story line of humanity after a cataclysmic event. Factions come with their own specialized <strong>technologies</strong> such as stealth, robots, drones or shields.<br/></li><li><u>Single &amp; Multiplayer</u>: A challenging AI for both single and multiplayer matches with co-op play. Cross-platform multiplayer including <strong>LAN</strong>/internet. ONLINE play comes with an award and rating system.<br/></li><li><u>Play Modes</u>: In addition to regular skirmish matches, the game supports missions such as elimination, survival, <strong>capture the flag</strong>, defense and <strong>battle royale</strong>. Available in both single and multiplayer also are escort and rescue missions.<br/></li><li><u>Structures &amp; Troops</u>: Common troops for land, sea and air warfare is available to all factions. Specialized elements such as stealth, shields, <strong>EMP</strong> weapons, nukes, <strong>portals</strong>, orbital weapons, assimilator and other troops and structures provide for additional variety.<br/></li><li><u>Research</u>: A <strong>tech tree</strong> and research options enable to build specialized structures and troops. A <strong>Tech Snatcher</strong> can be used to steal enemy technology.<br/></li><li><u>Modding</u>: A map editor is included allowing for player-modded maps including player-modded campaigns. All elements including troops, structures, as well as graphics and sound effects, can be modded if desired.</li></ul><br/>Although some troops are shared, the game is trying not to be a generic RTS-games. There are <strong>faction-specific technologies</strong> each with their strengths and weaknesses.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u>GRA Technology</u>: gives access to <strong>stealth</strong> and cloaking. Included are cloaked agents and spies as well as bombers with EMP and nuclear weapons. Available also are snipers and heavy airlifts. Can build uranium fabricators.<br/></li><li><u>ELC Technology</u>: provides <strong>robots</strong>, <strong>airships</strong> and robo dogs. Available also are a mechanic and heavy airlift. Can build stationary EMP-field generators.<br/></li><li><u>IDB Technology</u>: provides <strong>hovertanks</strong>, <strong>drones</strong> including EMP-field drones and drones equipped with napalm weapons. Can build fusion generators for power.<br/></li><li><u>Mayan Technology</u>: consists of <strong>decoy</strong> capabilities. Included are hologram tanks, transformers, dogs and dolphins. Can build <strong>portals</strong>.<br/></li><li><u>Ancient Technology</u>: provides <strong>shields</strong>, EMP soldiers, assimilators and napalm tanks. Can build matter fabricators.</li></ul><br/><strong>Free vs Paid (DLC or in-game)</strong>: The free version includes unlimited access to over 12+ multiplayer scenarios and Chapter 01 of the single player campaign. Purchasing the DLC <strong>"All Maps &amp; Modding"</strong> grants full access to the game. It includes everything for single player including the story campaign, skirmishing against the AI, ONLINE multiplayer or LAN-play with friends and family.<br/><br/><strong>No DRM</strong>: There is no DRM in the game. You <strong>don't need to connected to the internet</strong> to play single player games or the campaign. You don't need to be logged in to play LAN games either. You don't need to login either for WAN games (locally hosted games over the internet), but you will have to work out your router settings and do the appropriate port-forwarding so your friends can connect from remote.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Stars And Time</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1677310/In_Stars_And_Time/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FZzFSRUBXEC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/discordbanner620.gif?t=1701180941"/></a><br/><br/><strong>What would you do if you were forced to relive your failures over and over again?</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam5_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> tells the story of Siffrin and their adventurer friends—a found family bound together by fate in order to end the tyrannical reign of an evil king. But as victory is just within the party’s grasp, a tragedy occurs, the clock resets, and <strong>they have to do it all again</strong>. <br/><br/>As Siffrin’s the only one who notices this loop, each new start wears away at his cheerful veneer, yet he keeps going in hopes he can end this temporal tragedy once and for all.<br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> is a <strong>time-looping RPG adventure</strong>. With each loop, Siffrin gains a new perspective on the world around them, opening up new solutions to puzzles and allowing them to make better choices in conversation. Equip memories as armor, pray to the Change God to improve your team’s capabilities each loop, and challenge deadly foes to Rock, Paper, Scissors as Siffrin seeks the truth.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam4_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Our Adventurers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Siffrin (he/they):</strong> Stressed, depressed, and under duress. (Don’t worry about it. They’re doing fine.) The punmaster protagonist of our neverending tale.<br/></li><li><strong>Mirabelle (she/her):</strong> A caring and nervous housemaiden mysteriously blessed by the god she so ardently follows.<br/></li><li><strong>Isabeau (he/him):</strong> Defender with a heart of gold. Cares dearly for his people and his friends.<br/></li><li><strong>Odile (she/her):</strong> The mature and nonsensical researcher studying…something. (No, she will not tell you what it is.)<br/></li><li><strong>Bonnie (they/them):</strong> Wait a minute, who brought this kid along???</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Save the world through the power of Rock, Paper, Scissors in <strong>strategic turn-based RPG</strong> combat encounters.<br/></li><li>Ignore the limits of time and space to <strong>fix your past mistakes</strong> by repeating the same two days over and over again.<br/></li><li>Equip the <strong>memories you have of your friends</strong> to make your party stronger in combat. <br/></li><li><strong>Watch the fate of this world unfold</strong> as you escape the twists and turns of this endless(???) loop.<br/></li><li>Eat <strong>samossas</strong> with your friends!<br/></li><li>Get heckled by a <strong>cheeky ethereal being of infinite starlight</strong>.<br/></li><li>Pray to a god for good luck in your travels. <strong>You’re gonna need it.</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam2_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/>If any of this interests you, you might also want to play the game’s initial prototype, <u><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1691420/START_AGAIN_a_prologue/" rel="" target="_blank">START AGAIN START AGAIN START AGAIN: A Prologue</a></u>. While you don’t need to play it to understand In Stars and Time, it’s fun to see the game’s roots.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 5 Tactica</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2254740/Persona_5_Tactica/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join the Phantom Thieves as they lead an uprising of the heart! Assemble a team of beloved heroes in a brand-new story in this thrilling combat adventure set in Persona’s iconic universe. The Persona 5 Tactica: Digital Deluxe Edition includes the following content:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Repaint Your Heart Challenge Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Weapon Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Picaro Summoning Pack + Raoul Persona</li></ul><br/><strong>Ignite your heart— An emotional uprising begins!</strong><br/><br/>After a strange incident, the Phantom Thieves wander into a bizarre realm where its citizens are living under tyrannical oppression. Surrounded by a military group named Legionnaires, they find themselves in grave danger until a mysterious revolutionary named Erina rescues them and offers an enticing deal in exchange for their help. What truth lies behind Erina and the deal she offers to the Phantom Thieves?<br/><br/>Persona 5 Tactica features an all-new story, the return of fan-favorite characters, and brand-new allies and foes. Join the group as they lead an emotional revolution in this thrilling combat adventure!<br/><br/><strong>An Emotional Revolution</strong><br/>Lead an uprising of the heart in a brand-new storyline that takes place in Persona’s iconic universe.<br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Squad</strong><br/>Assemble a team of beloved heroes to fight oppressive armies in thrilling turn-based combat.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Combat</strong><br/>Overthrow your enemies with powerful Personas, an assortment of weapons, and wipe them out with style!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Saga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1320140/Small_Saga/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Venture below the streets of London, and you will find the medieval kingdom of rats, mice, moles, squirrels, and shrews known as Rodentia.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G8.gif?t=1701437888"><br/><br/>If the rodents have a cardinal law, it is this: never attack a god. But Verm never had much respect for the rule of law. His tail was stolen by the Yellow God of Death, and now the mouse will have to fight all manner of beasts and titans on his quest to get it back.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G5.gif?t=1701437888"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G1.gif?t=1701437888"><br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Team up with a colorful cast of misfit rodents.<br/></li><li>Encounter awe-inspiring titans. Clash with a swashbuckling water vole, a pious lab rabbit, a poetry-spewing kraken, and many more.<br/></li><li>Meet the hideous vermin who run society, then overthrow them.<br/></li><li>Brandish your tiny weapons in strategic, turn-based combat. <br/></li><li>There is no grinding. Small Saga is a tightly-focused and boss-oriented adventure.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero's Adventure: Road to Passion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1948980/Heros_Adventure_Road_to_Passion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FFPnrtuXddA" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/JOIN_OUR_DISCORD.png?t=1700823813"/></a><br/><br/>In <i>Hero's Adventure:Road to Passion</i>, you commence your journey as an underdog in the tumultuous Jianghu - a vibrant world teeming with martial artists - and are met with a wide array of choices as you navigate your heroic saga. Whether it’s training under a battle-hardened warrior to become a master of martial arts, or following Taoist rituals to reach self-enlightenment, you’re the hero, and this is your adventure.<br/><br/><br/>Play 1.0 Now!<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>[Unexpected Encounters Await]</strong><br/><br/>Throughout your journey, you will run into scripted and unexpected encounters. Perhaps you'll cross paths with an ambitious lieutenant amidst a power struggle at a humble inn, or you’ll run into a retired kung fu master in a nameless village. These will be the experiences you will learn to expect in the ever-changing Jianghu.<br/><br/>Beware, each encounter might associate and change your relationship with the 30+ factions involved in the power struggle in this chaotic Martial World. And remember: every choice you make, every person you befriend (or offend), and every faction you engage will leave a mark.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/Sparring.gif?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[Become the Master of Martial Arts]</strong><br/><br/>Whether you're decoding ancient techniques off a forgotten scroll, or prefer training with a battle-hardened warrior, there’s no correct solution for mastering martial arts. Choose from a variety of weapon types and explore 300+ martial arts skills, the Jianghu will be yours to conquer.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/High-level_Martial_Arts.gif?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[Explore a Living, Breathing World]</strong><br/><br/>In this Wuxia simulator, you'll get to explore 80 cities and villages that bring wuxia to life. Witness how villagers go about their daily routines, and experience the rhythms of ancient Chinese cities.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/Nameless_Village.gif?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[Craft Your Narrative]</strong><br/><br/>To provide an experience where you can embody your own martial spirit, Hero’s Adventure has over 10 distinct endings. Whether you choose to be a noble swordsman, a guardian of the nation, or an agent of chaos, you'll find an ending that aligns with your chosen path in Hero's Adventure. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/武林霸主_1_.png?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[New features that are added in v1.0:]</strong><br/>- New bondable female characters, boosting the total number to 18<br/>- A Homestead system to better manage your recruited characters, inherit your Martial Art and weapons to another playthrough<br/>- 200+ new narrative encounters, and adjusted 400+ of the existing encounters<br/>- New Jianghu Event system ensures your adventure doesn’t end prematurely with major events<br/>- Added duel option against high-rank NPCs for a test of mettle.<br/>- Enhanced customization and upgrades for team characters.<br/>- Early supporters will discover a special accessory as a token of gratitude.<br/>- Controller and steam deck support.<br/>- Steam Workshop 2.0</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Roads: Tournament</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1619570/Death_Roads_Tournament/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1619570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for a high-octane showdown in "Death Roads: Tournament," where <strong>vehicular combat, strategic card-play, and turn-based thrills collide</strong>. Dive headfirst into a frenzied competition where your destiny hangs in the balance. To secure the ultimate prize, you must annihilate all opposition in your path. There's no room for failure – it's victory or a fresh start!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1619570/extras/Pick_from_many_drivers,_cars_and_cards_ANG.png?t=1701179382"><br/>Before unleashing mayhem, handpick your driver and their mean machine, armed with an initial set of cards. Then, select a sponsor who will determine your starting point on the game map – choose wisely because there's no turning back.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1619570/extras/Shoot_bash_and_dodge_to_win_ANG.png?t=1701179382"><br/>The cards aren't just for blasting your rivals – use them to outmaneuver obstacles, secure superior positions, or simply crash head-on into your opponents for maximum impact.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1619570/extras/1_gif.gif?t=1701179382"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1619570/extras/High_risk_high_reward_ANG.png?t=1701179382"><br/>Remember to shift gears while on the road – higher gears mean access to more powerful cards, but with greater risk during skids. Master this mechanic and skid your way to triumph.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1619570/extras/Change_your_deck_to_upgrade_the_car_ANG.png?t=1701179382"><br/>Gather car parts from fallen foes and pimp your vehicle with various weapons, engines, and wheels. Experiment with different configurations to take your rivals by surprise and build formidable card combinations.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1619570/extras/3_gif.gif?t=1701179382"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1619570/extras/Every_race_is_deadly_and_unique_Features_ANG.png?t=1701179382"><br/>Every skirmish brings you closer to victory, but beware – "Death Roads" is a race where defeat lurks around every corner. If you falter, be prepared to restart your journey. Don't fret, though, as your hard-earned unlocks remain in your arsenal!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1619570/extras/FEATURES_ANG.png?t=1701179382"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Master</strong> turn-based battles with road events.<br/></li><li><strong>Unlock</strong> various cars and characters with special weapons.<br/></li><li><strong>Build</strong> card decks based on swapping around car parts.<br/></li><li><strong>Progress</strong> across a nonlinear world map.<br/></li><li><strong>Vibe</strong> with stylized graphics reflecting a thrilling race.</li></ul><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FpQ6vqqGb2V" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1619570/extras/discord.png?t=1701179382"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header_alt_assets_2.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astral Ascent</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1280930/Astral_Ascent/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Astral Ascent is a 2D platformer rogue-lite game set in a modern fantasy world. As one of 4 Heroes with very different personalities, you must escape from <i>the Garden</i>, an astral prison guarded by 12 powerful and vicious bosses, the Zodiacs.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CREATE YOUR OWN PLAYSTYLE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Gif_playstyle.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Unlock dozens of unique spells for your 4 distinct characters. Optimize your own build or try out new ones to take down 12 powerful bosses. Get stronger with time to match up with your foes. Each run will test your skills and your reactivity.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TWELVE ALMIGHTY BOSSES TO FACE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Zodiacs.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The Zodiacs are 12 experienced guardians dispatched over 4 gorgeous worlds. They’ll bring to the battlefield unique attacks, abilities, and patterns, backstories to uncover, and reasons to be fighting you. Get yourself warned!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>4 PLAYABLE CHARACTERS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/4_Character_banniere_steam7.png?t=1700851162"><br/><i>Unique characters. Unique weapons. Unique ways to play.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Ayla:</strong> The sole survivor of her guild of assassins, she uses her twin daggers to eliminate her enemies before they can react. Her speed and proficiency are unmatched.<br/></li><li><strong>Kiran:</strong> This orphan learned life the hard way. He uses his strength to deliver attacks powerful enough to create shockwaves. Brutal.<br/></li><li><strong>Calie:</strong> This talented sculptor wants her freedom back. She will use her magical gemstones to pierce enemy defenses and shred them to bits. She is unforgiving.<br/></li><li><strong>Octave:</strong> Trained by a powerful witch, this young fighter summons ethereal guns to attack his foes. When needed, he can conjure bigger weapons as well. Lethal in all cases.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A STORY THAT OPENS UP, ONE PIECE AT A TIME</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/ZimZim2.png?t=1700851162"><br/>Astral Ascent is a rogue-lite infused with narration. Replayability is part of our story which will be unraveled piece by piece. As you get stronger, you will discover more about the characters, their motivations, and the secrets of the world they’re trapped in.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>LOCAL CO-OP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Coop.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The weight of destiny is too heavy to carry by yourself? Don’t worry and bring a friend to play in our <strong>two-player co-op</strong> mode. Fight and crush your enemies together in local co-op or online using the <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/remoteplay?snr=1_614_615__1601" rel="" target="_blank"><strong>Steam's Remote Play Together</strong></a> feature.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A VAST, COLORFUL FANTASY WORLD WAITING TO BE EXPLORED</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Panning.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Dash across gigantic landscapes. Explore original and hand-crafted areas. Discover the world created by our artists, with a gorgeous art and frame-by-frame animation.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirate Fighting Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186400/Pirate_Fighting_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pirate Fighting Simulator is a free multiplayer PVP game developed in Unreal Engine 5 in which you fight other players using typical pirate weaponry. There are also cosmetics that you can unlock, these cosmetics can be either hats, weapon skins or in the form of a title that sits underneath your username. The game also includes emotes so you can absolutely boogie down silly style after destroying an enemy gamer. There are also two gamemodes one being TDM (Team Death Match)) and the second being FFA (Free For All).						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1699642767"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1700646226"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons 4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1643310/Dungeons_4/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Once upon a time in a realm far, far away, everything was lush and green. The unicorns mingled among the trees and the elves and humans lived peacefully in harmony with their surroundings. Yet somewhere at the edge of a clearing half-hidden among the trees, obscured by a rising veil of fog in the hazy half-darkness of a weather-beaten hut, a shape huddles over a large and ominously glowing crystal ball. A mumbling voice sings ancient formulae, urging the swirling glowing mists inside the crystal to part and give an insight into the future.<br/><br/>“All is in flux, nothing seems certain. Come, oh vagaries of space and time, separate the veil and show us what is yet to come”, the voice grumbles with the hint of an eye faintly reflecting the glow in front of its hood. The shape’s audience, only barely visible in the dim light, leans in closer and listens intently. “Time ebbs and flows, forming pools and wrinkles… but when the mists part only vague images rise from beyond the veil. Shhhh—don’t come too close, you don’t want to disturb my delicate magical weavings do you?” The shape, still bent over the orb, mutters and shoos the other back a bit more into the shadows. “Ah, now it seems to be clearing a little. I can see… something… several somethings, hints of voices echoing in the haze. A baby, something happening on Hill Doom and the coming together of the Council of Snots – what could all this mean?”<br/><br/>In a flash, the light reflected in the eye turns red and a distant evil laughter echoes through the woods. Stay tuned for the return of the Soothsaying Evil!</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/dungeons-4.gif?t=1701355158"><br/><br/>The Absolute Evil and its trusted *cough* servant, the Dark Elf Thalya, return in <strong>Dungeons 4</strong> after the events of its fabulous predecessor to bring about their triumph over the forces of good once more.<br/><br/><strong>Build a cozy and comfortable Dungeon</strong> to suit your creatures’ needs and rule over them, then send them out into the Overworld to kindly remind the good people living there that the Absolute Evil rules over their lands. <strong>Gather your Evilness</strong> in new and dynamic ways <strong>and unleash it upon</strong> the lush green forests and plains of <strong>the Overworld</strong> to turn them over to the dark side. But make sure that <strong>your Dungeon is well-secured</strong> by traps and defended by your creatures, for those pesky Overworlders won’t just twiddle their thumbs while you <strong>turn their land into the Absolute Evil’s most pleasurable holiday paradise</strong>.<br/><br/>But what is that noise? <i>“Gold, gold, gold and gems, gold and gems and gold!”</i> The ancient song echoes throughout the underworld, accompanied by the clanging steel of hammers and axes. <strong>The Dwarves have arrived</strong> to claim their share of the abundant resources and together with the Elves and Humans of the Overworld, they send out their raiding parties to find the Dungeon’s heart.<br/><br/>Dungeons 4 keeps the spirit of its predecessor, but everything is now <strong>bigger, better, and with even more dynamic Evilness™</strong>.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-1_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Everything is better with Dwarves™:</strong> The Dwarves have arrived to build their underground strongholds and the hardy little fellows (although they don’t like being called that) compete with the Ever-Expanding Evil for space and resources.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-2_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>It makes your Dungeon great again:</strong> Dungeons are up to four times larger than before and there are many more creatures who wait for the All-Commanding Evil’s orders to conquer the Overworld. Now the time has come for massive armies and truly sprawling dungeons!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-3_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Ripe for the taking:</strong> The Overworld is bigger than ever before. Gain Evilness by beating Mini Bosses like the obsessively harmonious Unicorn and use it to transform the Overworld into stunning biomes of pure evil.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-4_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>New and shiny:</strong> An ability-based Perk system for Thalya, the Absolute Evil’s trusted *cough* and most loyal subordinate, grants her impressive new powers. The Absolute Evil can now enjoy taking over the world, governing the creatures and slapping subordinates even more with the customizable Evil Hand.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-5_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Minions, everywhere:</strong> The Horde, the Undead and the Demons wait to do the Absolute Evil’s bidding, with more creatures than ever eagerly following the gesturing Evil’s orders, and Snots will play a much more prominent role this time.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-6_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Many ways to tell the story:</strong> A long campaign, narrated by the beloved English Narrator from previous titles, as well as several skirmish maps all to challenge your rule as the Absolute Evil.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-7_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Change the world:</strong> Spread your Evilness across the Overworld to bring lush and green environments over to the dark side, now shining even more vibrantly and beautifully evil as you spread your evilness across many new biomes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-8_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Work together, slay together:</strong> 2-player co-op multiplayer with both players managing one Dungeon together. All maps from the skirmish mode and the campaign are playable in co-op.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobalt Core</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2179850/Cobalt_Core/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_1.gif?t=1700087396"><br/><br/>Cobalt Core is a sci-fi roguelike deckbuilder with a unique single-axis combat system that will throw you for a loop. Many loops! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_2.gif?t=1700087396"><br/><br/>Give orders to your crew by playing cards: Will you <strong>raise shields</strong> to protect your ship, <strong>dodge</strong> incoming missiles and cannon fire to avoid damage outright, or <strong>strike</strong> preemptively to disable your enemy’s weapons? Outmaneuver your foes to stay just ahead of impending calamity, and reach the Cobalt Core!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/characters.png?t=1700087396"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fresh new spin on tactics –</strong>  dodge attacks and target weak points in this unique single-axis take on tactics combat. Outwit the enemy in a high stakes game of cat and mouse!<br/></li><li><strong>Customize your deck –</strong> hundreds of cards and split upgrade paths means no two runs will be the same. Find that perfect combo that brings your deck from powerful to overpowered.<br/></li><li><strong>Get to know your crew –</strong> each character comes with a completely unique playstyle and their own personal story. Bring 3 along, mix and match their decks, and see how these little goobers get along with each other.<br/></li><li><strong>Tons of replayability –</strong>  hundreds of different character+ship combinations before you even hit “start run”. Crank up the difficulty and really test your skills!<br/></li><li><strong>Forward momentum –</strong> untangle a narrative and unlock more playstyles as you go. Is there any escape from this time loop?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/grandma_cookies.gif?t=1700087396"><br/><br/>By the makers of <i>Sunshine Heavy Industries</i>, recipient of IGF's <strong>Honorable Mention for Excellence in Design 2022</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VDSC: VoltIsland</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2340910/VDSC_VoltIsland/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2340910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Shoot your way to the top.<br>
<br>
An Island, a bunch of dragons and guns. Volt Inu’s Sailor Club invites you to the greatest battle of your life. Fight other players for Honor, Wealth and Power. Land in strategic locations, loot weapons and supplies to survive the battlegrounds and be the last to be victorious.<br>
<br>
As a player you have access to 3 different weapons, a jetpack and various grenades. The goal is to be the last in the area and fight the other players.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Subtrahend</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2629200/Project_Subtrahend/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2629200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You’ve been invited to join Project Subtrahend. What could possibly go wrong?<br/><br/>…As it turns out, quite a lot! <br/><br/>In this thought-provoking choose-your-own-adventure visual novel, you’ll have the chance to get to know the stories, pasts, and personalities of nine unique characters after you've all been invited to help with an innocent social experiment. Explore the deep interpersonal relationships between them, learn about the politics of their world, and explore what it means to be human.<br/><br/>When things start going awry, and when the true intentions of the experiment are revealed, your choices will determine the possible endings you can get. It’s up to you who makes it out alive...<br/><br/>With a lore-filled world, entertaining gameplay, secret endings, rewards for achievements, bonus scenes, and an hour of playtime in each route, you won’t be getting bored anytime soon as you discover everything Project Subtrahend has to offer!<br/><br/><strong>Make impactful choices </strong><br/>When the time comes, you choose how to escape and who survives.<br/><br/><strong>Befriend (or be-enemy) nine vastly different characters. </strong><br/>Get to know their diverse life experiences, perspectives, and relationships.<br/><br/><strong>Learn about Sicknessism</strong><br/>A new religion has emerged in New Evenfall; you have the chance to learn about it, and maybe even join in ;)<br/><br/><strong>Earn extra content</strong><br/>Unlock achievements to fill out each character’s scrapbook and unlock bonus post-game scenes with each character!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hazeron Starship</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2239520/Hazeron_Starship/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2239520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Explore and colonize a vast universe. Twenty one galaxies filled with countless stars and planets and other things await your discovery.<br>
<br>
Start as an indigenous person on an undeveloped world. Hunt for food. Survive wild animals. Build a home.<br>
<br>
Discover natural resources. Build mines and wells to gather resources from the land.<br>
<br>
Establish an empire to govern your work.<br/>
<br/>
Found a city to manage its buildings. Build more buildings to manufacture things from natural resources and other things.<br/>
<br/>
Advance your civilization. Make space rockets to explore space. Venture out into your home solar system.<br/>
<br/>
Discover exotic natural resources in dangerous environments on other worlds. Build cities there to harvest resources and send them to factories on the home world.<br/>
<br/>
Travel directly to any star in the sky using a space rocket, a daunting task.<br/>
<br/>
Develop technology to make starships that can travel instantly through wormholes to other solar systems. Walk aboard them. Operate their controls. Command a crew of NPCs. Lift off. Fly up through the atmosphere to outer space. Land on other worlds, anywhere, not at designated places.<br/>
<br/>
Discover natural resources on other worlds, on land, beneath seas, in rings like those of Saturn, in coronas of stars, and in seas of liquefied gases on giant worlds like Jupiter.<br/>
<br/>
Design unique spacecraft and buildings with the built-in 3D modeler. Make them function, with operable doors, landing gear, lights, turbo lifts, transporters, engines, shields, weapons, and more.  Share your designs with others in the Steam Workshop. <br/>
<br/>
Not everyone is a 3D modeler; it is not easy. The Steam Workshop offers a growing assortment of fantastic spacecraft and buildings designed by people with a gift for 3D modeling. Their work is there for you to enjoy.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOFI Katana</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1723680/LOFI_Katana/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1723680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1723680/extras/Your_own_world.png?t=1701456917"><br/><br/><strong>Play the beats you usually study/relax to! 📚</strong><br/>LOFI Katana is a VR rhythm game with a unique atmosphere inspired by everyone’s favourite late night playlists.<br/>Leave your room and head to the highest rooftop. Find your musical sanctuary away from the city noise. Hit the shurikens with your katana and wave your fan to the rhythm of the music. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1723680/extras/lofika_map.gif?t=1701456917"><h2 class="bb_tag">Don’t stop the music!</h2>After mastering all the songs in the game, generate your own gameplay based on your favourite music. LOFI Katana uses a sophisticated procedural system that analyses the song and creates custom levels matching the rhythm and beat of any track.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>Enjoy your music with simple but challenging sequences that blend dance and combat:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>In Classic mode, flip your fan to match the incoming ones, and wield a katana in your other hand to slice the flying shurikens coming towards you. <br/></li><li>Select your difficulty level, from a calm and relaxing routine to a more challenging and energetic session.<br/></li><li>Try out the alternative modes: “Only Fans” and “Only Katanas” for a new take on the Classic gameplay.<br/></li><li><strong>LIV integration</strong> available for streamers and influencers who like to dance and move along with their favourite music!</li></ul><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1723680/extras/lofika_LIV.gif?t=1701456917"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1723680/extras/immerse_yourself.png?t=1701456917"><br/>The light and the environment around you change procedurally with the music. Feel free to take some time to relax and enjoy the cosy vibes.<br/>Experience the atmosphere around you reacting to your actions and immerse yourself in the flow of your favourite tracks.<br/>To integrate your music, you will simply need to drag your MP3 or WAV files into the /Tracks folder of the game. Our Algorithm itself will take care of creating a deterministic gameplay from the song and generating a level from the parameters you have chosen.<br/><br/>If you are looking for an escape to a relaxing world, this is the perfect game for you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1723680/extras/LOFI_KATANA_bout_de_page.png?t=1701456917"><br/><br/>Music Trailer: Forest Shrine by Kerusu						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Perplexing Orb: Bounce N' Roll</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2679130/The_Perplexing_Orb_Bounce_N_Roll/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2679130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Perplexing Orb returns in a brand new entry packed with new features! New art style, new levels, and new game play mechanics!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2679130/extras/Bounce.gif?t=1701456532"><br/><br/>In this third entry to The Perplexing Orb franchise, you have the ability to bounce your way through all new challenges!<br/><br/>The game contains <strong>40 all new story stages</strong> all designed around distance, height, and the ability to jump!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2679130/extras/CityPixel.gif?t=1701456532"><br/><br/>The game features an all new retro inspired art style with different graphical options. You can either play the game in crisp full HD or with a pixel filter to make the low poly art match closer to the PS1 era aesthetic! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2679130/extras/GraphicOptions1.png?t=1701456532"><br/><br/><strong>INSANE Challenge Mode Levels</strong> make a return in this entry! Once you conquer the main story stages, brace yourself for 8 incredibly difficult stages to test your resolve!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2679130/extras/InsaneChallenges.gif?t=1701456532"><br/><br/>Stage Designs are filled with all sorts of new obstacles and tools like cracking ice, elevators, moving platforms and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2679130/extras/Elevator1.gif?t=1701456532"><br/><br/><strong>ALL NEW TIME TRIAL MODE.</strong><br/>Race for gold medal times OR test yourself against incredibly difficult dev times in the brand new time trial mode!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2679130/extras/TimeTrials.gif?t=1701456532"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hexle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2672770/Hexle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Hexle is a small number-guessing puzzle game based on Sudoku! Each number can only appear once per line and per 4x4 square, but also binary restrictions apply inside of each square, limiting the numbers that can be placed on any one tile.<br>
<br>
Learn Hexle's rules with the game's introduction and then go forth completing generated puzzles in various difficulties. Come back every day to solve the daily challenges or to tackle the weekly 16x16 megaboards! As you complete puzzle grids you will unlock new color palettes to change the mood of the game! (light and dark palettes are available from the start)<br>
<br>
You can stop playing at any time and continue your puzzle later. There is one save slot per difficulty which you may continue or reset at any time. The game plays entirely with the mouse.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShadowStorm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2673750/ShadowStorm/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Explore a dystopian future where chaos reigns, and the intensity of combat reaches unparalleled heights. Get ready to experience the pure adrenaline of our virtual reality FPS. Boldness and strategy make the difference on the battlefield!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/>🎮 Captivating Solo Experience: Embark on solo missions to face teams of strategically moving bots. ShadowStorm offers an immersive solo experience that allows you to immerse yourself in competitive and captivating gameplay.<br/><br/>🌌 Frantic Multiplayer: Take on the challenge in frenetic multiplayer matches where you can battle against up to 16 players. Gather your friends to form teams or go solo to triumph over your opponents.<br/><br/>🤖 Battle Intelligent Bots: If you prefer to hone your skills before challenging other players, ShadowStorm provides the opportunity to fight against intelligent AI bots. Perfect for training or thrilling solo matches.<br/><br/>🔫 Advanced Arsenal: Choose from advanced weapons that match your playstyle and unleash technological power on the battlefield.<br/><br/>🏆 Free for All and Team Death Match Modes: Face up to 16 players in free-for-all battles, where only the strongest survive, or join a team and collaborate for victory in epic matches. Four teams can compete simultaneously. Cooperation and fierce competition are at the heart of the action.<br/><br/>🕹️ Ergonomic Controls: Enjoy a seamless virtual reality gaming experience with intuitive controls and a user-friendly interface. ShadowStorm is designed to allow you to focus on the action, not the controls.<br/><br/>Join us in ShadowStorm and get ready for an epic adventure in a future where only the most strategic and daring actions will lead you to victory. Whether you prefer solo play, challenging friends in multiplayer, or honing your skills against bots, ShadowStorm offers an unforgettable experience.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirates of Rectangular</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2470420/Pirates_of_Rectangular/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2470420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>"Shapes are what our world is made of"</i><br/><br/>The Shape Alliance is seeking brave sailors to combat the rebellious Pirates of Rectangular. <br/>Can you restore order to the geometric world and end the conflict?<h2 class="bb_tag">Navigate Your Ship!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2470420/extras/Navigate.gif?t=1701453755"><br/><br/>A true captain always has the ship under control! <br/>Dodge obstacles and skillfully navigate around your enemies.<h2 class="bb_tag">Utilize Your Weapons!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2470420/extras/Shot.gif?t=1701453755"><br/><br/>Use the available cannons and rockets to fight against the pirates. <br/>Sometimes, it takes more than just words for others to understand you.<h2 class="bb_tag">Don't Let Them Board!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2470420/extras/Damage.gif?t=1701453755"><br/><br/>Cannonballs are scarce for the pirates, <br/>so they'll try to ram your ship and board it!<h2 class="bb_tag">Keep an Eye on Your Surroundings!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2470420/extras/Oil.gif?t=1701453755"><br/><br/>There are things you'd better avoid! <br/>That includes leaking oil barrels that restrict your ship's movement.<br/><br/><br/><strong><i>What are you waiting for? Show us who the one true captain is! <br/>Join the fight against the Rectangulars and lead the Shape Alliance to victory!</i></strong> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>William and Sly: Classic Collection</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684790/William_and_Sly_Classic_Collection/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>William and Sly</strong> is a classic pair of platforming adventure Flash games. Play as the agile fox, Sly, assisting your closest friend William. These non-linear adventures are perfect for when you want to curl up on a rainy afternoon to explore gorgeous landscapes, take in hand-painted visuals and bask in it's meditative soundtrack. The gameplay emphasis ease of movement, with sleek platforming, and no fall damage.<h2 class="bb_tag">William and Sly</h2>In our introduction to this world, William's fantastic teleportation system has been deactivated, and it is up to Sly to fix it. Activate the stones, play around with mysterious fairyflies, and gather up mushrooms. The heart of the game is in exploration, venturing beyond the central task, and seeing what intriguing discoveries can be made in every corner of this sprawling landscape.<h2 class="bb_tag">William and Sly 2</h2>The troublesome gnomes have stolen and scattered the pages of William's journal! Alongside this main quest, you will discover shrines that offer up side quests and new abilities. Building off the serene, cozy gameplay of the original game, William and Sly 2 offers light puzzles to solve and more narrative touches to build up this world. But worry not, there are still plenty of mushrooms to munch and delightful secrets to uncover.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Build Your Igloo</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2416760/How_To_Build_Your_Igloo/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2416760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">SHARPEN YOUR SKATES...</h2><br/>Help the adventurous polar explorer Siku build his new, snowy home in the middle of the a-maze-ing Puzzle Pole! Guide him through more than 200 levels and grab the snow brick in each one to make the perfect igloo!<h2 class="bb_tag">... AND SHARPEN YOUR BRAIN!</h2><strong>How To Build Your Igloo</strong> takes a classic puzzle mechanic - the <i>slide forward until you can't</i> mechanic, as seen in many puzzle and adventure games - and makes it the core of a full puzzle game of its own!<h2 class="bb_tag">THE GAME FEATURES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>A simple core mechanic:</strong> you slide until you hit a wall, or something else. Easy, right?<br/></li><li> <strong>Five additional variants</strong> expanding the core mechanic from basic, labyrinthine levels to more complex grid-based logic puzzles with a touch of Sokoban.<br/></li><li> <strong>250 handmade levels,</strong> carefully crafted with pencil and paper!<br/></li><li> <strong>A puzzly overworld!</strong> Explore the Puzzle Pole, solve levels and clear the way towards your igloo. A handy map view is there to help you if you get lost.<br/></li><li> <strong>Fun for everyone!</strong> With tutorial levels, a gentle difficulty curve and multiple puzzles available in the main areas, the game can be tackled from puzzle lovers of every kind. Stuck on a level? Try another one in the area, or try moving to a different area!<br/></li><li> <strong>Fun for puzzle experts!</strong> Main levels are a piece of cake for you? The Puzzle Pole is worth its name... try reaching secondary, hard-to-reach areas to find more challenging puzzles!<br/></li><li> <strong>Full controller support</strong></li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GAME <u>DOESN'T</u> FEATURE:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Time trials.</strong> No need to rush, it's just you and the puzzles.<br/></li><li><strong>Multiplayer.</strong> But you can still ask your friends for help.<br/></li><li><strong>Actual igloo building.</strong> That feature will come in the future. A DISTANT future. Maybe.<br/></li><li><strong>Skins.</strong> Sorry, Fortnite fans.</li></ul><br/>What are you still doing here, reading? Go fasten your ice skates and launch yourself into the adventure!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Block Breakin' Logic Downstacker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2642980/Block_Breakin_Logic_Downstacker/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2642980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Block Breakin' Logic Downstacker is a puzzle game where you reveal a beautiful image hidden behind the stack of blocks using block breaking logic.<h2 class="bb_tag">IN THE ZONE</h2><br/>Smash those blocks non-stop and be amazed seeing the image slowly being revealed in real-time as the pile shrinks. A relaxing experience that keeps you totally engrossed. Your brain's gonna be like, "Just one more section, please!"<h2 class="bb_tag">AT YOUR PACE</h2>The interface was carefully designed to give you total freedom. Pick which part of the image to uncover, how many waves of blocks to bust, and how many will pop up from the bottom. Do not flood yourself!<h2 class="bb_tag">MAKE IT YOUR GAME</h2>Use your own images as stages! Hang out with your favorite pics or the curated list of +30 preloaded images as long as you like.<h2 class="bb_tag">EXTRA FEATURES</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Preview strip - </strong> Your upcoming piece is always at eye level. Less eye travelling and more focus.<br/></li><li><strong>Undo key - </strong>Made a mistake? No problem! Less frustration, more fun.<br/></li><li><strong>No Game Over -</strong> Checkpoints make sure you won't lose your progress.<br/></li><li><strong>Unlock Edit mode - </strong> after completing the stage.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1701456665"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1701456665"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1701456665"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannon Fotter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2485340/Cannon_Fotter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>(Please note that we are a two person indie team and this is a short (2-3.5 hour) game. With that out of the way...) </i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485340/extras/New_screenshot_13_inline.png?t=1701450046"><br/><br/> <h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Shoot yourself out of cannons, and <strong>destroy stuff in VR</strong>! Take down structures in creative and explosive ways.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Over 50 levels, and secret areas</strong>, present new challenges and puzzles, allowing you to strategize and plan your destructive path. <br/><br/></li><li><strong>Splinter wood, and  shatter rock</strong>... or whatever gets in your way! Create <strong>magnificent chaos</strong> by experimenting with different angles, velocities, and <strong>explosives</strong> to obliterate everything in your way!<br/><br/></li><li>Perfect your skills and <strong>earn the high score</strong> by using the fewest shots possible to cause the most destruction! </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485340/extras/New_screenshot_20_inline.png?t=1701450046"><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2><br/>You're one of a few surviving woodland Otters, fighting to take back your home from an invading army of adorable but absolutely <i>evil</i> Beavers. It's time for revenge!<br/><br/>Get ready to embark on an adrenaline-pumping, physics shaking adventure like no other with Cannon Fotter, the <strong>ultimate VR tower destruction game</strong>! Made by a two person team, Cannon Fotter makes you the master of demolition, armed with nothing but your courage, a powerful cannon, and your body.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485340/extras/ezgif-3-14a1f14ff3.gif?t=1701450046"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goofy Gorillas</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2627570/Goofy_Gorillas/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2627570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Goofy Gorillas, the largest (and greatest) nostalgia-driven virtual play centre!<br/><br/>Do you want to play Hide and Seek with your friends? Maybe you'd want to play Hide and Seek with dodgeballs, inflatable hammers and boxing gloves to raise the stakes a little more? Why not turn your friends into enemies in a free-for-all battle with all of the items mentioned? You and your friends can partake in these activities while also earning GP (Goofy Points). Levels are gained through earning GP, which can then be used to unlock unique cosmetic items to show off while you're winning in your game mode of choice!<br/><br/>If you just want to chill without the fear of being chased or you don't feel like turning your friends into enemies just yet, we have you covered! Goofy Gorillas prioritizes creating a social hub before any game mode begins, so you're able to do whatever you want to do - with small mini-games that can be played at any time too! <br/><br/>Goofy Gorillas is fitted with a football (soccer) pitch with a working score counter hidden within the play area, a bowling alley with two lanes also hidden within the play area, 2 large ball pits with large slides and there are some basketball hoops scattered around the entire venue - some easier to dunk than others! We hope there is something here for everyone!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>GAMEMODES</strong></h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Hide &amp; Seek</h2><br/>The classic game that everyone knows so well. Seekers must find all of the Hiders in the given time, and every round, both teams swap sides! Sounds simple, right? Well in Goofy Gorillas, we take it to the next level! Featuring an economy just for this gamemode, Hiders and Seeker have access to a shop with items and utility that will help them defend themselves as a Hider, or help catching the Hiders in style as a Seeker. <br/><br/>You want to make the Seekers slip on a banana peel? You can totally do that! <br/><br/>You want to hit the Hiders with an inflatable hammer? We highly encourage you to do that!<h2 class="bb_tag">Infector</h2><br/>Infector is another classic game. It plays just like Hide &amp; Seek, just without the economy. One player is chosen as the Infector, and by catching the Runners, they too will become an Infector. Once everyone has been caught, the Infector team will win... or lose if there's just a single player still standing. The first player that gets caught will be the Infector in the next round.<br/><br/>Be careful who you trust in this gamemode; once your "friend" has been caught, they will not be your friend anymore!<h2 class="bb_tag">Free For All</h2><br/>The standard of any multiplayer game. This is the perfect gamemode for those who want to mindlessly cause chaos with friends! Just spawn in with an item, get stuck in the brawl and come out on top, or just respawn with another item if you weren't successful! The first player to reach the score limit wins, or if no one reaches that, then the time limit will decide who becomes victorious!<br/><br/><br/>With all of these activities included, we hope you enjoy your time here at Goofy Gorillas!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Loop</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693330/Time_Loop/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Time Loop is a 2D platformer with hardcore elements, dynamic gameplay and nice graphics. In this game you need to pass a variety of levels and avoid enemies.<br>
This is a linear and very interesting platformer in which you will have to go through a variety of levels and try to avoid enemies.With each new level you will come across more enemies and various dangers. Think over your every step, avoid the trap and do everything that will help you successfully complete your task.After all, if you make a mistake, you will have to start over!<br>
<br>
KEY FEATURES:<br>
<br>
- Hardcore gameplay<br>
- Nice graphics<br/>
- Relaxing soundtrack<br/>
- An unforgettable experience						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreamwalker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2297600/Dreamwalker/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2297600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A visual novel about a man who discovers the existence of another dimension hidden in dreams.<br/><br/>Explore and learn the rules of a new reality, meet fellow dreamwalkers and solve the mystery of a disaster in the past, while simultaneously avoiding getting fired from your day job as a software designer. Make decisions, build relationships and strive to reach the best ending!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>An atmospheric and gripping storyline<br/></li><li>Player choices affect how the story develops<br/></li><li>Branching paths<br/></li><li>Built-in relationship system tracks what people think of you<br/></li><li>Beautiful character art<br/></li><li>A single playthrough time of a few hours</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Meet the Dreamwalkers</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2297600/extras/character_sonya_wide.png?t=1701449957"><br/><br/>⭐ A self-employed artist, <strong>Sonya</strong> is a young woman who will soon become an integral part of your adventures into the world between, a hidden dimension located between dreams and reality. She is creative and confident, but quickly you'll learn that she seems to be harbouring a secret of some kind. What is it she's not telling you? Will you remain acquaintances, become friends or perhaps even something more? The choices are yours to make.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2297600/extras/character_henry_wide.png?t=1701449957"><br/><br/>⭐ A knowledgeable and intelligent man, <strong>Henry</strong> and Sonya have known each other since childhood. Also a Dreamwalker, Henry has a tragic past, of which he doesn't much enjoy talking about. These past events have molded him into someone very serious and formal, and he rarely ever smiles - but a researcher and a coordinator, Henry is nevertheless someone you'll certainly want as an ally.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2297600/extras/character_yukiko_wide.png?t=1701449957"><br/><br/>⭐ Energetic, friendly and outgoing - anywhere else <strong>Yukiko</strong> might seem like a normal teenager, but in the world between it's immediately apparent that she's anything but. For some reason, the world doesn't seem to react to her the same way it does to anyone else. What is the mystery behind this young girl?<h2 class="bb_tag">Make the story yours</h2><br/>These are just a few of the people you'll meet in Dreamwalker. Experience the story yourself, coming in 2023.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Walking Dead: Destinies</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2192790/The_Walking_Dead_Destinies/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2192790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Begin your journey as Rick Grimes, waking alone in a hospital surrounded by the dead. Assemble allies and fight your way through the walker apocalypse across iconic locations from The Walking Dead, including Atlanta, the Greene family farm, the prison, and Woodbury. In crucial choice-driven moments, you’ll forever shape the destiny of your team of characters from the series. Heroes and villains, living and dead – it’s up to you to decide whether to stay the course of history or forge your own path through the world of AMC’s The Walking Dead.<br>
<br>
• Shatter Fate: Alter the story of AMC’s The Walking Dead by weaving your own path through the series’ events. Save the villain, kill the hero… and live with the consequences.<br>
<br>
• Slash, Bash, and Shoot the Undead: Slay hordes of walkers in third-person action with a variety of melee and ranged weapons, including bats, katanas, revolvers, shotguns, and crossbows.<br>
<br/>
• Play as 13 Iconic Characters: Assemble your roster from from AMC’s The Walking Dead, including Rick, Shane, Michonne, Carol, Daryl, and more.          <br/>
<br/>
• Survive the Apocalypse: Manage limited resources, scavenge for weapons and ammo, and maximize your party’s abilities to stay alive.<br/>
<br/>
• Experience the Tension: Defend your camp, rescue survivors, and fight through stealth and all-out combat. Get one last chance at survival in a “broken state” before the zombie threat overwhelms you.						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Octo Vinctum: Revenge of the Czar</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1899110/Octo_Vinctum_Revenge_of_the_Czar/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1899110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Octo Vinctum: Revenge of the Czar</strong> is retro game of epic proportions! Inspired by classic JRPGS of the 80's and 90's. It looks and plays just like the retro games you know and love. <br/><br/>The year is 1995. In the country of Vinland there lives a girl named Sabrina Lenster, who dreams of becoming a famous pop star. Join Sabrina and her friends as they travel across Vinland to defeat an evil entertainment company called Czar Entertainment. Along the way they'll meet a cast of quirky characters, some benevolent, some sinister, but all unforgettable! Using the power of their kind words and magical talents, Sabrina and friends will combat the forces who wish them harm. In the end, their journey might even take them to dimensions outside of time and space! Will you be able to defeat the infamous "Pop Czar" and the dark forces from beyond the galaxy that threaten Earth? <br/><br/><strong>EXPLORE THE WORLD OF OCTO VINCTUM</strong><br/>Travel around the country of Vinland using taxis or the legendary power of "Managic" to find new locations, and discover hidden treasures! <br/>Explore "dungeons" such a haunted theater, and an internet cafe in search of magical relics!<br/>Go shopping! Buy "weapons" such as microphones, books, and guitars that boost your talents!<br/>Interact with the townsfolk! Each town is full of memorable NPCs, some of which may reward you with special items!<br/><br/><strong>KILL YOUR ENEMIES WITH KINDNESS</strong><br/>In Octo Vinctum's traditional turn-based RPG battle system, you "Attalk" your enemies with your kind words!<br/>"Ignore" the enemy's rude remarks to survive!<br/>Use the power of your talents such as singing, dancing, and acting to turn the tide of battle!<br/>Lots of memorable characters with unique abilities!<br/><br/><strong>EXPERIENCE THE EPIC STORY TO SAVE EARTH FROM AN ANCIENT EVIL</strong><br/>Live the story through visual novel segments where players take control of Sabrina Lenster!<br/>Interact with the many usual and unusual people that populate Vinland!<br/>Build support between your allies through the Friendship system and watch their conversations to learn more about them!<br/>Will you be able to see past the bright, happy facade to see the true galactic threat that lies beneath?<br/><br/><strong>A RETRO GAME MADE WITH CARE AND LOVE</strong><br/>Pixel art based on the games of old!<br/>Hand-drawn character and envronment art!<br/>Inspired by all the classic RPGs of the 80s and 90s!<br/>A rockin' retro soundtrack!<br/>Full of secrets, sidequests, and hidden lore!<br/><br/>Are you a bad enough player to save the Planet and revive the power of MANAGIC?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1701448167"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1701448167"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Mashup</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1800000/Unreal_Mashup/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1800000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I am attempting to create a shooter experience tailored to our community's wishes. So what you see is what we all are looking for.<br>
<br>
Fast dynamic lateral movement and ideal projectile randomness incorporated with stylized animations which are generated dynamically via Unreal Engine's animation montage system, which by the way, is eye candy. <br>
<br>
We are using the Lyra shooter project as our base and as we go. I am planning to create customizable guns and characters along with providing stat based ranking and comparative match making.<br>
<br>
This will be the first game Ive created by myself so be aware Ill do my best to make this something good. This project was created for our community to have fun in a semi private way. As well this is a test of the unreal engines main shooter template LYRA which I'll be modifying as we go so updates will be a thing however I also know this thing is buggy! lol There are some audio glitching happening during respawns. Might just wanna turn that music volume down till I can get a fix for that.<br/>
<br/>
Now this is a basic third person shooter with a litany of baked in and ready to utilize features that over time I am going to learn and hopefully be able to modify and implement.<br/>
<br/>
I also want to point out that the networking system is janky ATM so we use Epic to run the game server hosting experience.<br/>
<br/>
All and all The game, so far, is functional and very small at a whopping 1.8 gigs<br/>
<br/>
So technically almost anyone can play it! <br/>
<br/>
Im hoping to have cross platform and VR worked out at some point in the future and honestly it could be working already however I have not been able to test it in that format yet. <br/>
<br/>
There are currently 10 maps included. Demon Station, Big Star Station, Convolution, Expanse, Space station, Soul Slum Forest, Soul Slum, Soul Cave, Shooter Gym and Overworld.<br/>
<br/>
There are currently 7 guns included. They are: Pistol, Shotgun, Rifle, Auto Sniper, Grenade, Grenade launcher, Rocket launcher.<br/>
<br/>
Health pickups are a thing as well.<br/>
<br/>
I hope you enjoy the project and Thanks in advance for any form of feedback going forward.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Red Juggernaut</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2638290/The_Red_Juggernaut/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638290/extras/trj-title.gif?t=1701447039"><br/><br/>A retro-style <strong>JPRG</strong> crossed with a<strong> modular ship building</strong> &amp; combat game.<br/><br/>Level up your ship, build it bigger...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638290/extras/trj-builder.gif?t=1701447039"><br/><br/>Battle enemy ships...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638290/extras/trj-battle.gif?t=1701447039"><br/><br/>Explore the solar system...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638290/extras/trj-explore.gif?t=1701447039"><br/><br/>And save the human race!<h2 class="bb_tag">Detailed Info:</h2><br/>You start off with three blocks (engine, mounting block, cockpit) that you can rearrange as you like, when you defeat enemies you gain XP, can level up to get more blocks to add to your ship. You also get money for defeating enemies, and you can buy things at space stations. Mountable weapons (<strong>guns, machine guns, lasers, launchers</strong>), a mountable <strong>shield</strong>, ammo (<strong>torpedoes and emp torpedoes</strong>), and consumable items for heating and in-battle stats increases. You can also find weapons and other items in certain places in the map.<br/><br/>You must make your way through the map and the various "dungeons" to find and defeat the Red Juggernaut. There are <strong>over 30</strong> types of enemy ships that you will encounter as you travel, with a varying degree of difficulty. In battle, once you drop their defense screens you can damage blocks individually. If you destroy a component that causes a large portion of the enemy ship to be detached from it's cockpit, those orphaned blocks will be destroyed as well. You can also evade torpedo strikes, and make yourself less vulnerable to attack by using your engines. As well, you can utilize <strong>EMP strikes</strong> to take down enemy shields, and disable enemy weapons temporarily.<h2 class="bb_tag">Controls:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Supports XBOX style controllers: DPad, A, B<br/> </li><li> Keyboard: Arrow Keys, Space/Enter for A, Z/Escape for B</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Credits:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> chadams - Coding, art, music, sfx<br/> </li><li> Lil Lyon - Beta testing<br/> </li><li> LZ - Beta testing</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idle Percent</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696530/Idle_Percent/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2696530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Idle Percent</strong> is something fresh in games of this genre. Unusual mathematics with various features and possibilities make this game worth trying!<br/><br/>Every upgrade in this game is a percent which is added to the upgradable value. Your progression is slow at the beginning but with time your income will become higher and higher!<br/><br/>Buy upgrades, discover complex prestige system and use other features to maximize your income. And unlike other idle games, you can complete this one!<h2 class="bb_tag">GAMEPLAY</h2>Click or wait for idle income. Upgrade your interest income or maximize click profit. Play as you want!<h2 class="bb_tag">PERCENTAGE PROGRESSION</h2>Unique mathematics based on percentages with a smooth increase in prices and income.<h2 class="bb_tag">UPGRADES AND PRESTIGE</h2>Buy base upgrades to increase your stats and income. Use prestige system to reset your progress and get powerful permanent improvements.<h2 class="bb_tag">SUPER PRESTIGE</h2>Even prestige upgrades can be improved! Buy super upgrades to maximize prestige power.<h2 class="bb_tag">GRAPHICS</h2>Nice minimalistic graphics and clean UI so nothing distracts you. You can even select your own background!<h2 class="bb_tag">MUSIC</h2>Dozens of calm ambient music tracks for your joy.<h2 class="bb_tag">ACHIEVEMENTS</h2>55 Steam achievements are waiting for you! Will you be able to collect them all?<br/><br/><strong>Idle Percent</strong> is not as simple as is looks. Try something really unusual and get guaranteed pleasure!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Conflict TD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2698320/Zero_Conflict_TD/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for an out-of-this-world gaming experience in "Zero Conflict TD," the ultimate tower defense game that pits you against a relentless alien invasion! The fate of Earth hangs in the balance, and it's up to you to lead the charge and protect our planet from these extraterrestrial aggressors.<br>
<br>
In a not-so-distant future, humanity has made contact with advanced civilizations among the stars. While most alien races are peaceful, a malevolent force known as the Ximarats has set its sights on Earth, seeking to conquer and exploit our precious resources. With their technologically superior weapons and relentless onslaught, they pose a formidable threat.<br>
<br>
As the commander of Earth's last line of defense, you'll embark on an epic journey to save our world. Your mission is to strategically place an array of powerful towers, each with unique weapons, across key locations on the planet. These towers will serve as your primary means of thwarting the alien invasion.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loading Screen Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2332450/Loading_Screen_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2332450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You've already been inundated with every type of simulator possible. Well, at least you thought that was the case. Like most everyone else, we think the simulator genre has gone too far (We're looking at you, KFC Dating Sim....).  However, instead of rallying against the deluge of downright weird simulators, we've decided to add to the growing abyss of them. Loading Screen Simulator started out as a joke between family members about the madness of the current simulator genre. Now it's progressed to a functional alpha build with goals to have a full game released by the end of the year. Keep checking back, as it's going to keep getting better? How, you ask? More loading screens, of course! Yes, there will be easter eggs for those of you that get through the first few loading screens. Will there be jump scares? Maybe. You'll have to progress through the loading screens to find out. Will there be some cool trivia hidden somewhere in the midst of all the loading screen madness? Possibly, if we can figure out how to code that. What's our end goal? World domination through a large amount of non-functional loading screens, of course! (We may be joking here, or there may be a Chinese spy balloon in there somewhere...If you're the CIA or any government agency reading this, we're just kidding! There's no spyware here). We just hope that our end product is as absurd as it sounds!<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
o Loading Screen images rotate randomly<br>
o Hundreds of loading screen images at launch, with more being added every day<br>
o Interactive loading screens (maze challenges, puzzles, and more!) that can be turned on or off<br>
o Real-life and fantasy scenery!<br/>
o Can be used as a safety screen in many situations. <br/>
o Music that can be turned on or off throughout the screens						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roll &amp; Ball</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2534470/Roll__Ball/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2534470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2534470/extras/gif_punt_003.gif?t=1701444320"><br/><br/>Roll &amp; Ball is an American Football board game where you can call plays and control a playmaker. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 2 Playbook Offense (11, 21)</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 2 Playbook Defense (34, 43)</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 30+ weather</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 24h cycle</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIES FLIES FLIES</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2330490/FLIES_FLIES_FLIES/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">An episodic, queer, sci-fi comedy visual novel</h2><br/>One day, before he can even graduate high school, Finn Flynn wakes up in the body of a housefly. Without the use of his voice, he'll have to enlist his prankster ex-boyfriend, and his dads, an insectophobic mad scientist and a punk rocker, to solve the mystery of his transformation, and maybe get his life back?<br/><br/>FLIES FLIES FLIES will contain 6 episodes of roughly 25 minutes' playtime each. 2 episodes will be available at launch, and the rest will be released as free updates throughout 2023 and 2024.<br/><br/><strong>FLIES FLIES FLIES is a linear, scripted experience.</strong> There are <strong>no</strong> player choices, alternate endings, etc.<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dark sci-fi comedy story full of twists and turns<br/></li><li>A diverse cast of lovable oddballs<br/></li><li>Eclectic collage art style<br/></li><li>Fully voice-acted with subtitles<br/></li><li>Sound captions<br/></li><li>You'll laugh<br/></li><li>You'll cry<br/></li><li>You'll turn into a fly??<br/></li><li>Just kidding<br/></li><li>But only about that last one</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoking Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2691390/Smoking_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2691390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Have you ever wanted to relax and have a good smoke in an atmospheric village? Then you are exactly at the right place - take a drag on your cigarette and go ahead and explore our wonderful world. It doesn’t matter whether you are an esthete or an amateur, everyone will find a piece of happiness in the Smoking Simulator, only here you can smoke a lot without any negative consequences, or you can go explore the atmospheric village, looking at the works of art on the walls and nature, as your heart desires.<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br>
-You can smoke 24/7 without any penalties/negative consequences<br>
-Relaxing soundtrack<br>
-You can take a running jump into the snow from a hill without fear of crashing<br>
-Atmosphere and humor<br/>
-Various references<br/>
-Beautiful next-gen graphics<br/>
<br/>
All similarities with real people, countries, places, etc. are purely coincidental. The game takes place in a fictional country - Cigaretteland.<br/>
<br/>
Enjoy!)						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat Leather Jackets</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1673830/Cat_Leather_Jackets/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1673830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cat Leather Jackets is a linear visual novel and music game about being a teenager in a punk rock band. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1673830/extras/CLJGameplayGifSteam.gif?t=1701458700"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1673830/extras/synopsis.png?t=1701458700"><br/><br/>Follow Priya and her bandmates Ian and Dave as they get together to write and rehearse songs, try to find gigs and ultimately an audience for their music – all the while trying to find independence and figuring out what they want to do with their lives.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1673830/extras/priya_bus.gif?t=1701458700"><br/><br/>The game features ten original tracks with gameplay segments, intertwining a kinetic novel style narrative with an indie comic book/ graphic novel aesthetic. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1673830/extras/features.png?t=1701458700"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A <strong>Story Mode</strong>: get to know Priya, Ian and Dave and play CLJ's setlist at their first gig;<br/></li><li>In Story Mode, win or lose in the<strong> Punk Mode</strong>. Just want to enjoy the story? Try the <strong>Default Mode</strong>.<br/></li><li>Play any and all unlocked songs for the highest score in the <strong>Practice Mode</strong>;<br/></li><li>Unlock all Steam Achievements;<br/></li><li>And enjoy <strong>ten completely original punk, ska and alternative rock playable beatmaps</strong>.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Christmas Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687190/100_Christmas_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687190/100_Christmas_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687190/100_Christmas_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/Wish+Follow.png?t=1701442822"><h2 class="bb_tag">⛄🌟 WELCOME TO 100 CHRISTMAS CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🎄🎨</h2>🎄 Dive into the most festive adventure in the heart of holiday cheer! 🌟 Discover the enchanting hand-drawn scenes of a holiday cityscape as you set out on a quest to uncover 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎅🎨<br/>😸 Test your attention and focus in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag"> 🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈 </h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/Cats.png?t=1701442822"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🎮 1 Extra Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 More Extra Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 2 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🏆 Many Leaderboards <br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Christmas Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692090/100_Christmas_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100ChristmasCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/Extra.png?t=1701442822"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692080/100_Christmas_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100ChristmasCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1701442822"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692100/100_Christmas_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=100ChristmasCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/Artbook.png?t=1701442822"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692110/100_Christmas_Cats__Donaiton_S/?utm_source=100ChristmasCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/Donation.png?t=1701442822"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/600x1.png?t=1701442822"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1701442822"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687190/100_Christmas_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetBot" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687190/100_Christmas_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetBot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Void Guard</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692960/Void_Guard/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Follow the Void Guardian as she inspects a space station after receiving a distress beacon from it. In Void Guard, you play as the Void Guardian to discover the space station's secret and vanquish the hidden evil.<br>
<br>
"Void Guard" is a Top-Down Metroidvania shooter/puzzle game where the Void Guardian can be moved with WASD. As the Guardian explores the station and the planetoids below, she will find the cause of the station's crew vanishing, encountering mind-bending puzzles, hostile fauna, and exciting suit upgrades. Some environments may be more hostile, and she might have to figure out how to survive. The combination of dangerous technology and biology will be an exciting challenge to overcome. <br>
<br>
In "Void Guard," there are many abilities, such as a gun, a suit upgrade, and a hidden dash ability. You may find some planetoids are more dangerous than others. The final challenge may be impossible to beat with just a gun, but you may find another solution along the way. <br>
<br>
Mouse and Keyboard Supported.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOTICE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2565260/NOTICE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2565260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>NOTICE </strong>is a short interactive experience that follows the story of having a panic attack, then using <strong>awareness </strong>and <strong>presence </strong>to overcome it. As you get home and start to breathe, you take control over your thoughts. By clicking on each object, <strong>you start to become aware of everything in your space and what it means to you.</strong><br/><br/>Each object has its own <strong>style</strong>, <strong>musical note</strong> and <strong>meaning </strong>- whether that be the can of soda lying on your desk or the guitar gifted to you from a friend back home.<br/><br/><strong>Headphones recommended.</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beneath The Earth - Backrooms</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2654040/Beneath_The_Earth__Backrooms/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/extras/About600x174.png?t=1701440416"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/extras/wishlist_follow.gif?t=1701440416"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/extras/DESCRIPTION.png?t=1701440416"><br/>Beneath The Earth - Backrooms is a Co-Op horror game that can be played with at least 1 and up to 4 players. Where you and your friends will fight to escape from the different levels of the backrooms, solving different puzzles with different mechanics in each one.<br/>This game is based on the famous "horrifying creepypasta of cursed dreams" with many real references implemented such as iconic entities and important elements. Explore the seemingly infinite expanse of eerily familiar levels in the backrooms.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/extras/Co-opMultiplayer.png?t=1701440416"><br/>Beneath The Earth - Backrooms with a team of up to 4 players. Be careful: players on your team may not be able to get to other maps, and each member of your team must find the exit alive to escape.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/extras/RealisticGraphics.png?t=1701440416"><br/>The best graphics in the co-op horror genre you'll ever play. Developed with Unreal Engine 5.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/extras/Levels.png?t=1701440416"><br/>The game currently has 5 levels, each level is huge and is designed to be more difficult than the previous one and each one with different puzzles and mechanics. Levels will be added in the future.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/extras/RichContent.png?t=1701440416"><br/>The game is rich in different mechanics, levels, interactive things, monsters, you won’t be bored...						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Into The Noid</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2675610/Into_The_Noid/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2675610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to a visual and atmospheric, Noid-like arcade experience in this classical brick-breaker genre turned VR.  <br>
<br>
Including physics-based gameplay and a cerebral visual experience through a host of 16 diverse and atmospheric, stylized levels.  <br>
<br>
Simple mechanics make for an enjoyable game that's also skill based.  It starts as a relaxing, colourful VR romp that's casual then demands higher levels of skill from the player, eventually evolving into a brick-breaker that is as challenging as it is fun.  Walls slide closer to the player, multiple balls appear, explosive balls help destroy the bricks while bonuses in the form of extra lives, larger and dual paddles fly at the player. <br>
<br>
The levels are visceral and the environments provide ample food for the senses.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racing the Gods - Beyond Horizons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1886990/Racing_the_Gods__Beyond_Horizons/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1886990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">The most epic race of all time is about to start.</h2>You have been selected as one of the drivers representing Earth. <br/>It’s a race of life and death as only the fastest will survive. <br/>Do you have what it takes?<h2 class="bb_tag">The ultimate racing tournament beyond time and space awaits!</h2>The gods of our galaxy have opened the gates of their habitats. <br/>They are inviting one driver from each planet to show off their racing skills in a sheer limitless world striking with beauty, extreme contrasts, and breathtaking constructions. <br/>But there is a lot on the line - the losing planets will be eliminated.<h2 class="bb_tag">Race in a vibrant and ever-evolving world beyond imagination</h2>The tournament features 27 tracks through a world beyond our imagination. <br/>It is unlike anything you have ever seen and only inhabited by titans - giant creatures that have been deemed worthy of staying within the realm of the gods. <br/>Racing has never been this epic!<h2 class="bb_tag">What to expect:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A fast-paced racing experience<br/></li><li>27 different tracks through the world of the gods<br/></li><li>Each world has a unique design and twist on the racing experience<br/></li><li>Giant structures, monuments, and monsters are just some of the obstacles that you have to overcome<br/></li><li>Different weapons to clear the way and fight against the other racers<br/></li><li>A unique art style and the most vibrant and interactive racing world<br/></li><li>Many cool upgrades and improvements for your hoverbike</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Boy and His Blob Retro Collection</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1147360/A_Boy_and_His_Blob_Retro_Collection/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1147360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							TROUBLE ON BLOBOLONIA™<br/><br/>Team up with an extraterrestrial lifeform named Blobert (affectionately known as Blob) to save Blob’s home planet! The evil emperor of Blobolonia™ is threatening to rule the planet with his army of minions. Thwart his plans for total conquest while forging an unbreakable bond by using the power of jelly beans! <br/><br/>Find hidden treasures across Blobolonia™ by discovering new secrets and gathering enough resources to buy new jellies. These tasty treats will give Blob the power to undergo miraculous transformations and help you save the world together. Sounds like a daunting task, right? Not with Blob by your side!<br/><br/>Try different jellybean flavors to see what effect they have on Blob. Overcome obstacles by transforming Blob into the right tool for the job! This shape-shifting ability becomes their ultimate weapon, enabling them to conquer seemingly insurmountable challenges. With enough jellybeans and flavors, the possibilities are endless!<br/><br/><br/>THE RESCUE OF PRINCESS BLOBETTE<br/><br/>Join the boy and his extraordinary companion, Blob, as they embark on a quest to save the beloved Princess Blobette from the clutches of the wicked Antagonistic Alchemist, who harbors grand ambitions of becoming Emperor of Blob’s home planet, Blobolonia™. But our heroes won't let that happen.<br/><br/>Imprisoned within the tower of the Royal Castle, the fate of Princess Blobette hangs in the balance, and it's up to you to ensure her freedom. But the Alchemist has laid a suite of treacherous traps to impede the boy and Blob’s progress. Join our dynamic duo as they encounter secret rooms, clever traps, and dangerous obstacles in the labyrinthine depths of the castle. <br/><br/>Fortunately, the Alchemist remains oblivious to our heroes’ hidden advantage—feeding Blob different flavors of jelly beans can transform him into various shapes. Armed with this knowledge, unlocking the tower's door becomes a mere trifle for our heroes, provided the right jelly bean is at hand. Blob’s ability to magically transform shapes will help this intrepid pair get past almost anything the Alchemist can conjure up!<br/><br/>FEATURES OF THIS RETRO COLLECTION:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Includes US and Japanese versions of both games.<br/></li><li> Music Player. Enjoy the original soundtrack of both games.<br/></li><li> Use save states in the game for the first time! No need to start over from the beginning each time. <br/></li><li> Our new launcher gives players different aesthetic options and filters to enjoy the game!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SteamWorld Build</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2134770/SteamWorld_Build/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-Homestead.png?t=1701453785"><br/>One final landrush! The planet is dyin', Astrid, and it's dig or die trying! <br/><br/>That mine under our town is sitting empty, and wouldn't you know there's rumours of ancient tech down there that might help us out of this predicament. Round up the posse, circle the wagons, and let's get to buildin' a new home! Collect resources above ground and ores down below so we can get those wealthy bots in here to help us build bigger, and we can get the heck out of here!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_1.gif?t=1701453785"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_manage.png?t=1701453785"><br/>As your borders expand, new steamfolk will find their way to you! Every bot is crotchety in their own way, and it's up to you to keep them steaming along. Barter to boost efficiency, keep goods flowing to and from the mines and keep everyone happy to make them work their darndest and hardest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_2.gif?t=1701453785"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-DIG-DEEP.png?t=1701453785"><br/><br/>Stare into the abyss long enough and it might just stare back... we're going looking for riches and something down there doesn't want to share! Have gun, dig gravel, and make sure the mines don't collapse upon you as you defend yourselves from the creepy crawlies that lurk within...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_3.gif?t=1701453785"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_features.png?t=1701453785"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break ground on a bustling SteamWorld town, inspired by the Old West.<br/></li><li>Keep your steambots from getting cranky by ensuring their complex needs get met<br/></li><li>Dig deep and spread wide to produce resources to aid your search for ancient technologies<br/></li><li>Defend your mine from the creepy varmints that lurk deep below your town<br/></li><li>Trade resources at the local train stop and welcome special visitors who'll lend a hand<br/></li><li>Five distinct maps littered with secrets for the discerning SteamWorld explorer to find<br/></li><li>Developed from the ground up for both mouse and controller, whichever takes yer fancy.<br/></li><li>Four difficulty levels, including a sandbox difficulty for when you just want to Build!</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
