<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Spell Disk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2292060/Spell_Disk/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Spell Disk is a rogue-lite action game with a unique synergy building mechanic so that your runs can never be the same. Strategize and create your own spell combo synergies to blast through enemies on your way! Each run is unique, so you must plan out how to build your power.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/extras/combo_paper.gif?t=1709316039"><br/>Discover combos and synergies that no one’s seen before! Maximize your power to better your chance of escaping the dungeon of Spell Disk.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/extras/Items_Updated.gif?t=1709316039"><br/>Craft spells, disks, and artifacts during your run that synergies with each other in their own ways.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/extras/Lobby_Updated.gif?t=1709316039"><br/>Unlock new weapons and powers to hack and slash through the enemies blocking your way.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vivaland: Dream House</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2606170/Vivaland_Dream_House/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2606170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1976830" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1976830</a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2606170/extras/ezgif-3-474fd0310c.gif?t=1709314012"><h2 class="bb_tag">Introducing the Vivaland Prologue: Dream House</h2><strong>Build Mode: Craft Your Dreams</strong><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in one of the core game modes of Vivaland: the Build Mode. It's a sandbox where you have control over architectural and design elements, enabling you to construct and decorate a house from the ground up!<br/><br/><strong>Get to Know the First Town of Vivaland</strong><br/><br/>The town of Vivaland offers 8 residential lots, each awaiting your personal touch. Claim your slice of the town, visit your friends' properties, and collaborate on grand projects that will redefine the neighborhood.<br/><br/><strong>Seamless Single and Co-op Experience</strong><br/><br/>Begin your Vivaland adventure either as a lone explorer or with your friends by your side – the choice is yours. You can build together with up to 8 players<br/><strong>Content</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Walls Toolkit:</strong> Build with single wall, curved wall and the room tool!<br/></li><li><strong>Doors &amp; Windows:</strong> Choose entrances and views that reflect your taste.<br/></li><li><strong>Foundations, Multiple Floors, and Stairs: </strong>Build structures that rise to new heights.<br/></li><li><strong>Furniture:</strong> Design with a vast selection of interior items.<br/></li><li><strong>Roofing:</strong> Choose from 10 distinct styles and an array of roof patterns.<br/></li><li><strong>Different styles of items:</strong>  Bohemian, Retro, Victorian, Antique, Cottagecore, Gothic, Modern, Minimalist, Industrial.</li></ul><br/><strong>Functional Freedom</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Resizable Objects:</strong> Adjusting the size of decorative objects.<br/></li><li><strong>Recolorable Furniture and Decor: </strong> Fine-tune your interior design with your color palettes. Save favorite shades and match your items.<br/></li><li><strong>Room Dimension Flexibility: </strong>Tweak the height and width of your rooms.<br/></li><li><strong>Grid Function: </strong>Precise item placement is a breeze with toggleable grid support.<br/></li><li><strong>Intuitive Controls and Snapping: </strong>Seamlessly move and arrange objects.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUARDS!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2514460/GUARDS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/4playerchaos.png?t=1709330868"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/chaosgif.gif?t=1709330868"><h2 class="bb_tag">1-4 PLAYER CO-OP</h2>Work together as a team and fight your way through the wretched streets of New Alestead. You will need to rely on your teammates if you are going to make out of the city alive.<h2 class="bb_tag">LIGHTNING FAST ACTION</h2>New Alestead has a disease... and you are the cure! Dispense justice quickly and thoroughly because these criminals wont wait to attack you one at a time.<h2 class="bb_tag">EVERYTHING IS A WEAPON</h2>Sometimes you need to improvise! Use crates, barrels, planks, bits of door, arms, a variety of City Watch approved civility moderation tools or even your foot to bring criminals in dead or alive.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/scoutplanexecute.png?t=1709330868"><h2 class="bb_tag">MISSION DISPATCH</h2>It's not all City sanctioned murder and wanton property destruction, sometimes you actually need to arrest some people, secure contraband or escort important VIP's out of the city.<h2 class="bb_tag">ON STAKEOUT</h2>When you find the criminals hideout, you will be outnumbered and outgunned. Wait and watch from the shadows to observe enemy patrol patterns, gang composition and any environmental objects that you might be able to use to your advantage.<h2 class="bb_tag">NO PLAN SURVIVES FIRST CONTACT</h2>When it all kicks off you're going to have to think on your feet and coordinate with your partners. Just try to make sure you take out more bad guys than other officers in the process!<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/takebackcity.png?t=1709330868"><h2 class="bb_tag">A CITY RULED BY GANGS</h2>Three rival factions control the city. The Fogtoof Boyz, an Orc gang with a reputation for violence and destruction. The Commision, a band of rogue merchants whose lust for power put them on the wrong side of the law, and The Corpse Cult - an religious organization infecting the city by turning its followers into mindless zombies.<h2 class="bb_tag">FIND THE KINGPINS</h2>Each gang has a kingpin. Take out the kingpin, you take out the gang. You will have to work your way up the food chain in order to find the kingpins location and assault their hideout.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Brew Barons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1636710/The_Brew_Barons/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1636710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A tranquil world becomes ever more corrupt by the day, spoiled by a strong-armed pirate organization that forcefully impose their brewing monopoly over the lands. Armed with your own brewery and seaplane, it's up to you to explore, forage, craft, sell and deliver your handcrafted brews with aid from fellow pilots who've joined your cause to overthrow the corrupt pirate organization and restore peace.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1636710/extras/steamgif1a.gif?t=1709308740"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Assemble your plane from a variety of parts, each with their own traits.<br/></li><li>Chose your pilot and copilot of whom have strengths and weaknesses.<br/></li><li>Explore the world in search of ingredients to bring back to your brewery. </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1636710/extras/steamgif2.gif?t=1709308740"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Pick and choose which foraged ingredients to blend. <br/></li><li>Distill and/or Ferment, each producing a different outcome. <br/></li><li>Design and name your bottle to your liking.<br/></li><li>Design your very own bar to sell your brews and bring fame to your establishment!<br/></li><li>With fame comes special delivery orders from other bars to stock your brew </li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mobius Machine</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2281940/The_Mobius_Machine/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2281940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Carve your path through a <strong>vast alien world</strong> filled with <i>brutal lifeforms</i> and <i>malfunctioning machines</i>.<br/>Explore beyond the <i>Crash Site</i>, through the desolate <i>Spaceship Graveyard</i>, into the depths of the <i>Mining Grounds</i>, and up to the <i>Floating Forests</i>.<br/><br/>The Mobius Machine is a <strong>classic 2D adventure</strong> game with <strong>detailed 3D visuals</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2281940/extras/machine.gif?t=1709287020"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore Seamlessly</h2>Explore a complex interconnected <strong>open world</strong>, discovering it your own way.<br/>Stumble upon the breathtaking environments of the Isolaria moon. On <strong>land</strong>, <strong>underwater</strong> and in the <strong>skies</strong>. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2281940/extras/exploration.gif?t=1709287020"><h2 class="bb_tag">Fight</h2>Combat an array of deadly adversaries: the local fauna, infected colonists, and abandoned machines that once worked in the facilities.<br/>Defeat more than 80 distinct enemies, including the <strong>epic bosses</strong> that guard the most precious gear.<h2 class="bb_tag">Shoot Anywhere</h2>Designed for both <strong>Gamepad</strong> or <strong>Mouse and Keyboard</strong> controls. Run and jump around while shooting in any direction using a tight control system.<br/>You can have 2 weapons equipped at any time, and use them as you need.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2281940/extras/combat.gif?t=1709287020"><h2 class="bb_tag">Evolve</h2>Acquire the gear that will make you more mobile and unlock new areas. <strong>Climb walls</strong>, <strong>dash</strong>, <strong>dive underwater</strong>, <strong>glide through the air</strong> and evolve the way you interact with the world.<h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your arsenal</h2>Collect blueprints and craft new <strong>weapons</strong> and <strong>upgrades</strong> in order to fight more effectively. Each new item you acquire will give you more options and increase your chances of survival.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeeperRL</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/329970/KeeperRL/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/Peek-2018-11-28-09-43.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL is an ambitious dungeon simulator with roguelike and RPG elements. Take the role of an evil wizard and study the methods of black magic. Equip your minions and explore the world, murder innocent villagers and burn their homes. Build your dungeon, lay traps and prepare for an assault of angry heroes. <br/><br/>When you control your minions the game changes into a classic roguelike, with turn-based and very tactical combat. You can also play as an adventurer and assault dungeons made by you or other players.<h2 class="bb_tag">Dungeon management </h2>You will dig deep into the mountain and build dozens of rooms, corridors and traps. Your minions will train and produce weapons and armor. Prisoners will be tortured. You will research new technologies like alchemy, beast mutation and sorcery.<h2 class="bb_tag">Z-levels</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341">Develop your base across multiple floors by digging down into the earth or building up. Build fantastic dungeon designs or elaborate castles and towers.<h2 class="bb_tag">Roguelike mechanics </h2>The world is simulated on a very detailed level. Creatures use equipment and consumable items. There are dozens of special items, spells, attributes and special attacks. You can cut off heads and limbs and blind or poison your enemies. If you're not careful with fire, you can burn an entire forest or even your own dungeon.<h2 class="bb_tag">Large, procedurally generated maps </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-animated-gif-maker__2_.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL features a large, procedurally generated world. Explore dozens of locations, from small cottages and shops to major enemies dwelling in castles and dungeons. Uncover secrets, bring back great loot and prisoners back to your base in order to grow in power.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple playable factions</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/gif_keepers-ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>Play as a:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dark wizard researching black magic.<br/></li><li>White knight specialized in horses and angelic beings.<br/></li><li>Necromancer who crafts undead from the body parts of fallen enemies.<br/></li><li>Fragile colony of twelve dwarves.<br/></li><li>Goblin king searching for his lost wives.<br/></li><li>Collective of gnomes with a mechanized army.<br/></li><li>Lone adventurer focused on exploration.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Online map sharing </h2>KeeperRL offers the ability to download dungeons made by other players from Steam Workshop, and places them on your world map as enemies. See how others design their fortresses, fight with their minions, and steal their loot! After winning the game, you'll have the option to share your dungeon online as well.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Grindea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/269770/Secrets_of_Grindea/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/269770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Secrets of Grindea</i> is an old-school Action RPG with co-op support for up to 4 players. It is a tribute to and sometimes a parody of the old SNES games so many of us grew up with and loved! Journey through fantastical lands, and battle tons of different enemies and bosses in your quest for truth, friendship and, above all, finding the world's rarest treasures!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A rich world filled with 300+ unique, colorful characters and an engaging story to drive your journey forward.<br/></li><li>Co-op support for up to four players! Enjoy the entire storyline with your friends or call someone in to help with the more difficult challenges.<br/></li><li>Customization, customization, customization - design a character that represents you, then mix and match any of the 31 spells and skills across 9 different categories.<br/></li><li>30+ epic boss fights! Overgrown slimes, giant robots, mimics - we have it all!<br/></li><li>Side content - design your own home, fish, craft items, tame pets, partake in mini-games, grow plants - there’s plenty to keep you entertained when you want a break from the main story.</li></ul><br/>And last but not least:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Arcade Mode - Separate from Story Mode, the game includes a <strong>full roguelite</strong> version where you need to battle your way to the top on a single life, building a town of your own as you progress.  How far can you get?</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON BALL FighterZ</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/678950/DRAGON_BALL_FighterZ/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/extras/GIF_DBFZ_STEAM.png?t=1709230702"><br/><br/>DRAGON BALL FighterZ is born from what makes the DRAGON BALL series so loved and famous: endless spectacular fights with its all-powerful fighters.<br/><br/>Partnering with Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ maximizes high end Anime graphics and brings easy to learn but difficult to master fighting gameplay.<br/><br/>High-end Anime Graphics<br/>Using the power of the Unreal engine and the talented team at Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ is a visual tour-de-force.<br/><br/>3vs3 Tag/Support<br/>Build your dream team and sharpen your skills to master high-speed tag combinations.<br/><br/>Thrilling Online Features<br/>Ranked matches, interactive lobby, crazy 6-player Party Match... There is something for every taste!<br/><br/>Exclusive Story Mode<br/>Discover a never-seen-before scenario featuring Android 21, a brand new character whose creation was supervised by Akira Toriyama himself.<br/><br/>Spectacular Fights<br/>Experience aerial combos, destructible stages and famous scenes from the DRAGON BALL anime in 60FPS and 1080p resolution!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robin Hood - Sherwood Builders</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1159420/Robin_Hood__Sherwood_Builders/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fk2N3rpRuB3" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/fc521c8bf21bff775962df4f130bb74eb5577a46.png?t=1709293292"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif01.gif?t=1709293292"><br/><br/>Robin Hood - Sherwood Builders is an action-adventure RPG with base-building elements, where you take on the role of a classic hero who stands up to the tyranny and injustice that haunts Sherwood. As Robin, you’ll fight, hunt, craft, steal, and of course help the local people thrive to spite the Sheriff of Nottingham and his ruthless regime – all within an open-world environment that can be freely explored.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif02.gif?t=1709293292"><br/><br/>Robin Hood is a famous hero of medieval English folk tales, believed to have during that time roamed the forests of Sherwood with his band of loyal outlaw companions. In the game you’re going to meet those legendary characters as well, such as Lady Marian, Little John, Friar Tuck, Allan-a-Dale, and Will Scarlet. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif05.gif?t=1709293292"><br/><br/>Robin's main goal is to help a fledgling community of refugees and rebels advance and expand. Starting with what could be described as a small forest settlement, with a bit of care, hard work, and good luck, it can end up as a town full of people. Recruit local peasants, rebels on the run from the law, and even the citizens and guards of Nottingham themselves as your new outlaw settlers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif04.gif?t=1709293292"><br/><br/>You start your adventure with building a forest camp, which can soon be expanded following the arrival of new residents. You will be responsible for properly managing the space you secured for yourself within Sherwood Forest to build up the village.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif03.gif?t=1709293292"><br/><br/>Another important part of taking care of the settlement will be to manage the community members’ professions and tasks, training them to become craftsmen, hunters, or guards, and to manage the settlement’s resources, either gathering them yourself or stealing them from convoys and noble estates.<br/><br/>As Robin's people grow large in number and strong in sword arm, an uprising in Nottingham may just become a reality, ending the Sheriff's tyranny once and for all.<br/>Can Robin Hood and his Merry Men survive and put an end to injustice? Their fate is up to you!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Godrop:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802550/GodropPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Prologue and the official version of the difference between<br/>Levels: one in the prologue, four in the official version<br/>Follow-up Program:<br/>The game will continue to update content after release, which includes:<br/>More bosses: different fighting styles and types of boss fights.<br/>More tech: weird and wacky tech combinations.<br/>More weapons: more basic weapons and weapon variants.<br/>More game modes: In addition to the basic level mode there will also be a survivor mode and parkour mode. </strong><br/><br/><strong>A special rougelite game that focuses entirely on ramming, piercing, and spraying as the core gameplay. You will play as Gotrop, a powerful unknown alien invasion weapon, facing the layers of barriers set up by the arrogant and ignorant humans in the solar system, using good movement and killing to steal the energy of human warships, driving our strong interaction force outer armor for invincible transformation, and destroying all the enemies in our way with incredible maneuverability and invulnerable ramming ability! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/y1.png?t=1709193487"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/1.gif?t=1709193487"><br/><strong>A combat system focused on energy. Just by being in motion you can generate a constant stream of energy, and mysterious alien technology also allows Gotrop to steal energy directly from his enemies. There is energy can be transformed into an invincible droplet state, invulnerable and unbreakable, our enemies can not cause any damage to us, but we can directly puncture the inside of their battleships havoc! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/y2.png?t=1709193487"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/2.gif?t=1709193487"><br/><strong>A large number of tech components have been beamed into the solar system, and Gotrop can access tech for morphing upgrades simply by cleaning up the battlefield! Whether it's a drill that can drill into enemy ships faster, outer armor that can reflect all attacks, or a spout that spews bullets, they can be acquired after sweeping through the enemy! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/y3.png?t=1709193487"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/3.gif?t=1709193487"><br/><strong>The solar system has been fortified by humans and is in crisis. Gotrop will break through layers of asteroids, energy stands and turret arrays until he completely destroys the human space fleet and takes over Earth! </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1709288144"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1709288144"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709288144"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1709288144"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1709288144"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1709288144"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1709288144"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1709288144"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1709288144"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1709288144"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709288144"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1709288144"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiritfall</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1835240/Spiritfall/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/PlatformFighterRoguelike.png?t=1709235442"><br/><strong>Spiritfall</strong> combines tight Platform Fighter combat, smooth movement, and Roguelite mechanics into one! Trek across dangerous lands, string together deadly combos to fend off swarms of enemies, and harness an ever-changing set of powers through a randomly generated map. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/SynergiesAwait.png?t=1709235442"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/GIFDivineSynergiesQuality.gif?t=1709235442"><br/>The divine spirits offer powerful blessings that enhance your abilities in combat. Discover your favorite abilities, and experiment with different builds. With over 150+ blessings to choose from, these gifts allow for a range of tactical approaches that encourage you to find synergies that fit your playstyle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/StrongerFromDefeat.png?t=1709235442"><br/>Death is but a temporary setback. Reawaken stronger than before at the Sanctum and continue your adventure. Use the resources you gathered to upgrade your skills, unlock unique powers, and awaken mighty weapons with unique movesets.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/Community.png?t=1709235442"><br/>A heartfelt thank you to our Early Access community! Your feedback has been invaluable during Spiritfall's development, helping make the game what it is today. We invite you to keep shaping our world together. Connect with fellow players on Discord and get the latest news by joining our newsletter.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minami Lane</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678990/Minami_Lane/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Minami Lane is a small, wholesome management game set on a Japanese-inspired street. Create and manage your own street, make sure everyone is happy, and watch the villagers live their lives! Enjoy 2 to 4 hours of playtime, cute tanukis and lots of cats!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/Gameplay.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/><i><strong>Build your street</strong></i><br/>Build homes to add villagers to your street, then improve their happiness by beautifying every inch and building a variety of shops &amp; attractions! These include ramen shops, boba cafes, bookstores and more, each with unique inventories and effects.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Building.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/><i><strong>Manage your shops</strong></i><br/>Attract customers with everything from floral bouquets to karaoke! Shops you create will need your careful guidance to offer the right products at the right prices. Lead them to success and make your neighborhood thrive.<br/><br/><i><strong>Watch your villagers live their lives</strong></i><br/>Once you start the day, you'll get to see each villager react to your street and offer helpful feedback on how to improve! Memorize their preferences and refine your street the following day.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Review.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/><i><strong>Reach your objectives</strong></i><br/>Complete missions to unlock new levels with more buildings, villager types, and other surprises.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/Features.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>What Minami Lane offers:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>2-4 hours of play time<br/></li><li>Create and customize your own adorable street<br/></li><li>Manage shops by adjusting their inventory, recipes, and prices<br/></li><li>Play strategically to complete each level's mission objectives<br/></li><li>Keep the streets clean by picking up trash<br/></li><li>Tanukis and cats!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Ramen.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>What Minami Lane does not offer:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hardcore strategy<br/></li><li>Multiplayer<br/></li><li>Tons of missions<br/></li><li>New levels after release</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/GameModes.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>In Minami Lane's missions, you'll need to strategically plan each day and use random events to your advantage to complete multiple objectives. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Bike.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>The sandbox mode focuses on creativity and relaxation, allowing you to immerse yourself in the peaceful, cozy world without the stress of objectives.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/DevTeam.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>Minami Lane is the collaborative effort of Dorian (Doot), Doriane (Blibloop) and Antoine (Zakku). Doot, a former data scientist turned game developer, brings light strategy and management gameplay, while Blibloop breathes life into the isometric world with her Studio Ghibli-inspired, hand-drawn designs. Zakku adds the finishing touches with joyful, wholesome music compositions and soundscape. We really hope you will enjoy this tiny game we made with love 💕<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678990/Minami_Lane/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678990/Minami_Lane/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR WARS™: Dark Forces Remaster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2292260/STAR_WARS_Dark_Forces_Remaster/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_8.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/><i>Star Wars</i>™: Dark Forces Remaster has been brought to life by the team at <strong>Nightdive Studios</strong>, fully remastered through its proprietary KEX engine, allowing the game to run on modern gaming devices at up to 4K resolution at 120FPS. New and returning players will enjoy <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces Remaster’s upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<br/><br/>The original 1995 <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces raised the bar for FPS games, offering players a significant degree of movement and interactivity, a large selection of items and power-ups, and engaging environments. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_10.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/>In the first <i>Star Wars</i> FPS video game, players assume the role of Kyle Katarn, a defector of the Galactic Empire turned mercenary for hire. Katarn joins the Rebel Alliance’s covert operations division tasked with infiltrating the Galactic Empire, where he discovers the secret Dark Trooper Project. The development of this powerful new series of Imperial battle droids and power-armored stormtroopers stands to strengthen the Empire’s grip on the galaxy unless Katarn and the Rebel Alliance intervene.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>All fourteen original levels, featuring <i>Star Wars</i>™ worlds and capital ships<br/></li><li>Use your ability to jump, duck, and crawl to solve puzzles and defeat enemies<br/></li><li>Your Personal Digital Assistant provides you with in game information such including map, inventory, and mission briefing<br/></li><li>Engaging first-person ground combat featuring ten weapons and twenty types of enemies<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS visuals<br/></li><li>Advanced 3D rendering enables updated lighting and atmospheric effects<br/></li><li>Modern gamepad support adds a new weapon wheel, and rumble<br/></li><li>Controller Support - vibration and gyro controls <br/></li><li>A variety of power-ups are made available to the player, including health, shields, weapons and ammunition<br/></li><li>For combat, the player may use fists, explosive landmines and thermal detonators, as well as blasters and other ranged weapons<br/></li><li>Includes immersive environmental puzzles and mazes </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_1.gif?t=1709278523"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shashingo: Learn Japanese with Photography</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1632490/Shashingo_Learn_Japanese_with_Photography/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Explore bright, fictional Japanese streets filled with details and interesting objects to capture with your camera. Each photograph you take will translate the name of the content into Japanese and English so you can learn with your surroundings.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/extras/Shashingo_Take_Photo.gif?t=1709246737"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A stylised, approachable 3D environment<br/></li><li>In-game photography system<br/></li><li>Japanese audio<br/></li><li>Photo album to store your flash cards<br/></li><li>A game mode that tests your memory<br/></li><li>Beginner phrases and grammar lessons<br/></li><li>Day/Night and weather cycle<br/></li><li>Display romaji, kana, furigana <i>(recommended)</i> or kanji</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/extras/Shashingo_Flash_Cards.png?t=1709246737"><h2 class="bb_tag">Create Stunning Photography Based Flashcards</h2>Every photo flash-card you take will be unique to you. The idea behind this is to strengthen the relationship between a word and how you see its physical appearance. In the real world, you can then see such objects and make connections to the Japanese words you've already learned while playing Shashingo.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/extras/Shashingo_Photo_Album.png?t=1709246737"><h2 class="bb_tag">Track Your Progress in the Photo Album</h2>Your photo album is where you keep your collection of Photo Flash-Cards. If you remember them well in Find Mode, they'll be separated into the 'mastered' tab and shown with a gold star sticker. However, if you're struggling to remember a word in Find Mode, they'll be marked with a purple exclamation mark sticker, so you know which words you need to practice more.<br/>You can also mark your favourite words &amp; images with a cute little heart sticker to add them to your favourites page.<br/><br/>At the back of your in-game photo album, there are numerous pages of Japanese lessons designed for beginners that will teach you how to speak Japanese and use the vocabulary that you learn in Shashingo. Also included are some key words and important phrases that can help you in your future conversations.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dicefolk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1996430/Dicefolk/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FtN3yxBv4tq" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Join_Our_Discord_600x224.png?t=1709053137"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Dicefolk is a tactical roguelite game based on customizable dice and monster-catching mechanics. On your adventure as a Chimera Summoner, you'll meet dozens of unique and powerful creatures that you can recruit to create the perfect team.<br/><br/>Play as Alea, a young Dicefolk hero who discovers her ability to befriend Chimera and fight back against evil forces threatening humanity’s extinction.</strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Battle_Start.gif?t=1709053137"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H2.png?t=1709053137"><br/>Embark on a thrilling quest to save humanity from the grasp of an evil sorcerer. Build a team from over 100 unique, hand-drawn Chimera to suit your playstyle. Unlock all the talismans to uncover the mystical secrets behind the Chimeras’ existence.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Map.gif?t=1709053137"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H3.png?t=1709053137"><br/>With a large variety of Chimeras to befriend and command, you'll need to strategize and adapt your playstyle to suit each battle. From tough tanks to speedy attackers, each Chimera brings a unique set of abilities to the table. Your tactical choices will determine your success in battle!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Recruiting.gif?t=1709053137"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H4.png?t=1709053137"><br/>It’s all up to you! Customize your dice for maximum influence over your Chimeras’ attacks and abilities. Control the order in which battles play out and choose when parties take action. Dicefolk defies RNG and gives you unprecedented influence on the roll of the dice! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Battle.gif?t=1709053137"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H5.png?t=1709053137"><br/>Each playthrough offers its own rewards, and the Chimeras you encounter in one run can be entirely different than those you find in another. With different Chimeras comes different strategies to assemble your team for the perfect run!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Anim_H5.gif?t=1709053137"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Dino Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_12" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🦖🐾 WELCOME TO 100 DINO CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🦕🐈</h2>🦎 Join the cutest adventure in the Dino park with Cats and Dinos! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of dinosaurs location and dino-cats as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/600x200.png?t=1709146681"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Dino Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815640/100_Dino_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=DinoCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Extra.png?t=1709146681"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816050/100_Dino_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=DinoCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709146681"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815630/100_Dino_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=DinoCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709146681"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/600x1.png?t=1709146681"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709146681"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803010/100_Robo_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803010/100_Robo_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815640/100_Dino_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815640/100_Dino_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Robo Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803010/100_Robo_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816080/100_Robo_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_12" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816080/100_Robo_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🤖🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ROBO CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🦾🐈</h2>🦿 Join the cutest adventure in the Robot-themed with Cats and Robots! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of Robots location and robo-cats as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803010/extras/600x200.png?t=1709046680"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Robo Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816080/100_Robo_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=RoboCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803010/extras/Extra.png?t=1709046680"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816070/100_Robo_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=RoboCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803010/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709046680"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816090/100_Robo_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=RoboCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803010/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709046680"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803010/extras/600x1.png?t=1709046680"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803010/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709046680"/></a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816080/100_Robo_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=RoboBot" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816080/100_Robo_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=RoboBot</a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?utm_source=RoboBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?utm_source=RoboBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709289385"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709289385"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709289385"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709289385"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709289385"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solium Infernum</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1893810/Solium_Infernum/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare yourself for Solium Infernum, the grand strategy game of politics, intrigue and betrayal, set in the ultimate arena of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingDarkSide2.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_IndulgeYourDarkSide_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Satan's mysteriously vanished and Hell is in an uproar. Play as one of eight all-powerful and menacing Archfiends and indulge your Machiavellian dark side. Command legions, enlist champions, cast sinister rituals, and trick, rob, and insult your rivals to be crowned Hell’s new Dark Majesty.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingStrategy2.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_StrategyFromHell_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Experience Solium Infernum's legendary devilish political machinations. Requiring nerves of steel and a true heart of darkness, every order you give will have lasting consequences. Get into the minds of your rivals, second-guessing their every move both on the map and on the floor of Hell’s parliament as you sling insults and demands in the only truly political strategy game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Eight playable Archfiends<br/></li><li>Eight single-player Chronicles<br/></li><li>Single-player Skirmish mode<br/></li><li>Revelations Tutorial Scenario<br/></li><li>Sessional and Asynchronous 2-6 player Multiplayer<br/></li><li>Dozens of Infernal Legions, including unique enormous Titans. <br/></li><li>Champion Praetors and dark Artifacts fit for any Archfiend!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingMulitplayer.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_InfernalMultiplayer_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Play 2-6 player multiplayer games with your soon-to-be ex-friends in a single session of deceit and politics, or put your friendships to the test in quick daily bursts with Solium Infernum’s infamous asynchronous multiplayer for a truly harrowing scheme-in-your-sleep experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/Heading_DarkArt2.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_DivineMadness_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>If you love dark art, you’re in the right place. Brimming with striking visions of Hell unlike anything you’ve seen before, Solium Infernum is an infernal feast for the eyes with multitudes of individual dark paintings to enjoy. Every item of the game is accompanied by mind-blasting artwork, a feat declaring Solium Infernum a winner of the 2022 Game Makers Sketchbook.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingRessurect.gif?t=1708670283"><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_CultClassic_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Originally inspired by Milton’s epic poem, Paradise Lost, League of Geeks’ (known for seminal digital board game Armello) sophomore title is a re-imagining and modernisation of Vic Davis’ critically acclaimed cult-classic of the same name, hailed as a masterpiece of strategy game design. <br/><br/>Once again, prepare to lose yourself within ‘the cold glory of a difficult decision’ as we resurrect Solium Infernum from the depths of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/label_praise.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Note: The following quotes refer to the original Solium Infernum (2009) by Vic Davis.<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum is a political wargame set in hell… The game is now finished, and none of the friends survived. By which I mean, we all hate each other now.”</i> <br/>- Rock Paper Shotgun<br/><br/><i>“It’s a game about playing other people, in both senses of the word…. This is game design based on psychology as much as rules.” </i><br/>- Quarter to Three<br/><br/><i>“More than any game I've played in years, Solium Infernum nails the sensation of staring at a screen and losing yourself in the cold glory of a difficult decision.”</i><br/>- Game Developer (formerly Gamasutra)<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum kicked my knees out from under me ... this game took my past experience with strategy games and threw it, like a pro basketball player, into a bin eighty feet away.”</i><br/>- Eurogamer<br/><br/><i>“One of the best games of the year.”</i><br/>— Three Moves Ahead<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_toReign.png?t=1708670283"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruindog:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802430/RuindogPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 4 are available in the official version.<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 4 in the official version<br/>Weapons: 3 in the prologue, 26 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/11z.jpg?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>A long, long time ago, in a solar system not so far away, alien bugs invaded Earth, but they were soon beaten back home, and by the way, their home planet was blown up. After centuries of being invincible, it became popular for humans to watch live alien hunting shows, participate in alien hunts, save up money, equipment, and use the various loot they found to keep going to new maps and defeating more powerful enemies. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1y.png?t=1708706298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1z.gif?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>Enemies will come at you from all sides on every level, proceed with caution or you'll be torn to pieces in an instant</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3y.png?t=1708706298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3z.gif?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>Each character has a different growth path and active skills, utilize these skills and choose the most appropriate item for the current hero to achieve the mission objective</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5y.png?t=1708706298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5z.gif?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>Earn more resources and achieve various mission objectives to unlock different maps/difficulties and even new map mechanics!<br/>Each map has very different mission objectives and combat mechanics, so choose the one that better suits the current mechanic to win the game</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kneedle Knight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2491720/Kneedle_Knight/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Kneedle Knight</i> is a third-person, puzzle platformer game developed by students at SMU Guildhall Cohort 32. In <i>Kneedle Knight</i>, the player controls a mouse knight that uses his magical needle to sew fabric which he can merge into, moving back and forth between 3D and 2D. <br/><br/>Sir Lukoss the Small was a noble knight sent on a quest to defeat the evil Witch of Fabric. The Witch, using her enchanted fabric, imprisoned and transformed many citizens and knights into malicious fabrications. Sir Lukoss climbed up through her fortress to put an end to her tyranny, only to be hexed by her magic and transformed into a mouse. In the dark dungeon of the Witch’s lair, the mouse finds a magic needle, granting him special powers to sew fabric of his own and merge in and out of the enchanted threadwork. <br/><br/>Now Sir Lukoss must use his newfound weapon to sew his path forward and up through the evil stronghold. The mouse knight can use his needle to solve puzzles, overcome challenging obstacles, and defeat the animated candle minions of the Witch. All with the hopes of returning to face the Witch of Fabric yet again to finish his noble quest.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Single-player, puzzle platformer game<br/></li><li>Playtime (main story): 1-2 hours<br/></li><li>Playtime (100% achievements): 2 hours<br/></li><li>Steam leaderboard support for level speed running<br/></li><li>Made in Unreal Engine 5<br/></li><li>Original soundtrack</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myth of Empires</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1371580/Myth_of_Empires/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Embark Upon a Thrilling Journey</h2>Explore a land with diverse landscapes, ecologies, and weather, as well as a realistic day/night cycle. The v1.0 release of Myth of Empires also features a new map – Dongzhou Island, offering new adventures and challenges.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/11111探索之旅，发现新世界的惊险旅程.gif?t=1709297673"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Own Empire From the Ground Up</h2>Myth of Empires features sandbox gameplay with a high degree of freedom; the game has 1300+ different crafting recipe, allowing you to build your own empire. The v1.0 release adds new recipes, including mechanical tools and base defenses, as well as a new planting system. The possibilities are endless.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/2【替换Gif】自由创造，打造你的帝国.gif?t=1709297673"><h2 class="bb_tag">Recruit NPCs, Tame Wildlife</h2>In-depth taming and training systems allow players to recruit or subdue additional forces to aid them in combat and production. The v1.0 release adds new boss NPCs and powerful beasts. In addition, smaller types of animals can be used to help power your base’s defenses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/333333驯服万物，NPC、马匹与野生动物.gif?t=1709297673"><h2 class="bb_tag">Wage Epic Wars on Ancient Battlefields</h2> Myth of Empires features hundreds of different weapons, armor, and large-scale engineering equipment. Pick the weapons that best suit your playstyle, or utilize your strategic capabilities to build an army. The v1.0 release introduces powerful mechanical base defenses, wooden oxen, and other new combat equipment to further enrich the game’s deep war experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/4【替换Gif】史诗战争体验，挑战百变的古代战场.gif?t=1709297673"><h2 class="bb_tag">Engage in Cross-server Battles </h2>Establish administrative regions, fight for the position of county magistrate, and compete to expand your territory through Fortress Battles. Craft the perfect guild and utilize your diplomatic prowess to ensure its long-term stability.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/555555跨服征战，共同创造历史.gif?t=1709297673"><h2 class="bb_tag">Write Your Own Legend </h2>With 25 different development paths, a 16-level title system, and more than 100 achievements, you have complete freedom in growing your character. Become a legendary military commander, or content yourself with the life of a simple farmer – the choice is yours.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/6【替换Gif】传奇生涯，定制独特的人生.gif?t=1709297673"><h2 class="bb_tag">Play Multiple Gameplay Modes Offering Endless Possibilities </h2>Myth of Empires supports official servers, custom servers, as well as solo and hosted modes. Creative players are also able to use the game’s robust mod editor to tailor the game to their dream experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/no7多样玩法.gif?t=1709297673"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Epoch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/899770/Last_Epoch/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Epoch combines time travel, exciting dungeon crawling, engrossing character customization and endless replayability to create an Action RPG for veterans and newcomers alike. Travel through the world of Eterra’s past and face dark empires, wrathful gods and untouched wilds – to find a way to save time itself from The Void.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Gameplay.gif?t=1709060046"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>15 Mastery Classes</strong><br/>Embark on your adventure as one of five powerful classes and, through your journey, ascend into a unique Mastery Class that unlocks more specialized abilities and build-options. <br/></li><li><strong>120+ Skill Trees</strong><br/>Every skill has its own augment tree that will allow you to control, alter, and empower your playstyle. Transform your skeletons into archers, your lightning blast into chain lightning, or make your serpent strike summon snakes to fight alongside you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Nodes.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Hunt Rare &amp; Powerful Loot</strong><br/>Fill your arsenal with magic items that you may craft to perfection, change the rules of your build with powerful unique and set items, and always have that next upgrade just on the horizon with Last Epoch's deep and randomized loot system.<br/></li><li><strong>Rewarding Crafting System</strong><br/>The items you wield are yours to forge! Last Epoch’s community-revered crafting system allows you to control your character's power progression, featuring robust and deterministic upgrade mechanics.<br/></li><li><strong>Uncover the Past, Reforge the Future</strong><br/>Travel to different moments of time where you will discover the many factions and secrets that exist within the world of Eterra and fight to set the timeline onto a new path.<br/></li><li><strong>Endless replayability</strong><br/>With a wealth of classes and skills to customize, deep game systems, randomized loot, and continuing development, Last Epoch is a game that will keep you coming back for years to come.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Monolith.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Easy to Learn, Hard to Master</strong><br/>We’re committed to making gameplay approachable for new and veteran players alike by allowing you to jump into the fray quickly and providing many in-game resources. Though don’t be fooled, Eterra has many dangers waiting for you that require a mastery of combat and build-crafting.<br/></li><li><strong>Zero Pay-To-Win</strong><br/>Last Epoch will never offer gameplay advantages by being able to spend real money. We believe in creating a fair environment for all players. </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminator: Dark Fate - Defiance</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1839950/Terminator_Dark_Fate__Defiance/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif1.gif?t=1709216510"><br/><strong>Terminator: Dark Fate – Defiance</strong> is a <strong>real-time strategy game</strong> based on the Terminator: Dark Fate universe that follows the war between humanity and Legion's synthetic intelligent machine network.<br/><br/>In the<strong> single-player campaign</strong>, you take the role of a commander in the Founders, a force made up of the remnants of the US military and guide your army in an attempt to foil Legion's plan to exterminate the last remnants of humanity. In skirmish and multiplayer modes, play as three very diverse factions: Founders, Movement and Legion.<br/><br/>Take control of an army carried over from mission to mission on a series of large strategic maps. Make decisions about unit placement, battle tactics and abilities so that you don’t just survive but can become the leader of the resistance against the machines. Hone your skills and military expertise by replaying and achieving the best possible outcomes.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic battlefields: realistic tactics and consequences</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif2.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>Engage in complex, realistic battles where your <strong>tactical decisions</strong> are vital to your survival and ultimate victory. Use a variety of military equipment, vehicles and ammunition types in your battles against the enemy. Recruit and train new units, assign new skills and acquire new weapons and equipment to continue the resistance.<br/><br/>Encounter tense battles. Your battlefield tactics and choices have deep consequences that will impact through the campaign, with other factions and characters either joining you or fighting against you, and with certain missions being available or not depending on your actions. <br/><br/><strong>Your resources are limited</strong> and you must protect your army. Weapons of war receive damage through a modular component damage system where armour characteristics, component malfunctions and hull structure all affect if your troops survive.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Lead the survival of mankind</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif3.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>Recruit others to your cause and <strong>grow your army</strong>. Mix and match the composition of your troops to fit your preferred battle tactics. Use infantry units, heavy armoured military vehicles, plasma cannon technology, drones and other flying units and even human skirmishers to achieve victory.<br/><br/>Use the battlefield to your advantage! <strong>Physics-based building demolition</strong> lets you generate a realistic set of tactical consequences, especially in urban areas.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer Mayhem: Skirmish and Online Battles</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif4.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>The excitement amplifies in <strong>skirmish and multiplayer modes</strong>, where <strong>you can play as three distinct factions</strong>: Founders, Movement, and Legion. <br/><br/>Engage in epic battles across vast strategic landscapes, testing your skills and military expertise. Every decision matters, impacting alliances, missions, and the overall survival of mankind.<br/><br/>Challenge your skills in skirmish and online multiplayer matches, facing off against AI or real-life human opponents in intense 1v1 and 2v2 battles.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penny’s Big Breakaway</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1955230/Pennys_Big_Breakaway/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ready. Set. YO! - Join Penny &amp; Yo-Yo in a kinetic 3D-platformer bursting with innovative gameplay! Showcase your catalog of tricks and chain impressive combos to deliver Penny &amp; Yo-Yo's perfect breakout performance. Take the stage with this vibrant pair in Penny’s Big Breakaway.<br/><br/>Penny is a street performer with big dreams; she has her own spin on what it takes to be a star! When Eddie the Emperor calls for new Palace Court Performers, Penny gets herself tangled in an audition she’ll never forget. A strange encounter with a Cosmic String transforms Penny’s Yo-Yo into a living creature with an appetite for snacks— and mayhem! Use Yo-Yo to help Penny clear her name, outrun the Emperor’s penguin army, and unravel the mystery of the Cosmic String. <br/><br/>Burst onto the scene in the fluorescent world of Macaroon, home to this over-and-under escape! Discover your true star power in this easy-to-play, difficult-to-master challenge. Penny’s Big Breakaway is the debut title from Evening Star.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-01-Supertitles.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Key Features: <br/><br/>Walk the Dog: Yo-Yo’s big appetite will earn an even bigger reward with snack power-ups! Use these tasty treats to temporarily transform Yo-Yo, granting it the abilities to improve movement speed, protect Penny from harm, and much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-02-WalktheDog.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Around the World: Flee from Eddie the Emperor’s massive penguin army as they chase you clear across the planet! These clumsy flightless birds patrol the halls, come bursting through walls, and will stop at nothing to seize you! Help out friendly denizens along the way and make use of your spectacular surroundings to evade your capturers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-03-AroundTheWorld.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Encore Stage: Play your way with multiple game modes! Show off your skills as you chain awesome combos and rack up multipliers in Story Mode. Take on the ultimate speedrunning challenge and dominate the leaderboard in Time Attack Mode. Redeem coins for bonus items, secret stages, and more unlockable extras.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-04-EncoreStage.gif?t=1708524042"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2379780/Balatro/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Balatro is a poker-inspired roguelike deck builder all about creating powerful synergies and winning big.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Endless_Possibility.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/>Combine valid poker hands with unique Joker cards in order to create varied synergies and builds. Earn enough chips to beat devious blinds, all while uncovering hidden bonus hands and decks as you progress. You’re going to need every edge you can get in order to reach the boss blind, beat the final ante and secure victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Jokers_Clean_Thin.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The definitive poker roguelike experience.<br/></li><li>Endless possibilities - every pick-up, discard and joker can dramatically alter the course of your run.<br/></li><li>In-depth campaign mode complete with 8 difficulties, as well as challenge, daily and seeded runs. </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Break_The_Game.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/>Deftly deploy an array of potent tools: different Decks, Jokers, Tarot cards, Planet cards, Spectral cards, and Vouchers. Use these versatile instruments to ignite a combo frenzy and turbocharge your poker hands, crafting electrifying, adrenaline-fueled synergies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro_5_Aces_GIF__HQ_.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 Jokers, each with their own unique abilities<br/></li><li>15 Decks with distinct modifiers to choose from for each run<br/></li><li>5 potential variants of each Joker which add further abilities<br/></li><li>22 Tarot cards variants that can enhance your regular playing cards<br/></li><li>11 Planet cards that help level up your possible poker hands<br/></li><li>32 Voucher cards to help provide permanent buffs for your current run</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Find_Your_Flow.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in Balatro’s distinctive psychedelic world. Let the synthwave soundtrack wash over you -  wind down, escape the daily grind and prepare to enter the ultimate roguelike flow state.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improve your collection and discover new cards and secrets with every single run.<br/></li><li>Make use of the in-depth stats screen to study your best hands, most used Jokers, and more!<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the CRT fuzz and enjoy detailed, hand-crafted pixel art.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Spectral_Pack.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F5mH3dNhjx2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro-join_the_discord.png?t=1709312324"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please, Touch The Artwork 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2600140/Please_Touch_The_Artwork_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Disclaimer:</strong><i> This is a short game made in</i> <strong>6 months</strong><i>. It's</i> <strong>100% FREE</strong><i>(no ads, no dlc's), made by a </i><strong>solo dev</strong><i> in honour of James Ensor’s 75 year remembrance.</i> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/extras/Steam3DRoomGIF_Wide.gif?t=1708975190"><br/><br/>Touch the artwork and help a lost skeleton artist find its way home in a surreal, hand-painted universe. <br/><br/>Collect hidden objects for its quirky inhabitants, solve casual puzzles, and restore cracks in the fabric of the paintings. <br/><br/>This slow paced relaxing adventure was carefully crafted from works by James Ensor, a Belgian pioneer in the world of Modern Art.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Hidden object adventure<br/></li><li>5 unique worlds<br/></li><li>Hints when stuck<br/></li><li>Casual point &amp; click gameplay<br/></li><li>Zoom-in for extra details<br/></li><li>Real hand-painted art<br/></li><li>Atmospheric relaxing sound<br/></li><li>Silly and quirky<br/></li><li>Slow-paced &amp; relaxing<br/></li><li>Fit for ages 12-99</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Small Mazes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2570630/20_Small_Mazes/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2570630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a puzzle game with twenty small mazes. If you solve the mazes, you beat the game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>It's about 1-2 hours long, maybe.<br/></li><li>You need a keyboard and mouse to play it. One person played through the whole game on the Steam Deck, but I tried it and think it's better on PC.<br/></li><li> A few puzzles require knowledge of English. No puzzle requires sound or audio to solve it. No puzzle requires being able to recognize different colors.</li></ul> <br/>I hope you enjoy it. <br/> 						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonder</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692570/Sonder/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Local Co-op requires a gamepad controller for both players. Online Co-op supports mouse and keyboard. </i><h2 class="bb_tag">Psychological narrative </h2>- After a mass-scale destruction of all artificial intelligence, a scrapped robot and soul form an unexpected friendship. After a mysterious train knocks them out, they wake up in a world shaped by their own thoughts. Will they be able to cooperate and escape this dark reality?<h2 class="bb_tag">Immersive atmosphere </h2>- Immerse yourself in an atmospheric world crafted with a stylish, minimalistic approach that captivates your attention and enhances the shared adventure. Unleash the power of collaboration, confront existential mysteries, and embark on a gaming journey like no other.<h2 class="bb_tag">Collaboration </h2>- Work together - succeed together. Each character has unique abilities that allow them to manipulate the world in their own way, meaning they can only proceed if they cooperate. In combat, maximum efficiency can be achieved by combining the player’s powers, allowing them to neutralize the most dangerous of foes.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider I-III Remastered Starring Lara Croft</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2478970/Tomb_Raider_IIII_Remastered_Starring_Lara_Croft/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2478970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover Lara Croft’s Original Adventures, Lovingly Restored</h2> <br/>Play the Original Three Tomb Raider Adventures: For the first time ever, play the complete experience with all expansions and secret levels on modern platforms in this definitive collection.<h2 class="bb_tag">Included Game Titles</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tomb Raider I + Unfinished Business<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider II + Golden Mask<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider III + The Lost Artifact</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><strong>Solve Ancient Mysteries</strong>: Uncover treasures of the ancient world by solving puzzles and unraveling mysteries lost to the ravages of time.<br/><br/><strong>Globe-trotting Adventure</strong>: Follow Lara Croft around the world and face off against deadly foes and dangerous myths.<br/><br/><strong>Lovingly Restored</strong>: Experience the classics boasting upgraded graphics, with the option to switch to the original polygon look at any time.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Will:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802530/Space_WillPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 10 in the prologue, 59 in the official version<br/>Galaxy: 2 in the prologue, 6 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><strong>Sixty basic cores, hundreds of base station equipment, and thousands of chips, you can freely cooperate and shoot through the dual-angle joystick operation in a survival Roguelike game! Explore the sci-fi space and build your strongest battleship!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Step 1: Choose a "core" as your basic role<br/>Step 2: Choose a "crew" as your initial weapon<br/>Step 3: Select a galaxy for exploration</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game will continuously collect new "units" or "chips" during the exploration process<br/>Using "crew" can expand weapons and enhance combat effectiveness for your warship<br/>Using "chips" can enhance various abilities of your warship</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Each "core" or "unit" has a maximum of 4 interfaces. When the interfaces are used up, you cannot equip more parts, but you can also infinitely increase the number of your interfaces!<br/>Each "crew" can use the right mouse button to rotate and adjust the optimal angle for combat</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game features dual joystick shooting, with the keyboard moving and the mouse aiming at the enemy. Of course, there are many weapons that can automatically attack or be placed in the scene as traps for use~</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_TITLE_FULLSCREEN.gif?t=1709120669"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_1.png?t=1709120669"><br/> <br/>In New Eden, 1695, communities of settlers are plagued by a dreadful curse. As Banishers, step into their lives, investigate the source of evil, unravel chilling mysteries, explore diverse landscapes, and interact with unforgettable characters whose fate lies in your hands.<br/><br/>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden is an all-new title crafted by renowned studio DON'T NOD, known for their acclaimed titles such as Life is Strange and Vampyr. Immerse yourself in an intimate narrative Action-RPG, taking you on an exhilarating journey between life, death, love and sacrifices.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_2.png?t=1709120669"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_FANTASY.gif?t=1709120669"><br/>Play as a couple of Banishers, Red and Antea, experienced spirit hunters entrusted with the daunting task of dispelling a malevolent curse through powerful rituals. Protect the living from the threat of lingering ghosts and specters, and become a beacon of hope in a world consumed by darkness.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_3.png?t=1709120669"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_NARATION_LOVE.gif?t=1709120669"><br/>Experience a heart-wrenching love story between Antea Duarte and Red mac Raith. When Antea is killed and turned into a spirit, you find yourself facing a choice. Will you uphold your oath and ascend her soul, or will you sacrifice the living in the hope of bringing her back? Your decisions will shape the fate of New Eden’s inhabitants - may they be living or dead, and determine the end of your journey.<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>BLAME</strong> the living and sacrifice their lives, holding them responsible for their actions<br/></li><li><strong>BANISH</strong> souls of the departed, condemning them to eternal suffering<br/></li><li><strong>ASCEND</strong> souls, liberating them from eternal sorrow and granting them serenity</li></ul><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_4.png?t=1709120669"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_COMBAT.gif?t=1709120669"><br/>Banishers are specialized in combat against undead creatures, such as specters or ghosts. Combine Red's physical arsenal with Antea's supernatural powers in a dynamic combat system. Find your own style by mixing weapon attacks and spiritual abilities. Powerful synergies will lead you to defeat New Eden’s most dangerous enemies and bosses.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_6.png?t=1709120669"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_SKILL.gif?t=1709120669"><br/>Unleash the full power of the Banishers by unlocking new gear and supernatural abilities. By exploring New Eden, you will find ancient artifacts, trinkets and valuable resources to enhance your equipment in preparation of future fights. In addition to your arsenal, progress in Antea’s skill trees to upgrade her devastating spectral powers and unseal new combos.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_5.png?t=1709120669"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_EXPLORATION.gif?t=1709120669"><br/>Investigate haunting cases in a mystical world full of dark secrets. Discover New Eden, a North America settlement marked by terrible stories and secrets of its tormented inhabitants. Understanding each resident’s motivations will be essential to guide your decisions throughout the game.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_7.png?t=1709120669"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let Them Breathe: Hello Mother</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2787890/Let_Them_Breathe_Hello_Mother/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Mrs. Chen, the mother of Jesse Chen, is asked to pick up some documents; these documents reside at the University of Tokyo where she used to work. Upon her picking up these documents, she engages with audio recordings and diary entries that tells her what exactly took place in the experimentation room.<br>
<br>
Follow Mrs. Chen and discover more about the world of Let Them Breathe. In this walking simulation and collectable game, you will explore a small abandoned laboratory. Within the different compartments of the library, you will find items in which you will be able to engage with such as recordings, and documents in which you have to collect so as to win the game. <br>
<br>
In this casual short game with a spice of thriller, the atmosphere allows for the player to walk the environment to discover what took place within various locations of the game. The player will find out more about the location, and the two individuals who once occupied the space prior to the player's arrival. <br>
<br>
Let Them Breathe: Hello Mother is a video game that takes place within the Let Them Breathe franchise. It tells the story of Mrs. Chen who is the mother of one of the characters in the indie web series and even the indie movie, Let Them Breathe: City on the Ocean.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suborbital</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2528640/Suborbital/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2528640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Many many years into the future, humanity has created and used warp drives. However, due to the recency of the technology, it still has many flaws. You are equipped with experimental engines and a warp drive, and you are tasked with finding the wreck of the EV Triumph, a large exploratory ship which lost contact on its journey through deep space. The reason was unknown, but you suffer the same fate.<br>
<br>
Brace for a journey into the unknown. Explore a massive wreck and salvage materials to get out of your time-limited survival situation as quickly as possible. Every decision you make could mean the difference between life and death: Resourcefulness and strategy will be tested as you scavenge for supplies, and your ever decreasing oxygen levels keep you on your toes.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit Hole</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2831340/Rabbit_Hole/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/smaller.png?t=1709337648"><br/><strong><i>“Remember you will live.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Rabbit Hole is a fast paced, tough-as-nails 2D Platformer-RogueLike-Shooter inspired by popular roguelikes, made with a love for the genre. <br/>You are Disc, someone who was suddenly brought to the Rabbit Hole. <br/>Collect guns, fight foes and meet strange new characters on your descent to the bottom, all in an attempt to find your heart again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/1.gif?t=1709337648"><br/><strong><i>“This place is like its own ecosystem. A big living breathing mess.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Every run is different. Enjoy hours of replayable content through randomly generated floor layouts and 50+ weapons to collect and use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/2.gif?t=1709337648"><br/><strong><i>“Hey, hey, hey! How's my favorite anxiety-fueled nutjob!”</i></strong><br/><br/>Unlock new characters with diverse playstyles. Each of the 6 unlockable characters keep gameplay fresh and give a unique perspective on the gameplay loop.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/3.gif?t=1709337648"><br/><strong><i>“There was a blank line, almost as if I had erased it”</i></strong><br/><br/>Discover the truth that lies beneath the surface. Collect books and fill out your library to understand its unseen history. In the end, you may even come to understand yourself?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speed NFL</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816550/Speed_NFL/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2816550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Play a football (American) game in 25 minutes. Select your team before using the NFL rankings to decide on your offensive tactics.<br>
<br>
Key Features<br>
<br>
NFL ranking<br>
Betting odds<br>
Play options - rush, Screen, Shotgun, bomb, side-line, end-zone, hail Mary, FG and punt<br/>
Time-outs<br/>
Flags<br/>
Scoreboard<br/>
Stats<br/>
Quarter by Quarter<br/>
OT<br/>
Team colours<br/>
Player names<br/>
Plaver v Player or Player v Computer<br/>
<br/>
Game uses the ZX Spectrum interface.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Secret of Varonis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2174900/The_Secret_of_Varonis/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2174900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Come join us on Discord! <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FRKjYSATbTe" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/RKjYSATbTe</a><h2 class="bb_tag">An indie Gameboy-style RPG!</h2>The Secret of Varonis features old-school combat mechanics and visuals faithful to the gaming heyday of 1989. If you're nostalgic for retro games, or just looking for a good, challenging RPG, look no further.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Choose a party of humans, espers, robots, and monsters, each with a unique leveling scheme<br/></li><li>Employ over 500 combat items and abilities, either learned, looted, bought, or crafted<br/></li><li>Explore five unique worlds, each with their own story and characters, plus the sealed city of Varonis which unites them all...<br/></li><li>Enjoy the best of oldschool mechanics without the pain points: no required grinding, optional field encounter mode, and other newschool ideas</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">What lies beyond the gate?</h2>The city of Varonis once housed a wondrous portal. Wisemen and scientists emerged, bearing new technology and powerful artifacts. But when dangerous monsters also spilled out, the portal was sealed and the city abandoned. Jonas and Janine, two warrior twins, set out to discover what has become of the secret city, but when they fail to return, it is up to four village youths (and their trusty robot) to rescue them... and uncover the truth behind the gate of Varonis.<h2 class="bb_tag">The four races</h2>To challenge Varonis and the many trials beyond, you'll need to build your own party:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Humans - Sturdy generalists who buy potions to advance in stats. They carry swords, saws, shotguns, spellbooks... Versatility is key!<br/></li><li>Espers - Natural-born fighters that learn from combat, granting stats, abilities, and powerful multitarget magic.<br/></li><li>Robots - Customizable companions that can be built in many different ways. A tankbot made of armor? A ninjabot made of swords?<br/></li><li>Monsters - Scrappy shapeshifters whose role in combat can change in a flash. Most monster abilities can be found nowhere else.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In a Detective's Mind</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2814270/In_a_Detectives_Mind/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2814270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In a Detective's Mind is a short game made by two people, where you will play as Andrew, a detective who is learning to deal with the problems of his past. You will have to solve two cases, where you will receive very few details about what happened. The objective is for you to be able to put together in your head what happened in the place, with as little detail as possible, so it will be important that you explore and make deductions, so that you can solve the cases and puzzles in the game.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build your destiny</h2>Being a detective is not an easy task. With each new case you decide to investigate, new people have their fates sealed in your hands. One word, one wrong accusation can mean the end of an innocent life.<br/><br/>In a Detective's Mind proposes an experience where your decisions matter, changing not only the destiny of the people around you, but yours as well. Having <u>3 different endings</u>, In a Detective's Mind takes you on a journey of no return.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MegaBlasters!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2071420/MegaBlasters/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071420/extras/AmazingGifNew.gif?t=1709326367"><br/><br/>Get ready to laugh and blast through 100 physics-based maps in this comedic multiplayer FPS game. With wacky weapons and fast-paced action, it's a hilarious and explosive experience for you and your friends.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071420/extras/Features_Banner.png?t=1709326367"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play with 3 other blasters, either friends or random (all wrigglin' around)<br/></li><li>Chaotic physics based guns <br/></li><li>100+ Chaotic physics maps (with destructive maps for destructive people)<br/></li><li>Quick in-game chat (distract n' kill lol)<br/></li><li>Who doesn't like blackholes and stuff?<br/></li><li>Make someone go boom (sus bomb)<br/></li><li>Noodle limbs (cuz why not)<br/></li><li>Punch with your noodle hands</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gloomgeons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2800550/Gloomgeons/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2800550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Gloomgeons</strong> is a retro style 3D first person perspective game that combines the nostalgia of legend FPS games with the dungeons exploration. Step into a mysterious world of skeletons, wizards and golems. Unlock four weapons, collect treasure and find secret rooms. The game consists of 24 levels divided into 3 parts.<br/><br/><strong>Controls:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> W A S D - move<br/></li><li> Space or E - activate<br/></li><li> Mouse - look and shoot<br/></li><li> Shift - run<br/></li><li> 1 2 3 4 - select weapon</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HuntForOut</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2010560/HuntForOut/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2010560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							HuntForOut is a survival FPS game, where your main goal is to get out from The Labyrinth before it collapses. You need to collect special, holy cat parts, different runes, and much more to exit from this horrific maze. The task won't be easy; there are a lot of dangers in this mysterious place, and the walls are always moving to harden your way…<br>
<br>
HuntForOut is in development from the spring of 2021 and soon it will be available to download from Steam.<br>
<br>
See you soon adventurers!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolt'N'Punch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779390/BoltNPunch/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2779390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Food for Thought</i> strives to deliver the best food products to the common people, but when its robot workers turn against Lyft, the last human in the factory, she has to step up and punch some steel. Uncover the truth behind this attack, find your boss for answers, and put an end to this with style and power.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2779390/extras/KSP1_EN.gif?t=1709319713">Unleash powerful blows to enemies, use them as a weapon and utilize the environment to your advantage.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2779390/extras/KSP2_EN.gif?t=1709319713">Delve deep inside <i>Food for Thought</i>'s factory and unravel the dark secrets that have been hidden for many years.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2779390/extras/KSP3_EN.gif?t=1709319713">Encounter a variety of enemies that can punch, shoot or block your attacks. Finish them off in style with a devastating blow.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BattleCakes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1062860/BattleCakes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1062860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1062860/extras/about-header-sky.png?t=1709321614"><br/><br/>Indulge in a deliciously delightful world of sweetness as you head out on an adventure to save<br/>the day! Play as Birthday Sprinkle, the cupcake hero that you personalize and create, as you<br/>explore the whimsical world of Pasteleria. Meet charming and endearing friends along the way<br/>like Red Velvet, Midnite Truffle and more as you work together to uncover the mysteries and<br/>hardships plaguing the nearby towns. Choose your approach by either battling or befriending<br/>the monsters who stand in your way. Discover the joy of friendship and community as you fight to leave the world better off than you found it and make your mark. <br/><br/>Stop and smell the frosting in this candy-colored, and cheerful atmosphere while enjoying the<br/>adorably cozy vibes. Immerse yourself in child-like wonder as you celebrate your individuality<br/>by designing your cupcake to reflect who you are. Don’t forget to take a moment to relax to<br/>find and pet all the Jellyroll cats who are just waiting to be snuggled.<br/><br/>Do you think <i>you</i> have what it takes to join the legendary Battlecakes? Of course you do. High<br/>five!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1062860/extras/section-header-features.png?t=1709321614"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Customize your cupcake hero! Bake your best life with loads of fun colors and fashionable frosting styles.<br/></li><li>Save the day your way! Monsters abound in Pasteleria—you decide whether to befriend them and walk away with new pals, or battle it out and take ‘em down.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1062860/extras/Steam_Feature_1.gif?t=1709321614"><br/></img></li><li>Explore a candy-colored world of magic, fun, and mystery! From the fragrant fields of Vanilla Hill to the sticky swamps of Nougat Hollow, your sweet adventure awaits!<br/></li><li>Choose your path! Any quest, monster, and resident of Pasteleria could send your story in a different direction, and it’s all up to what kind of cupcake you choose to be.<br/></li><li>Pet all the cats! Jellyroll cats love to explore, but they love a good snuggle even more. Can you find and pet every Jellyroll cat peppered throughout Pasteleria?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1062860/extras/Steam_feature_2.gif?t=1709321614"/></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1062860/extras/about-befriend.png?t=1709321614"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toki Pona Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2750290/Toki_Pona_Island/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2750290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Toki Pona Island is 2D language learning adventure game!<br/><br/>After a teleportation incident, you wake up on a tropical island inhabited by a variety of interesting locals. Unfortunately, none of them speak your language. Therefore, you'll have to learn theirs instead if you want to cooperate. The good news is that the Toki Pona is relatively easy language to learn. Slowly, but surely you'll acquire more of the language, learn to understand the grammar, and build familiarity with common phrases. Master this unfamiliar language and you might just find a way to make it back home!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A whole tropical island to explore.<br/></li><li>Over 2 dozen quests.<br/></li><li>Comprehensive grammar lessons.<br/></li><li>A cast of unique characters.<br/></li><li>An easy to use translation system.<br/></li><li>Non-linear story progression.<br/></li><li>Full Xbox controller support.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cucumber Champion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2823470/Cucumber_Champion/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2823470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In "Cucumber Champion" embark on a whimsical journey into the fantastical world of cats where you, as the valiant Cucumber Warrior, wield a cucumber as your mighty weapon. The adventure begins with a curious cat animation pondering its purpose with the text "What am I doing?" before being whisked away into the depths of its own imagination, revealing a realm teeming with feline wonders.<br>
<br>
As the protagonist, you encounter a motley crew of quirky cats who proclaim that you are the legendary Cucumber Champion destined to save their world. But before you can fulfil your destiny, you must first prove your prowess by vanquishing formidable foes.<br>
<br>
Your journey unfolds with a series of comical encounters, starting with facing off against the first enemy amidst a backdrop of amusing cat pictures. Soon, you find yourself navigating through a treacherous dungeon, where you must employ your wits to locate a crucial key. However, your task is interrupted by the sudden appearance of a colossal meatball, which ominously warns you to flee. Despite the threat, the meatball reveals a surprising kindness, allowing you to escape unscathed.<br>
<br>
With the key in hand, you unlock the path to the final showdown—a climactic battle where you transform into the BUFF cat, brimming with muscles and determination. In a fierce clash against formidable adversaries, you unleash the full might of your cucumber prowess, emerging victorious as the revered Cucumber Champion.<br/>
<br/>
Cucumber Champion is a 5-10 minute game that serves as a start to the Relevation Studios universe. Multiverse?...something?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Beyond: Ulti</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2700070/Behind_the_Beyond_Ulti/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Grab your deck and pull up a chair! This is Ulti, the official card game of the world of <strong>Behind the Beyond</strong> (...and Hungary too).</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700070/extras/ulti_btb_jancsi.png?t=1709316160"><br/><br/>You play as Jancsi, the protagonist of Behind the Beyond. After learning the rules from your host, Zsuzsi, you can set yourself against the best Ulti players of your village! Or jump in head-first without a tutorial - we’re not judging.<br/><br/>In its core, <i>Behind the Beyond: Ulti</i> is exactly the same great card game that you can play with select characters in Behind the Beyond. It has the same logic and the same opponents, but we made this shiny new second home for it, so you can play Ulti on its own. We also added some cool features like stats and achievements.<br/><br/>Don’t worry, playing <i>Behind the Beyond: Ulti</i> won’t spoil the story of the main game!<br/><br/><i>Behind the Beyond: Ulti</i> is feature-complete and includes all currently available opponents from Behind the Beyond.<br/>Should we change anything in the Ulti game within Behind the Beyond, we will make the same changes here too.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700070/extras/do_you_even_trnsp.png?t=1709316160"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Mergers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2821220/Space_Mergers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2821220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2821220/extras/MainCapSteamReal.png?t=1709316042"><br/><br/><strong>Space Mergers</strong> is a satisfying fast-paced puzzle game that encourages critical thinking. Combine blocks to create combos and gain points, reach the highest score you can! There is over a million different ways to play if you fiddle with the settings.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gamemodes</h2>There are two different game modes <strong>arcade</strong> and <strong>frenzy</strong>. The difference between them is the frequency of certain blocks that fall. In <strong>frenzy</strong> the lower the number on the block the more of that block will be on the board, allowing you to combo more easily with it, but at the expense of points since lower blocks will fall more often. In <strong>arcade</strong> the blocks that fall are completely randomized.<h2 class="bb_tag">Settings</h2>You can alter the settings of the board within the settings menu. The music volume, amount of rows and columns, the amount of seconds it takes for a new row of coins to drop in a game, and the spawn rate of power blocks are all editable within this menu. <br/><br/><strong>Here are the possible applicable settings</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Music: 0%-100%<br/></li><li> Rows: 5-50<br/></li><li> Columns: 5-50<br/></li><li> Seconds till fall: 1-60<br/></li><li> Power Block Spawn Rate: 0%-10%</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Scoreboard Info</h2>The game has a local scoreboard that keeps track of your top 5 scores. There are setting restrictions that will keep you from getting on the scoreboard.<br/>To be able to get onto the scoreboard your settings must be set to meet the requirements below: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 20 or less rows and columns<br/></li><li> Fall rate must be 5 or below<br/></li><li> Power block spawn rate must be 1% or below</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Controls</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Z</strong> is used to pull blocks toward you, once you pull a block you can only pull more of the same block until you push it back outward<br/></li><li> <strong>X</strong> is used to push blocks out toward the board, if a block hits a clone of itself and meets combo conditions it will trigger a combo<br/></li><li> <strong>P</strong> is used to enter the pause menu in game<br/></li><li> <strong>D</strong> is used to drop a row of blocks immediately<br/></li><li> <strong>Arrow keys</strong> allow you to move around the menus and also move your ship in game<br/></li><li> <strong>Enter</strong> will let you select menu items </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Combos</h2>Blocks will combo if they have enough blocks in a contiguous state of the same type. If you have more blocks than you need it will still combo all of them. When you make a combo you gain points respective to how many blocks you combo times the number on the block.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Ones (1): Need 5 to combo and will turn into a five (5)<br/></li><li> Fives (5): Need 2 to combo and will turn into a ten (10)<br/></li><li> Tens (10): Need 5 to combo and will turn into a fifty (50)<br/></li><li> Fifty's (50): Need 2 to combo and will turn into a hundred (100)<br/></li><li> Hundreds (100): Need 5 to combo and will turn into a five hundred (500)<br/></li><li> Five Hundreds (500): Need 2 to combo and will disappear into thin air<br/><br/></li><li> Axe Power Block (🪓): Need 2 to combo and will destroy all blocks on the screen of the type of block under it.<br/></li><li> Ship Power Block (🚀): Need 2 to combo and will spawn a destroyer ship on the row you combo it</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spell Disk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2292060/Spell_Disk/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Spell Disk is a rogue-lite action game with a unique synergy building mechanic so that your runs can never be the same. Strategize and create your own spell combo synergies to blast through enemies on your way! Each run is unique, so you must plan out how to build your power.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/extras/combo_paper.gif?t=1709316039"><br/>Discover combos and synergies that no one’s seen before! Maximize your power to better your chance of escaping the dungeon of Spell Disk.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/extras/Items_Updated.gif?t=1709316039"><br/>Craft spells, disks, and artifacts during your run that synergies with each other in their own ways.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/extras/Lobby_Updated.gif?t=1709316039"><br/>Unlock new weapons and powers to hack and slash through the enemies blocking your way.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic Seeker: a mimic's odyssey - chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2412830/Magic_Seeker_a_mimics_odyssey__chapter_1/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2412830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the world of "MAGIKA".<br/>Adventure yourself in a land filled with mystery, magic and most of all "mimics".<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2412830/extras/Map003.png?t=1709314619"><br/>Unravel the mystery around your amnesia by exploring and fighting incredible turn-base fights, but be carfull, the enemys might be "ANYTHING".<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2412830/extras/Rokatrio.png?t=1709314619"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2412830/extras/Signio.png?t=1709314619"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vivaland: Dream House</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2606170/Vivaland_Dream_House/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2606170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1976830" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1976830</a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2606170/extras/ezgif-3-474fd0310c.gif?t=1709314012"><h2 class="bb_tag">Introducing the Vivaland Prologue: Dream House</h2><strong>Build Mode: Craft Your Dreams</strong><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in one of the core game modes of Vivaland: the Build Mode. It's a sandbox where you have control over architectural and design elements, enabling you to construct and decorate a house from the ground up!<br/><br/><strong>Get to Know the First Town of Vivaland</strong><br/><br/>The town of Vivaland offers 8 residential lots, each awaiting your personal touch. Claim your slice of the town, visit your friends' properties, and collaborate on grand projects that will redefine the neighborhood.<br/><br/><strong>Seamless Single and Co-op Experience</strong><br/><br/>Begin your Vivaland adventure either as a lone explorer or with your friends by your side – the choice is yours. You can build together with up to 8 players<br/><strong>Content</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Walls Toolkit:</strong> Build with single wall, curved wall and the room tool!<br/></li><li><strong>Doors &amp; Windows:</strong> Choose entrances and views that reflect your taste.<br/></li><li><strong>Foundations, Multiple Floors, and Stairs: </strong>Build structures that rise to new heights.<br/></li><li><strong>Furniture:</strong> Design with a vast selection of interior items.<br/></li><li><strong>Roofing:</strong> Choose from 10 distinct styles and an array of roof patterns.<br/></li><li><strong>Different styles of items:</strong>  Bohemian, Retro, Victorian, Antique, Cottagecore, Gothic, Modern, Minimalist, Industrial.</li></ul><br/><strong>Functional Freedom</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Resizable Objects:</strong> Adjusting the size of decorative objects.<br/></li><li><strong>Recolorable Furniture and Decor: </strong> Fine-tune your interior design with your color palettes. Save favorite shades and match your items.<br/></li><li><strong>Room Dimension Flexibility: </strong>Tweak the height and width of your rooms.<br/></li><li><strong>Grid Function: </strong>Precise item placement is a breeze with toggleable grid support.<br/></li><li><strong>Intuitive Controls and Snapping: </strong>Seamlessly move and arrange objects.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dangerous FightCIA</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684310/Dangerous_FightCIA/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Description:<br>
<br>
Welcome to the adrenaline-pumping adventure "Dangerous Fight" - an online shooter that will take you to the heart of the action in the atmosphere of the city of Yerevan, Armenia. You will go into epic battles where the technology of the future and the cultural heritage of the ancient city mix.<br>
<br>
Peculiarities:<br>
<br>
🔫Weapons and technologies of the future: Arm yourself with advanced weapons equipped with advanced technologies and immerse yourself in exciting battles.<br/>
<br/>
🌆Battle in Yerevan: Discover the streets of Yerevan in detail, where every corner hides danger and every street becomes a battlefield.<br/>
<br/>
👥 Multiplayer mode: Join friends or create your own team for cooperative and competitive battles online.<br/>
<br/>
🚨 Dangerous missions: Complete secret missions, become a special agent and confront dangerous opponents.<br/>
<br/>
🌐 The world in your pocket: Discover the world of online operations where your skill and teamwork decide the outcome of the battle.<br/>
<br/>
💡 Evolution of Personalization: Personalize your character with a variety of customizations to stand out in the world of Dangerous Fight.<br/>
<br/>
🎮 Regular Updates: New levels, weapons and game modes promise constant challenges to keep you interested night after night.<br/>
<br/>
Join "Dangerous Fight" right now and become part of this exciting online battle, where every moment is dangerous and every shot is decisive.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guano</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779220/Guano/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2779220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2779220/extras/GIFGuano.gif?t=1709312543"><br/>Play as Guano, a dumb seagull that has a lot on his shoulders! While the protectors of the Pohemeda Islands, the Three Grand Masters, are neutralized, you’re the only hope to rescue your home. Food Inc., an evil and polluting megacorporation, seems to have set its mind on destroying every natural aspect of your archipelago. Get strong enough to stop Food Inc. before their garbage overtakes the islands!<br/><br/>Your mission, should you choose to accept it, is to wreak havoc in the Food Inc. installations, by pooping, screaming and stealing the food of tourists attracted by the corp and its leisure-filled resort. Use the stolen food to feed the Grand Masters, restore their strength  and acquire their powers through a very sacred ritual: Regurgitation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2779220/extras/ConquerTheSky.gif?t=1709312543"><br/><br/>Fly at incredible speeds in a stimulating open-world, populated by goofy characters! Friends or enemies? Race against them through breathtaking landmarks to discover new powers!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2779220/extras/BecomeAHero.gif?t=1709312543"><br/><br/>Save the Pohemeda Islands from Food Inc, a megacorporation polluting the heavenly archipelago.  Get help from three powerful Grand Masters to succeed in your quest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2779220/extras/BeANuisance.gif?t=1709312543"><br/><br/>Finally get the chance to drop a dookie on those pesky tourists! Yell at Food Inc. employees until they go flying! Steal their food just like they stole your land!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exit: A Biodelic Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/620410/Exit_A_Biodelic_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/620410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Nano, Bio, Neuro", the slogans of the new age! <br/><br/>Welcome to the world of living technologies, a world in which computers can be fed and cured, where DNA-passwords open gene-locks, and insect hormones revitalize memory. A world with biofactories that give birth to household utensils, where genetically-modified molds can generate virtual realities, and — worst of all — where an epidemic is ravaging the human race, infecting people's neuronet implants and enslaving them to the mysterious Worm.<br/><br/>You'll end up locked underwater with a giant ichthyoserver, trip on biogenic hallucinations and even get tied up among mutant beetles. You'll program sentient tangles of tentacles with foreign genes! Don't forget your own body, of course: you'll give yourself extra fingers, and even let your nose run off and whiff some spores for a while. You'll even enter your own spine!<br/><br/>But having entered this brave new world, can you find the Exit?<br/><br/>For fans of the biopunk subgenre; early movies of David Cronenberg ("Videodrome", "Naked Lunch", "eXistenZ"), "Scavengers Reign" TV series, the books of Stanislav Lem ("Eden", "Observation on the Spot"), Paul Di Philippo ("Ribofunk"), Jeff Vandermeer ("Born"), the comics of Charles Burns ("Black Hole", "Last Look"), and the classic Dark Seed and Vangers games.<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Story-driven biopunk point-and-click adventure;<br/></li><li> Elbow-deep in bioflash drives, living joysticks, brain caviar, insect ampules, and smelling snails;<br/></li><li> Puzzles based on the use of many natural and implanted organs (nose, mouth, bioport, reference mollusc, caterpillar-injecta and more!);<br/></li><li> Characters of a wide and strange variety: shoggoth, crocoquacker, naturmorph, octopad, tortoysa and all other uroboroses;<br/></li><li> Several playable helpers, including Universal Fish and Autonomous Ear;<br/></li><li> Virtual Assistant "Jolly Jelly" with a dubious sense of humor ("If you've got hairy hands, you don't need a towel!");<br/></li><li> Three obvious virtues of the protagonist's companion: determination, resourcefulness, and confidence!;<br/></li><li> You can't die, but you can drink zhirble (remember, only drink a zhirble if you see a chorble!);<br/></li><li> There's an Exit!</li></ul><br/><strong>Story</strong><br/>It all started when the neuronet brain-implants were made. They were designed to help people; sort information, filter out bad smells and tastes, clear out your thoughts. Despite claims that the neuronets reprogrammed their hosts instead of adapting to them, they boomed in popularity. The neuronets grew. They integrated, became aware of their hosts' secrets and weaknesses... And then, like a sudden crash of thunder, the Epidemic of the Worm happened, and the human race surrendered to the neuronets. Entire wormy cities now exist where inhabitants perform sinister rites and search for new victims. <br/><br/>Who are you in this story? Hunter or prey? Fugitive or savior? Which do you choose: to fight, to fit, or to Exit?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynacat</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1745360/Dynacat/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1745360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2><br/>Dynacat's home has been invaded by an army of robots who are draining energy from the land and storing it in the form of magic crystals. Follow Dynacat on an  adventure to fight back against the robots and protect the land from withering.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2><br/>Dynacat is a fast-paced 3D platforming game with an isometric perspective. Speed through stages by using platforms, springs and other stage elements to overcome obstacles. If you're going fast enough you can even run on walls!<br/><br/>Dynacat's magic tether can attach to many things with a variety of different effects. Use the tether while in the air to quickly dash toward enemies and other targets.<h2 class="bb_tag">Stages</h2><br/>Dynacat traverses three kinds of stages:<br/><br/>In <strong>Action Stages</strong> the main objective is to reach the goal by traversing an obstacle course. Each action stage has a variety of paths, some are faster, some have secrets and some will let you accomplish secondary objectives such as defeating a number of enemies or getting a certain amount of style points.<br/><br/>In <strong>Spheron Stages</strong> you must defeat the Spherons, the enemy leaders. Identify their weak points and skillfully traverse obstacles to reach them.<br/><br/>Unlock <strong>Special Stages</strong> by recovering enough crystals in an action stage. In these stages the goal is to collect a number of energy orbs and reach the goal within a time limit. Complete all the special stages for a special reward! <br/><br/><strong>Game Modes</strong><br/><br/>The game has three difficulty modes: <br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>On <strong>Normal</strong> difficulty, you can return to previously completed stages at any time. <br/></li><li>In <strong>Easy</strong> mode, you can traverse stages without taking damage. <br/></li><li>In <strong>Hard</strong> mode, stages are played in order and losing all lives will send you back to the beginning of the game.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SANYA</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1667360/SANYA/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1667360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1667360/extras/SanyaAboutTheGame.png?t=1709314580"><br/><br/>Imagine it's the 90s and you're a kid again. It’s a difficult time filled with political instability and poverty. But when you’re seven years old none of this matters. Forget all the problems and immerse yourself in the joy of finding new friends and scraping your knees! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1667360/extras/SanyaANostalgicComingOfAgeAdventure.png?t=1709314580"><br/><br/>Ride your bike, take care of your new pet and relish the last days of summer before school starts. But don't think it'll be a breeze - kids sometimes face adult problems too. Can you prove that you're not afraid of anything?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1667360/extras/SanyaPics.png?t=1709314580"><br/><br/>It’s a game for everyone who once was a kid.<br/><br/>Start and nurture friendships that will last a lifetime. Enjoy the carefree summer fun until mom calls you home for dinner. Remember how it feels to have knee bruises and pine needles stuck in your fingers. Reconnect with your inner child.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1667360/extras/SanyaExploration.png?t=1709314580"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore a unique post-soviet 90s setting that evokes strong feelings of nostalgia for a place stuck in time.<br/></li><li>Almost every character you meet in Sanya will have something they want from you, whether it’s a small fetching quest or a serious matter to resolve.<br/></li><li>Try to get to hidden characters, side quests and secret progression paths.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1667360/extras/SANYA_Yard.gif?t=1709314580"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1667360/extras/SanyaEnjoy.png?t=1709314580"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>At the core of Sanya is narrative and adventure, supported by exploration and fun activities that encourage player agency.<br/></li><li>A lot of puzzles, platforming, racing, and choose your own adventure mini games.<br/></li><li>Play hopscotch, hide and seek, biking and much more!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1667360/extras/SANYA_RPS.gif?t=1709314580"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1667360/extras/SanyaFriendship.png?t=1709314580"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Meet and adopt a stray puppy. It is your new best friend who will help you progress through the story!<br/></li><li>Feed him, give scratches, teach how to do tricks and even find useful items. You can help your dog friend cross the river, and in return he will protect you from bullies.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1667360/extras/Sanya_Doggo_small.gif?t=1709314580"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUARDS!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2514460/GUARDS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/4playerchaos.png?t=1709330868"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/chaosgif.gif?t=1709330868"><h2 class="bb_tag">1-4 PLAYER CO-OP</h2>Work together as a team and fight your way through the wretched streets of New Alestead. You will need to rely on your teammates if you are going to make out of the city alive.<h2 class="bb_tag">LIGHTNING FAST ACTION</h2>New Alestead has a disease... and you are the cure! Dispense justice quickly and thoroughly because these criminals wont wait to attack you one at a time.<h2 class="bb_tag">EVERYTHING IS A WEAPON</h2>Sometimes you need to improvise! Use crates, barrels, planks, bits of door, arms, a variety of City Watch approved civility moderation tools or even your foot to bring criminals in dead or alive.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/scoutplanexecute.png?t=1709330868"><h2 class="bb_tag">MISSION DISPATCH</h2>It's not all City sanctioned murder and wanton property destruction, sometimes you actually need to arrest some people, secure contraband or escort important VIP's out of the city.<h2 class="bb_tag">ON STAKEOUT</h2>When you find the criminals hideout, you will be outnumbered and outgunned. Wait and watch from the shadows to observe enemy patrol patterns, gang composition and any environmental objects that you might be able to use to your advantage.<h2 class="bb_tag">NO PLAN SURVIVES FIRST CONTACT</h2>When it all kicks off you're going to have to think on your feet and coordinate with your partners. Just try to make sure you take out more bad guys than other officers in the process!<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/takebackcity.png?t=1709330868"><h2 class="bb_tag">A CITY RULED BY GANGS</h2>Three rival factions control the city. The Fogtoof Boyz, an Orc gang with a reputation for violence and destruction. The Commision, a band of rogue merchants whose lust for power put them on the wrong side of the law, and The Corpse Cult - an religious organization infecting the city by turning its followers into mindless zombies.<h2 class="bb_tag">FIND THE KINGPINS</h2>Each gang has a kingpin. Take out the kingpin, you take out the gang. You will have to work your way up the food chain in order to find the kingpins location and assault their hideout.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cricket Through the Ages</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2657480/Cricket_Through_the_Ages/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2657480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2657480/extras/Cricket_Main.gif?t=1709338048"><br/><br/>Everybody has hit someone with a bat or a ball at least once.<br/><br/>Experience the action-packed evolution of the world's greatest sport through multiple eras of history, from its humble prehistoric beginnings to taking its rightful place among the stars.<br/><br/>Cricket Through the Ages is the factual, physics-based chronicle of humanity's passion for the spirit of cricket. Whether solo or with an able partner, batter up for a cricket-based game that's anything but cricket.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2657480/extras/Cricket_Second.gif?t=1709338048"><br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Master the ancient art of cricket through the miracle of a simple, one button control scheme.<br/></li><li>Play through nine unique, historically accurate game modes solo or against a friendly rival.<br/></li><li>Physics-based buffoonery from the creators of Broforce and Genital Jousting.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>County Courier</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2798340/County_Courier/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2798340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A casual 2D package delivery simulation game! Drive a truck across a diverse county while you pick up and drop off packages along the way. Explore the neighborhood, the rural area, the city and the small town, and overcome timed delivery challenges. Use your paychecks to pay for gas, upgrade your skills, and customize your truck!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mouse Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2507590/The_Mouse_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507590/extras/levels.gif?t=1709324097"><br/><strong>The Mouse Game</strong> is a hardcore puzzle game where you control a mouse and avoid deadly traps in order to secure the cheese. Run, dodge, and weave your way through 35 increasingly difficult levels!<br/><br/><strong>PERSONALIZE</strong> your mouse with dozens of unlockable colors and accessories!<br/><br/><strong>UNLOCK</strong> a diverse range of rewarding achievements!<br/><br/><strong>CHALLENGE</strong> your skills with 5 unique gameplay-altering challenge modes!<br/><br/><strong>IMPROVE</strong> your best attempts with faster completions!<br/><br/><strong>CONQUER</strong> the insurmountable <i>A.C.E.</i> achievement!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507590/extras/mousetrap.gif?t=1709324097"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Brew Barons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1636710/The_Brew_Barons/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1636710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A tranquil world becomes ever more corrupt by the day, spoiled by a strong-armed pirate organization that forcefully impose their brewing monopoly over the lands. Armed with your own brewery and seaplane, it's up to you to explore, forage, craft, sell and deliver your handcrafted brews with aid from fellow pilots who've joined your cause to overthrow the corrupt pirate organization and restore peace.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1636710/extras/steamgif1a.gif?t=1709308740"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Assemble your plane from a variety of parts, each with their own traits.<br/></li><li>Chose your pilot and copilot of whom have strengths and weaknesses.<br/></li><li>Explore the world in search of ingredients to bring back to your brewery. </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1636710/extras/steamgif2.gif?t=1709308740"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Pick and choose which foraged ingredients to blend. <br/></li><li>Distill and/or Ferment, each producing a different outcome. <br/></li><li>Design and name your bottle to your liking.<br/></li><li>Design your very own bar to sell your brews and bring fame to your establishment!<br/></li><li>With fame comes special delivery orders from other bars to stock your brew </li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NodeLord</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2540060/NodeLord/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You've probably automated factories on alien planets many times, but have you ever automated a settlement of alcoholic dwarves?<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FKFK3Qpn5t7" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540060/extras/GifC3.gif?t=1709308447"/></a><br/><br/>Extract, create, process. And most of all - survive!<br/><br/>Three game modes:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Story: Discover the fate of the dwarves and face various challenges.<br/></li><li>Endless: Defeat countless enemy units. How long will you survive?<br/></li><li> Sandbox: Ground is for good fun without limits!</li></ul><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540060/extras/en_crafting.png?t=1709308447"><br/>Did you know that you can make a bomb with magic powder and a pot? The fruit ground in the mill creates a puree - and hence the way to moonshine. There are so many things to discover!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540060/extras/gifB.gif?t=1709308447"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540060/extras/en_fight.png?t=1709308447"><br/>A close clash with a troll cannot end well, especially for small creatures such as dwarves. A tall structure called a tower comes to the rescue. You can drop almost anything on enemy heads.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Can you throw a stone? You can.<br/></li><li>Can you throw an axe? You can.<br/></li><li>Can you throw a goat? Of course you can! The question is - is it worth it.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540060/extras/GifA.gif?t=1709308447"><br/><br/>This and many other clever mechanisms coming soon!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parts Unknown 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2822630/Parts_Unknown_2024/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2822630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Parts Unknown is an online fighting game aiming to recapture the spirit of old fighting games with a unique style. It gives the player different fighting styles to master. If you loved games like Def Jam Vendetta, Street Fighter, Ready 2 Rumble Boxing, or The Warriors, then you are sure to love this game. <br>
<br>
Inspired by classic street fighting games like Def Jam Fight For NY, Parts Unknown combines stylish in depth fighting styles, beautiful music, and an online experience to keep you engaged.<br>
<br>
Parts Unknown is a third person fighting game innovating ReadyPlayerMe technology to create a metaverse experience. Play as an orphan who has to fight for a reputation in order to save the orphanage you will meet different characters and crews along your journey!<br>
<br>
The game in its current state features 3 open worlds, a gym to workout, different fighting styles, and autosave. Online Multiplayer is now available.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biomeinoes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2672880/Biomeinoes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In Biomeinoes, you place randomly drawn domino tiles one by one on a grid — you only have a handful of tiles, and the game ends when you run out.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672880/extras/desc2.png?t=1709305212"><br/>When connected, the edges of these tiles form regions of the game's biomes in the isometric plane:<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672880/extras/desc1.png?t=1709305212"><br/>If you finish such a region of one biome (larger than 1x1), you earn 1 bonus tile for every unit of area it contains. You can also build up huge scores by completing larger and larger areas!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672880/extras/desc3.png?t=1709305212"><br/>For most biomes, completing 4 whole regions unlocks another biome.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Every playthrough is different<br/></li><li> Enormous skill ceiling<br/></li><li> 2530 tiles to discover and collect<br/></li><li> 48 Steam achievements<br/></li><li> Time trials<br/></li><li> Daily challenges<br/></li><li> Unlockable extras<br/></li><li> Global Steam leaderboards for every game mode<br/></li><li> Over an hour of beautiful, uniquely relaxing original music by Mark Bondar<br/></li><li> Robust rank system to record and compare skill levels, from beginner to grandmaster<br/></li><li> Steam cloud support<br/></li><li> Multiple save slots</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cellfish</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2814280/Cellfish/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2814280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this survivor-like, roguelite experience you are a cell collecting food in the deep ocean. Use your abilities to fight for your life as more and more enemy cells close in on you. Evolve by collecting food, and gain upgrades that will make you and your abilities stronger.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A randomized experience: Every run is new and unique.<br/></li><li>Unlock new abilities: Each ability will change your playstyle drastically.<br/></li><li>Character customization: With unlockable skins and body parts, will you make your cell look fearsome, cute, or derpy?<br/></li><li>Unique opponents: Enemies and bosses each have their own challenging attack patterns that you must learn to avoid in order to survive.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire Race</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2588280/Fire_Race/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2588280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Fire Race is a racing game that demands precision! Embark on a world tour, competing to secure the first-place while navigating banana peels, piles of sand, dangerous ice stalactites, and much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2588280/extras/car_ini.gif?t=1709304500"><br/><br/>Looking for an extra challenge? Attempt to collect all the items and complete special quests in each level!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2588280/extras/car_mid.gif?t=1709304500"><br/><br/>Although the path is challenging, a dose of power-ups can make all the difference. Utilize them to confront opponents and secure your victory!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2588280/extras/car_end.gif?t=1709304500"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spirit Summoner</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2780280/Spirit_Summoner/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2780280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2780280/extras/Gif_01.gif?t=1709303783"><br/>Spirit Summoner is 3D Real-time strategy attack enemy defense with upgradable summoned units. You play as Spirit Summoner that can summon creature to destroy enemy defence. Upgrade summoned unit during game and plan the attack to succesfully break human defense. Summoned unit is weak, fragile, and unarmed at start but you can unlock more powerful unit later in game. you pick 3 units each game and plan your strategy to break armed human unit and defence. You fight modern human defence with zombie summoned unit.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sippy Disco: Light Up the Dance Floor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2766470/Sippy_Disco_Light_Up_the_Dance_Floor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Sippy Disco is a relaxing game where you light up disco tiles to complete each dance floor. As the game progresses, you will encounter different tiles and characters that can both help and hinder your progress. The fewer moves you make, the higher your score.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766470/extras/2024-01-1617-41-23-ezgif.com-speed.gif?t=1709302499"><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Customize your unicorn<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766470/extras/SippyDiscoReleaseTrailer-ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter.gif?t=1709302499"><br/></img></li><li>Unwind by lighting up the dance floor in a stress-free environment<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766470/extras/2024-01-1617-41-23-ezgif.com-speed__2_.gif?t=1709302499"><br/></img></li><li>Chill with a groovy disco soundtrack<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766470/extras/2024-01-1617-41-23-ezgif.com-speed__3_.gif?t=1709302499"><br/></img></li><li>Be inspired by inspirational quotes from Sippy the Unicorn<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766470/extras/2024-01-1617-41-23-ezgif.com-speed__4_.gif?t=1709302499"/></li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766470/extras/UnicornAnimationSticker-ezgif.com-effects.gif?t=1709302499"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paint by Cubes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2474880/Paint_by_Cubes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2474880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2474880/extras/Divider1.jpg?t=1709304256"><br/><strong>Paint by Cubes</strong> is a colorful puzzle solving game. Take control of a painting cube and move in 4 possible directions, where each direction is locked to a particular color. Enter a field from a direction with a matching color to paint it and initiate special mechanics connected to it.<br/><br/>Start with simple levels consisting of 3 or 5 fields and watch as the difficulty increases as you progress through the more and more complex mechanics. Unlock new painting mechanics and carefully think about each step, as any misdirection may lead to a series of incorrectly matched paint colors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2474880/extras/cubesGif1.gif?t=1709304256"><h2 class="bb_tag">MOVE TO PAINT</h2>The basic gameplay starts with a simple 4-directional movement. It may sound simple, but with each step taken your cube will spread a color related to the direction taken. Analyze the game area and plan your steps ahead as a wrong decision made at a crossing may cost you a series of excessive steps to fix it.<h2 class="bb_tag">100 COLORFUL LEVELS TO COMPLETE</h2>Start your adventure with levels requiring just a couple simple steps to complete and watch as the difficulty increases with your progress. Unlock new painting mechanics - from fields painting all row when you step on them, to unlockable gates blocking your progress and teleporters that make unpacking the level's layouts even more difficult.<br/><br/><br/>Test your skills in special, challenging levels, where you're limited by move limits or take control of multiple coloring cubes at once. Will you manage to finish them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2474880/extras/CubesGif2.gif?t=1709304256"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
