<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Few Nights More: Genesis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713070/Few_Nights_More_Genesis/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Please note: This is a free prologue and it includes act 1, and only 1 playable character and blood school is playable, The maximum heritage gained is limited to 50, and the maximum difficulty can be set to 2. As well only one castle will be available. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Blood3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Conquer castles and claim your birthright!</strong><br/> <br/>The fight to reclaim your place in this world begins. Rebuild lost ruins, make them stronger and defend them against your enemies. After you regain your strength, move on to conquer more territories and eventually claim your birthright.<br/><br/>Few Nights More offers the unique fusing of castle management and turn based rogue-like combat. Fight against humanity, the undisputed masters of this world in your absence. Choose between eight different Vampire Lords, each with their own ambition and history. Find your trinkets, skills and perks along your way. Design your very own castle by placing the right rooms, adding decors that directly contribute to your army and your Vampire Lord. Conquer more castles so your influence and power grow, until you claim your birthright.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Ferocity3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Core Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Design your castle by adding new Rooms, Traps and Minions. Stack up on some buffs with shiny decors to get ready for the invasion screen to defend it to the end of every night!<br/> <br/></li><li> Choose among 7 different Vampire Lords with unique History, Gameplay and Abilities.<br/> <br/></li><li> Master 1 out of 3 Disciplines each time you play, each with 60 unique skills.<br/> <br/></li><li> Acquire new random skills, perks and trinkets to survive the nights.<br/> <br/></li><li> Excel in either being a Prestigious Vampire, a Seductive one, or master a Terrifying presence against your enemies.<br/><br/></li><li> Test the builds you made against a variety of Hunters, Veterans and Unique Bosses in an action packed turn based combat system.<br/> <br/></li><li> Endure three acts across 12 difficulty levels, striving to survive and progress. Accumulate Heritage Points to enhance your lord's starting stats, skills, and unlock new castles and talents unique to each lord.<br/><br/></li><li> Engage in the boundless challenge of Infinity Mode, where you can continuously test your limits without relying on a castle. Each night, you will be presented with three options to advance, growing stronger as you push yourself to see how far you can go.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703259090"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703259090"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703259090"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703259090"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703259090"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703259090"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1702674942"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grimhook</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667430/Grimhook/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667430/extras/Logo_Text_Small.png?t=1702093226"><br/>Embark on a harrowing journey beneath the ruins of the once-vibrant city of Miletos. <br/><br/>Grimhook, a fast-paced, first-person action-adventure game, thrusts you into the heart of a flooded wasteland where robotic minions reign supreme and an ancient deity lies dormant beneath the city's surface. As Dart, you'll harness powerful abilities to navigate through cavernous depths; grapple, bounce, dash, and slash your way through relentless automata in intense combat arenas while you experience a grim world and a somber narrative.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667430/extras/HighresScreenshot001182.png?t=1702093226"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <i>Fast-paced First-Person Platforming:</i> Unleash a myriad of Lovecraftian abilities as you navigate the caverns of Miletos. Time and combine your powers to swiftly traverse the game's terrain and outmaneuver your enemies.<br/></li><li> <i>Tightly Tuned Combat:</i> Engage in intense battles in multiple combat arenas, utilizing your powers to dodge bullets and decimate robotic foes. Watch as fully destructible adversaries explode, leaving a chaotic aftermath on the battlefield.<br/></li><li> <i>Explore a Cavernous World:</i> Traverse dilapidated skyscrapers, rushing rapids, and forgotten excavations in a sprawling subterranean world. Encounter diverse biomes that add depth and variety to your adventure.<br/></li><li> <i>Hand-Painted Art Style:</i> Immerse yourself in a somber environment brought to life by a carefully hand-painted art style, capturing the melancholic beauty of a city on the brink of ruin.<br/></li><li> <i>Immersive Audio Experience:</i> Immerse yourself in the tragic journey with over 10 electronic tracks in the musical score, composed by BelowCloudNine.<br/></li><li> <i>Voiced Characters:</i> Two fully voiced characters bring intimacy to the narrative and characterize the unlikely camaraderie between Dart and the dormant deity beneath the city.<br/></li><li> <i>Dynamic Animations and Cutscenes:</i> Dynamic first-person animations strike a vivid contrast with the desaturated world. Multiple fully authored first-person cutscenes enhance the immersive storytelling experience.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1703307979"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1703307979"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1703307979"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1703307979"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1703307979"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1703307979"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1703307979"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1703307979"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1702562956"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1702562956"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1702000678"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1702000678"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1703186631"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1703318086"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1703318086"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 5 Tactica</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2254740/Persona_5_Tactica/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join the Phantom Thieves as they lead an uprising of the heart! Assemble a team of beloved heroes in a brand-new story in this thrilling combat adventure set in Persona’s iconic universe. The Persona 5 Tactica: Digital Deluxe Edition includes the following content:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Repaint Your Heart Challenge Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Weapon Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Picaro Summoning Pack + Raoul Persona</li></ul><br/><strong>Ignite your heart— An emotional uprising begins!</strong><br/><br/>After a strange incident, the Phantom Thieves wander into a bizarre realm where its citizens are living under tyrannical oppression. Surrounded by a military group named Legionnaires, they find themselves in grave danger until a mysterious revolutionary named Erina rescues them and offers an enticing deal in exchange for their help. What truth lies behind Erina and the deal she offers to the Phantom Thieves?<br/><br/>Persona 5 Tactica features an all-new story, the return of fan-favorite characters, and brand-new allies and foes. Join the group as they lead an emotional revolution in this thrilling combat adventure!<br/><br/><strong>An Emotional Revolution</strong><br/>Lead an uprising of the heart in a brand-new storyline that takes place in Persona’s iconic universe.<br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Squad</strong><br/>Assemble a team of beloved heroes to fight oppressive armies in thrilling turn-based combat.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Combat</strong><br/>Overthrow your enemies with powerful Personas, an assortment of weapons, and wipe them out with style!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1702747783"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobalt Core</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2179850/Cobalt_Core/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_1.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>Cobalt Core is a sci-fi roguelike deckbuilder with a unique single-axis combat system that will throw you for a loop. Many loops! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_2.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>Give orders to your crew by playing cards: Will you <strong>raise shields</strong> to protect your ship, <strong>dodge</strong> incoming missiles and cannon fire to avoid damage outright, or <strong>strike</strong> preemptively to disable your enemy’s weapons? Outmaneuver your foes to stay just ahead of impending calamity, and reach the Cobalt Core!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/characters.png?t=1703278835"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fresh new spin on tactics –</strong>  dodge attacks and target weak points in this unique single-axis take on tactics combat. Outwit the enemy in a high stakes game of cat and mouse!<br/></li><li><strong>Customize your deck –</strong> hundreds of cards and split upgrade paths means no two runs will be the same. Find that perfect combo that brings your deck from powerful to overpowered.<br/></li><li><strong>Get to know your crew –</strong> each character comes with a completely unique playstyle and their own personal story. Bring 3 along, mix and match their decks, and see how these little goobers get along with each other.<br/></li><li><strong>Tons of replayability –</strong>  hundreds of different character+ship combinations before you even hit “start run”. Crank up the difficulty and really test your skills!<br/></li><li><strong>Get in the groove –</strong> featuring 90+ minutes of catchy and electrifying original music by <i>Minecraft</i> composer Aaron Cherof!<br/></li><li><strong>Forward momentum –</strong> untangle a narrative and unlock more playstyles as you go. Is there any escape from this time loop?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/grandma_cookies.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>By the makers of <i>Sunshine Heavy Industries</i>, recipient of IGF's <strong>Honorable Mention for Excellence in Design 2022</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658820/Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							10 possible fruits and one goal, reach the Watermelon.<br/>Your job is to combine matching fruits to evolve them to the next one and eventually reach the coveted Watermelon.<br/>To help you, you have 3 different abilities at your disposal. But watch out, using these will cost you some of your points. Be smart about when you use them to get the highest score!<h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLAYER</h2>Measure your fruit skills against another player.<h2 class="bb_tag">GET THE WATERMELON</h2>How many Watermelons can you combine before your basket overflows?<h2 class="bb_tag">USE YOUR ABILITIES</h2>Power, level up and destroy — These abilities will help you reach the Watermelon, using any of those will also allow you to angle your aim.<h2 class="bb_tag">GOLDEN FRUIT</h2>If luck is on your side, you might even see the mysterious Golden Fruit. Find it and witness its effect firsthand.<h2 class="bb_tag">STATISTICS</h2>Track your progress with in-depth statistics. Visit the menu to see the number of fruits you've combined, your ability usage, and much more.<h2 class="bb_tag"></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.codecks.io%2Fwatermelon-game" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/extras/Roadmap_Banner.png?t=1702238677"/></a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football Manager 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2252570/Football_Manager_2024/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2252570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a real boss and write your own football story in Football Manager 2024, the most complete edition in the series yet. <br/><br/>Whether you’re a manager who likes to build from the bottom or prefers to chase immediate glory, the perfect challenge awaits. The arrival of the new Meiji Yasuda Insurance Ltd J. League licence unlocks J1 League, J2 League, J3 League for the first time ever, giving you the opportunity to explore new horizons in Japan.<br/><br/>Wherever you manage, it's up to you to build a team capable of competing with the world's elite.<br/><br/><strong>Game Description </strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Continue your relentless journey to the top of the footballing world by using the new ability to import your existing career from Football Manager 2023.<br/></li><li>Craft a winning tactical approach, incorporating modern football’s most popular systems and cutting-edge positional innovations to deliver victories on the pitch. <br/></li><li>Master the transfer market, using new ways to shape your side to cultivate a squad capable of achieving your goals. <br/></li><li>Level up your players on the training field, developing the mentality and teamwork needed to transform contenders into champions. <br/></li><li>See your tactical vision come to life on Matchdays, with every game elevated by improvements to ball and player movements.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">NEW FOR THIS SEASON</h2><br/><br/><strong>TRUER FOOTBALL MOTION</strong><br/><br/>Enhancements to player animations, ball physics and lighting deliver the most immersive Match Engine in Football Manager history. Move to the cutting edge of football by using the new Inverted Full-Back player role, while more intelligent player rotational movements add more fluidity to every highlight. <br/><br/><strong>DOMINATE FROM SET PIECES</strong><br/><br/>Make an impact at both ends of the pitch with an overhauled Set Piece Creator. Lean on the expertise of brand-new Set Piece Coaches to develop winning routines in every scenario that will help you to outsmart your rivals. <br/><br/><strong>BRACE FOR TRANSFER BATTLES</strong><br/><br/>Showcase your squad-building skills in our most refined transfer market yet. You’ll face a trickier battle for talent as your rival opposition managers are now more strategic than ever in their recruitment decision-making. <br/><br/><strong>NEW AGENTS TO BUILD A DREAM SQUAD</strong><br/><br/>Better shape your perfect squad with the introduction of new Intermediaries that will help you offload surplus players for a cut of the final transfer fee. Additional functionality for existing Agents and the debut of TransferRoom, a football marketplace for transfers in real life, gives you more real-world powered tools than ever to build an elite team and dominate the competition.<br/><br/><strong>ELEVATE PERFORMANCES WITH TARGETS</strong><br/><br/>Motivate your team to achieve more on and off the field by setting them individual Targets. Whether you’re focusing on goals scored in a season or average training performances, challenge your star players and top prospects to maximise their ability. <br/><br/><strong>A HOST MORE ADDITIONS</strong><br/><br/>Enjoy greater variety in every career with the arrival of two new game modes. Real World mirrors when players actually joined your club. Your World sets club squads and budgets at the day your career starts, meaning that only players who joined before that date will be in your squad, giving you the opportunity to rewrite your team’s transfer window.<br/><br/>Elsewhere, you can look to dominate international management and plan for your country's future with a revamped National Pool that gives you a better overview of the talent at your disposal. Match preparation and briefing meetings deliver you winning insights before each fixture. <br/><br/>That’s not all though, with many more changes waiting for you to discover in every career.<br/><br/><i>This version contains information that is still under approval process by rights holders and may contain data that does not, at this time, accurately reflect real world data. For context, some club and player assets may be absent during this version.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buns: Bunny Survivor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684450/Buns_Bunny_Survivor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help the magical bunny girl to survive for 10 minutes against hordes of evil. Collect gems to get new skills, find bunnies to heal, carrots to recharge. <br>
<br>
This is tiny roguelike bullet heaven with a bunny girl made for Pico-8 fantasy console.<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
- incredibly crisp 128x128 resoltuion<br>
- an explosion of color with a massive palette of 16 whole colors!<br/>
- super hard game, can be beaten in 10 minutes but it will be impossible, some players played it for 100+ hours!<br/>
- don't need mouse to play<br/>
- cute bunny<br/>
- CARROTS						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visit From Above</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2709810/Visit_From_Above/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Visit From Above is a sit-and-survive horror game (inspired by Five Nights at Freddy's) that puts you face to face with aliens. You will have to survive 3 nights using different methods to defeat the aliens including a flashlight, turning power on/off, and closing your eyes (pretend to sleep).<br>
<br>
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------<br>
<br>
In the quiet town of Crestwood, something sinister lurked beyond the starlit sky. The Stevenson family, comprised of John, a high-ranking military officer, his wife Lisa, a scientist, and their teenage daughter, Mia, lived a seemingly ordinary life in their suburban home.<br>
<br>
One fateful night, as the family settled in for dinner, an unnatural darkness enveloped the neighborhood. The power grid failed, plunging the Stevenson household into an inky blackness. As the family groped for flashlights, a blinding flash illuminated the sky. Unbeknownst to the unsuspecting Earthlings, an alien race with nefarious intentions had set their sights on Crestwood.<br/>
<br/>
From the shadows emerged extraterrestrial beings capable of mimicking any form they encountered. These shape-shifters, driven by a malevolent agenda, had been observing humanity and plotting their infiltration for years. The power outage provided the perfect cover for their invasion.<br/>
<br/>
Silently, the alien doppelgangers assumed the appearance of the Stevenson family, mimicking every detail down to the last freckle. With their disguises in place, they infiltrated the Stevenson home, lurking in the corners like predatory phantoms.<br/>
<br/>
The real Stevenson family, armed with flashlights, cautiously navigated their darkened house. Unease hung in the air as they felt an unnatural chill. Unknown to them, their doppelgangers now sat at the dinner table, their eyes glinting with an otherworldly malevolence.<br/>
<br/>
As the power outage persisted, tensions within the household escalated. The alien clones, adept at replicating human behavior, exploited the confusion and paranoia that gripped the real Stevenson family. Whispers in the dark and eerie laughter echoed through the halls, sowing discord among the unsuspecting inhabitants.<br/>
<br/>
The turning point came when John, suspicious of his surroundings, stumbled upon the imposter version of himself. A chilling confrontation unfolded, revealing the true horror that had invaded their home. The alien doppelgangers, no longer able to maintain their facade, shed their human forms, exposing grotesque, otherworldly features.<br/>
<br/>
A desperate struggle ensued as the real Stevenson family fought to protect their home and each other. The alien invaders, relentless and ruthless, revealed their plan to conquer Earth and subjugate its inhabitants. The once peaceful Crestwood became a battleground, with the fate of humanity hanging in the balance.<br/>
<br/>
In Visit From Above, you are put in the shoes of John Stevenson, after the rest of his family has already been overtaken by their alien clones. Your job will be to keep the aliens at bay until the government broadcasts a special audio frequency harmful only to the extraterrestrials. But be warned, nothing is as it seems...						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grapple Tournament</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1384320/Grapple_Tournament/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1384320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Grapple. Shoot. Score. Master the vertical combat.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>VIRTUAL REALITY ARCADE SHOOTER</strong></h2>Built from the ground up for virtual reality, Grapple Tournament is a thrilling VR arcade shooter where you can enjoy movement freedom using your 3D maneuver abilities and your grappling hook while fighting with a wide variety of multifunctional weapons (even dual wielding) in various multiplayer game modes and co-op challenges through an alluring stylized world.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1384320/extras/gtvr_hydro_grapple_flak_grenade.gif?t=1703350710"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>3D MOVEMENT FREEDOM</strong></h2>Run, jump and double jump to get yourself into position, wall jump to evade incoming harm, pull yourself up with the grappling hook to get the high ground or grapple-swing around corners to surprise your enemies. Learn how to chain these abilities with your 3D maneuvering gear to perform untraceable movement combos and outsmart your enemies like never before in a VR game! Maps are specifically designed with vertically in mind to get the most out of it.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1384320/extras/gtvr_container2_high_ground.gif?t=1703350710"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>MULTIFUNCTIONAL WEAPONS</strong></h2>More than 12 weapons eagerly await to get into battle under your command. From the common mechanical guns through the plasma pistols to the energy rifles, single-fire or automatic, instant shot or projectile based, you can have everything.<br/><br/>Target-following laser? Shotguns and grenade launchers? You got them. Rockets? Let them rain! Your VR dream is to become a turret with massive firepower? Go with dual miniguns! Double handed weapons have both primary and secondary fire modes letting you choose the perfect reaction for any situation. By the way you always have your melee weapon - the energy blade - on your side. You know, for slicing cake.<br/><br/>Play the game any way you like, use the grappling hook with a weapon or dual wield any weapon combination. Mobility versus firepower. Your call.<br/><br/>Did we mention that you can also summon an energy bow and shoot an arrow any time?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1384320/extras/gtvr_temple_railgun_combo.gif?t=1703350710"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>MULTIPLAYER</strong></h2>Multiplayer is the heart of the Tournament. Starting individually or with your friends, matchmaking will find you worthy opponents and let you fight in various game modes on engaging, stylized maps which were created with verticality in mind. The currently available game modes are:<br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Deathmatch: Everyone against everyone, up to 6 players. It can be messy and chaotic but you just can’t stop until you win. Can you be the very best on your own?<br/></li><li>Team Deathmatch: Fast-paced, frantic 3v3 combat. Get your weapons and defeat the enemy team with pure skill or finesse. Teamwork is essential here: shield your allies, assist in attacks and if all is critical, heal your teammates.<br/></li><li>Capture Point: Strategic point capture mode to spice up 3v3 team battles. Stay in the point areas to capture them and utilize all your arsenal to keep them at all cost. The team with the most points wins.<br/></li><li>Mutant: Eliminate the mutant to become the Mutant. When being the mutant you are stronger but everyone is hunting you.</li></ul><br/>During multiplayer you will visit a plethora of carefully crafted arenas, both outdoors and closed space maps for your all-terrain grapple experience. From sci-fi factories through cave excavations to japanese temples or greek monuments and more. You'll certainly find some maps to your liking.<br/><br/>Bots: Feel free to play with bots to master your skills or have some light-hearted fun.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1384320/extras/gtvr_parthenon_grapple_plasma_double.gif?t=1703350710"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>PRACTICE RANGE</strong></h2>Yeah, we have this too for 3D training purposes. With drones... with hats. You can try all the weapons in sandbox mode here.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CUSTOMIZATIONS</strong></h2>Customize your character to your liking with crazy hats and accessories.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Nefargad</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707090/The_Nefargad/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You've been abducted completely defenseless from your home and brought to a dungeon. You have no idea who did this to you or why. You must find your way out of this dungeon, where you were forcibly brought, by solving puzzles. Luckily, there have been others before you who came into this dungeon to explore it. They have previously solved the mysteries you now have to solve, and left notes about the solutions. With these notes, you can progress more efficiently. Thanks to the left messages, you will also learn about what happened here before you, but you are determined not to trust anyone.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Tension and Horror</strong><br/>The dungeon seems to respond to your every move. Sometimes it might feel like someone is watching you. If you’re not using your torch, you should extinguish it. Staying in the darkness for too long might not be a good idea either. You must balance the dark and light well. Also, don’t forget that puzzles may sometimes have alternative solutions. Random and unpredictable events will make the experience in this dungeon unique and irreplicable!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707090/extras/1.gif?t=1703358267"><br/><br/><strong>Your Knowledge, Insight, and Patience Will Be Tested</strong><br/>As you progress, the fundamental mechanics of the puzzles in the dungeon will change. Sometimes your knowledge about a subject will be tested. Sometimes how you approach problems will be examined. When you can’t find a solution, you will test your patience through trial and error!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707090/extras/2.gif?t=1703358267"><br/><br/><strong>Multilayered Story</strong><br/>As you progress through the dungeon, you will not only write your own story but learn about the stories of the researchers who entered this dungeon before you. What happened to those researchers? Did they share the same fate as you? Were they brought here forcibly? Were they able to get out? This dungeon is ready to tell you all this and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707090/extras/3.gif?t=1703358267"><br/><br/><strong>Warnings</strong><br/>The Nefargad includes profanity and slang in its game content. <br/>The Nefargad contains flashing and/or rapidly blinking lights in both game content and promotional materials. Consult your doctor before viewing any content related to the game or playing it if you have a history of epilepsy.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sci-fi builder</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2438540/Scifi_builder/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2438540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Sci-Fi builder is a simulator and third-person sandbox game defined by creativity and fantasy, it's a game where you can do whatever you want and create anything and everything. It's like a sandbox with a lot of items where you will entertain yourself starting from landing and to the very end, but what is the end? Well, you have to come up with yourself.<h2 class="bb_tag">STORY</h2>Play as the head manager in the completely new and empty space station in the planet number 1188 in the Constellation Centurion. Your task is to make here a new thriving colony. The game play begins with the landing on the space station, you are alone here and have to make a create job to build your own world and hire other characters. A short list of tasks at the very beginning will help you to learn more about the game functions. You will find out how to go to certain room, put props, teleport NPC, like humanoids, alien races, creatures and robots, set up interaction between the NPC and main character, other NPC and props, so you can easily build your own world.<br/><br/>Please remember, that game is in Early Access, and I will add a lot of new modules into it. And it depends on you, what modules it would be. Please, go to the discussion's sections and post all of your notes and ideas there.<br/><br/>Turn on your creativity, in Sci-fi builder, you are free to do whatever you want.<br/>Arrange all elements the way you want. No placing by the grid - complete freedom of action. If you don't like where you put a piece of furniture, just move it or remove it at any time. No limits on the number of objects in the room. If you do not like the main colors of your space station or any item's color, you can easily change it in the color settings. In the light settings menu, you can change the light in the whole station and adapt it to your needs.<br/><br/>Sci-fi builder is a simulation game about building sci-fi rooms and station and create your own society. A huge selection of characters, whom you can give commands, devices which you can manage, furniture, construction elements, computers and other interior details await you.<h2 class="bb_tag">GAME PLAY</h2>Enjoy over hundreds of different characters which you may use as the main character or NPC in the game. Players can freely guide character movements and interact with the objects to influence character reactions. Every room is fully sounded and contains a variety of action options.<br/>Personalize the characters, manage their wardrobe and decide how they will behave.<br/><br/>Good luck in your new life in a space station!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>screamdown</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1303390/screamdown/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1303390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Screamdown is a PvP horror game where players face off in free-for-all matches. Throw enemy players into the void with your vocal attacks and earn enough points to win the game. Play online in public lobbies or with friends!<br/><br/><i>Note: A microphone is not necessary, you can also sound like a train horn.</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Talk to players with proximity chat, or use it to throw them at force into the void.<br/><br/></li><li> Office theme with physics on nearly every object. <br/><br/></li><li> Horror style gameplay, hide from other players and search around with your flashlight.<br/><br/></li><li> Customize your own character with styles, colors and hats.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACCELERATE ZONE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2464190/ACCELERATE_ZONE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2464190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							------------------------------------------------------------------------<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">■ABOUT</h2></strong><br/>This is the early access version of the FULL-THROTTLE STG "ACCELERATE ZONE".<br/>This is an action shooting game where the faster you go, the better your strategy.<br/>It's okay to take your time and go at your own pace.<br/><br/>------------------------------------------------------------------------<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">■PURPOSE</h2></strong><br/>The goal is to reach the goal while avoiding enemies and obstacles.<br/>If the energy runs out in the middle, it will be a mistake.<br/><br/>If you destroy an enemy with a shot, a cube that can replenish energy will appear.<br/>The trick is to proceed while replenishing frequently.<br/>If you get an option, you can use an option shoot that can destroy obstacles.<br/>Let's use it in case of emergency.<br/><br/>------------------------------------------------------------------------<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">■HOW TO</h2></strong><br/>It supports operation with keyboard and Xinput compatible gamepad.<br/><br/>------------------------------------------------------------------------<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>■CREDIT</strong></h2>game design:mdkGAMES<br/>illustration:七条メルル<br/>BGM:OtoLogic						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Santa's busy day</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2723640/Santas_busy_day/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>"Santa's Busy Day"</strong> is an<i> atmospheric little arcade game</i>. You control Santa's sleigh and <strong>fly</strong> over roofs, trees, churches, and more. The goal is to <strong>drop</strong> presents at the right time, so they fall into the right place.<br/><br/>There are two modes in this game:<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723640/extras/Competitive_Mode.png?t=1703323387"><br/><br/><br/><strong>Compete</strong> with players around the world. Who can drop <strong>the most</strong> presents without crashing into a building? This mode will get progressively <u>harder</u> and <u>faster</u>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723640/extras/Relaxed_Mode.png?t=1703323387"><br/><br/><br/>For everyone who wants to enjoy the <i>peace</i> and <i>atmosphere</i> of Christmas. It's <strong>specifically designed</strong> to be relaxing. There's no score, and it doesn't get faster – just for you to enjoy.<br/><br/>If you're not yet in a Christmas mood, <u>maybe you will</u> be because of this game. <strong>That's our goal.</strong> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artillery Blast</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2723740/Artillery_Blast/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Come and cum! The young ladies feel so uncomfortable, they are trapped inside and can hardly breathe.<br>
<br>
Game introduction:<br>
	This is a casual shooting game. Players will master a powerful gun and shoot various colorful balloons that appear in front of them by moving the gun horizontally. The goal of the game is to pop all the balloons and unlock exquisite CG images.<br>
<br>
Gameplay:<br>
<br/>
	Operation method: Players can adjust the shooting angle by sliding the bottom of the screen to move the position of the gun left or right.<br/>
<br/>
	Shooting mechanism: The gun automatically fires unlimited bullets, and players do not need to shoot manually. The bullets move at a moderate speed, requiring clever movement of the gun to hit the fluttering balloons.<br/>
<br/>
	Types of balloons: Balloons of different colors represent different scores. Players need to prioritize targets according to the color of the balloons. Some special balloons may have additional effects, such as acceleration, deceleration, etc.<br/>
<br/>
	Level design: The game is divided into multiple levels. The number and movement trajectories of balloons in each level will be different, increasing the difficulty and challenge of the game.<br/>
<br/>
	game props:<br/>
<br/>
		Bullets become faster: The speed of bullets is greatly increased, making it easier to hit fast-moving balloons.<br/>
		Stronger attack power: Increase the attack power of guns, making each bullet more destructive.<br/>
		Freeze Everything: Temporarily freeze the movement of all balloons, giving players time to shoot accurately.<br/>
		Restore HP: Restore a certain amount of HP to stay in the game longer.<br/>
		Increased movement speed: The movement speed of the gun is increased, making it more flexible to avoid balloon attacks.<br/>
<br/>
	Clearance reward: For every level successfully passed, the player will unlock a beautiful CG picture to reward their efforts and skill improvement.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skoory Rush</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2399810/Skoory_Rush/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2399810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join our acorn-obsessed, furry protagonist on a wholesome platform-hopping mission through a world of colorful chaos. Outwit wacky woodland creatures, collect crunchy acorns, and perform gravity-defying, combo chaining stunts in this interactive fruit machine collect 'em up. Swim in underground oceans and be the one of the first squirrels to reach outer space. Challenge your friends and climb your way up the online leaderboards. Watch out for those pigeons - they may look friendly, but they'll send you crashing back down to earth in no time.<h2 class="bb_tag">WHAT IS SKOORY RUSH?</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> A game where you can jump and collect as many items as possible.<br/></li><li> A game where you can earn combo points by collecting items without getting hit.<br/></li><li> A game where you die a lot and restart fast. <br/></li><li> A game with no menus, that goes straight into the action. <br/></li><li> A game you can play in short bursts (unless you want to keep retrying to get a better score). <br/></li><li> A game where you can zone and chill out to while listening to your own soundtrack.<br/></li><li> A game with slot machine like colorful graphics and energetic sounds inspired from casino games.​<br/></li><li> A game with Steam leaderboard and achievements. </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">HOW TO PLAY</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Skoory is very light and floaty. Jumping gives vertical momentum, but horizontal momentum is also maintained. <br/></li><li>The longer you hold jump, the higher the jump. A quick tap equals low jump.<br/></li><li>You can't jump while in the air, but a limited number of consecutive wall jumps are allowed. You can even 'bird jump', 'fruit jump' or 'acorn jump' with practice. There is a trail effect after performing a 'wall jump'.<br/></li><li>Enter 'frenzy mode' by collecting 4 acorns without getting hit. Every acorn you collect during frenzy mode has a points multiplier, the birds give more acorns during frenzy mode.​<br/></li><li>Collecting 2 or 3 fruits without touching anything else (including platforms or sides of the screen) will trigger a 1000 or 5000 points bonus. Always go for fruit combos for maximum points.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> You can pause with escape and change the volume with the +/- keys.​<br/><br/>Now, unleash your inner squirrel parkour skills and let the Skoorily shenanigans begin!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lovely Defenders</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2723450/Lovely_Defenders/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Introduction</h2>"Lovely Defenders" is a tower defense and real-time strategy game. Deploy your forces strategically based on different terrains, defeat powerful monsters, and help the girls reclaim their precious belongings – they will respond with real actions.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> You can choose and control multiple adorable defenders in battle.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Each girl possesses unique skills, allowing players to freely mix and match them, creating various tactical combinations. Skillful coordination of abilities will be crucial for overcoming monsters.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>In battle, you can also use the protagonist's skills, such as burning, marking, and more. Help the girls defeat powerful enemies!</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Use coins wisely; defeat monsters to earn coins, which can be used to enhance the abilities of the girls for the current session or strategically saved to upgrade permanent talents.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Flexible defense strategies: Depending on different enemy attack routes, you need to cleverly control the locations where the girls defend. Facing diverse enemies and terrains, adapt your defense strategy to ensure the safety of precious items. </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infinite Borders</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2516570/Infinite_Borders/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Do you want to define your own war style in a strategy game? Infinite Borders is calling you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516570/extras/444x208.jpg?t=1703300460"><br/><br/>With over 10 million downloads, Infinite Borders is one of the most popular strategy games in East Asia. When you enter Infinite Borders, you will return to the Three Kingdoms period--a turbulent dynasty in Chinese history--and have a chance to pen your epic. You will play as a lord and fight alongside Liu Bei, Cao Cao, Lv Bu, and other great Three Kingdoms heroes. Form unique teams with diverse combinations of generals and tactics to defeat more enemies and conquer more lands. You can make special policies and guide your city towards prosperity. In Infinite Borders, grasping the final victory requires not only strength, but also intelligence and strategy. <br/>Now, on the brink of war, it's time to join the battles and rewrite history, my lord!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build Your Estate, Gain Abundant Resources</strong></h2>Construct buildings and upgrade facilities in your city to attain numerous supplies like wood, iron and soldiers. Devote your resources to expansion and development! <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516570/extras/2.gif?t=1703300460"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Command Your Troops, Various Generals Collocation</strong></h2>There are over 300 heroes with different skills waiting for you to recruit. Assemble your generals and formulate kinds of lineups to defeat your enemies! <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516570/extras/3-_400x225.jpg?t=1703300460"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong> Fighter or Farmer, Diplomat or Spy, Make Your Choice</strong></h2>How to rise to the top in this chaotic world? You can be an aggressive fighter who crushes the battlefields. You can be a hardworking farmer who concentrates on building and defending. You can be a sociable diplomat who establishes good relations with other alliances. You can be a mysterious spy who disintegrates enemy forces secretly. Determine your law of victory and write a new chapter of history in this war game!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516570/extras/4-_400x225.jpg?t=1703300460"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516570/extras/5-_400x225.jpg?t=1703300460"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Open Eastern World, Free To Explore</strong></h2>The upgraded 3D graphics restore an authentic ancient eastern world with dozens of famous historic landmarks like Yangtze River, Yellow River and Yueyang Tower, proving immersive gameplay experience. Embark on your unrestricted adventure right now!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516570/extras/6-_400x225.jpg?t=1703300460"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railbreak</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2587170/Railbreak/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2587170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							It's Saturday night in Cypress Ridge which means the city is in ruins, hordes of flesh eating undead are on the prowl, and you have the arcade all to yourself! Grab your lightgun (or keyboard, mouse, or gamepad), select your survivor, and blast your way to safety as the city burns around you in this on-rails survival horror shooter. Oh, and don't forget to bring a friend for zombie fodder, er, we mean multiplayer experience!<br/><br/>Railbreak melds a classic on-rails arcade experience with the cutting edge Unreal Engine 5. In this prelude to Outbreak: Shades of Horror, you'll get an opportunity to see the sights and sounds of Cypress Ridge and get chomped on by a zombie or four! Face the city alone, or bring a friend along with optional 2-player co-op supported across the entire game<br/><br/>Featuring a wide cast of survivors each with their own loadouts and traits, you'll find plenty of replayability in this absurd take of a survival horror game in a survival horror game. A full story mode experience awaits across six scenarios. Bonus modes include Score Attack, and the endless Onslaught Mode that keeps ratcheting up the difficulty until the undead finally seal your fate, as well as Boss Rush, the Shoutout Shootout, and the rogue-like semi-procedurally generated Glitch Gauntlet where anything can happen!<br/><br/>Crack open your piggy bank, snag a fizzy soda, and take a trip back to the 1990’s arcade.<br/><br/>Features:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Next-generation arcade experience with cutting edge graphics powered by Unreal Engine 5.<br/></li><li>Multiple ways to face the undead - Story Mode, Score Attack, Onslaught Mode, Boss Rush, Glitch Gauntlet and Shoutout Shootout!<br/></li><li>8 unique survivors to unlock with their own unique loadouts and perks!<br/></li><li>First class support for mouse, keyboard, gamepads, and the Sinden Lightgun.<br/></li><li>Unpredictable glitch system that dynamically changes game mechanics in real-time to keep you on your toes!<br/></li><li>Unique and thrilling cast of special infected and glitched boss creatures that hunt you across Cypress Ridge in epic fights for survival.<br/></li><li>Extreme gore and dismemberment as you tear apart the undead with a massive arsenal of powerful weapons.<br/></li><li>The cheesiest dialogue and voice acting ever featured in an on-rails shooter.<br/></li><li>Optional 2-player co-op across the entire game.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Score tracking across every mode in the game!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUNSET OF ATE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2575850/SUNSET_OF_ATE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2575850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							SUNSET OF ATE will take you on an adventure on a planet called Ate, which orbits a Red Dwarf. You have to search for lost spare parts for the damaged equipment installed in the laboratory in a completely unfamiliar extraterrestrial environment.<br>
However, the communication with the mothership is disrupted, and the indigenous inhabitants are not particularly friendly towards Earthlings. In addition, there are some strange creatures along the way. And, did I mention a mysterious disease? You will never know what is really happening in this extraordinary world until you collect all the puzzles and place them in correct positions. The truth will definitely blow your mind!<br>
Join this game and experience the challenges and adventures on the magnificent alien planet! Explore the open world with a large map, use exquisite shooting techniques to fight against different alien animals, collect items that can help you recover, and accept tasks from aliens with different personalities. Most importantly, search for hidden secrets on the planet based on the alien's mission!						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skeletery</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2228430/Skeletery/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2228430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Living as ordinary skeleton is hard - you are dead, but now you need to defend your cemetery against evil humans.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Unconventional setting of being a good skeleton, trying to live the undead life in your cemetery.<br/></li><li> <strong>Attack</strong> with weapons! <strong>Block</strong> with shield! <strong>Roll</strong> with style! Collect <strong>bones</strong>! Buy <strong>buildings</strong>! Get <strong>buffs</strong>! <strong>Doot</strong>!<br/></li><li> Dark fantasy RPG, with light touch on story and heavy focus on melee combat and base building.<br/></li><li> Complex fighting, where success is achieved by a careful balance between attacks, blocks and movement.<br/></li><li> Base building in Skeletery unlocks powerful buffs that will increase your chances to survive waves of humans.<br/></li><li> A single-player game with levels progression, where each level represents a unique cemetery that attracts new types of enemies.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Car Mess</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2691200/Tiny_Car_Mess/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2691200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">About The Game:</h2>Tiny Car Mess invites you to a chaotic world of miniature mayhem! Get ready to drift, crash and destroy! Whether you're flipping your opponents, dodging obstacles, causing delightful mayhem or just enjoying this fun little car game, Tiny Car Mess offers a compact carnival of destruction and laughter. So, what are you waiting for?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2691200/extras/gif1.gif?t=1703286288"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Epic Derby Action:</strong> Join a derby with up to 24 participants, creating a whirlwind of chaos on the tracks. Compete with friends or dive into intense 1v1 showdowns. Every collision is a chance for glory!<br/></li><li><strong>Control Variety:</strong> Choose your preferred playstyle with support for keyboard, PS controller, and Xbox controller inputs. Feel the drift, master the turns, and outmaneuver your opponents with the control scheme that suits you best.<br/></li><li><strong>Customization Galore:</strong> Personalize your tiny car with a spectrum of colors. Stand out on the track and showcase your style as you leave a trail of chaos in your wake.<br/></li><li><strong>Steam Remote Play:</strong> Share the joy of chaos with friends far and wide using Steam Remote Play. Invite friends to join the derby madness, regardless of their location, for an unforgettable multiplayer experience.<br/></li><li><strong>Global Fun:</strong> Tiny Car Mess speaks the language of excitement in 19 different languages. Immerse yourself in the fun, no matter where you are, with localization that ensures everyone can enjoy the derby mayhem.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2691200/extras/gif2.gif?t=1703286288"><br/>Embark on an unforgettable derby journey filled with adrenaline-pumping races, hilarious collisions, and non-stop action. Tiny Car Mess is the perfect invitation to a world where mayhem knows no bounds. Are you ready to drift, crash, and dominate the derby? The wheel is yours!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easter Bunny</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2652050/Easter_Bunny/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2652050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A very small Running game, where a Rabbit has to collect as many easter eggs as possible. But be aware, there are children hunting you, if you come too close to them. If they catch you, you'll lose valuable time. Keep watching the timer and get more time by eating carrots. Who will collect the most easter eggs? Compare your score with your friends and family.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moorhuhn Invasion - Crazy Chicken Invasion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667020/Moorhuhn_Invasion__Crazy_Chicken_Invasion/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Help! The invasion of alien Moorhuhn chickens has begun!</h2><br/>Chicken aliens have been watching us from the depths of space. Now they have come to establish their base and take everything that is not nailed down: trees, cows, mountains, grouse…<br/><br/>But we are prepared! Many hidden extras for our defense will give the aliens a hard time and even their superior technology won't be able to save them when we strike back with our shotgun…<br/><br/>Let them come!<br/><br/>90 seconds to hunt as many chickens as possible and score points. Beat your own record and compete against players around the world.<br/><br/>Score at least 800 points to unlock the bonus level. This will give you another 45 seconds to push your score really high.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hidden extras by the dozen<br/></li><li>great graphics and a cool soundtrack<br/></li><li>bonus level<br/></li><li>a strictly confidential hidden EASTER EGG</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2323080/Tiny_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2323080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Tiny Survivors is a short and sweet roguelite autobattler.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><br/>- Endless waves. Survive for as long as possible!<br/>- Collect gold and spend it at the shop between waves1<br/>- Weapons and their synergies are randomly generated every run!<br/>- Fight hundreds of enemies at once!<br/>- Dash! Great for defense, <i>and</i> offense.<br/>- A dozen skins!<br/>- 15-minute runs!<br/>- Play with one hand! Combat is automatic, just walk around!<br/>- Custom engine! Expect great performance on any computer.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZANZIBART</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2708570/ZANZIBART/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>ZANZIBART... FORGIVE ME...</strong><br/><br/>ZANZIBART is a simple roguelite where you avoid bullets &amp; hordes of enemies while mowing them down as fast as you can. Collect diverse items with infinitely stacking effects, and accumulate more with each run's progress to finally reach the end and avenge ZANZIBART.<br/><br/>The game is a comical homage to certain classic Japanese ARPGs &amp; dungeon crawlers - every character, item, and enemy is some kind of riff or reference.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708570/extras/zanzibart_steam_inline.png?t=1703270089"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Run</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1471580/Death_Run/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1471580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1471580/extras/logo_deathrun_about.png?t=1703269850"><br/><br/><strong>Death Run: The Ultimate First-Person Parkour Game in the Sky!</strong> Embark on an exhilarating journey across floating platforms suspended above the clouds. Your mission? Stay alive and navigate to the portal that leads to the next level. Beat the clock to achieve the highest score. Dodge obstacles and avert death through strategic navigation and precise jumping. Are you up for the challenge to conquer the game?<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>No Checkpoints: A single mistake means restarting from the level's beginning.<br/></li><li>Challenging Levels: Each level ramps up in complexity with deadly traps and obstacles.<br/></li><li>Original Soundtracks: Immerse yourself in multiple catchy tunes while playing.<br/></li><li>Built-in Timer and Death Counter: Track your progress and improve your strategy.<br/></li><li>Open Sky Environment: Enjoy vast, cloud-top landscapes without any claustrophobic indoor constraints.<br/></li><li>Varied Mechanics: Master different skills to achieve top scores and beat the game.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brittle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2711120/Brittle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2711120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In the game "Brittle," you will need to fend off pirates and bats by shooting from a cannon. The flying projectile follows the laws of physics, so you must accurately calculate the strength of your shot. Occasionally, the laws of physics are overturned, and you have to adapt to new conditions. Various obstacles will be in your path, such as moving platforms, fragile blocks, teleporters, and more. By carefully calculating the projectile's trajectory, you will reach your goal!<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Beautiful graphics<br/></li><li> Interesting and relaxing gameplay<br/></li><li> 40 levels<br/></li><li> Steam achievements support</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dude Simulator Six</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2719420/Dude_Simulator_Six/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2719420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dude Simulator Six is an open world sandbox game.<br>
A mortal danger looms over humanity. The planet was invaded by representatives of a distant planetary system. Their goal on Earth is to carry out a massive campaign to subjugate humans and use them to extract and transfer resources to their planet.<br>
The game begins in a small town called Palomino Creek. People are kidnapped here every day, and in the outskirts of the city there is a base for the invaders. The government is asking for your help. You will have to get to the main base of the uninvited guests and put an end to this.<br>
From now on, the fate of humanity is in your hands.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milo and the Christmas Gift</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2716140/Milo_and_the_Christmas_Gift/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							After his adventure in Milo and the Magpies, Milo is looking forward to spending a cosy Christmas at home. But a Christmas gift is about to upset his holiday celebrations, especially when said gift disappears after a little misunderstanding! Can you help Milo bring home the lost Gift and save Christmas for Marleen… and himself?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_playing_1.gif?t=1703268967"> <br/><br/>Milo and the Christmas Gift is a free-to-play short and atmospheric point-and-click adventure game created by artist Johan Scherft. The game is a spin-off story following the events in Milo and the Magpies. The game has 5 chapters and a gameplay time of around 30 minutes!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/>■ Relaxing yet stimulating game-play<br/>Join Milo in his home and revisit some of the neighbouring gardens, but this time in a wintery Christmas wonderland! Interact with the festive environment and solve small point-and-click / hidden-object puzzles.<br/><br/>■ Captivating artistic atmosphere<br/>Each hand-painted, interior and snowy garden Milo has to search through has its unique personality, reflecting that of Milo’s owners and next-door neighbours respectively.<br/><br/>■ Atmospheric soundtrack<br/>Each chapter has its own festive theme song composed by Victor Butzelaar.<br/><br/>■ Average playtime: 15-30 minutes<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_snow_1.gif?t=1703268967"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virago: Reality New</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2582740/Virago_Reality_New/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2582740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Virago: Reality New invites you to delve into an immersive narrative that follows the tumultuous journey of Willow, a young girl escaping an abusive home only to find herself entangled in a realm of terror and intrigue. This third-person adventure/horror game offers an intense pursuit experience, blurring the lines between reality and nightmare as you strive to outsmart relentless pursuers.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2582740/extras/PicHospital__1_.png?t=1703268104"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2582740/extras/Gif__2_.gif?t=1703268104"><h2 class="bb_tag"> Storyline</h2><br/>Embark on a haunting odyssey as Willow breaks free from the chains of her troubled past, seeking refuge amidst the enigmatic cityscape. Unforeseen alliances offer fleeting solace, until a sudden abduction compels Willow to ingest a toxic substance. As poison courses through her veins, Willow's reality fractures, plunging her into a surreal realm of hallucination and dread.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2582740/extras/Gif__1_.gif?t=1703268104"><h2 class="bb_tag"> Gameplay</h2><br/>Virago: Reality New promises an adrenaline-charged gameplay experience, where you must navigate a perilous world teeming with danger. Equipped only with a torchlight, skillfully maneuver through dimly lit environments, leveraging the flickering light beams to disorient stalkers and unveil concealed pathways. Survival hinges on your resourceful evasion and mastery of stealth tactics.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2582740/extras/Gif__3_.gif?t=1703268104"><h2 class="bb_tag"> Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intense Third-Person Adventure: Immerse yourself in Willow's harrowing journey, racing against relentless stalkers and confronting the horrors born from the depths of her psyche.<br/></li><li> Eerie Atmosphere: Traverse an atmosphere saturated with suspense, seamlessly blurring the boundary between reality and illusion to maintain an unrelenting tension.<br/></li><li>Stealth and Survival: Utilize your surroundings to outsmart tireless pursuers, employing strategic cunning to elude danger at every juncture.<br/></li><li>Torchlight Mechanics: Manipulate the eerie torchlight to your advantage, distorting stalkers' perceptions while illuminating paths toward safety.<br/></li><li>Mind-Bending Hallucinations: Experience Willow's fragmented reality firsthand, grappling with disorienting hallucinations that twist the very fabric of her environment.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catnight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1779070/Catnight/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1779070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1779070/extras/steam_cats_text_70.gif?t=1703274522"><br/>😼<strong>Wake up Kitty, you have cats to shoot</strong>😼<br/>Catnight is an online multiplayer game that will heat up any meeting with friends. You will not only fight with your opponents and the enormous amount of furry bullets in the air, but you will also need to survive special gameplay circumstances, which will make every match more dynamic and funnier. Don’t forget to team up. It will double the fun.<br/><br/>😼<strong>Team time</strong>😼<br/>From now on you will never be alone. Team up with your friends and crush the opponents together. Take over the beacons to destroy the enemy's core.<br/><br/>😼<strong>Player vs Environment</strong>😼<br/>Level up and acquire new skills to survive hordes of enemies. You can fight for victory alone, but it's more fun in a team.<br/><br/>😼<strong>Online Multiplayer </strong>😼<br/>We know that the best moments are those, that you spend with your amazing friends, so now you have a chance to have fun with them even if they are far away. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1779070/extras/steam_cats_text02_70.gif?t=1703274522"><br/><br/>😼<strong>So much fun</strong>😼<br/>You are fed up with the puffed-up TPP games? Then Catnight is just for you. You will find overwhelming joy in this game. Only the rivalry during the matches will be serious. Are you still reading this? Just fasten your seat belts and arm yourself with kitties.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Slush Force</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2117940/The_Slush_Force/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2117940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2117940/extras/SteamPage-HeroesComeFromUnlikelyPlaces-616px.png?t=1703294327"><br/>Aliens have invaded, and you, for no fault of your own, find yourself at the epicenter. It is up to you to expel these extraterrestrial interlopers from your home. Methodical, turn-based strategy meets high-intensity real-time tactical combat as it is up to you defend the world. Against a relentless enemy, combined arms is not optional!<h2 class="bb_tag"><i><strong>What will you do?</strong></i></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2117940/extras/SteamPage-StoryDrivenTurnBasedAndRealTime-616px.png?t=1703294327"><br/>Take the role of the titular character Slush as you defend your home against an inexplicable and relentless enemy. While the aliens may seem to be a superior ground force, they also seem strangely inadequate in other ways... <br/><br/>And when the unexpected happens, it will be up to you to decide the future!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2117940/extras/SteamPage-MultiLayeredGroundCombat-616px.png?t=1703294327"><br/>Methodically mop up alien forces across different landscapes, ranging from forests to roads to plains. Your positioning on the turn-based map will determine the parameters of the fights that occur. <br/><br/>Attacked an enemy vehicle without anti-tank weapons? Sounds like your problem…<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2117940/extras/SteamPage-DeepCombinedArmsTactics-616px.png?t=1703294327"><br/>Is the enemy too powerful? Maybe that airplane can help out with a 500 kg bomb or two, or that rocket artillery can remove the enemy's firing positions.<br/><br/>You made sure to position it close by, right...?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2117940/extras/SteamPage-PhysicsDrivenBattles-616px.png?t=1703294327"><br/>All action occurs on a physics-driven landscape. Projectiles are modeled ballistically, objects are fully destructible, and armor can deflect impacts at oblique angles. <br/><br/>You can either use this to your advantage, or fall victim to it...<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2117940/extras/SteamPage-DiverseArsenalAndTacticalFlexibility-616px.png?t=1703294327"><br/>Fight using weapons ranging from outdated rifles to modern tanks… or if you can get your hands upon them, captured or reverse-engineered alien equipment. A plasma rifle in the 40 watt range? <br/><br/>With so many options, there is no "right" way to play... if it works, it works.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons of Dragons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2716190/Dungeons_of_Dragons/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>"In an age of guns, swords, and magic, the Philosopher's Stone, which maintains the balance of Dungeons and Dragons, has been stolen. The world hangs in the balance. It's all up to you..."</strong><br/>Honestly, we can't make it all up all the time. Let's have an adventure together! <br/>It is a dungeon adventure game with extremely simple and intuitive controls. Its super smooth and enjoyable gameplay, mixed with roguelike elements, will keep you hooked from the first run! <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716190/extras/Sprite-0004.png?t=1703265052"><br/>Features:<br/>*  7+ Unique Heroes – Ancient Swordsman, Sharpshooter, Magician... There's always an option that fits perfectly with your playstyle. * 50+ weapons – guns, swords and wands... Multiple ways to collect weapons from abyssal and normal dungeons!<br/>*  Tons of dungeons – dark forests inhabited by goblins, medieval castles infested with zombies... Raid tons of monster lairs, loot treasure and encounter different NPCs.<br/>*  Multiplayer mode is available! Team up with friends from all over the world for online co-op adventures, or play solo in single-player mode.<br/>*  Various game modes and features. Prefer brains to brawls? Strategize to strengthen your defenses and attacks, defeat the Abyss Lord, and get treasures! <br/>*  A pixel roguelike adventure game with offline options that combine action and survival. Grab a sword and start your dungeon adventure!<br/><br/>【Three Professional Heroes】<br/>Ancient swordsman, sharpshooter, magician. You can create your favorite characters for dungeon exploration without limits, challenge dungeons and abysses, dungeons and warriors in fantasy pixel games.<br/>【Unique Skills】<br/>Sword Qi Fluctuation, Furious Hurricane, Magic Sword Summoning, Rapid Burst, AWM Expansion Bomb, Fire Core Grenade, Magic Bullet Rain, Demon Bat Raid, Great Demon Contract.<br/>【Powerful Monsters &amp; Levels】<br/>A variety of powerful abyss bosses and dungeon bosses are waiting for you to challenge.<br/>【Multiple Ways to Play】<br/>In the normal dungeon exploration mode, you can also consume abyssal magic stones to challenge the abyss mode. Abyss mode has a higher explosion rate than normal mode. You can also collect material cards to trigger dungeon effects, and players can team up with you to play together. You can also stand on the street and set up stalls and chat, and other players can buy your equipment. After each level, there is still a 50% chance to trigger the Little Black Shop.<br/>【Equipment &amp; Pets】<br/>Plain white, blue. Purple Rare Equipment, Pink Superb Equipment. Epic Orange Gear Premium. Magic Sword - Azles, Shadowless Sword, Meteor Fall, Platinum Revolver are waiting for you to hunt for treasure. Equipment and weapons can be enhanced, and after strengthening, not only the attributes will be enhanced, but the appearance will also change. There are also countless pets waiting for you to adopt, enhancing the combat effectiveness of the owner. There are many more skin kit skins for you to choose from.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revenge Of The Colon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2710950/Revenge_Of_The_Colon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2710950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are a respected gastroenterologist at the height of your profession. You have seen it all and treated it all. There is nothing you cannot handle. You do not know it yet but this is your final week.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>You will spend your time deep in the claustrophobic colons of your patients. You will have to identify and treat any and all ailments you discover in order to ensure the future health of your patients. You will have access to a range of specialized medical instruments to aid you in this task.<h2 class="bb_tag">Story Driven</h2>The game is played in five chapters. Each chapter focuses on treating the ailments of a different patient. The week starts off normally but as the week progresses you encounter the things of a gastroenterologist's nightmares.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple Endings</h2>How you play the game makes a difference to the ending of each chapter and to the ending of the game as a whole.<h2 class="bb_tag">Body Horror</h2>It is not just about generic blood and guts. Each chapter of the game focuses on different aspects of body horror so that players will have something different to encounter with every patient.<h2 class="bb_tag">Visual Style</h2>We chose the retro PS1 style because we know it is much enjoyed by fans of the indie horror genre. The crudeness of the visual style combined with the game's subject matter helps to create an atmosphere of nostalgic unease.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Renovation Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707460/Dungeon_Renovation_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FzFQMrGZpaV" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707460/extras/dc.png?t=1703358592"/></a><br/><br/>Dungeon Renovation Simulator: Prologue offers a glimpse into the world of our upcoming medieval-inspired cleaning adventure. Play as a “Cursed Goblin” cleaner and renovator in this single-player simulation game, which serves as a sneak peek into the first and fourth level of the forthcoming release. Get ready to dive into the captivating world of cleaning, physics-based challenges, and hidden quests.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707460/extras/DRS_Gameplay_GIF.gif?t=1703358592"><br/><br/>Prologue Highlights:<br/>- Explore a unique medieval-inspired environment.<br/>- Master the use of the 'Arcane Sucker' to clean even the messiest of dungeons.<br/>- Interact with objects using realistic physics, allowing for creative freedom.<br/>- Embark on immersive 'physics-based quests' to uncover hidden stories.<br/>- Prepare for the full release, featuring five distinct levels of adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707460/extras/DRS_Renovation_GIF.gif?t=1703358592"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in the oddly satisfying world of Dungeon Renovation Simulator: Prologue, and get a taste of what awaits in the complete experience!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707460/extras/1111.gif?t=1703358592"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animus Toil</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2566030/Animus_Toil/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2566030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i><h2 class="bb_tag">"Ahead of you lies the temple of my creation."</h2></i></strong><br/>Welcome to <i>Animus Toil</i>, the debut video game from Mindset Makers!<br/><br/>The Temple Of The Herring was a legend to the people of Thera, said to be cursed by an evil wizard known only as Somnus. Two explorers find their way into the illusive temple, finding themselves trapped in a dynamic, yet parallel path towards their own fates.<br/>Who exactly is Somnus? Why is the temple cursed? What is the secret behind the mysterious artifacts? And how does this tale all tie into the future of our humanity?<br/><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2566030/extras/Animus_Pieces__Steam_Image_.png?t=1703264437"><br/><br/><i>Animus Toil </i>is an experimental puzzle-adventure game, featuring two playable characters and randomized room sequences, giving each player different experiences. While each puzzle can be solved on their own, it is encouraged for players to exchange solutions and reach the game's end together.<br/>Each playthrough has an estimated completion time of 1-2 hours, and there are 4 possible endings to discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong><i>"Proceed with curiosity."</i></strong></h2><br/>Play the PC port for FREE! This native Windows version is the original Game Boy ROM running on GB Studio's built-in emulator and exported to an executable. This version allows for easy windows/screen-resizing, as well as plug-and-play support for controllers (such as the newer Xbox controllers, which have been tested and working).<br/><br/>The controls are as follows:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Arrow Keys = move player<br/></li><li>Z = A/select/interact<br/></li><li>X = B/back</li></ul><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2566030/extras/Animus_Toil_Bonus_Content__transparent_.png?t=1703264437"><h2 class="bb_tag">Receive the transmission in your own world.</h2>Donate to gain access to all bonus content! This includes access to the Game Boy ROM itself, as well as an exported version for Analogue Pocket, allowing you to experience the game natively through hardware or emulation. Also included is the official soundtrack, enhanced and exported to both FLAC and MP3 formats, as well as assets to create your own physical copy.<br/><br/><i>Animus Toil </i>has been tested and working on most Game Boy emulators, although please be mindful when saving is implemented. VisualBoyAdvance is recommended. For the most authentic experience, as the creator intended, play on Game Boy Color hardware using a burned cartridge (requires battery for saving) or flashcart of your choice with stereo headphones.<br/><br/><strong>Thank you for playing. Good luck, explorers!</strong><br/><br/>Credits:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Story, graphics, gameplay, and music all created by <i>Hunter Gerace</i>.<br/></li><li>GB Studio engine created by <i>Chris Maltby</i>.</li></ul><br/>*STEAM DECK DISCLAIMER:<br/>Unfortunately, <i>Animus Toil</i> has been tested on every version of Proton and currently fails to launch. Until a solution is found, we recommend using the Game Boy ROM.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trim For Your Dream</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2437230/Trim_For_Your_Dream/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							🌿 Welcome to "Trim For Your Dream" - where the vibrant streets of Los Angeles meet the mellow world of cannabis trimming. Ditch the dull 9-5 grind and step into a life where your scissors and dreams lead the way. In this unique point-and-click adventure, experience a journey not just about making it big, but also about chilling out and tuning into the rhythmic pulse of a cannabis trimmer's life.<br/><br/><strong>🎮 Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><strong>Unique Trimming Experience: </strong>Dive into the world of cannabis trimming. Prepare plants, carefully trim buds, and hone your skills in a game experience like no other.<br/><br/><strong>Chill &amp; Play: </strong>Relax with a game that’s laid-back yet engaging, perfect for unwinding.<br/><br/><strong>Custom Visual Style:</strong> Immerse yourself in a distinctive, custom illustrated world that brings the LA cannabis scene to life.<br/><br/><strong>Dream Big &amp; Achieve: </strong>Set your goals on the dream board, work your way up, and upgrade your entire house as you succeed.<br/><br/><strong>Mellow Sounds: </strong>Get lost in the soothing sounds of cannabis history narrated professionally, or tune into the Kingdom of Kush for cannabis-themed fairy tales.<br/><br/><strong>Dub Music Vibes:</strong> Chill out to mellow cannabis dub music, setting the perfect background for your trimming journey.<br/><br/><strong>Achieve &amp; Unlock:</strong> Earn achievements and rewards as you progress, adding depth and replayability.<br/><br/><strong>🏠 Your LA Story:</strong><br/>From the moment you arrive in LA, bag in hand and dreams in your heart, a world of rhythm, color, and the heady scent of cannabis awaits. Reconnect with old ties and trim your way to the top. It's not just about the luxuries; it's about finding your path and chasing dreams that truly matter.<br/><br/><strong>🌱 A Simulator Like No Other:</strong><br/>Set against the backdrop of LA's cannabis culture, "Trim For Your Dream" is a simulator that stands apart. Engage with stories that span thousands of years, listen to cannabis histories, and let the city of angels show you a greener side to life.<br/><br/><strong>🎧 The Sounds of Your Journey:</strong><br/>From the snip of your scissors to the beats of dub music, every sound in "Trim For Your Dream" enhances your experience. Tune into in-game radio stations for an extra layer of storytelling and relaxation.<br/><br/><strong>🌟 Embark on Your Dream-Chasing Adventure:</strong><br/>The time has come to reclaim your place in LA. Pick up your trimming scissors, set your goals, and immerse yourself in a world where dreams take root. "Trim For Your Dream" isn't just a game; it's where your dreams get trimmed into reality.<br/><br/>"Trim For Your Dream": A journey of rhythm, dreams, and cannabis in the heart of LA. 🌆🍃						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disaster Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1888860/Disaster_Island/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1888860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							By yourself or with friends, try to accomplish various tasks and get out of island! Gather materials, supplies and build necessary structures to survive in extreme conditions. You will have to deal with extreme situations,scenarious and conditions but It's  up to you to discover what and who can kill you :)<br/><br/>The game currently offers a couple of game mods, both single player and multiplayer. While playing you gain experience and money for which you can upgrade and unlock upgrades that will help you on harder difficulties. And if you're lucky you'll find some cosmetic stuff in the crate.<h2 class="bb_tag">Natural Disasters</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1888860/extras/Store_1.jpg?t=1703261971"><br/><br/>The game takes place on a strange island, which is accompanied by very strange phenomena. It is very likely that you will encounter dangerous disasters that will make it very difficult to escape from the island. In the blink of an eye, a beautiful sunny day can turn into a fight for survival.<h2 class="bb_tag">Environment</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1888860/extras/Store_2.jpg?t=1703261971"><br/><br/>The island is located in the Bermuda Triangle, which was previously used for experimenting with various technologies. There are a lot of abandoned buildings, bunkers and factories that have long fallen into disuse, but they have left plenty of resources<h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic weather</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1888860/extras/Store_5.jpg?t=1703261971"><br/><br/>The game features a completely dynamic weather system that impresses with both graphics and sound. Watch out for a deep night where the flashlight is your best friend. You could easily get lost or fall into some trap that could cost you your life.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1888860/extras/Store_4.jpg?t=1703261971"><br/><br/>The game offers both singleplayer and multiplayer play in both co-op and versus. You can choose between multiple game mods that will always bring a new experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrades and Cosmetic items</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1888860/extras/Store_3.jpg?t=1703261971"><br/><br/>While playing, you can find crates that will bring you more money. The more difficulty you play the more chances you have to find a rarer crate. And if you're really lucky, you might get a cosmetic item. You can get a weapon skin or  new player skin.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veranoia: Nightmare of Case 37</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2709220/Veranoia_Nightmare_of_Case_37/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Created by: Unreal engine 5.2<br>
Step into the chilling world of 'Veranoia: Nightmare of Case 37' and play as Vera Herdman, a gifted detective thrown into the darkest corners of the human psyche to unravel the mysteries of the deceased. Are you ready to face your deepest fears and unveil the horrors that lurk in the shadows?<br>
In this hair-raising horror adventure, you'll explore nightmares of the departed to uncover the sinister truth behind their untimely demise. Can you navigate the treacherous terrain of their subconscious and solve the sinister enigmas that shroud their deaths?<br>
Prepare to be immersed in a world of macabre riddles and eerie stages, where your wits and courage will be tested. Unlock the secrets of cryptic events and pave your way out of this living nightmare, for the clock is ticking, and an eternity trapped within this nightmare awaits those who fail.<br>
Will you help Vera escape the clutches of this haunting realm, or will she become forever entangled in its nightmarish grip? Her fate rests on your shoulders. Dare to confront the nightmares that lie within, and unveil the chilling mysteries that await you in 'Veranoia: Nightmare of Case 37.'						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atoms and Time</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2603740/Atoms_and_Time/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2603740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2603740/extras/smol_egg.png?t=1703250755"><h2 class="bb_tag">Star in your own paleontology documentary!</h2> Atoms and Time is an evolution survival game with a strong scientific focus, powered by new technological advances in ecosystem simulation. Unlike other evolution simulators, Atoms and Time inserts you right into this world, filled with other species that adapt just as fast as you can. The story of your organism's survival is told in a simplified format inspired by games like Oregon Trail, skipping the wilderness-wandering and throwing you right into the highlights of your creature's life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2603740/extras/bug_options.gif?t=1703250755"><h2 class="bb_tag">Advanced Evolution Prediction</h2>Playing through one organism's lifetime is fast, but the road of evolution is a long and complex one. Atoms and Time does not ask the player to wait around for an interesting mutation to randomly appear in your simulation, or provide the player unrealistic creative tools for character creation. Instead, the algorithm of "auto-evo" calculates the selection pressures that affect your species, given the current environment and known laws of biology. As the player, you get to choose one of a few scientifically plausible pathways to pursue. After that, it's up to you to survive with the tools given to you by nature.<br/><br/>Alternatively, you can play Atoms and Time as a simulator, producing in seconds what other evolution simulators might take hours to accomplish. In addition, auto-evo allows the simulation to understand HOW a species is surviving, and why certain mutations were selected, providing a new window into the story of your simulated life.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Max's Tales</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2477790/Maxs_Tales/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to a magical world full of adventures in "Max's Tales"! This 2D platform game,<br/>has been carefully designed to capture the essence of Mario and Super Nintendo (SNES) classics.<br/><br/>Max and Lily, two brave heroes determined to recover a baby named Johnny, who many years ago was stolen by a fearsome Evil Wizard.<br/>With a blend of unique abilities and teamwork, Max and Lily embark on an epic journey.<br/>through enchanted lands, facing dangers, overcoming challenging obstacles and facing cunning enemies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477790/extras/SoloCoop.png?t=1703250639"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477790/extras/Coop_340p.gif?t=1703250639"><br/><br/>Throughout the adventure, the heroes will find several variations of levels, different challenges<br/>and meetings with bosses. Furthermore, the game offers a variety of power-ups and secret items to discover,<br/>encouraging exploration and rewarding players' curiosity.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477790/extras/PowerUps.png?t=1703250639"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477790/extras/Poderes_340.gif?t=1703250639"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477790/extras/Puzzles.png?t=1703250639"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477790/extras/Puzz_340p.gif?t=1703250639"><br/><br/>With colorful and captivating visuals, an immersive soundtrack and responsive controls,<br/>"Max's Tales" brings the nostalgia of classic games combined with a modern and challenging gaming experience.<br/>Get ready to dive into this exciting journey and help Max and Lily rescue Johnny from the Evil Wizard!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477790/extras/Gameplay_ING.png?t=1703250639"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477790/extras/SnowMobile.png?t=1703250639"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477790/extras/Snow_340p.gif?t=1703250639"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477790/extras/Submarine.png?t=1703250639"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477790/extras/Submarino_340p.gif?t=1703250639"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477790/extras/WishlistNow.png?t=1703250639"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
