<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>GGST Additional Character 11 - Elphelt Valentine</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2524040/GGST_Additional_Character_11__Elphelt_Valentine/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2524040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							This allows the character "Elphelt Valentine" to be used in-game.<br>
<br>
※This product is also included in a bundle. Please be careful not to make duplicate purchases.<br>
※The main game (sold separately) is required to use this product.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sims™ 4 For Rent Expansion Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2140610/The_Sims_4_For_Rent_Expansion_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2140610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Build Residential Rental lots in any livable World with up to 6 units per lot and households of up to 8 Sims per unit. Choose to live as a tenant or property owner in The Sims™ 4 For Rent Expansion Pack. Your Sim can now own and manage multiple Residential Rental lots or move into a home where they’re closer to their neighbors than ever (perfect for snooping!). From potlucks to evictions, there’s a lot to do and a bustling new world to do it in. Purchase through January 18 to get bonus items** to bring the Night Market home for your Sims.<br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Street Eats Digital Content</strong> — Bring night market flavor home with a grill cart, street umbrella, and fruit basket, available when you order from November 2 through January 18**.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>New Lot Type</strong> — New Residential Rental lots give you the chance to get creative with multi-family dwellings. Give your Sims a basement suite to rent out, a duplex to keep 2 families close, townhomes for multiple families, or even build apartments of up to 6 units (or more if you know the cheat). Each Residential Rental can be customized to your specifications.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Property Management</strong> — Property owner Sims can be present property managers, living among their tenants, or they can live in a separate residence while generating income from several property investments. If your Sim doesn’t want to manage the whole property, then perhaps the new Handyperson Career might be better suited to them. Property owners should keep their Unit Ratings high because, if they don’t, they could face consequences like a Tenant Revolt.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Closer Than Ever</strong> — Sims in Residential Rentals will inevitably get tangled up in each other’s lives. They’ll meet with other tenants at Social Events like a community potluck, in the garden, or other common areas at their Residential Rental, and have ample opportunity to discover their neighbor’s secrets by eavesdropping, snooping, or even breaking and entering. If you discover something juicy, you can blackmail other Sims for a bribe, too!<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Bustling and Beautiful</strong> — One of the most iconic scenes Tomarang has to offer is the Night Market where your Sims will savor new foods and add unique objects such as the pressure cooker and electric kettle to their homes. As you explore the world, you might even see children playing new games of marbles and hopscotch or discover the 4 new traits and 4 new aspirations unique to For Rent.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1701985511"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1701985511"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1701985511"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1701985511"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader - Season Pass</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Gain access to the two upcoming major expansions for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader and save with the bundle price!<br>
<br>
1. Void Shadows<br>
(coming June 2024)<br>
<br>
The first major story expansion is all about the Rogue Trader's voidship, the life of its crew, and the threats lurking in its holds. Dive into a new epic story integrated into the main narrative, battle new enemies, and recruit a new companion — a death cult assassin. Explore new decks of your voidship, unlock new upgrade options, and master the mechanics of void combat. Meet new members of your crew on the bridge, such as the Astropath, the chirurgeon, and others.<br>
The events of this story will be reflected in the game's epilogue.<br/>
<br/>
This expansion offers 15 hours of gameplay.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
2. Lex Imperialis<br/>
(coming December 2024)<br/>
<br/>
The second major story expansion sees the Lord Captain join forces with a new companion — a member of the Adeptus Arbites. As the past of House von Valancius begins to present itself in a new light, the Rogue Trader faces difficult decisions that may affect the future of the entire Koronus Expanse.<br/>
Over the course of this story, you will get a chance to learn more about the collection of the Imperial Tithe, otherwise known as the Grand Harvesting. Interfere with this fundamental process of the Imperium at your own peril. Discover new areas, game mechanics, and archetypes — and of course, encounter new horrors of the Immaterium.<br/>
<br/>
This expansion likewise offers 15 hours of gameplay.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader - Deluxe Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682660/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Deluxe_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2682660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Gear up for Koronus Expanse with additional in-game items and digital goodies!<br/><br/>This pack includes:<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Digital Artbook<br/>Explore the beauty of the Koronus Expanse in this artbook made by our talented artists and designers!<br/></li><li>Digital OST<br/>Relive every moment through Rogue Trader’s breathtaking soundtrack, crafted by a team of talented composers. Listen at any time in the best format available, including tracks in FLAC and MP3 quality.<br/></li><li>Wallpaper Pack<br/>Get access to amazing game art in formats ideal for use as wallpapers on your PC/Mac or phone.<br/></li><li>In-Game Item - Firestorm-Class Frigate<br/>An alternative voidship to suit your needs, with alternative starting gear and a unique appearance!<br/></li><li>In-Game Item - Blast Wave Shotgun<br/>Blast your enemies away with this unique shotgun! It allows you to push your adversaries back even if you miss the shot.<br/></li><li>In-Game Item - Wrath of Saint Drusus Chainsword<br/>Show those heretics how it’s done. While this Chainsword removes the ability to make area attacks, it offers some amazing single target damage through truly devastating combos with your party. <br/></li><li>In-Game Item - Heirloom Autopistol<br/>The von Valancius Dynasty is venerable and proud, having access to some truly ancient weaponry – this Autopistiol, for example. The mastery required for creating this pistol has been lost to time, but the sheer craftsmanship enables the user to take their gunning skills to the next level.</li></ul><br/>Digital Goodies: Steam\steamapps\common\Warhammer 40,000 Rogue Trader\DigitalOSTArtbookWallpapers						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1702000678"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1702000678"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Born of Bread</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1555140/Born_of_Bread/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Beings from another age are causing havoc across the land! And with their mischief comes a great threat to everyone. The unlikeliest hero, a golem born of bread, will find himself and his newfound buddies in the middle of a drama that's thousands of years in the making. Together, they will visit incredible locals and meet fascinating characters. Although he may not look like much, Loaf might be the hero this land kneads.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Sentient Bread on a Quest</h2><br/>Play as a flour golem who possesses a never-ending childlike wonder and a set of odd abilities in this 2.5D adventure game!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Cinematic_opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/>Explore the different regions of a wonderful world ripe with mysteries and team up with a colorful cast of fleshed-out characters. With the help of your buddies, face off against menacing and weird baddies and engage in a fun and quirky turn-based combat system.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Enviro_opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/><strong>A home-cooked battle system</strong><br/>Born of Bread puts a twist on turn-based combat tropes with a fun interaction system that will test your reflexes.<br/>This interactive system also features a weaknesss and resistance system that makes battles more strategic.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Combat_Opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/><strong>Team up with your buddies</strong><br/>Loaf can't do it alone. Meet new characters during your adventure, each with their own abilities and personnality. Use their unique skills to overcome threats and obstacles whether in fights or when exploring.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Buddies_opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/><strong>Stream your fights to a fake audience!</strong><br/>Your dragon buddy Dub will let you save your progression but also stream your fights to a fake audience with his little laptop! Gather more viewers and answer their demand to get rewards!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>While the Iron's Hot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1906830/While_the_Irons_Hot/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/WTIH_Steam_Banner_Game_Header__1_.png?t=1701795624"><br/><br/>In the faraway land of Ellian, legendary artisans have gathered for ages to perfect their craft. Now it’s your turn to join them.<br/><br/>Step into the boots of a journeyman blacksmith on a quest to become a master in While the Iron’s Hot, a crafty adventure assembled with mystery, wit, and charm. Forge, smelt, and combine works of metal to grow your smithing skills and discover exquisite new items to create. Explore an island filled with resources, treasures, puzzles, and fellow artisans with their own motives and designs. Rebuild the ruins of Ellian’s long-abandoned blacksmiths’ village to restore its former glory and grow your own crafting capabilities—and ultimately become a true master smith.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/Village_Upgrade_Gif_-_640x360.gif?t=1701795624"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/WTIH_Steam_Banner_Features__1_.png?t=1701795624"><br/><br/><strong>Forge, smelt, assemble</strong><br/>Master every step of the smithing process. Smelt ore and metal into ingots, and shape them into useful parts. Grind each piece to perfection, then use your creativity, knowledge, and finely honed observation skills to assemble alloyed works of art.<br/><br/><strong>Smith a solution</strong><br/>In a land of artisans, you can forge your own key to almost any challenge. Repair machinery to open up pathways. Overcome puzzling environmental conundrums. Win over the isle’s most hardened personalities with your crafty smithing wiles.<br/><br/><strong>Unearth a whimsical adventure</strong><br/>The land of Ellian is a bright, even a little mystical, world populated by charismatic and quirky characters. Explore tunnels with puzzles and resources, and embark on a combat-free journey to reforge the links of a world where crafting connects everything.<br/><br/><strong>Discover the island’s secrets</strong><br/>Ellian is a land of creativity cloaked in mystery. Craft the equipment you need to venture out to new regions. Meet villages full of adept alchemists or skilled shipwrights, but take care—not everyone trusts that you have the best interests of Ellian at heart.<br/><br/><strong>Rebuild a legendary smiths’ village</strong><br/>Forge a new home in Stal, a former haven for blacksmiths, now in ruin following a mysterious disaster. Revitalize the village to upgrade your own capabilities, and prove to the artisans of Ellian you’re worthy of becoming a master blacksmith.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/Environment_Gif_-_634x356.gif?t=1701795624"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Highland Song</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1240060/A_Highland_Song/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Works beautifully on Steam Deck!</h2><i>We're still waiting for Valve to officially verify A Highland Song for Steam Deck, but we've designed it from the ground up to work perfectly there. So if that's your preferred platform, you're in for a treat!</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Moira McKinnon is running away.</h2>To reach the sea, Moira must first cross the Scottish Highlands—a wilderness of paths, peaks, shortcuts, dangers, and song.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/waterfall-jump.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Platforming</h2>Climb peaks to orient yourself and plan your next steps. Spelunk caves, scale cliffs, jump from rock to rock and slide down scree slopes as you make your way forward.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/survival.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survival</h2>Wind, rain and cold are your enemies. Moira is no superhero, and the Highlands are not to be underestimated. Shelter to survive.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/ascend-peak-shorter.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Navigation</h2>Collect and position 100 map fragments to discover faster routes. The hills are crisscrossed with paths: some well-trodden, others hidden away.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/narrative.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Narrative</h2>Learn the stories and the secrets of the hills, which are filled with lost things, echoes, and memories.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/music-run-sunrise.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Rhythm runs</h2>Skip and jump through the valleys to the incredible music of TALISK and Fourth Moon. The landscape itself forms itself around the shape of the music.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/branching-paths.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Replay</h2>Get ready to make the journey more than once, because a single trip isn't nearly enough to discover the Highlands' deepest secrets.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/moira-and-deer.png?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">The Story</h2>Moira McKinnon has never seen the sea. <br/><br/>For fifteen years she’s lived with her mum in a small house on the edge of the Scottish Highlands—then one day she receives a letter from her Uncle Hamish urging her to come to the coast. If she can reach his lighthouse in time, a wonderful surprise will be waiting...<br/> <br/>And so, Moira runs away.<br/><br/>The hills are full of secrets and stories, but what you find will depend on where you go. The narrative is not branching but weaving; a mesh of history, mythology and family secrets. What truths will you discover? <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/zoom-to-lighthouse.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">The World</h2>In the Highlands, every peak has a story to tell and every valley echoes with song. Giants sleep, ghosts sing, crows carry messages, and eagles lift the dead. <br/><br/>But the Highlands’ crags are unforgiving and its summits are cold—Moira’s trek will not be easy. <br/><br/>Can you help her find a way across this winding wilderness in time?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/talisk.jpg?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">The Music of the Highlands</h2>A Highland Song’s soundtrack is composed by Laurence Chapman alongside two multi-award-winning giants of the Scottish folk scene, TALISK and Fourth Moon. Royalty of the festival circuit, these two bands combine virtuosic instrumental playing with fast, inventive rhythms, to produce new tunes in traditional styles played with beauty, energy and swagger.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood West</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_steam_text_header.png?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>Weird West legends meet eldritch horror in <strong>BLOOD WEST</strong>, an immersive stealth FPS. Become the Undead Gunslinger, doomed to roam the barren lands until he finds the means to purge their curse and free his soul. No, this isn’t your typical Wild West desperado redemption arc. This is a damnation arc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_episodes_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The Canyons, the Swamp, and the Mountains. Each swarming with abominable monsters and unholy demons, these are open-ended worlds for you to explore freely at your own pace. It will take the player over 20 hours on average to complete all three scenarios, and over 35 if they want to see everything the barren lands have to offer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_stealth_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/><strong>Blood West</strong> is a stealth FPS inspired by the genre classics such as the Thief series (whose fans will be happy to hear the voice of Stephen Russell, the actor voicing the master-thief Garrett, returning here as the protagonist), S.T.A.L.K.E.R. games, or - from the contemporary catalog - Hunt: Showdown. The gameplay rewards the careful approach: scouting the area, stalking your enemies, and striking from the shadows. Can you figure out a way to clear a fort full of ghouls and monsters without raising an alarm?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_horror_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The Barren Lands present the player with a nightmarish, twisted vision of the Wild West legends. The curse that has befallen the realm has corrupted every living thing, defiled the land itself, while summoning restless spirits and dark entities. In this mixture of gunslinger pulp and Lovecraftian horror, dark occult magick presents just as much of a threat as sudden lead poisoning.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_characters_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>In <strong>Blood West</strong> you will meet many colorful, yet strangely twisted, fully-voiced NPCs. Just as much prisoners of the Barren Lands as you are, they will sometimes share their unusual stories and send you on various missions. Play nice and they might reward you or become your allies. Cross them and risk their wrath.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_secrets_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The game won’t hold your hand. You’ll have to explore the land for yourself (buying a map from a vendor might prove useful!), and figure out your own way to approach quests. As you poke around the three expansive maps, keep an eye out for hidden places and secret stashes. There’s gold in the mountains! Fair warning - it’s probably cursed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_brutal_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>If sneaking around isn’t exactly your thing, or you feel that you have a power advantage over your enemies, you can always take the head-on approach and meet your enemies guns blazing. <strong>Blood West</strong> comes from the creators of the fan-favorite boomer shooter <strong>POSTAL: Brain Damaged</strong>, so much gratuitous fantasy violence and pixelated blood splatter is to be expected!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_inventory_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>One man’s hell might be another hoarder’s paradise! From simple one-use items like bandages, through medical tinctures, explosives and incendiaries, straight to arcane artifacts that - once slotted - can change the way you play the game, the Barren Lands are just filled with STUFF. There are tons of useful items to discover, and there’s a special player’s stash crate for all those super-rare potions that you’ll hoard and never use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_weapons_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>A gunslinger without a gun would be just a regular slinger. Where’s the fun in that? <strong>Blood West</strong> makes sure you’ll have plenty of weapons to choose from. Revolvers, rifles, shotguns, carabines - a great variety of firearms, from standard army-issue to those infused with powerful magic, or straight-up possessed. And if you prefer not to cause a ruckus, there’s a wide selection of hand-to-hand combat weapons and archery weapons to pick your favorites from.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_skills_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The RPG-like perk-based progression system in <strong>Blood West</strong> will allow you to highly customize the gameplay experience to your liking. Become a stealthy hunter, a revolver-fanning gunman or a relentless berserker. You will gain experience and progress through the skill tree, while discovering new artifacts in each of the scenarios that will bestow on you additional abilities. Combining skills and load-out creates more possible playstyles than you’d normally be able to explore in one playthrough.<h2 class="bb_tag">Are you ready to take back the frontier from the dark forces of demonic corruption and earn the right to move on to a better world? The Barren Lands call you, Gunslinger!</h2><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley: A Rift in Time</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2632050/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley_A_Rift_in_Time/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Once an ancient kingdom full of treasures and magical artifacts, Eternity Isle has become lost in time as a result of Jafar’s meddling in magic. Journey to this faraway land and utilize a mysterious new Royal Tool—the Hourglass—as you discover new secrets and uncover lost treasures. Stop Jafar’s scheme to steal the Spark of Imagination, an ancient relic that holds the fabric of Dreamlight Valley together. With the help of the Hourglass, you are the key to fixing rifts in time and putting an end to Jafar’s evil plan!<br/><br/><strong>Unravel a Whole New Story on Eternity Isle</strong><br/>Help foil the plans of the nefarious Jafar as you meet new friends and find treasures lost in time in a new story unfolding in three acts. Secrets from Dreamlight Valley’s past can be uncovered using a new Royal Tool, the Hourglass, as you reveal what happened long before the Forgetting…<br/><br/><strong>Discover a New Island </strong><br/>Delve into three new Biomes, each with new areas to explore and make your own. From Ancient’s Landing to the Glittering Dunes and the Wild Tangle, each has a fully customizable layout to decorate with lost treasures and exclusive Disney- and Pixar-inspired furniture.<br/><br/><strong>Spend Time with Four New Villagers</strong><br/>Reunite EVE with WALL·E, help Rapunzel start an art class, take lessons in heroics from Gaston, and decide if you can really trust Jafar. Explore Eternity Isle with your new friends… or move them back to live in Dreamlight Valley!<br/><br/>Play Scramblecoin, a new board game that your Villagers are waiting to play with you.<br/><br/><strong>Wield the Royal Hourglass</strong><br/>Find a new Royal Tool, the Hourglass, and use its magic to find Relics lost in time. Build Ancient Machines to help automate Activities such as gardening and cooking, which makes it easier than ever to run your island. Take your new Hourglass back to Dreamlight Valley and explore the Realms to see what other treasures you can find!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Svarog's Dream</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2004640/Svarogs_Dream/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2004640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Ever-changing world</h2>In Svarog's Dream, you will have absolute freedom to explore the world and make decisions.<br/>However, freedom comes with consequences; over time, your actions will shape the world around you, either for the better or worse.<h2 class="bb_tag">Soul lost between worlds</h2>You start as a lost soul, and you will inhabit human hosts who are desperate enough to accept you. With each death, you will revisit the underworld and return through new characters with their unique backgrounds and talents.<h2 class="bb_tag">A pawn in the game of Gods</h2>While humans are waging their wars on Earth, the Gods are battling each other in the sky.  <br/>Their power is immense; however, everyone is bound to the threads of destiny, except for you. <br/>You possess a valuable power—the power of free will—and because of that, <br/>the gods will see you as an important piece and will try to persuade you to join their side.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2004640/extras/BogoviBaner14.png?t=1702050950"><br/><br/><strong>The old prophecy:</strong> <br/><i>"Svarog, the first god, created six worlds and fell asleep.<br/>In his dream, he created the seventh world, Earth.<br/>Once he wakes up, Earth will cease to exist."</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Immersive gameplay</h2>In Svarog's Dream, you will discover over a hundred quests, more than a hundred unique abilities, and over five hundred unique items. <br/>You will have to eat, cook, sleep, craft potions, upgrade gear, buy houses, take loans, and even evade debt collectors or headhunters, and much more.<br/>We have done our best to make the world around you feel alive and responsive to your decisions.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1701702754"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1701702754"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1701702754"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1701865363"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1701865363"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SteamWorld Build</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2134770/SteamWorld_Build/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-Homestead.png?t=1702026390"><br/>One final landrush! The planet is dyin', Astrid, and it's dig or die trying! <br/><br/>That mine under our town is sitting empty, and wouldn't you know there's rumours of ancient tech down there that might help us out of this predicament. Round up the posse, circle the wagons, and let's get to buildin' a new home! Collect resources above ground and ores down below so we can get those wealthy bots in here to help us build bigger, and we can get the heck out of here!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_1.gif?t=1702026390"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_manage.png?t=1702026390"><br/>As your borders expand, new steamfolk will find their way to you! Every bot is crotchety in their own way, and it's up to you to keep them steaming along. Barter to boost efficiency, keep goods flowing to and from the mines and keep everyone happy to make them work their darndest and hardest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_2.gif?t=1702026390"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-DIG-DEEP.png?t=1702026390"><br/><br/>Stare into the abyss long enough and it might just stare back... we're going looking for riches and something down there doesn't want to share! Have gun, dig gravel, and make sure the mines don't collapse upon you as you defend yourselves from the creepy crawlies that lurk within...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_3.gif?t=1702026390"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_features.png?t=1702026390"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break ground on a bustling SteamWorld town, inspired by the Old West.<br/></li><li>Keep your steambots from getting cranky by ensuring their complex needs get met<br/></li><li>Dig deep and spread wide to produce resources to aid your search for ancient technologies<br/></li><li>Defend your mine from the creepy varmints that lurk deep below your town<br/></li><li>Trade resources at the local train stop and welcome special visitors who'll lend a hand<br/></li><li>Five distinct maps littered with secrets for the discerning SteamWorld explorer to find<br/></li><li>Developed from the ground up for both mouse and controller, whichever takes yer fancy.<br/></li><li>Four difficulty levels, including a sandbox difficulty for when you just want to Build!</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalypse Party</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2351560/Apocalypse_Party/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">The moment of "Apocalypse" approaches, this time... ...you fight for yourself!</h2><br/><strong>「Apocalypse Party」</strong> is distinct from the former 「Project Zero」<br/>In this installment, you will delve deeper into this long-standing battle, with the story gradually becoming incredible! Time travel? Apocalypse? Saving the world? You will face many more unknown challenges... ...<br/>But it still retains our beloved RogueLike + mowing-down-enemies combo, and you will face this catastrophe online with your friends (of course, you can also face it alone)!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Engaging and Deep Mechanics ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT01_Skills_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/><strong>Talent pool expanded to 450! And most of them are mechanics that can change the course of battle</strong><br/>Additionally, there are:<br/>- Hundreds of distinct ranged and melee weapons!<br/>- A plethora of divine ultimate skills!<br/>- 35 varied hero characters, hundreds of unique hero skills<br/>The richness has increased by <strong>more than 10 times compared to the former installment</strong>! Can you build the strongest combo?<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Supports Multiplayer, shall we join the hunting party tonight? ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT02_MutiplePlayerMode_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>Support <strong>up to 3</strong> multiplayer online! <br/>Massive hordes of zombies, exhilarating mowing-down action, why enjoy it alone?<br/>Imagine the joy of roaming through a sea of zombies with your friends!<br/>Call them, support each other, move forward or retreat together, survive here!<br/><strong>Of course, we kindly remind you, a "friendship-ends" scenario is not excluded :)</strong><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ You crave some real challenge, don't you? ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT04_Boss_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>In this game, you will face the ultimate challenge.<br/><strong>9 highly challenging Bosses!</strong><br/>Only rapid growth can help you withstand the fierce attacks from the Bosses, accept the challenge, defeat them, and show them who’s boss now!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Perhaps we can do some time traveling! ■</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT05_Medivel_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>A brand new storyline takes you into this familiar yet strange world, continuing a tale of redemption amidst time traveling:<br/>The tragic death of loved ones<br/>The desperate nuclear explosion<br/>The eerie rebirth<br/>The deathly quiet town<br/>The dark dungeons<br/>... ...<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ We are continuously focusing on your gameplay experience! ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT03_Combat_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>We have keenly listened to the feedback from the players of our former installment, reworked the combat system of the game, continuously bringing more fluid gaming experiences to players.<br/>-<i>Mix and use combat methods like melee weapons, firearms, spells, summoning, witchcraft... ...</i>! They will bring you a fun experience.<br/>-<i>Drive vehicles, summon planes, dragon flying, use otherworldly ninjutsu, even use the mysterious Dual-vector Foi</i>, and more easter eggs await your exploration.<br/>-This game encourages an online experience, but undoubtedly, the single-player part can still experience all the systems and joy of this game.<br/><br/>Smooth operation (handling) is also an important part we continuously focus on！<br/>We have made the game’s operation &amp; flow experience more user-friendly.<br/><strong>Easy to get started, yet "easy to learn, hard to master"!</strong><br/><br/><strong>"Since the apocalypse is here, join us for the last revelry."</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/Library_Hero_EN.jpg?t=1701678706"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-4 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">4-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with three other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1701703276"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinball M</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2337640/Pinball_M/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-1.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-2.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free<br/>- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage<br/>- Thrilling competition<br/>- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation<h2 class="bb_tag">Sink your teeth into these tables as purchasable DLC: </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">- Chucky's Killer Pinball:</h2> Step into a twisted realm where the innocent becomes sinister, and the playful turns menacing. Navigate through an eerie playfield where Chucky lurks in the shadows, ready to pounce.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Dead by Daylight™️ Pinball:</h2> Become the hunter or even the hunted in a thrilling fusion of classic pinball and the excitement of one of the most popular horror games ever created.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Duke Nukem's Big Shot Pinball:</h2> Enjoy the biggest, grooviest, most BADASS pinball table ever made packed with guns and babes. Push start and play with balls of steel!<h2 class="bb_tag">- The Thing Pinball: </h2>Use your pinball skills and battle against the shape-shifting alien through the arctic chill of U.S. Outpost #31. Can you trust anyone, even yourself?<br/>- Even more coming...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-4.png?t=1701703297"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn back immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Option</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.<br/>If you are easily intoxicated, changing the following settings may help.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera shake】</strong><br/>The camera shakes when you walk or run, but if you set the value to 0.0, the camera will not shake.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Acceleration】</strong><br/>If you set the maximum value to 30.0, the camera will move without delay.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Sensitivity】</strong><br/>If the sensitivity is high, the camera will move significantly when the mouse is moved. <br/>Adjust the value if you find it difficult to operate the camera with the default value of 1.<br/><br/><strong>【Motion Blur】</strong><br/>Afterimages will appear when the camera is moved. Recommended to disable at 30FPS<br/><br/><strong>【Preset】</strong><br/>Set the overall graphic settings.<br/>If you do not have sufficient specs, it is better to set it to "Low" to avoid sickness.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1701853441"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1701853441"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1701853441"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats and Seek</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2672090/Cats_and_Seek/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							😻 100 Cats!<br/>🔍 Hint system<br/>🎨 Choose your favorite color<br/><br/>Let's play hide and seek with 100 cats!<br/>Can you find them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/extras/game_play.gif?t=1702029387"><br/><br/>And if bored with black and white doddles you can choose <strong>your own favorite color</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/extras/change_color.PNG?t=1702029387"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1701808865"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobalt Core</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2179850/Cobalt_Core/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_1.gif?t=1701600866"><br/><br/>Cobalt Core is a sci-fi roguelike deckbuilder with a unique single-axis combat system that will throw you for a loop. Many loops! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_2.gif?t=1701600866"><br/><br/>Give orders to your crew by playing cards: Will you <strong>raise shields</strong> to protect your ship, <strong>dodge</strong> incoming missiles and cannon fire to avoid damage outright, or <strong>strike</strong> preemptively to disable your enemy’s weapons? Outmaneuver your foes to stay just ahead of impending calamity, and reach the Cobalt Core!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/characters.png?t=1701600866"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fresh new spin on tactics –</strong>  dodge attacks and target weak points in this unique single-axis take on tactics combat. Outwit the enemy in a high stakes game of cat and mouse!<br/></li><li><strong>Customize your deck –</strong> hundreds of cards and split upgrade paths means no two runs will be the same. Find that perfect combo that brings your deck from powerful to overpowered.<br/></li><li><strong>Get to know your crew –</strong> each character comes with a completely unique playstyle and their own personal story. Bring 3 along, mix and match their decks, and see how these little goobers get along with each other.<br/></li><li><strong>Tons of replayability –</strong>  hundreds of different character+ship combinations before you even hit “start run”. Crank up the difficulty and really test your skills!<br/></li><li><strong>Forward momentum –</strong> untangle a narrative and unlock more playstyles as you go. Is there any escape from this time loop?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/grandma_cookies.gif?t=1701600866"><br/><br/>By the makers of <i>Sunshine Heavy Industries</i>, recipient of IGF's <strong>Honorable Mention for Excellence in Design 2022</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658820/Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							10 possible fruits and one goal, reach the Watermelon.<br/>Your job is to combine matching fruits to evolve them to the next one and eventually reach the coveted Watermelon.<br/>To help you, you have 3 different abilities at your disposal. But watch out, using these will cost you some of your points. Be smart about when you use them to get the highest score!<h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLAYER</h2>Measure your fruit skills against another player.<h2 class="bb_tag">GET THE WATERMELON</h2>How many Watermelons can you combine before your basket overflows?<h2 class="bb_tag">USE YOUR ABILITIES</h2>Power, level up and destroy — These abilities will help you reach the Watermelon, using any of those will also allow you to angle your aim.<h2 class="bb_tag">GOLDEN FRUIT</h2>If luck is on your side, you might even see the mysterious Golden Fruit. Find it and witness its effect firsthand.<h2 class="bb_tag">STATISTICS</h2>Track your progress with in-depth statistics. Visit the menu to see the number of fruits you've combined, your ability usage, and much more.<h2 class="bb_tag"></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.codecks.io%2Fwatermelon-game" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/extras/Roadmap_Banner.png?t=1701768047"/></a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Her Head</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2681240/In_Her_Head/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2681240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>"In Her Head"</strong> - a captivating visual novel that offers players a unique glimpse into the daily struggles of the main character with social anxiety. Immerse yourself in her inner world, where anxiety, procrastination, and unease are constant companions. In this visual novel, you will experience several days in her life, with the central challenge being a single task — making a phone call to schedule a haircut. But what is it like when every call feels like a trial? Help her overcome her fears and take this step.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/>4 Endings: Your decisions impact the storyline's outcome.<br/>Dive into her mind: Explore the main character's inner world through her thoughts and internal dialogue.<br/>Stylish visual design: Enhances the game's atmosphere.<br/>Sound design that accentuates emotions and the character's states.<br/>Unusual immersion into the world of inner struggles.<br/><br/>The game addresses the timely topic of mental health.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiki-Chiki</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2238010/ChikiChiki/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2238010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2238010/extras/Title_Resized.gif?t=1702050970"><br/><br/>Every now and then, the ocean hosts the most exciting and glorious competition ever created by fishkind : the The Great Lagoon Cup. This tournament of the first water, gathers countless competitive Bubble-eye hustlers from all around the ocean. <br/><br/>They like going by the name of <strong>Chiki-Chiki</strong>.<br/>You might ask, “what is so special about this fishie-specie ?”<br/><br/>First of, they look fantastic. <br/>Secondly, they can <strong>reach outstanding speed</strong> thanks to their strong native seahorse-power, at the cost of <strong>pretty challenging maneuverability</strong>. <br/><br/>Folks from far miles of sand came to witness first-class achievements, tragic yet comical events. And by fighting strong currents, entangled in seaweed, knocked away by coral turnstiles.. the fish with oversized cheeks will deliver, the best show ever. <br/><br/>The reefs are calling upon their new champion, and you just might have the chance of your life to take part.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2238010/extras/Algues64_lossy35.gif?t=1702050970"><h2 class="bb_tag">Did someone say fishrace? </h2><br/><strong>Yes we did.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2238010/extras/Laby64_lossy35.gif?t=1702050970"><h2 class="bb_tag">Whether you’re here for <strong>Fun</strong> or for the <strong>Speedrun</strong>...</h2><br/>To play Chiki-Chiki, you will need a controller with 2 joysticks to impulse your bubble-eye fish’s cheeks to victory.<br/><br/><strong>Easy to learn, awesome to master</strong>, the gameplay revolves around <strong>accuracy and physical simulations</strong>. Challenge everyone in this fun and frenzic 2D racing game, through a wide pan of crazy hurdles.<h2 class="bb_tag">What’s in the game?</h2><br/>• Many <strong> gorgeous fishies</strong><br/>• <strong>4</strong> colorful <strong>racing maps</strong><br/>• <strong>Physic simulated environments</strong> filled with obstacles<br/>• A <strong>local multiplayer 1v1</strong> game mode<br/>• A <strong>single player time attack</strong> game mode <br/>• <strong>Awesome soundtracks</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2238010/extras/Courant64_Hexa_lossy35.gif?t=1702050970"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2238010/extras/01_a_propos.png?t=1702050970"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1702050756"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1702050756"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1702050756"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1702050756"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1702050756"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1702050756"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1702050756"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1702050756"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lollihop</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/825160/Lollihop/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/825160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">So Real You Can Taste It!</h2>Embark on a journey through three distinct, beautifully rendered worlds. Each realm in <strong>Lollihop</strong> is brimming with vibrant colors and lively characters, setting the stage for an immersive and enjoyable experience. Your mission is to navigate these realms, using the unique lollihop to leap, bound, and collect a variety of juicy fruits scattered throughout the levels.<h2 class="bb_tag">Innovative VR Experience</h2>Lollihop leverages the power of VR to enhance traditional platforming mechanics. The stereoscopic vision offered by VR headsets allows for unparalleled depth perception, enabling you to make more precise and challenging jumps. This innovative use of technology not only enriches the gameplay but also brings a fresh perspective to the platformer genre.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Sweet, Bite-Sized Adventure</h2>Perfect for those seeking a short yet satisfying gaming experience, Lollihop combines the joy of classic platformers with the innovative features of VR. Whether you're a longtime fan of platforming games or new to VR, Lollihop promises a sweet, diabetes-inducing adventure that's not just a game, but a delightful journey through a world of wonder and excitement.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retro Blaster : Mech Madness #1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2640420/Retro_Blaster__Mech_Madness_1/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2640420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Retro Blaster: Mech Madness is a fast-paced FPS shooter, action, and platformer puzzles, created by one-man development Time Warp Game Studio using Unreal Engine. Combine a variety of weapons and skills, Jump higher and slam attack to critical damage and take the enemy down!<br>
<br>
In Retro Blaster: Mech Madness you play as a young boy Max who has awakened in a sci-fi colorful world in his own dream, full of puzzles, traps, and a platformer waiting for you ahead, armed with your toy hammer, weapons, and skills ability to against the mecha robots<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
Features : <br/>
<br/>
Explore – Discover the sci-fi colorful world. Interact with platformers, traps, and puzzles, hit the box with your hammer, and get a gear item to get more shield, and find hidden items like ammo, grenades, diamonds, health to help you a lot in this journey<br/>
<br/>
Battles - Conquer chaotic and fun battles, face off against enraged mecha robots, and defeat their bosses with lightning-fast mechanics and incredible weapons. Jump higher and slam attack to more critical damage to take the enemy down!<br/>
<br/>
Solve Puzzles - Make your way through a colorful world, Explore and crack a variety of fun puzzles, like moving the magnesis box, platforming, and traps, explore the world, and use your imagination and logic to complete the challenging puzzles.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
About The Developer :<br/>
<br/>
Time Warp Games Studio Indie game developer and outsource services founded by the one-man developer, began work on Retro Blaster: Mech Madness as a full-time project after working as an Environment artist in the Game-Dev Industry.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaserPoint</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1993190/LaserPoint/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The turn-based strategy game that requires you to use building elements to hit all the laserpoints on each level with lasertrons! In this game, you'll encounter a variety of lasertrons that can be reflected, refracted, decomposed into a spectrum of lasertrons, or change colors.<br/>It's important to note that white lasertrons can destroy blocks and laserpoints of any color, while color lasertrons can only destroy blocks and laserpoints of the same color. You'll also need to keep in mind that the number of generated lasertrons is limited, as well as the number of reflections for each lasertron. To complete each level, you'll need to build strategically, taking into account the possibilities of the missing game blocks.<br/>The game features 3 difficulty levels: Easy, Medium, and Hard, so you can choose the level that suits your skills. Additionally, there are two save modes available: checkpoints or passed levels, so you can take a break and continue playing where you left off.<br/>The complete game distribution includes 60 levels, so you'll have plenty of challenges to keep you entertained for hours. Get ready to clean the playing field by generators of lasertrons and show off your skills in this exciting turn-based strategy game!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993190/extras/help_ex.png?t=1702048309"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phantoms</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2702020/Phantoms/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2702020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Behold the moon! Be my harbinger, and you shall be rewarded with miracles!</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2702020/extras/steam1_1_.gif?t=1702047774"><br/><br/><strong>Phantoms</strong> is a first-person horror game that takes place on a strange train. You're on route to see your old friend Floyd, but all of a sudden, you sense something's not quite right. What was a simple, relaxing train ride mere moments ago, transforms into a hunting ground in a blink of an eye... and <i>you're</i> the prey.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2702020/extras/steam2.gif?t=1702047774"><br/><br/>The game takes inspiration from retro PlayStation™ graphics and aesthetics, combined with analogue horror and a hint of eldritch mystery. No two levels ever play the same as the layout of the train, and the items you need to collect, are randomized every time. <strong>Phantoms</strong> offers five story levels (the final one being hidden in conjunction with the secret ending), a custom level mode and two potential endings to the story.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2702020/extras/steam3.gif?t=1702047774"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Detective: The Case of the Rebel Robot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2697690/Space_Detective_The_Case_of_the_Rebel_Robot/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697690/extras/Space_DetectiveV2.png?t=1702047143"><br/><br/>Embark on an otherworldly investigation in "Space Detective: The Case of the Rebel Robot"! Tragedy strikes at The Diogenes Science Station as Dr. Helga Steiner, the Chief Science Officer, meets an untimely end in the DNA Lab. Suspecting a deeper conspiracy, the Astral Federation calls upon Captain Sophia van Buren and her adept crew to uncover the truth. Navigate through the enigmatic corridors, interrogate the crew, and decipher the space station's encrypted files to reveal the chilling reality—a meticulously planned murder, not a mere accident. Grab your detective hat, traverse the cosmic frontier, and bring justice to this orbital science station. The fate of the galaxy hinges on your investigative prowess. Can you unveil the secrets before the rebel robot strikes again? The cosmic clock is ticking, Detective.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697690/extras/GAME_FEATURESv3.png?t=1702047143"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> A juicy Sci-Fi Mystery Storyline<br/></li><li> 3 different endings influenced by who you accuse as the perpetrator<br/></li><li> 3 different romanceable women<br/></li><li> Cool Elctropop and Synthwave Soundtrack<br/></li><li> Anime style character art</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neon Heights</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2702940/Neon_Heights/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2702940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this 3D precision platformer jump and climb your way thorough various obstacles while trying to reach your way to the top of the level. Be sure to use all the tools and abilities you gain along the way to help aid you in reaching the goal at the end of the level. The level is also timed, so race to see if you can get the quickest time possible. But be warned, just one misstep and you'll fall your way back to the bottom. Speed and strategy is key to reaching the goal.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Night Shift</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2628070/Last_Night_Shift/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2628070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2628070/extras/gifui_pilkas.gif?t=1702046030"> <br/><br/>An employee arrives for his night shift at the motel. Tonight will be his final night at this job. His cheerful colleague, Sarah, goes home for the night and he is left alone. His final night seems just as boring as any other at the motel. As always, it is an empty, forgotten place. The man is performing his usual duties, when he suddenly starts to see disturbing, blood-curdling visions. When a strange and scary visitor appears in the forgotten motel, the man’s final night shift turns into a nightmarish fight for his life.<br/>Last Night Shift is a first-person horror game that creates a spooky atmosphere and tension. The game has a walking simulator and psychological horror genre elements. The action develops quite quickly and engages players from the beginning. Players solve mild puzzles, search for hidden items and complete various objectives.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I commissioned some cats 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635720/I_commissioned_some_cats_8/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A hidden object game where you must find all the cats and wool to complete each level.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key features:</h2>🖼️ 15 Unique artworks<br/><br/>❓ 1500+ Hidden objects total<br/>🐈 750+ Cats<br/>🧶 750+ Wool<br/> 💡 ∞ Unlimited hints if you get stuck<br/>♻️ Restore a small number of hidden objects to a painting so you can find them again!<br/>🎵 Music for each artwork<br/>⌨️ Use your keyboard to move/zoom in if you have no scroll wheel<br/>💾 3x save slots<br/>🗑️ Reset progress entirely and play again<br/>🕒 Timer included to show how long you took to complete each level<h2 class="bb_tag">Context:</h2>The brief was simple. I commissioned artists to create a fantasy world, and hide as many cats and wool as they can inside it. Now it’s your job to find them all! With 15 art pieces to choose from, you will have a lot of searching to do.<h2 class="bb_tag">Controls:</h2>Use your mouse to move around the image and zoom in / out. When you find a cat or wool, click it and it will disappear. You can also use WASD to move and the arrow keys to zoom.<h2 class="bb_tag">Difficulty:</h2>A full range of difficulty is included, but all levels start unlocked, your progress is saved as you play, and you can use hints if you get stuck.<h2 class="bb_tag">Get immersed:</h2>Each painting has its own music to help you connect with the world, as you search for everything.<h2 class="bb_tag">Replayable</h2>You can restore a small number of hidden objects back into a painting so you can find them again! It’s much harder when there are only a few hidden objects left (especially randomly). You can also use up to 3 save slots so you can replay without progress loss. Alternatively, you can reset your progress for the entire game if you’d like to start over.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungry Jungle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2706720/Hungry_Jungle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a 2D survival game. You need to control the movement of the character to complete the survival challenge.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>In order to find the fun and passion of life, you come to the jungle alone to explore and survive here by collecting and making items.<br/></li><li> There are not only jungles, but also beaches, wetlands, and plateau maps. The items that can be collected in each map are different, and the climate is also different. You need to adapt to the environment here.<br/></li><li>The protagonist has attributes such as water, satiety, mentality, endurance, and weight.<br/></li><li> The setting of randomly encountering wild beasts, be ready for battle at any time, there are too many accidental events in the jungle.<br/></li><li> Has a rich production system including axes, fire, shelters, spears, and can even burn kilns and smelt iron.<br/></li><li> Try to simulate the experience of a real jungle as much as possible</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevermind This</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2181100/Nevermind_This/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2181100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2181100/extras/DO_Not_NEVERMIND_wide.png?t=1702040724"><h2 class="bb_tag">Overview</h2>Step into the infernal hut of 'Nevermind this', a drive-crazy horror game that takes place in deep woods. Mike, a lumberjack who has been living and working alone for more than a couple of decades, one freezing winter evening as usual returns home. It was supposed to be a usual routine evening. Supposed. The game challenges you to face your deepest fears as you navigate through a labyrinth of confusion, solitude, chaos, and distraction. As you move through the cursed hut, you must ignore the strange and unsettling surroundings and manage to survive the unknown horrors that are hiding in the dark.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2181100/extras/ezgif.com-resize.gif?t=1702040724"><h2 class="bb_tag">The Main Gameplay Highlight</h2>In 'Nevermind this' you are thrust into a dark and foreboding world where every turn hides something new. The game features a mix of first-person exploration and adventure gameplay, as you must find solutions to many paranormal and blizzard situations. Gameplay forces you to doubt truthfulness of your surroundings. Experience unpredictable events, weird stuff and surreal scenes. The game's dynamic environment is designed to keep players on edge and in a state of constant fear, with unexpected scares and challenges around every corner.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2181100/extras/ezgif.com-resize__1_.gif?t=1702040724"><h2 class="bb_tag">The Atmosphere</h2>The cursed hut at the heart of 'Nevermind this' is the home of a mysterious and lonely Mike-the-old lumberjack. The only thing that can remind us about civilization is the railway. As you explore the hut and the surrounding area, you will uncover clues and hints about the history of the lumberjack and the curse that has befallen the area.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garage Flipper: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2414010/Garage_Flipper_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414010/extras/click_follow3.gif?t=1702045721"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1764270/Garage_Flipper/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1764270/Garage_Flipper/</a><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2487060/Anonymous_Hacker_Simulator/" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2487060/Anonymous_Hacker_Simulator/</a><br/><br/><strong>The Prologue is only part of the full game and is completely free. Every player will be able to play it and see what awaits them in the full version of the game.</strong><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FrrXhM8TF6y" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414010/extras/joindiscordGI.png?t=1702045721"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414010/extras/Banner_Garage_A.gif?t=1702045721"><br/>You're an ambitious contractor with a passion for repair shops. The task seems simple, but is it really? Will you handle demolishing walls without having the roof collapse on your head? Can you give them a nice, even paint job? Starting's always tricky but remember – practice makes perfect!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CLEAN UP</strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414010/extras/Banner_Garage_C.gif?t=1702045721"><br/>Many people treat their garage like a dumpster and, unfortunately, before you can get to decorating the interior, you'll first have to liberate it from old junk. Rusty mufflers, used-up batteries, shelves of empty cans, as well as old fridges and washing machines are just some of the things people tend to stuff and forget in their garages. Sort the recovered materials or try to sell them to scrap collectors.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>REMAKE THE GARAGE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414010/extras/Banner_Garage_E.gif?t=1702045721"><br/>Go for your hammer and bust open the old walls! You can make rooms bigger by building new ones and installing new roofs and floors. Choose your preferred paint color and soon you'll see new life breathed into the garage!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>BUY NEW FURNITURE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414010/extras/Banner_Garage_F.gif?t=1702045721"><br/>Place a brand new workbench and tool cabinets, as a more expensive preset, or create a collection yourself by laying out tools individually. Remember that everything needs its proper spacing and placement.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harmonic Depths</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594480/Harmonic_Depths/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Overview</strong><br/>Embark on a relaxing journey in an underwater realm. Glide through captivating environments, embracing the tranquility of exploration and survival found in these Harmonic Depths. Play in Survival Mode, managing your health, which gradually decreases over time, and replenishing it by feasting on the abundant fish that surround you, or immerse yourself in Casual Mode, exploring the ocean at your own leisure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594480/extras/Harmonic_Depths_Gif_1.gif?t=1702039649"><br/><br/><strong>Controls</strong><br/>To move up, press the W key, or use the up arrow key. To move down, use the S key, or the down arrow key. For left turns, press A or the left arrow key, and for right turns, use D or the right arrow key. Hold down Left Click to boost. You can pause the game anytime by pressing the Escape Key. Press the Enter Key to return to the main menu.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knight Speed</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2579000/Knight_Speed/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2579000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Overview</strong><br/>Embark on an epic medieval adventure in this fast-paced endless runner. As a valiant knight, leap across perilous towers, skillfully shoot down enemies with your trusty bow, and protect your kingdom while racing against the relentless passage of time.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2579000/extras/Knight_Speed_Gif_1.gif?t=1702039582"><br/><br/><strong>Controls</strong><br/>To jump, press the Spacebar. Press the Spacebar again in the air to double jump. Aim using the Mouse Cursor, and while jumping, click the Left Mouse Button to shoot. You can pause the game at any time by pressing the Escape key.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D PUZZLE - Wild West</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2703210/3D_PUZZLE__Wild_West/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Collect a 3D puzzle, transferring things to the right places to create a beautiful place.<br>
<br>
The game is a 3D puzzle, the player needs to put in place the missing pieces of the puzzle (items) scattered around the location. To create an entire location.<br>
<br>
You need to go to the item, take it by pressing the left mouse button and take the item to the desired location marked in green. If you brought the correct item, it will snap into place and you will receive leaderboard points and achievements for this.<br>
<br>
Collect as much items as possible as quickly as possible to get more points for the leaderboard.<br>
<br/>
If you brought the wrong item, you can throw it away, it will return to the starting location so that you can pick it up again.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D PUZZLE - World War II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2703220/3D_PUZZLE__World_War_II/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Collect a 3D puzzle, transferring things to the right places to create a beautiful place.<br>
<br>
The game is a 3D puzzle, the player needs to put in place the missing pieces of the puzzle (items) scattered around the location. To create an entire location.<br>
<br>
You need to go to the item, take it by pressing the left mouse button and take the item to the desired location marked in green. If you brought the correct item, it will snap into place and you will receive leaderboard points and achievements for this.<br>
<br>
Collect as much items as possible as quickly as possible to get more points for the leaderboard.<br>
<br/>
If you brought the wrong item, you can throw it away, it will return to the starting location so that you can pick it up again.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shy Dogs Hidden Orchestra</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2509550/Shy_Dogs_Hidden_Orchestra/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2509550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Another Hidden Orchestra will be on tour!  The puppies are clumsy, but they are musical!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2509550/extras/gif1.gif?t=1702034110"><br/><br/>The Shy Dogs Hidden Orchestra is a hidden object game with musical elements. It's a sequel to the game Shy Cats Hidden Orchestra, where each hidden character found unlocks a new musical instrument inside each game's level. Thus, you'll be able to create your own songs as you find cute little dogs hidden by beautiful 2D cartoon backgrounds.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2509550/extras/gif2.gif?t=1702034110"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Explore ten more new levels in cartoon hand-drawn style.<br/></li><li> Build ten new songs composed exclusively for the game.<br/></li><li> Find over 200 hidden shy puppies and special hints.<br/></li><li> Solve a riddle in each level to enable the secret puppy.</li></ul><br/><strong>Make your own music!</strong> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Collar</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594430/Color_Collar/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<u><strong>Easy to Pick Up and Play:</strong></u><br/><strong>Color Collar is a free and simple game playable for all ages.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594430/extras/Steam_gif_3.gif?t=1702033734"><br/><br/><br/><u><strong>Lighthearted And Colorful:</strong></u><br/><strong>Enjoy a simple story unfold about a robot dog and his scientist.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594430/extras/Steam_gif_1.gif?t=1702033734"><br/><br/><br/><u><strong>Multiple Worlds to Explore:</strong></u><br/><strong>Enjoy the many levels Color Collar has to offer.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594430/extras/Steam_gif_2.gif?t=1702033734"><br/><br/><br/><u><strong>Challenge Yourself:</strong></u><br/><strong>Unlock rewards by beating levels with the perfect solution.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594430/extras/Steam_gif_4.gif?t=1702033734"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MundusHex</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2705380/MundusHex/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2705380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Description:</h2><br/><strong>MundusHex</strong> is a logical adventure game that will transport you to a world full of puzzles and mysteries. Controlling a character from a third-person perspective, you will travel through diverse, amazing locations in a 3D world. Your task is to collect items, combine them in unexpected ways, and talk to characters who reveal more parts of the story to you.<h2 class="bb_tag">Main Features:</h2><br/><strong>Interactive World:</strong> <br/>Explore an open world full of life and possibilities, where your choices impact your journey.<br/><br/><strong>Puzzles and Brain Teasers: </strong><br/>Solve puzzles that require creative thinking and the combination of collected items.<br/><br/><strong>Fluid Narration:</strong> <br/>Immerse yourself in a deep story, where each scene unveils another part of a fascinating tale.<br/><br/><strong>3D Aesthetics: </strong><br/>Enjoy unique graphics that combine elements of medieval landscapes with futuristic accents.<br/><br/><strong>Suitable for Everyone: </strong><br/>Regardless of age, MundusHex offers challenges that will satisfy both younger and experienced players.<h2 class="bb_tag">About the Game:</h2><br/>In <strong>MundusHex</strong>, each scene is a new challenge that forces you to think and explore. The right combination of items can unlock secrets that lead to solving the main mission. Your deductive skills will be tested in this thoughtful adventure, which is as beautiful as it is demanding.<h2 class="bb_tag">Join Our Community:</h2><br/>We are enthusiasts of logic and adventure games, and we care about making MundusHex a game that brings people together around common challenges and successes. Follow our social media channels to stay updated with the latest news, share your achievements, and join the growing community of MundusHex fans.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chill Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2579840/Chill_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2579840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Introduction</h2>Make a plan you want to focus on, and then start a comfortable and undisturbed time.<br/><br/><br/>Music is always helpful to improve efficiency, Chill Drive has multiple relaxing music to help you focus on your plans in a comfortable atmosphere. In addition, custom music lists also support importing local music you like.<br/><br/>Tomato clock supports custom focus time and break time, switch between multiple styles of backgrounds and different environments white noise. Through various settings options, you can design suitable arrangements and environmental atmosphere.<br/><br/>In the calendar, you can view records of daily completion plans, as well as statistics of total time and completion quantities. NO STEPS, NO MILES. In Chill Drive, you can review every step of the past.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2579840/extras/AboutGame.png?t=1702032716"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Tomato clock</strong><br/>Customizable tomato clock function, set a goal and complete it!<br/></li><li><strong>Relaxing music</strong><br/>20 relaxing music tracks and support for importing local music<br/></li><li><strong>Dynamic background</strong><br/>Multiple styles of dynamic backgrounds, for entering an immersive state of focus<br/></li><li><strong>Environmental white noise</strong><br/>Choose white noise suitable for your focused atmosphere, shut out external "noise"<br/></li><li><strong>Calendar and Statistics</strong><br/>Record each goal you have completed, and count the cumulative number and time of tasks completed</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rune in the Three Kingdoms</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398720/Rune_in_the_Three_Kingdoms/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Rune In The Three Kingdoms<br>
<br>
Version 1.4 added new runewords, totaling 13<br>
Add runewords: Ice,Faith,Dream,Destruction,Last Wish,Brand,Phoenix,Famine,Hand of Justice,Doom,Pride,Breath of the Dying,Absolute Defense<br>
<br>
Version 1.3 added new runewords, totaling 13<br>
Add runewords: Exile,Call to Arms,Delirium,Fortitude,Grief,Bramble,Dragon,Chains of Honor,Eternity,Infinity,Wrath,Beast,Fury<br/>
<br/>
Version 1.2 added new runewords, totaling 27<br/>
Add runewords: Black,White,Smoke,Bright,Memory,Melody,Harmony,LionHeart,Obedience,LawBringer,Voice of Reason,Treachery,Passion,Wealth,Enlightenment,Duress,Gloom,Bone,Stone,Crescent Moon,Sanctuary,Oath,Prudence,Kingslayer,Heart of the Oak,Death,Silence,Exile,Call to Arms,Delirium,Fortitude,Grief,Bramble<br/>
<br/>
Version1.1 Add new runewords, totaling 20<br/>
Add runewords: Steel,Nadir,Malice,Stealth,Leaf,Ancient's Pledge,Zephyr,Holy Thunder,King's Grace,Strength,Edge,Spirit,Myth,Rhyme,Peace,Honor,Insight,Lore,Radiance,Enigma<br/>
<br/>
Game play introduction:<br/>
The game currently adopts Diablo-like gameplay and data. the concepts of anger system, general system, and attack distance have been emphasized. In order to enhance the game experience, the levels and values ​​required for some data have been modified.<br/>
The game is divided into three entrances: Normal, Nightmare, and Hell. Enemies that are immune to different types of damage will gradually appear at the entrance of Nightmare and Hell. Rainbow Jewelry and Halo (not yet online) can break the immunity. In the following different entrances, you can get different amounts of gold coins, diamonds, experience, and general points.<br/>
Rage system:<br/>
1) There are 6 types of anger: normal attack, shield, fire, lightning, cold, poison.<br/>
2) Normal attacks and shields must bring anger, and other elemental damages are added according to the damage type of the player character.<br/>
3) There are several balls at the bottom left of the game. When attacking or being attacked, the anger value will increase.<br/>
4) When the anger value reaches a certain value, click to release, during which the anger will be consumed at a rate of 10% per second.<br/>
5) During the release of anger, the gain of anger will no longer be increased.<br/>
6) During the release of anger, the damage skills corresponding to anger will be improved, and the shield will receive global damage reduction, up to 100%, effective for all damage.<br/>
7) Different rage values ​​can trigger different skill types, and each type has 4 attack skills.<br/>
General system:<br/>
1) The protagonist can choose between male and female, and can carry up to 5 generals.<br/>
2) Both generals and protagonists can be fully equipped with the same equipment.<br/>
3) The consumption of equipment durability is the same for the protagonist and generals.<br/>
4) Both the protagonist and generals have normal attack and skill attack, and each general has its own skill attack damage type.<br/>
5) The unlocking of generals needs to meet the points requirements, and the points can be obtained by killing the boss corresponding to the character.<br/>
6) The points given by the boss are different in different difficulties: 1 point for normal, 2 points for nightmares, 5 points for hell, doubled in death mode.<br/>
Attack distance:<br/>
1) Since the current game form is a battle formation, players cannot control the movement of characters in the battlefield.<br/>
2) The attack distance is calculated according to the front and rear distance positions of the battle formation, and the distance will be reduced by 1 every time a row of enemies is found forward.<br/>
3) Added the concept of adding 1 horse and subtracting 1 horse: -1 horse, the effect is -1 when you calculate the distance from others; +1 horse, the effect is +1 when others calculate the distance from you. There is a value of 2 at most, which enhances the offensive and defensive positions.<br/>
Pet system:<br/>
1) Pets provide attribute bonuses such as blood recovery and mana recovery for all teams in the battle formation through the aura.<br/>
2) Pets can only be equipped on the protagonist. If the protagonist is killed, the pet aura will be invalid.<br/>
Death Mode:<br/>
1) All reward attributes (gold coins, diamonds, experience, military commander points, acquisition of magic equipment, etc.) are doubled.<br/>
2) However, in this mode, the generals killed by the player will die and can no longer participate in the game, and the equipment on the dead character will also be lost.<br/>
3) Players can forcibly dismiss the game to avoid death, but only if all equipment or props in the backpack are lost.<br/>
4) Players cannot leave the battle in the combat state, and cannot advance or leave the game. Can only be forced to disband or forward teleportation.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur &amp; Susan: Almost Detectives</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2629650/Arthur__Susan_Almost_Detectives/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2629650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Arthur and Susan solve three mysterious cases in this funny, original and cozy point &amp; click indie game. <br>
<br>
Arthur and Susan are the two main playable characters, offering unique perspectives. Decide who speaks and when, as each has their distinct way of tackling challenges.<br>
<br>
30 captivating characters, each one with their own tales, motives and secrets. Each one is a puzzle on its own. Each one has a different text font and around 100 combination of body poses and face gestures that we have diligently defined, even if you'll only see a fraction!<br>
<br>
More than 100 inventory items, that you will need to watch, use, give or combine in order to solve the countless logical puzzles.<br/>
<br/>
One exclusive hit track, “Corazón de Pollo”.<br/>
<br/>
No more straining your eyes! While the game offers a single difficulty, choose to wield the optional magnifying glass, revealing all interactable items in a scene. Say goodbye to pesky pixel hunting - unless you're into that!<br/>
<br/>
An estimated 1000 jokes and puns sprinkled throughout your adventure.<br/>
<br/>
Available in English and Spanish.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle Simulator: Counter Stickman</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2623090/Battle_Simulator_Counter_Stickman/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2623090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The stickmen terror forces must be stopped with a tactical strike! You are the battle commander of the counter terrorist stickman (CTS) forces.<br>
<br>
▶battle simulator - style gameplay<br>
▶3D stickmen, levels and gun models<br>
▶Help win the stickman war.. on terror!<br>
▶Accurate stickman tactics						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy Fighters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2350090/Fantasy_Fighters/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2350090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command a colorful army of medieval characters in epic battles!<br/><br/>Welcome to the exciting world of <strong>Fantasy Fighters</strong> a local multiplayer game that combines cute, cartoonish graphics with immersive tactical gameplay. Choose your faction from a selection of humans or elves, each with their own unique set of characters, including wizards, kings, mages, knights, and more.<br/><br/>With turn-based combat, you'll have time to plan and strategize your moves, carefully positioning your troops and unleashing devastating attacks on your opponents. The colorful tile map provides a stunning backdrop for your battles, with detailed environments that add depth and complexity to your gameplay experience.<br/><br/>As you play, you'll discover a rich and immersive world filled with challenging quests and engaging characters.<br/><br/>So gather your friends and prepare to battle for supremacy in the world of <strong>Fantasy Fighters</strong>. With its charming graphics, engaging gameplay, and endless possibilities for adventure, this is a game you won't want to miss!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Panadero -The Baker-</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2313180/El_Panadero_The_Baker/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2313180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A 2D Action Arcade-like Platformer!<br/>Featuring Mexican Battling Bakers Vs Man-Eating Plant Life from OUTER SPACE. <br/>Hand drawn, animated, coded, designed, etc, etc by (mostly) one dude. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Enjoy simple controls to shoot and melee in different directions. <br/></li><li>Shoot to stun enemies, melee them at close range! Hit stunned enemies for MASSIVE DAMAGE!<br/></li><li>Fight in locales ranging from one of oldest cities in Mexico to An Alien Spaceship. <br/></li><li>Pick up and play gameplay. Pick the controller, punch aliens!<br/></li><li>Play solo or with a friend in local co-op. <br/></li><li>About 20 short diverse stages for 45 to 60 minutes of breezy, gutsy action! <br/></li><li>Replay to get better score! Bring a friend!<br/></li><li>Two Characters to choose!<br/></li><li>Featuring music by Tokyo Based Music Producer Ghostpops, and City-Pop Sensation Neko Milkshake and the Mex Lo-Fi Legend Palmasur. </li></ul><br/><br/>* Note on coop: It requires two controllers connected to the same pc for local coop. For remote play, it requires one controller per pc.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>moci over it</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2644850/moci_over_it/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2644850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use simple controls to control『moci』and reach the summit.<br>
<br>
Climbing is the accumulation of the past, it is like life.<br>
Here is a future waiting to be built up for you and a life of moci.<br>
Come join us in reaching the summit.<br>
<br>
・Click and drag to bounce the head and tail up and forward.<br/>
・Various narrations &amp; BGMare played as the event progresses.<br/>
・You can look back at the photos and videos you have collected.<br/>
・There is an auto-save function.<br/>
・It is compatible with the joystick of the game pad (the one with two joysticks).<br/>
・You can distribute the entire game, including play screens and clear bonuses.<br/>
<br/>
Half of the people who have played this game have given up,<br/>
another half of the remaining people are angry,<br/>
another half are disappointed,<br/>
and the last remaining people are lovable freaks.<br/>
<br/>
To those friends I send this game, and I hope you are one of them.<br/>
<br/>
This game could not have been created by me alone.<br/>
My utmost respect to the great pioneers.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
"SE.BGM"<br/>
・Iwashiro Sounds works<br/>
・MusMus<br/>
・music by audionautix<br/>
・OtoLogic<br/>
・Thumbwash						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocket Frog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2677000/Rocket_Frog/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677000/extras/Frog_Description_Dr._Toad_3.png?t=1702023414"><br/><br/><strong>Rocket Frog</strong> is an amusing, action-packed precision platformer.   Chester will test your patience and try your skill, blasting through the scenic hills, cities, lakes, and mountains.<br/>Can he overcome this critical test of physics, trying out Dr. Toad's and Dr. Frog's rocket boots and magnetic bowling ball?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677000/extras/Frog_Ready_to_jump.png?t=1702023414"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features:</h2><strong>-A challenging platformer!</strong><br/><br/><strong>-Charge the rocket boots to elevate your jumps!</strong><br/><br/><strong>-Wrestle against the weight of the magnetic bowling ball!</strong><br/><br/><strong>-Each Level gets more difficult the farther you go!</strong><br/><br/><strong>-Collect Infrognito Outfits!</strong><br/><br/><strong>-Collect Music CDs and Dr. Toad Tokens!</strong><br/><br/><strong>-Bonus unlockables!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677000/extras/Frog_Mt_Mctoad_2.png?t=1702023414"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blagmoz</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2614970/Blagmoz/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dash, cast, and buff your way to the top of Blagmoz Tower in this lightning-fast PVP precision platformer. Power up by drinking potions, getting kills, and sacrificing your friends at the Altar. Become the ultimate glass cannon in this one-hit-kill battle of sorceries!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614970/extras/fireball_dodge_1.gif?t=1702023950"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build streak and power up!</h2>Increase your streak by getting kills and sacrificing other wizards' bodies at the Altar to gain extra mobility and spell slots! Sacrificing wizards with lots of Streak lets you steal most of it back from them.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614970/extras/sacrifice.gif?t=1702023950"><h2 class="bb_tag">Battle on the couch or online!</h2>Play locally or host an online match for your friends. But who needs friends anyway, because Blagmoz has a public server browser, too!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614970/extras/frogif.gif?t=1702023950"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>2-4 player online or local multiplayer + a public lobby browser<br/></li><li>60+ levels across 3 areas<br/></li><li>16+ potions that buff you up, hinder your opponents, and turn people into frogs<br/></li><li>Mysterious rising sea of goo<br/></li><li>Wall jumping, wave dashing, and head stomping action<br/></li><li>Unlockable areas, potions, and costumes</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614970/extras/bouncy_mushrooms.gif?t=1702023950"><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fk7sqY8JYSg" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614970/extras/discord_gif.gif?t=1702023950"/></a> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Tones: Loss</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2435600/The_Dark_Tones_Loss/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2435600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Dark Tones: Loss — will tell you a tragic story, the source of inspiration of which is the cult series of Silent Hill games and an equally iconic work — Cry of Fear<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2435600/extras/Logo_2.png?t=1702023147"><h2 class="bb_tag">Attention to detail and surroundings</h2>All game levels were created from scratch in order to provide the player with a unique environment, and not the same type of locations purchased on marketplaces. All the content of the game was arranged manually with great attention to detail in order to create a lively, filled and interesting game world.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2435600/extras/TheDarkTonesImage_1.png?t=1702023147"><h2 class="bb_tag">The Dark Tones: Loss – is an atmospheric plot-oriented work</h2>The short duration of the passage is compensated by the saturation and variety of events in the passage. <br/>Here you will not find the same type of riddles, hours of searching for objects or aimless wandering around locations. <br/>All the efforts, resources and time spent on the development of this game were aimed at creating an interesting, bright and meaningful work in which the duration of the gameplay plays a secondary role.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2435600/extras/TheDarkTonesImage_2.png?t=1702023147"><h2 class="bb_tag">The realism of the story</h2>Here you will not have to flee from the zombies, run from the ridiculous monsters and demented maniacs, but living the life of the main character you will face something much more terrible, everything that happens has a deeper meaning than it may seem at first glance, you have to get to the truth and put the puzzle together, but I hope that after the game no one will remain indifferent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2435600/extras/TheDarkTonesImage_3.png?t=1702023147"><h2 class="bb_tag">Modern game engine and technology</h2>The game is being developed on the latest version of the Unreal Engine 5 engine using a realistic Lumen lighting system.<br/><br/>The world of dark tones will meet not only with a gloomy story and atmosphere, but also with pleasant realistic graphics with high detail of objects and textures.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2435600/extras/TheDarkTonesImage_4.png?t=1702023147"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luster Beasts</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2691800/Luster_Beasts/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2691800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Luster Beasts is a tactical JRPG creature collection game. In Luster Beasts the player will be given complete control over their party. This will allow them to fully customize their move sets, as well as their stats, giving players a lot more control over their team than other games in their genre. The goal is to clear as many opponent's teams as possible in order to gain high scores.<br>
<br>
How high will your high score be?						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smokey's Rescue Team</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2585180/Smokeys_Rescue_Team/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The game is developed for Windows PC. Players will start in an empty cat rescue home, where they will gradually receive abandoned cats. Players must ensure the cats' stats are good to maintain their well-being. If a cat's stats decline, it will interact with furniture, causing a mess. As time passes, people visit the rescue house to adopt cats, providing donations to support the operation. The game offers a great experience of simulation of cat care, interaction, and management.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exp10sion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2618850/Exp10sion/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2618850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Every 10 seconds, a bomb explodes. <br/>Each explosion marks the start of a new round. <br/>In each round, traces of the previous bomb remain. <br/>In every level, there are Exp10sions!!!</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Exp10sion, a puzzle platformer:</h2>You will play as a bomb that <strong>explodes within 10 seconds</strong>, managing to reach the Target Door before explosion. <br/><br/>Each explosion respawns the bomb, starts a new round, and generates a "<strong>Time Shadow</strong>" representing your trail of previous round. <br/><br/>Skillfully use your shadow and level's mechanisms to overcome numerous obstacles and unravel puzzles, in the cycle of explosions and rebirth!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2>🕒 Tick-Tock Tensions: In "Exp10sion", time takes center stage. As the clock steadily ticks away, your adorable bomb character faces an explosive fate. Can you unravel time's mysteries at a leisurely pace?<br/><br/>🌟 Pixel Art: Immerse yourself in the enchanting pixelated scenes of "Exp10sion".  Explore meticulously crafted levels inspired by retro aesthetics, each offering a cozy atmosphere and a touch of nostalgia.<br/><br/>🧩 Whimsical Puzzles: "Exp10sion" challenges your intellect with a wide array of time-centric puzzles in over 70 levels. Magnets, lasers or even something that can stop the ticking timer.<h2 class="bb_tag">Ludum Dare:</h2>The prototype of this game is made during Ludum Dare 51, under the theme of "Every 10 seconds".						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Espresso For The Demon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1268200/Espresso_For_The_Demon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268200/extras/title2.png?t=1702014738"><br/><br/>Visual Novel, ADV, Romance, otome<br/><br/>A new coffee shop suddenly opened in the city. On-time, because Wisa really needs a moonlighting. She gets a job with her classmates: cheerful Frank and quiet Estr. What could possibly be wrong?<br/><br/>Game features:<br/><br/>* Lots of beautiful artwork<br/>* Multiple endings<br/>* Three completely different love interests						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Petey Pedro unBEETable Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2636200/Petey_Pedro_unBEETable_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A nostalgic game for those RAD 80's and 90's kids. Help Petey Pedro get back home after falling into a magical world where the SWEETS he chose over a healthy beet are now his worst nightmare.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636200/extras/Heading7nostalgic.png?t=1702011674"><br/>Over 55 Levels to beat and master. Hand crafter themed pixel graphic levels each with a unique soundtrack.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636200/extras/IMG_0040.GIF?t=1702011674"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636200/extras/HeadingUpgrade.png?t=1702011674"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">*Collect coins to upgrade your <strong>GLASSES</strong> giving you <strong>VISION POWER</strong> with new <strong>SKILLS</strong></ul><ul class="bb_ul">*Collect Hidden Magical Eggs</ul><ul class="bb_ul">*<strong>GET the Speed Runner Glasses</strong></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636200/extras/IMG_0059.GIF?t=1702011674"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636200/extras/Headingsecret.png?t=1702011674"><br/>Every world has a puzzle stage to find.  Your KEY to finding these are your observation skills.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636200/extras/IMG_0064.GIF?t=1702011674"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636200/extras/Headingspeedrun.png?t=1702011674"><br/>Unlock a SPECIAL badge icon if you can beat the RECORD.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636200/extras/IMG_0061.GIF?t=1702011674"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636200/extras/HeadingSeasonalLevels.png?t=1702011674"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636200/extras/HeadingSteamExclusiveENG.png?t=1702011674"><br/>As a big thank you to those of you who purchase the game at launch thru steam, there will be <strong>NEW FREE LEVELS ADDED</strong> in the future.  In 2024, four seasonal theme levels with fun new challenges will be added.  Reserve your copy today!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636200/extras/StreamEng.png?t=1702011674"><br/>Indie games are all a labor of love and our amazing community is the driving force behind some amazing games.  I want to reward all of you amazing players that stream your favorite games.  If you play Petey Pedro unBEETable Adventure and stream it in your channel please write to us at <a href="mailto:contact@sparkleybarkleygames.com">contact@sparkleybarkleygames.com</a> and we will add your name or handle to the special thanks section in the credits. Deadline is 12/5/2023  THANK YOU FOR PLAYING!!!<br/><br/>Warning: Game contains colorful imagery that may be harmful to players with photosensitive epilepsy or similar condition.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
