<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Living With Sister: Monochrome Fantasy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2429860/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1711168850"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_1__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/>Living in a fantasy world, it's always been your dream to grow up to be a famous adventurer just like your father. Reality proves to be more boring than fiction, however, as your days are mostly spent doing odd jobs for the villagers. With your friends by your side, you enter the Tournament of the Eights and strive for something greater: the chance to become the top guild in the country. Will you realize your ambitions, or will your hopes slip through your fingers and doom you to a life of monochrome monotony?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_2__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/>As a member of your town's Adventurers' Guild, it's your job to protect the townsfolk. Go on hunts, kill dangerous beasts, and hone your abilities to better tackle whatever challenges tomorrow brings.<br/><br/>Once you get home from work, you'll have your sister to attend to. She's a very sickly girl who needs a lot of help. Manage your household finances well, build up your relationship with your sister, and who knows, perhaps you might even be able to solve the mystery behind her illness.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_3__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Big_Brother_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Little_Sister_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Kana_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Yui_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Kasumi_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Yukari_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Akatsuki_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_4__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><strong>Hand-Drawn Monochrome Art</strong><br/>Though it may lack color, this game's world is anything but colorless! The stunning black-and-white art is chock-full of personality and is sure to leave you with plenty of marvelous monochrome memories!<br/><br/><strong>Unique Combat System</strong><br/>With tons of bizarre and ferocious monsters to fight and dozens of unique skills to unlock, your adventures are sure to be full of challenge and excitement!<br/><br/><strong>Charming Characters</strong><br/>Build up your relationships with your guildmates and your sister to learn about what makes them tick and unlock character-specific abilities to further assist you in your quest to become the top guild in the country!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Chilla's Art] Shinkansen 0 | 新幹線 0号</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2793370/Chillas_Art_Shinkansen_0___0/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2793370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Shinkansen 0 | 新幹線 0号 is a game set in Japan where players are tasked with finding anomalies in the Shinkansen. (Japanese bullet train)<br/><br/><i><strong>Supporter content can be turned on and off at the title screen. (It is on by default) </strong></i><br/><br/><i><strong>Motion Blur and Headbob is turned off by default.</strong></i><br/><br/><strong>Controls:<br/><br/>WASD - Move<br/>Left Click - Interact　<br/>Right Click - Zoom<br/>Shift - Run<br/>ESC - Options</strong><br/><br/>Easy mode - There is an easy mode in the mainmenu available for everyone to enjoy<br/><br/>Auto-save: auto-save for each chapter<br/><br/>Endings: There are two endings<br/><br/><strong><i>If you encounter any technical issues, do the following:<br/><br/>-Update GPU driver<br/>-Lower the Graphics settings/Screen resolution<br/>-Update Windows OS<br/>-Check if your anti-virus software is blocking the game or its save data. (Save Data location: C:\Users\[YOURUSERNAME]\AppData\LocalLow\Chilla's Art, LLC\Shinkansen0)<br/>-Delete save, then try again (Save Data location: C:\Users\[YOURUSERNAME]\AppData\LocalLow\Chilla's Art, LLC\Shinkansen0)<br/>-Check if your PC meets the system requirements</i></strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears In Space</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1309620/Bears_In_Space/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FG6w3Zxbp8W" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/Steam_CTAbutton_Discord.png?t=1711123009"/></a><br/>Get ready to unleash your inner bear in Bears in Space, the over-the-top<br/>bullet-hell FPS that's bound to have you ROARING with excitement! Dive headfirst into hordes of oil-thirsty robots as you embody Maxwell Atoms, a Spacetronaut turned extraterrestrial castaway, whose DNA has been merged with Beartana, the She-Bear. <br/>Embark on a zany and humorous out-of-this-world adventure that'll have you blasting your way across exciting and varied locations, from wastelands to space carnivals to ancient hidden temples and more as you quest to find your way back to earth and if there’s time, save your crew.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fast-paced Mayhem</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/BulletHell_acid2.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Bears In Space offers non-stop, high-energy gameplay. Fight your way through waves of fiendish robots using an arsenal of outrageous weaponry and gadgets. Double jump, dash, and dodge enemy attacks in the tradition of the best old-school shooters.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Mighty As A Bear</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/BearMode.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Consume elusive honey pots and unleash your Ursine rage, transforming into a bear!  <br/>Use your unique DNA fusion to your advantage, carving up robot enemies with your mighty bear powers and masterful knowledge of the ancient art of Bear Fu and the fabled Kuma No Ken.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Upgrade Your Arsenal</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/UpgradeRadial.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Complete challenges and break open loot crates to purchase guns, choosing from a diverse range of over 25 weapons!<br/>Most weapons upgrade, with each kill gaining your equipped weapon XP until it evolves into its next evolution tier! So, get out there and let the lasers fly!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Varied Gameplay</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/Varied_Gameplay_BasketCube.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Venture beyond the ordinary FPS experience and discover Substories, secrets and collectibles across every level!<br/>Learn how to bake a cake, investigate a crime scene, battle a Rock God, play a round of Basketcube and even bust some ghosts! All while meeting a colourful cast of characters with their own quirks and stories to tell.<br/>Completing these exciting optional encounters brings with it a hefty loot pay off, making these encounters even more rewarding to search out as you save up for your next weapon!<br/><br/>Choose your difficulty and play the game your way!<br/>Modify your difficulty with independent sliders for incoming and outgoing damage. You can also engage our Platform Helper mode, making all platforming segments of our game significantly easier to conquer! Perfect for kids or gamers new to the FPS genre!<br/><br/><br/>Whether you're a seasoned gamer looking for a blast from the past or a casual player seeking a fun-filled adventure, Bears in Space promises a fun and absurd, action packed time. Get ready to shoot, chuckle, and unleash your inner bear in this one-of-a-kind bullet-hell FPS adventure that’s truly out of this world!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4D Golf</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2147950/4D_Golf/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2147950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>4D Golf</strong> is a mind-bending golf game unlike any other because it's set entirely in a 4-dimensional space. Complete fun and unique golfing challenges as you gain hands-on experience of the 4th dimension and beyond!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2147950/extras/SteamGIF_1.gif?t=1711121562"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 120 levels and 7 vibrant themed worlds<br/></li><li>Tons of visualization options to master 4D space<br/></li><li>Build your own 4D courses in the level editor<br/></li><li>Race the clock in Marble Platforming Mode<br/></li><li>Navigate hidden paths, moving platforms, shifting gravity, speed boosts, and more!<br/></li><li>Unlock custom accessories by completing challenges</li></ul><br/>Now open your third eye and unleash your full potential!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Forgotten World:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827510/The_Forgotten_WorldPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FVuKggh6WYN" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/dss.png?t=1711106032"/></a><br/><br/><strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 8 in the official version.<br/>Chapters: 2 prologues, 6 official versions</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/111.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>This is about Alice after Wonderland.<br/>Oblivion is the vilest of spells. As an adult, Alice also experiences a less fairytale-like life and stops dreaming, which also means that everything about Wonderland is slowly disappearing. The people of Wonderland have even forgotten why they exist, and before everything dissipates, the Cheshire Cat casts a phantom spell to try to find Alice in the hope that she can save Wonderland once more.<br/>But the Cheshire Cat can't remember the spell either, and the wrong spell sends it traveling to a parallel world, a world where Alice has no idea that Wonderland even exists.<br/>In order to keep Wonderland from being forgotten, the Cheshire Cat brings Alice from each parallel world back to Wonderland, trying to awaken people's memories, and despite failures after failures, the Cheshire Cat still believes that he will find the right Alice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/1y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/1.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Play as different Alice and utilize different abilities and decks to defeat your enemies, each Alice has her own story! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/2y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/2.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Spellbound "monsters" are not real monsters, so defeat them to break the spell and discover their true nature! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/3y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/3.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Playing cards, which seem to be everywhere, will become your biggest fighting force at this moment! Poker soldiers can get different runes to increase combat power! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/4y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/4.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Arrange Poker Pawns of the same number of points or color to get a reinforcement effect, they don't have emotions but are very good at fighting! </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2054970/Dragons_Dogma_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Note: There are other sets that include this item.<br/><br/>Set forth on your grand adventure, Arisen!<br/><br/>Dragon’s Dogma is a single player, narrative driven action-RPG series that challenges the players to choose their own experience – from the appearance of their Arisen, their vocation, their party, how to approach different situations and more. Now, in this long-awaited sequel, the deep, explorable fantasy world of Dragon’s Dogma 2 awaits.<br/><br/>On your journey, you’ll be joined by Pawns, mysterious otherworldly beings, in an adventure so unique you will feel as if accompanied by other players while on your own adventure.<br/><br/>All of these elements are elevated further through physics technology, artificial intelligence (AI) and the latest in graphics, to create a truly immersive fantasy world in Dragon’s Dogma 2.<br/><br/><br/><strong><u>Action that challenges your creativity </u></strong> <br/><br/>Wield swords, bows, and chant magick.<br/>The vocations in Dragon's Dogma 2 give you the ability to approach combat the way you want.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_01.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Company in your single-player experience </u></strong> <br/><br/>Players can customize their own main Pawn, who will always accompany your Arisen, <br/>and enter a covenant with up to 2 additional Pawns from other players through the network. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_02.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Facing the monsters in this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Beyond the town borders, you will encounter diverse monsters that inhabit the lands. <br/>You will need to decide between engaging in battles or finding alternatives; <br/>so be aware of your party’s setup, the terrain around you, and the monsters you face.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_03.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Inhabitants of this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Travelers, merchants, soldiers and other folk go about their daily lives. <br/>Preoccupied by their own objectives and motives, they all exhibit different emotions.<br/>At times, they may lead you to a quest by approaching you and asking for a favor. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_04.gif?t=1711067553"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cureocity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2612680/Cureocity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							We are "Bread On Board," a collective of independent game developers spread across four countries, united by our passion and meeting during a GameJam. <br/>Our game demo was born in the "BOOOM CHALLENGE", a GameJam by GCORES. With only 21 days, we created a game based on a given theme. After the competition, we even won the "Most Popular Game" award at an Online Game Trial Event.<br/>The full playthrough of our game will take about an hour. We hope to give you a short, but super heartwarming and loving adventure❤️.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/1.奇幻而治愈（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>A rookie adventurer fresh on the scene and a former mercenary who was transferred into an adventurer due to injury. Two protagonists with contrasting personalities will embark on an adventure of fantasy and healing together. In the mysterious ruins of an underground dungeon that lies in the depth of a jungle, what awaits them will be...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/2.两位冒险者（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>According to the tavern's adventurer logs, the team heading into the dungeon features a rookie adventurer and an ex-mercenary who is now working as a healer. The adventurer looks as charming as a doll, and the enthusiasm never disappears; the healer is cool and a bit traditional, acting as a guiding figure for their adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/>What stories have unfolded between these two contrasting characters, and what challenges will they face together in this adventure? The continuation of this adventurous story is yours to discover.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/3.注重手法的回合制解谜（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>"People think battles need powerful weapons, but strategy at hand is key." <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_3_en.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/>In "Cureocity," the power of your strategy is materialized as the numerical values of your hands in combat. You can swap different weapons or items held in your left and right hands to alter your character's attack and defense stats. You may also change "gestures" to focus attacks or land heavy blows on specific enemies.As you delve deeper into the dungeon, you will take the unique traits of monsters into consideration and discuss strategies with your allies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/4.你的选择决定冒险归途（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>In this adventure, you'll discover not only the secrets hidden within the dungeon, but also the truths about the world and the  characters themselves. When faced with contaminated monsters, you can choose to either fight them or attempt to purify them. Of course, you also have the option to let things take their own course.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_4_en.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/>With each decision,the fate of the protagonists may change. The end of this adventure... is yours to decide.<h2 class="bb_tag">About the Publisher</h2>GCORES PUBLISHING is an independent game publishing venture formed by GCORES, committed to bringing you more outstanding indie games from the BOOOM CHALLENGE.<br/>Feel free to follow our <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/44750639" rel="" target="_blank">publisher webpage</a> for future updates.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midnight Ghost Hunt</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/915810/Midnight_Ghost_Hunt/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/915810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>MIDNIGHT GHOST HUNT IS A <i>PETRIFYING</i> PROP HAUNT GAME TO PLAY WITH PALS! </strong><br/><br/>Lying in wait across a series of cursed locations, relentless spirits stalk the halls. Assigned to eliminate them are the Ghost Hunters, armed to the teeth with the ghoul-busting tech to banish them to another realm! Play both Ghost and Hunter in a chaotic 4v4 struggle between the living and the dead.<br/><br/><strong>TONGUE-IN-CHEEK HIDE-AND-SEEK</strong><br/>As a Ghost, conceal yourself inside seemingly harmless pieces of furniture to evade preying Hunters… but when their backs are turned, turn the environment against them with telekinetic bombardment. No chair, lamp, or grandfather clock is innocent in this hijinks-heavy frenzy.<br/><br/><strong>MIDNIGHT MAYHEM</strong><br/>The fun isn’t over yet...when the clock strikes twelve, the witching hour begins, and the Hunters become the Hunted. The tables turn and Ghosts become supercharged, giving Hunters a limited amount of time to survive their vengeful wrath.<br/><br/><strong>MURDEROUS 4v4 MULTIPLAYER</strong><br/>Play together and communicate with your team and ensure a triumphant victory, giving each other pointers on the paths enemies tend to tread. Create synergies with your team's abilities to outthink and outwit your opponents.<br/><br/><strong>HARNESS SUPERNATURAL ABILITIES</strong><br/>The restrictions of reality don’t apply to Ghosts, of course. Claim your supernatural powers, which include turning invisible, causing furniture to float, and conjuring a dangerous Ghostly miasma. Ghosts can even hide in plain sight by masquerading as a Hunter’s doppelgänger!<br/><br/>Ghostly Perks include dramatically increasing your weight, extending your possessing range, the ability to see nearby Hunters through walls, and much more. <br/><br/><strong>ARMED AND READY</strong><br/>Hunters must choose their weapons from a full range of hi-tech gadgets designed to cast out Ghosts from our plane of existence. Detect ghostly presences with the Spectrophone, Radar and Pathfinder, capture them with a Trap, and suck up their spectral remains with the Vacuum – or just blast them to smithereens with the Spectral Cannon, sledgehammers, harpoons, salt-spewing shotguns, and more.<br/><br/>Hunters can also select Perks to give them a special boost. Choose from an extra burst of speed, health-replenishing capabilities and a host of other powers to get ahead of the game.<br/><br/><strong>A BEVY OF BLOOD-CURDLING MAPS </strong><br/>Explore ten unsettling locations, including an abandoned theatre, eerie mansion and cursed carnival. Each map brings with it different tactical considerations and items to throw about… as well as plenty of opportunities to play tricks on the enemy.<br/><br/><strong>FRIGHTENING NEW FEATURES</strong> <br/>As it crept through Steam Early Access, Midnight Ghost Hunt picked up a gaggle of game-changing features, built on the feedback of its community of Ghosts and Hunters.<br/><br/>Dedicated servers and host migration support make setting up matches a breeze, while the Progression Tier and Challenge systems bring added competition to the hunt. Looking for less of the silly and more of the scary? The Experimental Darkness game mode lends a chill to the chaos. Not to mention crossplay, full controller support, and even the GhostMaster minigame to pass the time during the van ride to your next match!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horizon Forbidden West™ Complete Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420110/Horizon_Forbidden_West_Complete_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/extras/horizon_forbidden_west_cinemagraph_610x610.gif?t=1711032993"><br/><br/>Join Aloy as she braves a majestic but dangerous new frontier that holds mysterious new threats. This Complete Edition allows you to enjoy the critically acclaimed Horizon Forbidden West on PC in its entirety with bonus content, including the Burning Shores story expansion that picks up after the main game.<br/><br/>Explore distant lands, fight bigger and more awe-inspiring machines, and encounter astonishing new tribes as you return to the far-future, post-apocalyptic world of Horizon.<br/><br/>The land is dying. Vicious storms and an unstoppable blight ravage the scattered remnants of humanity while fearsome new machines prowl their borders, and life on Earth is hurtling toward another extinction.<br/><br/>It's up to Aloy to uncover the secrets behind these threats and restore order and balance to the world. Along the way, she must reunite with old friends, forge alliances with warring new factions and unravel the legacy of the ancient past.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>See every gameplay detail with Ultrawide 21:9 and Super Ultrawide 32:9 resolutions, as well as 48:9 triple monitor support.*<br/></li><li>Witness the Forbidden West coming to life, with NVIDIA DLSS 3 upscaling and frame generation, image enhancing NVIDIA DLAA and latency reducing NVIDIA Reflex. AMD FSR and Intel XeSS are also supported.**<br/></li><li>Customize graphic settings to your preference, with the potential for unlocked frame rates.**<br/></li><li>Take control with full support for the DualSense™ controller, including haptic feedback and adaptive trigger functionality.*** </li></ul><br/>* Compatible PC and 4K display device required. <br/>** Compatible PC required. <br/>*** Wired connection required to experience the full range of in-game controller features.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age of Water: The First Voyage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2841350/Age_of_Water_The_First_Voyage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The First Voyage is the very beginning of your Age of Water experience. Jump right into the intense naval combat, craft your first boats, explore the waterworld and get a good idea of what Age of Water is about. Don’t forget to wishlist the full game now!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_ship_anim.gif?t=1711025025"><br/><br/>Become a sea captain on a post-apocalyptic Earth completely covered in water and go on an adventure in a huge open world. Sail through storms, fight and trade, capture other people's boats or build your own, extract resources from the bottom of the ocean, reveal the secrets of the Age of Water world.<br/><br/><strong>Water post-apocalypse</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_1.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>The ocean destroyed a once great civilization, but people survived and adapted. They built settlements on the roofs of tall buildings and the tops of other man-made structures. People travel across the ocean in tiny boats and huge combat vessels. The ocean provides everything they need, including extractable resources on the seabed. And yet, the dream of real land is still alive.<br/><br/><strong>True open world</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_2.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Explore the world at your own pace, discover new settlements and meet their inhabitants. Complete tasks, search for and extract valuable resources from the bottom of the ocean, earn money on trade or simply sell the artifacts you have obtained, and when you get the idea of how this world works, build your own base.<br/><br/><strong>Hundreds of unique ships</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_3.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Build boats from scratch or modify existing ones. Players have access to dozens of hulls and hundreds of parts, from which they can assemble anything ranging from a small boat to a hefty vessel 30 meters long, and then install equipment, armor and weapons. It’s important not to forget to gather a team of good crewmembers so that there is someone to stand behind machine guns and cannons or do other work on board.<br/><br/><strong>Fierce naval battles</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_4.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Pirates are always waiting for you at sea, and in some cases more aggressive players even start to chase you, so do not forget to install enough guns on your deck.  You can destroy an enemy vessel, or you can capture it in battle and take it for yourself forever. Adventures might also get you into storming enemy fortresses and defending allied settlements!<br/><br/><strong>Personal naval base</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_5.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>This shelter is reliably protected from enemies, and it allows a player to organize the production of everything that the captain may need on it. Build factories for the production of equipment, weapons, hulls for boats of all sizes, as well as the necessary resources.<br/><br/><strong>Flexible balance between PvE and PvP</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_6.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>At first, you will only meet computer opponents, but later you can challenge other players if you are confident enough in your skills and gear. Always be on the lookout: if your task is to transport illegal goods, then other players may well take the quest to hunt smugglers. In Age of Water, everyone decides for themself who they are today - a peaceful traveler or a bloodthirsty pirate.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slice &amp; Dice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1775490/Slice__Dice/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1775490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Slice &amp; Dice is a tactical dice battle roguelike.<br/><br/>Take control of 5 heroes, each with their own unique dice. Fight your way through 20 levels of monsters and try to take on the final boss. If you lose a single fight you have to start over so be careful/lucky!<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/>- 3D dice physics, choose which dice to reroll<br/>- Simple turn-based combat<br/>- Level up a hero or gain an item after each fight<br/>- Randomly-generated encounters<br/>- Ridiculous combos<br/>- Undo actions as much as you like<br/>- Each turn is like a mini-puzzle<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/>- 128 hero classes (+99999?)<br/>- 73 monsters<br/>- 473 items<br/>- Too many modes<br/>- ∞ curses<br/>- Weird modding<br/>- Online leaderboards<br/><br/><strong>Credits</strong><br/>- Created by tann (it took ~7 years)<br/>- Pixel art by a3um<br/>- Music by Ziggurath, Aleksander Zabłocki, Louigi Verona, Cold Sanctum, Ro'sø, Andrew Goodwin<br/>- Trailer by Everdraed<br/><br/>I plan to not participate in any sales/deals/bundles. No AI was used to make this game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone in the Dark</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1310410/Alone_in_the_Dark/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Alone in the Dark weaves a chilling tapestry of psychological horror and Southern Gothic charm, reimagining the iconic game that set the benchmark for the genre. We invite you to join us on a journey into madness, where each encounter could be your last. With each step you take closer to unravelling Derceto's mystery, the eyes that watch from the darkness grow hungrier. Every bullet means the difference between survival and an unthinkable end. The next door you unlock could lead to a nightmarish realm offering nothing but slashing claws, grasping tentacles, and frayed sanity.  Journey to interbellum Louisiana, where an era of decadence hides a darker tale - of escape from past traumas and an intolerant society, into the waiting grasp of something darker, something that has patiently lurked for impossible eons. This is Alone in the Dark as you've never seen it - a skillfully-woven narrative of Southern Gothic elegance and eldritch madness that pays homage to its legendary origins while taking the next step forward in survival horror storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_VIPIntro_2.gif?t=1710945887"><h2 class="bb_tag">A Haunting Tale of Mystery and Madness</h2>Step inside Derceto Manor, an asylum shrouded in intrigue, guarding a terrible secret. Client Emily Hartwood and private investigator Edward Carnby embark on a harrowing quest for answers; Emily to the mystery of her missing uncle, Edward to the toughest case he will ever face, and both to questions they dare not ask themselves. This re-envisioned classic invites you to explore an unforgettable single player adventure rich with suspense, frights, and revelations that will test the limits of your imagination.<h2 class="bb_tag">Featuring Hollywood Talent</h2>Experience some of the greatest acting survival horror has ever seen through the performances of award-winning actors Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow) in their first videogame roles. Jodie and David’s immaculately captured likenesses breathe life into Emily Hartwood and Edward Carnby, lending a deeply personal aspect to Alone in the Dark’s story that demands it be played twice to get the full experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Tribute to Horror Pioneers</h2>Rediscover the essence of psychological horror in a game that respectfully nods to its 1992 origin, the game that established the survival horror genre. Alone in the Dark is your gateway to an experience steeped in the atmospheric dread of classic horror, with next-generation storytelling and gameplay. A must-play for fans of twisted tales, nerve-wracking exploration, and desperate combat.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Story That Challenges Reality</h2>Envisioned by Mikael Hedberg, acclaimed writer behind modern horror classics “SOMA” and “Amnesia”, Alone in the Dark’s intricate web of mystery delves into themes of trauma, faith, evil, and abandonment. Whether you choose to brave the nightmare as Emily or Edward, you will uncover secrets that defy everything you thought about videogame storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Atrmo_2.gif?t=1710945887"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore Derceto Manor in this reimagination of Alone in the Dark, a love letter to the 90’s cult classic horror game.<br/></li><li>Return to the roots of psychological horror and experience an atmospheric journey worthy of the game that started the genre.<br/></li><li>Dive into a world full of sounds that make your skin crawl with a haunting, yet mesmerizing doom jazz soundtrack.<br/></li><li>Enjoy the thrill of desperate survival in a world where reality starts to crumble, evil lurks in every shadow and ammunition is scarce.<br/></li><li>Experience this nightmare from either Emily Hartwood’s or Edward Carnby’s perspective and unearth the dark secrets of a gothic mansion.<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in a deep psychological story that goes beyond the realms of the imaginable, by Mikael Hedberg, cult horror writer of SOMA and Amnesia.<br/></li><li>See Emily and Edward brought to live by the Hollywood talent of Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow), who lend their voices, their appearance, and their formidable acting skills to the protagonists.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Riddles_2.gif?t=1710945887"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raw Metal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2279600/Raw_Metal/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2279600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Raw Metal is a sci-fi stealth-action dungeon crawler with a focus on smooth, stylish gameplay.<br/><br/>You are a lone scavenger on the distant, barren exoplanet Charybdis. In search of gear and supplies, you infiltrate the depths of Katabase 6, a massive mining facility run by a corrupt megacorporation known as Orpheus Tech. Sneak through the mines undetected, cleverly utilizing various gadgets and equipment to your advantage, but beware; if you're caught, you'll need to rely on your combat skills for a fighting chance to escape.<h2 class="bb_tag">High-Stakes Stealth</h2><br/>Use taser darts, noisemakers, improvised concussion grenades, and more to slip past and isolate guards. The shadows are your domain; manipulate your environment and your enemies well enough and they'll never see you coming.<h2 class="bb_tag">Breakneck Combat</h2><br/>Combat in Raw Metal is fast and punishing. The guards stationed at Katabase 6 are stronger and more heavily armored than you, so fighting them head on will take skill, cunning, and a great degree of risk. However, mastering combos and using your environment will allow you to come out on top, and yield far greater rewards. Depending on whether it is initiated through a clever ambush or a stealth slip-up, combat can range from a calculated risk to a desperate fight for survival.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Blend of top-down stealth and third-person beat 'em up combat<br/></li><li>Freeform combo system that rewards aggression, improvisation, and precise timing and positioning<br/></li><li>50+ unique gear pieces to find and upgrade<br/></li><li>Distinct visuals for each gear piece to customize the look of your character<br/></li><li>Risk vs. reward extraction system that grants you the choice of cashing out your loot, or pushing deeper into the facility<br/></li><li>3 memorable and challenging boss fights, each with their own fighting styles, twists, and story development<br/></li><li>9 hand-crafted levels to infiltrate, with a few variants each to mix up your approach each time<br/></li><li>Environmental hazards and enemy variants to keep you on your toes as the game progresses<br/></li><li>5 deployable gadgets to utilize to your advantage in stealth and combat alike</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Park Baseball 25</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384620/Out_of_the_Park_Baseball_25/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_banner_1.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/>We are incredibly excited to announce <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong> - the special 25th Anniversary edition of our award-winning baseball strategy series. Can you believe it's been a quarter of a century? Out of the Park Baseball is not just a game - it's a legacy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_henry.png?t=1710574531"><br/><br/>If it happens in real baseball, it happens in Out of the Park Baseball! Discover new talent, draft the next superstar, negotiate with free agents, enter trade talks with other teams, build your dynasty and guide a franchise into an infinite future! As a manager, dive into the more hands-on management and set your team's lineups, pitching staffs, in-game strategy and call the shots from the dugout. You can oversee your league at a high level, or play out each game in the gorgeous 3D game mode, managing play by play or even pitch by pitch. OOTP has it all covered!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_badge.png?t=1710574531"><br/>Here are just a few of the new features coming to <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong>:<br/><br/><strong>A game-changing new Player Development Lab!</strong><br/><br/>Shape the future of your upcoming stars! You can channel your inner Player Development Director like never before. A modern new Player Development Lab is here for every team that allows you to give players individual programs to work on, developing them how you like. Do you want your hitter to work on improving their baserunning? Bunting? Contact? Would you prefer your pitcher to work on building up their stamina? Developing a new pitch? Velocity? It's all up to you - for each of your upcoming future stars!<br/><br/><strong>Massive Player Ratings and AI Upgrade!</strong><br/><br/>It’s the most comprehensive player ratings upgrade in the 25 year history of Out of the Park Baseball! Batting, Pitching, and Fielding ratings have been painstakingly modified to capture the essence of baseball, with modifications to Contact and Power for hitters, Movement and Stuff for pitchers, the addition of Catcher Framing and Stealing Aggressiveness, and much more. BABIP is now front and center for hitters and hurlers, while new internal ratings updates allow for even more flexibility for Commissioners around the world to adjust the game to their detailed delight. Plus, the AI throughout the game has been improved dramatically to deliver the most challenging OOTP experience ever! <br/><br/><strong>Even More Detailed Player Development Control!</strong><br/><br/>Delegate how each and every player on your team will spend their time day in, day out with coaches at practice. Want your power hitter to worry less about avoiding strikeouts and put that time and effort into working on his home run swing instead? Want your aging starter to spend more time practicing his control instead of spending that time worrying about his stuff? By allocating their time and focus to the areas you want, over time you can influence how players develop, maintain their skillset, and fight the aging curve.<br/><br/><strong>2024 Rosters and Rules!</strong><br/><br/>As always, Out of the Park Baseball features up-to-the-minute 2024 MLB rosters that get updated all season long, with every franchise represented from its big league club all the way down to the low minors, and everywhere in between! Plus, OOTP 25 features officially licensed leagues from South Korea (KBO) and Europe.<br/><br/><strong>Improved Historical MLB Modes!</strong><br/><br/>Set up historical MLB games in an all new streamlined way - and benefit from vastly improved historical player ratings! It’s never been faster or easier to experience the entire history of Major League Baseball, now producing even more realistic outcomes thanks to those comprehensive ratings and simulation engine upgrades.<br/><br/><strong>New Retro Visual Immersion!</strong><br/><br/>Watch games with a variety of experiences, including retro-style black and white, ‘50s-era, and ‘70s-era television presentations. Choose from all of these to play games, watch highlights, or just catch a ballgame from a bygone era!<br/><br/><strong>New Licensed Leagues!</strong><br/><br/>For the first time ever, Out of the Park Baseball features an officially licensed Honkbal Hoofdklasse league from The Netherlands and the British Baseball Federation from the United Kingdom! Look for their official clubs, players, competitions, and more!<br/><br/><strong>For the first time ever - an official partnership with the Baseball Hall of Fame!</strong><br/><br/>What happens when you combine the only game that has the entire history of baseball and the the greatest Hall of Fame in sports? An incredible, year-long journey! Join us as we partner with the Baseball Hall of Fame all season - and beyond. Explore Hall of Fame Plaques, with the official, accurate text for each Hall of Famer. Discover incredible Hall of Fame artifacts, curated and released in fun "exhibits" over the course of the season in concert with the Hall - and more surprises too. It's going to be amazing! <br/><br/><strong>Dozens of upgrades big and small!</strong><br/><br/>--&gt; Updated in-game engine base advancement and camera movements<br/>--&gt; A new manager decision history screen gives you a look back on your best and worst trades and transactions<br/>--&gt; Improved trade packages for prospect packages <br/>--&gt; Updated two-way functionality with injured players<br/>And much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/pt_store_text_banner2.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/><br/><strong>Perfect Team is back - bigger than ever!</strong><br/><br/>It’s an all-new Perfect Team! There’s nothing in the world like the incredible online competitions of Perfect Team. Featuring by far the largest player pool ever, and taking advantage of all the player rating and balance upgrades, this year’s Perfect Team is a whole new ballgame.<br/><br/><strong>Brand New Perfect Team Combinator Series Cards!</strong><br/><br/>Pulled non-live cards have a chance to be a special Combinator Series version of the card! Use other cards that share a link (for example being teammates) with the player to get a chance to boost the raw ratings of the Combinator Series card.<br/><br/><strong>A Perfect Team Tournament Roster Builder!</strong><br/><br/>Want to design rosters for the incredible array of Perfect Team Tournaments - all on your own? For the first time ever, Perfect Team will feature a Tournament Sandbox! You can tinker to your heart's content with varying rosters for every type of tournament, with no pressure. This long-requested feature makes its debut in Out of the Park Baseball 25!<br/><br/>In addition to the brand-new Tournament Roster Builder and Combinator Series, Perfect Team 25 also features:<br/><br/><strong>Team Chemistry</strong> - Players who played together in real life will get extra bonuses when on your roster together. Players gain bonuses for seasons they played together, as well as simply being part of the same team or from the same decades<br/><strong>Perfect Team competitions starting on the first day</strong>, including a huge Opening Weekend of Tournaments with big prizes and Perfect Team Championship Series qualifying from Day One! <br/><strong>New content all season long - and beyond!</strong> All new programs, missions, competitions, and excitement await you every day.<br/><br/>Out of the Park Baseball 25 runs on PC/Mac and features the American League and National League logos, the World Series trophy, official logos and jerseys for all 30 MLB teams and 15 KBO teams, over 150 Minor League Baseball league and team logos, and historical MLB logos.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcast - A New Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1013140/Outcast__A_New_Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							20 years after the award-winning action adventure hit, Outcast, pioneered the genre of non-linear open-world games, the long-awaited sequel sees Cutter Slade return to the spectacular alien world of Adelpha. Resurrected by the almighty Yods, he has returned to find the Talans enslaved, the world stripped of its natural resources, and his own past intertwining with the invading robot forces. It's up to him to go on a mission and save the planet again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/flight_8mb.gif?t=1710511218"><br/><br/>The original team behind Outcast 1 has reunited to create this fascinating world, full of dangerous creatures and home to the Talan people – an ancient culture whose fate has become inextricably linked with earth since the events of the first game. You play as Cutter Slade, ex-Navy SEAL, sporting the same dry wit he had back in the 90s – however, the world around him has changed and eventually, so will he.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/combat01_6mb.gif?t=1710511218"><br/> <br/>To save Adelpha, you will … <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>use your jetpack to jump, air-dash, glide, and quickly traverse the fantastic in-game open world <br/></li><li>combine dozens of different modules to create your own personal weapon for taking down the robot invaders <br/></li><li>have total control to approach the story at your own pace in this non-linear world <br/></li><li>explore the world without boundaries, discover hidden temples and dangerous wildlife <br/></li><li>get familiar with the Talan culture while helping them free their villages and gain access to ancient Talan powers that use forces of nature to destroy your enemies <br/></li><li>experience a beautiful, hand-crafted world accompanied by an epic soundtrack by Outcast's original composer, Lennie Moore </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/combat02.gif?t=1710511218"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Museum Mystery: Deckbuilding Card Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2717450/Museum_Mystery_Deckbuilding_Card_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Museum Mystery</strong> is a fusion between deckbuilding rogulite game and narrative adventure with intriguing secrets waiting for you to uncover.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717450/extras/MM_steam_battle.gif?t=1710453320"><br/><br/>Your first night as a museum security guard takes a disastrous turn.<br/>Animated exhibits, awakened gods, and total chaos. And it’s your job to restore order until dawn.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Explore Various Eras</strong></h2>Museum halls are portals into history. Literally. Walk through each era, from Ancient Egypt to the 19th century, to find the roots of what’s happening.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717450/extras/MM_steam_lvl_run.gif?t=1710453320"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Battle With Unique Enemies</strong></h2>Museum exhibits have come to life. And most of them are mad. Try to calm down this amazing pieces of art.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717450/extras/MM_steam_enemies.gif?t=1710453320"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Master Hundreds of Cards</strong></h2>Find cards of ancient artifacts or practices. Combine them, unlock new mechanics and craft your perfect hand.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717450/extras/MM_steam_cards_eng.gif?t=1710453320"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Adventure Through History and Art</strong></h2>Talk with historical figures, complete side-quests and help legendary characters!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Features</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>4 historical eras to explore<br/></li><li>150+ cards to create the best deck possible<br/></li><li>Unique relics that give unprecedented power</li></ul><br/><strong>Can you solve this Mystery?</strong> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Shire: Room One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517850/Toy_Shire_Room_One/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FkhSxB2MSgD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/Toy_Shire_-_Discord_Banner.png?t=1710352808"/></a><br/><br/><br/>Play through the <strong>three levels in Kevin's Room</strong> and defend your room against your old toys. Face Memphis-X in the final level and put a stop to his assault as he crushes your soldiers in an attempt to get to your base.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyVengeance.png?t=1710352808"><br/>You received new toys from your family. Isn't that lovely? Oh, it's for sure... <br/>Your old toys, though, aren't getting along as well. They are no longer cared for and have been forgotten. So what follows next? They're going to join together against you and assault your brand-new toys, so be prepared. But never worry! You're in luck since your brand-new toys are troops of green soldiers. They still require your aid though! Control, strengthen, and defeat the opposing forces! However, focus with care, the enemies you encounter might not be your old playthings!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/InteractiveTowerDefense.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Tower building alone won't be sufficient to repel incoming attackers. Build up your own troops in the best feasible positions, then unleash attacks into enemy territory. Never abandon your towers, and deploy your troops in accordance with the traits of the enemy. First, the attacking forces will attempt to get past your defenses. Build and improve towers to aid your army. By using unique abilities, you can support your troops and towers as well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/EpicBattles.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Safeguard your base against waves of attackers. You need to pick the right troops if you would like to prevail. Clean the paths and guard any open routes. Upgrade your troops and unlock new ones to take down the waves and claim victory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyRealm.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Enter a world and a narrative built around the toys that enriched your youth, including toy soldiers, dinosaur sets, robots, building blocks, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_3.gif?t=1710352808"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dune: Imperium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1689500/Dune_Imperium/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Header.png?t=1710955211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body0_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Experience the ultimate blend of strategy and intrigue as you navigate the treacherous landscapes of Arrakis in the award-winning board game <i>Dune: Imperium</i>!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle online, locally with AI, or against the formidable House Hagal.<br/></li><li>Earn Achievements that showcase your prowess as a leader.<br/></li><li>Embark on more than a dozen Challenges that will test your wit and cunning.<br/></li><li>Compete for badges in the rotating Skirmish Mode where no two games are the same!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body1_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Arrakis. Dune. Desert Planet. Raise your banner above the vast wasteland before you. As the Great Houses of the Landsraad marshal their forces and their spies, whom will you influence, and whom will you betray? A tyrannical Emperor. The secretive Bene Gesserit. The shrewd Spacing Guild. The ferocious Fremen of the Deep Desert. The power of the Imperium can be yours, but war is not the only way to claim it.<br/><br/><i>Dune: Imperium</i> blends deck-building and worker placement in a deeply thematic new strategy game where the fate of the Empire hangs on your decisions. Will you seek political allies or rely upon military might? Economic strength or subtle intrigues? A council seat… or a sharpened blade? The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body2_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>In <i>Dune: Imperium</i>, you'll step into the role of one of the leaders of the Great Houses of the Imperium in a struggle to control the planet Arrakis and the invaluable Spice it provides.<br/><br/>The game plays out in a series of ten rounds, each of which is defined by a new Conflict on the surface of the planet; some award critical resources, and some provide Victory Points that will propel you to dominance. But choose your battles wisely: spread your forces too thin, and you'll find your enemies growing too strong to oppose.<br/><br/>Each round, you'll draw a hand of five cards from your deck, which will get stronger over the course of the game as you acquire new cards. Each card can be played in one of two ways: To send an Agent out into the Imperium to gather resources, or to Reveal at the end of the round to purchase new powerful cards. You must maintain a careful balance to get the most of the resources available to you. How will you find your path?<br/><br/>As your game progresses, you'll vie for Influence with four factions of the Imperium: The Emperor, the economically powerful Spacing Guild, the mysterious Bene Gesserit, and the ferocious Fremen of the deep deserts. Earning Influence among the various groups helps you to earn the Victory Points you need...but will you compete with your rivals for their favor, or abandon alliances to pursue other opportunities?<br/><br/>Many strategies are at your disposal, and many paths to victory. The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Footer.png?t=1710955211"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals Zero Hour</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732960/Command__Conquer_Generals_Zero_Hour/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals Zero Hour brings you closer to the enemy than ever before. Engage opposing forces at hot spots around the globe as you match strategies and arsenals against the new masterminds of modern war.<br/><br/><strong>Arsenal.</strong> Unleash the next generation of 3D new units and 20 new upgrades including China's ECM Tank, GLA's BattleBus and the USA's Spectre Gunship.<br/><br/><strong>Missions.</strong> Take on 15 new missions and make tomorrow's headlines. Root out a splinter cell in Cairo, steal deadly toxins from a U.S. lab and more.<br/><br/><strong>Generals.</strong> Match strategies and arsenals against 9 enemy commanders with unpredictable personalities and tactics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Tiberian Sun™ and Firestorm™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229880/Command__Conquer_Tiberian_Sun_and_Firestorm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Second Tiberium War begins in this legendary sequel to the original Command &amp; Conquer. <br/><br/>With his forces stronger than ever, arch villain and leader of The Brotherhood of Nod - Kane - is pitched in an epic battle against the world's war machine - the Global Defense Initiative. Now you must orchestrate the fate of mankind.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on Dynamic Battlefields. Nature itself provides tactical opportunities - destroyable and deformable terrain, forest fires, treacherous ice fields and many more surprises that help or hinder your strategies.<br/></li><li>Exciting New Strategies and Units. Jump Jet Infantry, Hover Tanks, Tunneling APCs, Hunter Seekers, Laser Fences, Mechanized Battle Units and many more.<br/></li><li>The "Veterancy" Factor. Units can become faster and stronger as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>New Kinetic Battlefields. Flying shrapnel, shock waves and crashing debris are just a few of the exciting new technologies developed to enhance the in-game experience.<br/></li><li>The mood and attitude of the battlefield comes alive like never before - covert night missions, searchlights and new defenses intensify the thrill and excitement.</li></ul><br/>Then take the battle further in <strong>Firestorm, the official expansion pack for the game</strong>. Includes all-new campaign missions, cinematics, and units to decide the future of mankind.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Renegade™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229890/Command__Conquer_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer gets up close and personal in this classic First Person Shooter for one of the most iconic franchises.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wreak Havoc</strong> - Experience the Command &amp; Conquer universe on foot as Havoc, wise-cracking GDI Commando.<br/></li><li><strong>Make Your Own Rules</strong>  - Take on the evil Brotherhood of Nod using your own mix of brute force, stealth, and strategy.<br/></li><li><strong>Assault at Ground Level</strong>  - Dish out the damage in either first or third person.<br/></li><li><strong>Total Access</strong>  - Sneak inside and explore full-scale structures, like immense Tiberium Refineries and the ominous Hand of Nod.<br/></li><li><strong>Grind the Gears</strong>  - Beef up your arsenal by commandeering lethal vehicles, such as Nod Buggies, Flame Tanks, and Mammoth Tanks.<br/></li><li><strong>Weapons of Mass Destruction</strong>  - Choose from a multitude of weapons, including the Tiberium Auto Rifle, Chemical Sprayer, and the devasting Personal Ion Cannon.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™, Counterstrike™ and The Aftermath™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229840/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_Counterstrike_and_The_Aftermath/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert</strong> pushed the envelope for the RTS genre in the mid-1990s and became one of the most iconic strategy games of all time. <br/><br/><strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert</strong>  gives you the opportunity to be more devious, cunning, and ruthless than ever before. Red Alert puts the fate of the world in your hands!<br/><br/><strong>Counterstrike</strong>, the exciting expansion pack to Red Alert, is full of clandestine activity, experimental technologies, and disavowed tactics. Includes 16 all-new missions, where you decide the ultimate fate of the struggle between the Allies and Soviets.<br/><br/><strong>In The Aftermath expansion pack</strong>, prepare for guerilla tactics, insidious strategies, and forbidden weapons. Includes 18 all-new missions and multiple units in a showdown that will test your mettle.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ and The Covert Operations™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229830/Command__Conquer_and_The_Covert_Operations/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The legendary RTS game which started it all. Will you side with the humanistic GDI or bring the world to its knees with Kane and the Brotherhood of Nod. Your adversaries are without mercy. And so are you.  <br/><br/>Includes the <strong>The Covert Operations</strong> expansion pack with a range of challenging new missions.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rental</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2796550/Rental/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796550/extras/Gif_Final__2___1_.gif?t=1709834139"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Great Deal!</strong></h2><br/><i>Perfect cabin for a family of four. Close to the beach with great vibes!<br/>For more information about this rental, contact the caretaker!</i><br/><br/>For summer vacation, Umi's family rents a cabin near the beach. However, Umi soon realizes that the offer was not as grand as promised...<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Explore the summer cabin in this short game reminiscent of classic survival horror games.<br/></li><li> Meet and talk to a quirky cast of characters as you try to piece together the secrets of the cabin. <br/></li><li> Find items that will help you advance and find out what is wrong with this place. </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Controls</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Arrows or WASD to move<br/></li><li> Space to interact</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit Hole</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2831340/Rabbit_Hole/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/smaller.png?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Remember you will live.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Rabbit Hole is a fast paced, tough-as-nails 2D Platformer-RogueLike-Shooter inspired by popular roguelikes, made with a love for the genre. <br/>You are Disc, someone who was suddenly brought to the Rabbit Hole. <br/>Collect guns, fight foes and meet strange new characters on your descent to the bottom, all in an attempt to find your heart again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/1.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“This place is like its own ecosystem. A big living breathing mess.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Every run is different. Enjoy hours of replayable content through randomly generated floor layouts and 50+ weapons to collect and use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/2.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Hey, hey, hey! How's my favorite anxiety-fueled nutjob!”</i></strong><br/><br/>Unlock new characters with diverse playstyles. Each of the 6 unlockable characters keep gameplay fresh and give a unique perspective on the gameplay loop.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/3.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“There was a blank line, almost as if I had erased it”</i></strong><br/><br/>Discover the truth that lies beneath the surface. Collect books and fill out your library to understand its unseen history. In the end, you may even come to understand yourself?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Grindea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/269770/Secrets_of_Grindea/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/269770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Secrets of Grindea</i> is an old-school Action RPG with co-op support for up to 4 players. It is a tribute to and sometimes a parody of the old SNES games so many of us grew up with and loved! Journey through fantastical lands, and battle tons of different enemies and bosses in your quest for truth, friendship and, above all, finding the world's rarest treasures!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A rich world filled with 300+ unique, colorful characters and an engaging story to drive your journey forward.<br/></li><li>Co-op support for up to four players! Enjoy the entire storyline with your friends or call someone in to help with the more difficult challenges.<br/></li><li>Customization, customization, customization - design a character that represents you, then mix and match any of the 31 spells and skills across 9 different categories.<br/></li><li>30+ epic boss fights! Overgrown slimes, giant robots, mimics - we have it all!<br/></li><li>Side content - design your own home, fish, craft items, tame pets, partake in mini-games, grow plants - there’s plenty to keep you entertained when you want a break from the main story.</li></ul><br/>And last but not least:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Arcade Mode - Separate from Story Mode, the game includes a <strong>full roguelite</strong> version where you need to battle your way to the top on a single life, building a town of your own as you progress.  How far can you get?</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<br/><br/>※ <i>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</i> is the free-to-play version of <i>Meta-Ghost: The breaking show</i>, to showcase some of the gameplay content.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709870080"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2510720/Artifact_Seeker/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/DS.png?t=1711340449"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/11y.png?t=1711340449"><br/><strong>The unique “Artifacts sharing code function” allows you to share the Artifacts you collect with your friends! !<br/>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/1y.png?t=1711340449"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/1z.gif?t=1711340449"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/2y.png?t=1711340449"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/gif1.gif?t=1711340449"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/3y.png?t=1711340449"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/3y.gif?t=1711340449"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/4y.png?t=1711340449"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/4y.gif?t=1711340449"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/5y.png?t=1711340449"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/5y.gif?t=1711340449"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/6y.png?t=1711340449"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/6y.gif?t=1711340449"><br/><strong>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journey to the West Survivor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2450100/Journey_to_the_West_Survivor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2450100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Welcome to the World of Journey to the West</strong></h2><br/>"Journey to the West Survivors"is a pixelated, casual pleasure game with a survival rogue-like gameplay.  The storyline draws inspiration from the four classic novels "Journey to the West" and incorporates traditional Honghuang Xixian world views.  Players can choose from 12 characters, each possessing unique abilities such as Sun Torture wielding dual guns, Tang Three Burial with an invincible iron fist, Tyu excelling in farming and eight-ring killing techniques, Bad Fish skilled at clean kills, Red Boy controlling a doll car, Aoliet commanding the White Dragon car, Yang Jian leading a special attack team along with his powerful crouping dog Boston.  With over 200 massive skills and resonances available for exploration, players are encouraged to freely combine various gameplay elements and genres.  Additionally, players can engage in social activities by making friends within the game's community while also enjoying features like farming and construction to recruit allies for cooperative battles against enemies.  The game consists of two main parts: survival mode (offering simple, ordinary, difficult levels as well as hellish challenges) and farming mode (allowing players to cultivate crops including spiritual grasses), craft tools and build houses;  continuous updates aim to enhance these aspects further.  We welcome you to try out this immersive gaming experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2450100/extras/Fist-to-save-sentient-beings.png?t=1711335424"><br/><br/><strong>Use the Iron Fist falling from the sky on the monsters that need to be purified, or directly take out the Gatling gun for physical salvation, or even summon a screen full of arrow towers to become an idle tower defense! There are more than 200 skills to choose from, and there are also elemental reactions and skill resonances, allowing you to beat the six-eared macaque in a fancy way!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2450100/extras/铁拳_合并_-原版.gif?t=1711335424"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2450100/extras/图鉴.gif?t=1711335424"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2450100/extras/Each-shows-hisher-special-power.png?t=1711335424"><br/><br/>Incarnate into the traditional Journey to the West master and apprentice quartet, a sexy and hot banshee, or directly transform into an Autobot and go on a rampage? There are up to 12 optional characters, each with 3 advanced talents that fundamentally change the gameplay! Provide you with a variety of human choices to beat monsters!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2450100/extras/选人.gif?t=1711335424"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2450100/extras/开车-原版.gif?t=1711335424"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2450100/extras/Exotic-monsters.png?t=1711335424"><br/><br/>Weird monsters from foreign lands have broken into the world of Journey to the West. It's time to show off your real skills! Use your agility to avoid the energetic guy who flips tricks, investigate the mysterious man who loves to play basketball, and most importantly, be careful of all kinds of poop!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2450100/extras/击败创世共工-原版.gif?t=1711335424"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2450100/extras/Meet-a--Taoist-couple.png?t=1711335424"><br/><br/>Facing the overwhelming monsters coming, one person really can't stop him! Quickly equip the Taoist companion with two skills, and then send them out to draw hatred! Tips: Properly performing dual cultivation can make Taoists stronger~<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2450100/extras/道侣2.gif?t=1711335424"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tempus Rail</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2301560/Tempus_Rail/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2301560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Trapped forever on a train to nowhere. Once seen as the greatest invention of the 1800's, the Tempus Rail was a vast locomotive that breached the temporal rift and gifted it's passengers eternal life. Free from consequence and even death, the passengers aboard the Tempus Rail travelled the temporal streams at the precise speed to reset time each day. But when the maiden voyage ended and it was time to leave the temporal rift, the train never stopped. Now countless cycles beyond, the train has devolved into chaos with few who have held their sanity. <br/><br/>As one of these lucky (or unlucky) few who find themselves barricaded in the rear of the train, you must fight your way to the front of the train in the hopes of stopping the train before days end.<h2 class="bb_tag">Deck-Builder</h2>Fight your way through deadly carriages using a turn-based combat system in which your deck holds the key to your survival. Collect rare and powerful cards on your journey from fallen enemies, or through optional story missions and quests. Start each run with a different deck as you unlock and discover more abilities tied to the mysterious crystal shards that grow on the outside of the train.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2301560/extras/Steam_Banner_1a.gif?t=1711333351"><h2 class="bb_tag">Death Is Not The End</h2>Cursed with eternal life, each death is just an opportunity for progression as you awake in your bed again each morning. Do not expect the encounters to be the same each day as factions beyond the barricade fight for control in a never ending conflict.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2301560/extras/Steam_Banner_2a.gif?t=1711333351"><h2 class="bb_tag">A Wild West Unlike Our Own</h2>Fight your way through a world scarred with the technological advancements unseen in our own history books. Encounter machines awakening to their own existence and those who seek modifications to themselves that would be deemed most unholy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2301560/extras/Steam_Banner_03.gif?t=1711333351"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seduction of Beauty</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733530/Seduction_of_Beauty/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2733530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Seduction of Beauty" is a brand new first-person immersive interactive video game, where you will embark on a unique and extraordinary love journey with six distinctive female protagonists. <br/><br/>In this virtual world, you will experience a series of emotional ups and downs, from getting to know each other, falling in love, to arguments and making choices. All of these will be presented in a first-person perspective, allowing you to deeply immerse yourself in a genuine interactive experience.<br/><br/>Is she sharp, mature, and steady?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2733530/extras/张馨妍.gif?t=1711332986"><br/>Or is she sexy, plump, and seductive with a fiery allure?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2733530/extras/李诗盈.gif?t=1711332986"><br/>Or is she petite, lively, and lovely?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2733530/extras/黎美萱.gif?t=1711332986"><br/>Of course, it can also be our outgoing social bully<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2733530/extras/夏若汐.gif?t=1711332986"><br/>Or it could be a noble, dignified, mature young lady~<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2733530/extras/方欣.gif?t=1711332986"><br/>Or is it a simple, gentle and peaceful little princess?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2733530/extras/余慧.gif?t=1711332986"><br/><br/>Game Features:<br/><br/>First-person immersive interactive gameplay with live-action filming: Unique first-person perspective allows you to fully immerse yourself in real-life scenes and interact with characters. The game features real actors performing in real environments, delivering genuine emotions of love through a distinctive perspective.<br/><br/>Multiple branches and endings: The game offers over a hundred story branches and supports up to twelve different endings, including hidden storylines and Easter eggs. Each choice made allows for a deep exploration of the charms of love. Some important choices will influence the game's progression and ultimate outcome, encapsulating the diversity of life within a few crucial decisions.<br/><br/>Unique gameplay and details: Not limited to just making choices, players can discover key storyline clues through interactive scenes. Perhaps an inconspicuous detail will impact your ending.<br/><br/>In this game, you will experience the sweetness and helplessness of love, navigate complex interpersonal relationships, and face off against rivals for love. Each female lead possesses unique personalities and charms, and you will encounter various choices and challenges, unfolding a unique love story of your own. We hope you can fully immerse yourself and feel the emotions of real-life love.<br/><br/>After all, life doesn't come with a save and reload option, but in this game, you can try different choices multiple times and create your own unique story.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morph!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2791300/Morph/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791300/extras/Animation6.gif?t=1711329497"><br/>Morph is a casual indie game that allows you to play in a variety of styles, such as 'possessing' over 100 different objects in a given world to find and chase other players, or quietly hiding.<br/><br/><strong><u>Possess yourself with another object!</u></strong><br/>Possess with a variety of objects to blend in perfectly with your surroundings to hide your presence and strategically gain a tactical advantage.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791300/extras/Animation4.gif?t=1711329497"><br/><br/><strong><u>Find other players!</u></strong><br/>Find, chase, and slay other players.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791300/extras/Animation3.gif?t=1711329497"><br/><br/><strong><u>Hide naturally!</u></strong><br/>Hide your possessed object inconspicuously by blending it seamlessly into its environment.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791300/extras/Animation2.gif?t=1711329497"><br/><br/><strong><u>Use your skills!</u></strong><br/>Create your own play style by combining various skills and enjoy the game.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791300/extras/Animation1.gif?t=1711329497"><br/><br/><strong><u>Play with variety maps!</u></strong><br/>Enjoy the game using numerous objects on maps of various concepts.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791300/extras/Animation5.gif?t=1711329497"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AKAZU Off limits</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2848610/AKAZU_Off_limits/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2848610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Summary</h2>I found myself lying in a strange place.<br/>I had no idea where I was or why I had come here.<br/>The only thing I knew was that I had come looking for something.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>By exploring slowly and carefully,<br/>Please enjoy the atmosphere as if you were here for a liver test.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play time</h2>10-15 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">Genre</h2>A short walking simulator horror game.<h2 class="bb_tag">Control</h2>【WASD】Player Movement<br/>【LMB】Interact<br/>【F】Flashlight On/Off<br/>【Shift】Run<br/>【Enter】Page turn<br/>【ESC】MENU<h2 class="bb_tag">Attention</h2>*You may be asked to download the UE5 runtime when you start up the program for the first time,<br/>In that case, follow the instructions to download the latest runtime and restart your computer.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tastrion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2720360/Tastrion/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2720360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Somewhere in the vast unknown, a rogue planet drifts endlessly into space, once belonging to an advanced civilization that has now been consumed by Tastrion, an artificial mutagen that is the most potent genotoxin ever made. The last hope of humanity has been deployed from Ginsaria 9, a space colony that has developed a gunship titled ''Desolazor'' wielding a powerful weapon to fight back and eradicate the infestation before it spreads further across the galaxy...<br>
<br>
Tastrion is a Shoot 'Em Up inspired by 90's classics such as Gradius, Arrow Flash, and Gleylancer. The weapon system is simplistic. 4 Buttons, 3 shots. Main frontal Photon lasers, multi-directional Ion spread, armor-piercing rail gun, and an all-powerful solar-powered radiant bomb. with the help of upgradable pickups across your missions, turn your weaponry and ship into the ultimate massacre machine.<br>
<br>
The game includes:<br>
<br>
- 6 Stages, 12 bosses, 5 secret rare power-up containers, and 1 secret super difficult stage.<br/>
- 1 Single-player game mode<br/>
- Weaponry upgradable up to 8 times.<br/>
- Dark-synth and industrial-themed music.<br/>
<br/>
Tastrion is a modern take on 16-bit 90's era shmups with modern aspect ratio, it isn't entirely a bullet hell, but expect a challenge.<br/>
<br/>
Notes:<br/>
- The trailer is not a complete representation of the final product, so expect enemy placements and details in stages may be slightly different on release.<br/>
- There will be some future updates after release and it will be added to the game.<br/>
- supports Xbox and Playstation controllers but mainly focused on Xbox users.<br/>
<br/>
This game has been made with SHMUP Creator! A versatile tool for creating Shoot 'Em Up genres.<br/>
Kudos to the talented creators and the community!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gloves On!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2567880/Gloves_On/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2567880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i>Gloves On!</i></strong> is a boxing experience with realistic controls and a unique perspective of fighting games. Step in the ring with a fighter created by you or chosen between multiple options and fight a full match of boxing packed with adrenaline and action.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2567880/extras/Banner-_Gloves_On.gif?t=1711306979"><br/><br/>Simple and straight to the point, the first official game release of <strong><i>Deep Cave Studios</i></strong> is not messing around and will push you to the limit. Practice and learn the boxing fundamentals with real and accurate movements and techniques. Fight against fighters controlled by CPU or by a real person with Local or Online PvP or practice your punches against the punching bag.<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Realistic Controls</strong> - Dynamic and Immersive controls to master<br/></li><li> <strong>Training</strong> - Step into the Gloves On! Gym and master all the movements required to be a real fighter<br/></li><li> <strong>Character Customization</strong> - Choose your equipment between 15+ types of shorts, gloves and headgear.<br/></li><li> <strong>Local or Online PvP</strong> - Fight against people from all over the world or by connecting an extra controller<br/></li><li> <strong>Multiplayer Ranking</strong> - Compete for a place in the global leaderboards</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLAYER:</h2><br/>Coming soon to the game, the multiplayer experience will include character customization and a competitive setting with weekly and monthly leaderboards so fighters will compete for first place. Make your own history and become the best fighter the world has ever seen.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Physics</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2837320/Unreal_Physics/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dive into the dynamic world of physics with Unreal Physics an immersive 3D physics sandbox and demo collection that pushes the boundaries of Unreal Engine. This unique experience combines the cutting-edge FluidNinja and Chaos physics systems to deliver a mesmerizing showcase of fluid dynamics, destruction, and realistic simulations.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837320/extras/up1.gif?t=1711299996"><br/><br/>Fluid Dynamics Unleashed: Witness the incredible power of FluidNinja as it brings fluid simulations to life in ways you've never imagined. Whether it's the graceful flow of water, the mesmerizing realism of smoke, or the viscous flowing of molten lava, the fluid dynamics in this sandbox will leave you in awe.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837320/extras/up2.gif?t=1711299996"><br/><br/>Chaos Physics on Display: Brace yourself for a revolution in destructible environments and realistic physics simulations with Unreal Engine's Chaos Physics. Experience the sheer thrill as structures crumble, debris scatters realistically, and chaos ensues in response to your every action. The level of destructibility will redefine your expectations of in-game physics.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837320/extras/up3.gif?t=1711299996"><br/><br/>Endless Possibilities in the Sandbox: Engage with a variety of physics-driven demos and sandbox environments that showcase the versatility of FluidNinja and Chaos Physics. From tinkering with fluid dynamics to unleashing controlled chaos, each demo invites you to explore, experiment, and marvel at the beauty of physics in action.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837320/extras/up4.gif?t=1711299996"><br/><br/>Visual Spectacle: Immerse yourself in stunning visuals that showcase the capabilities of Unreal Engine. From the realistic rendering of fluid surfaces to the intricate details of destructible objects, every frame is a testament to the technological prowess that FluidNinja and Chaos Physics bring to the gaming landscape.<br/><br/>Embark on a adventure into the realms of physics with Unreal Physics a playground for FluidNinja and Unreal Engine physics showcasing the possibilities of current physics systems. This sandbox experience isn't just a game – it's a showcase of innovation, creativity, and the awe-inspiring power of physics simulations						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactic Boxing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2740280/Tactic_Boxing/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2740280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Tactic Boxing is a hardcore boxing simulator with ragdoll physics, local multiplayer and a career mode.<br>
<br>
- Local Multiplayer (a controller is required for local multiplayer)<br>
- Active Ragdoll Physics<br>
- 3 Boxing Styles: Puncher, Slugger, Out-Boxer<br>
- 9 skills (strength, accuracy, health, stamina, footwork, attack speed, chin, HP and SP recovery)<br>
- 40 boxers (not real)<br/>
- Career mode<br/>
- Mouse and keyboard controls<br/>
- Gamepad controls						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.Forty-Five</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2691350/FortyFive/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2691350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A perfect mix of card game, rogue-lite, and pure wild west mayhem. Explore an ever-changing map, collect interesting cards, and battle enemies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2691350/extras/steamtextpics_1.png?t=1711299607"><br/><strong>Explore and Collect</strong><br/>Explore the Frontier and add powerful cards - bullets - to your collection. Each one equipped with its own unique effect. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2691350/extras/steamtextpics_2.png?t=1711299607"><br/><strong>Build</strong><br/>Each bullet has an individual effect, used to create powerful synergies. Use them to build your deck and to become an Outlaw Legend!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2691350/extras/steamtextpics_3.png?t=1711299607"><br/><strong>Load and shoot to kill!</strong><br/>Load your cards into the revolver and use the effects to your advantage, while also utilizing the limited amount of chambers and the rotations of the revolver. Then, shoot the enemies and send them 6 feet deep! But watch out, he won't just stand there letting you shoot him down so easily…<br/><br/><br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><strong>Completely free &amp; Open Source:</strong> And thats a great price if you ask me. No ads or any kind of microtransactions, I promise. Read down below to find out more about the open-source licence that .forty-five is under.<br/><strong>Over 50 unique cards:</strong> some serious and some … a little bit … less serious.<br/><strong>Innovative gameplay:</strong> allowing the player to achieve creative combos with the revolvers rotation.<br/><strong>100% handdrawn assets:</strong> I might not be the next picasso, but hey, I'm trying okay …<br/><strong>A procedurally generated map:</strong> ever-changing, guaranteeing a new experience every run.<br/><strong>Deckbuilding</strong>: to truly personalize your way of … shooting people.<br/><strong>Different enemy types:</strong> so you'll never run out of things to shoot at.<br/><strong>Unique biomes:</strong> each … you know what just download and find out it's free.<br/><br/><br/>We are open source!<br/>The source code of .forty-five is public under the GPLv3 license. But what does that actually mean? It means that anyone is free to view and share the code of the game. Also, everyone can make their own modified versions of our game and redistribute it, as long as they maintain the GPLv3.0 license.<br/><br/>Want to know more? Read about the license here: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fchoosealicense.com%2Flicenses%2Fgpl-3.0%2F" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://choosealicense.com/licenses/gpl-3.0/</a><br/><br/>Want to take a look at our code? Visit our Github: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FblueUserRed%2Fforty-five" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://github.com/blueUserRed/forty-five</a><br/><br/>Project Infos:<br/>.Forty-Five is developed as a Diploma Thesis by five students of the higher technical vocational school "HTL Rennweg" in Vienna. We hope you will have as much fun playing, as we had developing.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lunatic Taxi Driver</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2862030/Lunatic_Taxi_Driver/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2862030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Lunatic Taxi Driver is an exciting and fast-paced game that puts you in the shoes of a taxi driver who is determined to show the world what it means to be a truly exceptional driver. Your goal in Lunatic Taxi Driver is to pick up passengers, transport them to their destination, and do it all with speed, efficiency, and style. But being a great taxi driver isn't just about speed and skill - it's also about customer service. In Lunatic Taxi Driver, you'll need to keep your car clean, well-maintained, and fully fueled at all times, while also being friendly, courteous, and professional with your passengers. Even if you break the rules of the road in your quest for speed, you'll always make sure that your passengers are safe and comfortable. Whether you're a seasoned driver or just looking for a fun and challenging simulation game, Lunatic Taxi Driver is sure to provide hours of thrilling entertainment. So why wait? Get behind the wheel and start driving today!<br/><br/><strong>Game features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>5 business taxis<br/></li><li>2 Game Modes ( City / Offroad)<br/></li><li>20 levels</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Park Bus Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2862020/Lets_Park_Bus_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2862020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Have you ever been challenged to measure your accuracy skills? Well, Let's Parking: Bus Edition comes with dozens of challenges.These will consist of all kinds of parking behind the wheel of a large bus. You will encounter all kinds of obstacles that will prevent you from performing a correct parking. As a result, you will be rewarded with stars that will once again demonstrate your professionalism in driving a massive engine. Stop thinking, show it to everyone who is the coolest in the parking lot,right now!<br/><br/><strong>Game features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>More than 20 levels<br/></li><li>3 attempts in case you hit the bus<br/></li><li>2 types of buses with automatic transmission</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild Animals Transporter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2862060/Wild_Animals_Transporter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2862060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world keeps changing. Unfortunately, not all things work out for the best. Some animals are endangered. As a driver, you will help transport these innocent creatures to be rescued from poaching. You will meet all kinds of species: rhinos, zebras, oxen that need a new home. Be careful how you drive, they are sensitive to it because they are wild. In this way you will also contribute to saving the lives of these wonderful creatures!<br/><br/><strong>Game features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>More than 9 levels<br/></li><li>Sharp Turns<br/></li><li>Big trailer that holds these animals ( rhynos,zebras,oxen)<br/></li><li></li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megis Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2203100/Megis_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2203100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Description</strong><br/>"Megis Adventure" is an open - world RPG pixel game. You find yourself on an isolated, faraway island, and starts an adventure to overcome mysteries, foes and dungeons - all in hope to help the citizens of the island. The story is not complex, yet fun and full of surprises which leads to enjoyable and immersing gameplay experience. <br/><br/><strong>History</strong><br/>"Megis Adventure" was developed by a solo developer in early 2023. The development is completely independent of everything, including capital. Which makes it 100% focused on pure fun gameplay and makes it the game the developer wants to make. The developer obligated to create an ad free and in-purchases free game with all future updates to be given free to anyone who purchase the game, with a commitment to never change that decision.<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/>- Available in 26 languages!<br/>- Experience retro pixel art game with old-school and nostalgy game style!<br/>- Explore lively open world, visit different buildings, NPC's, islands, zones, and more!<br/>- Get in action by exploring dungeons, overcoming traps, monsters and bosses!<br/>- Go for adventures, more than one hundred quests to complete!<br/>- Choose your favorite play style by building your talents tree, out of twenty-seven different talents options!<br/>- Strengthen your character by unlocking passive bonuses and progress in level, professions and equipment!<br/>- Gather resources - chop wood, mine stone, fish more than one hundred unique fish!<br/>- Hundreds of items and consumables to buy and trade, as you progress in level, new items are unlocked!<br/>- Unlock friendly pet that will join you in your adventures!<br/>- Pick your favorite class out of three classes: Swashbuckler, Beast Master and Sorcerer!<br/>- Follow an engaging story with rich lore!<br/>- Immerse into hand-designed fantasy world with warm sensibility of pixel art!<br/><br/><strong>Start your epic adventure!</strong><br/><strong>Hop into the pixel RPG open world of "Megis Adventure" today!</strong><br/><br/><strong>Available in 26 different languages:</strong><br/>English, Spanish, Portuguese, Bulgarian, Finnish, French, German, Greek, Latvian, Hungarian, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Chinese, Thai, Vietnamese, Swedish, Romanian, Ukrainian, Norwegian, Dutch, Amharic, Hindi, Russian, Turkish.<br/><br/>---<br/><br/>"Megis Adventure promises to bring the most exciting entertainment hours." - 2Game<br/><br/>"Megis Adventure: An RPG in the spirit of The Legend of Zelda." - App-Time						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACK WEREWOLF</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2865910/BLACK_WEREWOLF/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2865910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							BLACK WEREWOLF - Werewolves from neighboring lands invaded your lands and began to destroy all your property. The village elder had no choice but to send you to deal with the enemies and find out what was going on. You need to be extremely careful and unnoticed to deal with enemies and return the stolen goods.<br>
<br>
Explore mysterious forests, destroying enemy werewolves. In this dark game, your character must collect stolen items and uncover secrets to defeat ferocious enemies. On your way you will encounter different types of werewolves, each of which has its own unique abilities.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
- Atmospheric gameplay with intense battles<br>
- Various locations filled with dangers<br/>
- Various types of werewolves with unique attacks						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soul Eater</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2836250/Soul_Eater/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2836250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">About this Game</h2>"Soul Eater" is an exhilarating 2D platformer roguelike game that offers players a dynamic and constantly evolving gaming experience. With every playthrough, the game dynamically adjusts the positions of enemies and map layouts, guaranteeing that players face fresh challenges and surprises each time they engage with the game. Moreover, players have the option to randomly upgrade their skills, introducing an element of unpredictability and strategic decision-making to their gameplay.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Story</h2>The player embarks on a journey through a sword containing the soul of a being desperate for revenge against their past betrayers. The soul within the sword shares the player's past wounds and anger, fueling a desire for vengeance against their enemies. As the player travels the world, they seek out those who betrayed them in the past, and with each encounter, they have the opportunity to seize their souls. These acquired souls are absorbed into the player, further empowering the player, and allowing player to control the enemy.<h2 class="bb_tag">Controls</h2>Move the character "W","A","S","D" <br/>Throw the sword "R" <br/>Interact with NPC "V"<br/>Skill "Q"<br/>Attack "Left Mouse Click"<br/>Parrying "<strong>Drag while holding down the right mouse button</strong>"<h2 class="bb_tag">Requirement</h2>"Soul Eater" only work Window system						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move Ball to Green</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2871080/Move_Ball_to_Green/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2871080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Just draw anything. Make the ball move to the green zone!<br>
It is a puzzle game that can be your best brain teaser.<br>
MBG is also good for teaching physics science to your own baby.<br>
<br>
- How to play<br>
You can draw things by touching and dragging the screen. Your drawing will be dropping by gravity. Bump it to move the ball to the goal. Or you can make other construction as a tool to move the ball like ancient people.<br>
<br/>
** Exit menu added. Thanks for the reply! **						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LetMeOut</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2604230/LetMeOut/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bundy is a scholar with a long history. <br/><br/>You witness deep within him his research to cure his wife's dementia. <br/><br/>The research involves extracting all electrical signals from neurons in living people, and you may also be a victim.<br/><br/>You must escape from deep memories and solve various puzzles that he prepares to test others.<br/><br/>Escape by solving problems such as chess, which he enjoyed playing with his wife, complicated hospital facilities, and locked doors.<br/><br/>He must also run away from his wife's symptoms, the attacks from the test subjects, and his memories of the past.<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/>Let Me Out is a game in which players must survive through five stages by finding items that can help them escape from each test subject. Solve puzzles, gimmicks, subject tracking, and more to survive and pass the final stage.<br/><br/><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604230/extras/example_1.png?t=1711280551"><br/>Bundy studied dolls with artificial nerves to preserve memories for long periods of time.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604230/extras/example_2.png?t=1711280551"><br/>He recruited outstanding scholars from various fields to the academy to treat his wife. And we tested whether they had developed memories and brains.<br/><br/>Let Me Out consists of a total of 5 stages and experiences various places in Bundy's memories. <br/><br/>There are also past images in the form of electrical signals. <br/><br/>You must retrieve your mind and memories through the countless puzzles and layers of memories he shared with Julia. <br/><br/>No, should I take it back? <br/><br/>Does it matter?<br/><br/>We must remember, in memory.<br/><br/>---------<br/><br/><strong>Part of Bundy's research diary</strong><br/><br/>Is the human subject the body? Is it mental?<br/><br/>If it is the mind, is it memory? Or is it something like a soul that creates thoughts?<br/><br/>If someone else can take it, will I be that person?<br/><br/>Dementia...isn't it about losing that...?						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crawlspace Multiplayer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2585530/Crawlspace_Multiplayer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A nightmarish playground awaits beneath the floorboards. Join forces with your friends to conquer the crawlspace and retrieve the baby dolls that are trapped in its depths.  But watch your back... killer dolls thirst for your fear.  In this suffocating battle for survival, teamwork is your only lifeline. Can you mend the ventilation system and escape, or will the crawlspace become your eternal tomb?<br>
<br>
Maximum 4 players.<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
*Nights: Complete 5 challenging nights in the crawlspace.<br>
*Unique dolls: Multiple dolls with different attacks to avoid.<br>
*Motivating Messages: Enjoy motivating messages from your employer.<br/>
*Proximity Voice Chat: Talk with your friends sometimes.<br/>
*Multiplayer: Use teamwork to have fun with your friends. Or slap them.<br/>
*Singleplayer: If you have no friends. <br/>
<br/>
Coming soon: <br/>
*New map with new dolls and gameplay.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forest Keeper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2861750/Forest_Keeper_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2861750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Forest Keeper 2 is a continuation of the first part of the game! Plunge back into a little adventure with the forest guardian!<br>
<br>
The Guardian of the Forest has called you again! This time a snowstorm has hit peaceful lands and only you can stop it! Solve puzzles with different cubes and go to the end. In the game you will find many unique blocks and levels that can be completed in different ways!<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
- Lots of levels<br>
- Convenient controls<br/>
- Physics<br/>
- Colorful graphics						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic Ring</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2861860/Magic_Ring/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2861860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Magic Ring is an exciting 3D game that takes you on a dangerous journey through the desert to take part in a legendary tournament! You have to fight various monsters and bosses using magical powers! Use your skills and tactics, fight, collect artifacts and become a legend of the desert tournament and win the main prize - a magic ring!<br>
<br>
Peculiarities<br>
- Colorful graphics.<br>
- Dangerous opponents<br>
- Great soundtrack.						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getaway Driver</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2870670/Getaway_Driver/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2870670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							INFO<br>
<br>
Take on the role of a former bank robbing getaway driver as you explore a fully realized city. Cruise through bustling downtown streets, beaches, deserts and more in a handful of vehicles including sedans, sports cars, SUVs and others. Go for a drive or unleash your weapon and cause mayhem across the city. You own this town! Be sure to view the controls when running the game to know how to play.<br>
<br>
<br>
FEATURES<br>
<br/>
-A fully open 2D sprite-based world.<br/>
-Cities, beaches, deserts and other explorable areas.<br/>
-Hijack and drive vehicles, from sedans, sports cars, SUVs and more.<br/>
-Pedestrians such as joggers, hikers, construction workers and others.<br/>
-Wildlife including deer, coyotes, rabbits and more.<br/>
-Classic shoot-'em-up style gameplay.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
ADDITIONAL INFO<br/>
<br/>
You can always view the in-game controls if you are stuck or do not know how to play the game. This game is meant to be played on Windows platforms using the mouse and keyboard. The game does not feature any kind of controller support. Please keep in mind that this game is meant for a mature audience. Thanks for playing!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARASiTE FLOWER</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2855480/PARASiTE_FLOWER/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							PARASiTE FLOWER is a beautiful yet disturbing side scroller game where you slowly uncover the story of Ari.<br>
A short disturbing horror game where you're playing as Ari Yeong, she is re-living the same day over and over again. With each loop the world around her get's darker and more dangerous. Choose the right options to keep her alive and get her to class.  <br>
<br>
<br>
The game is interactive, with cut scenes, original watercolor-like artwork. You can enjoy the beautifully drawn scenery, although in contrast will have to go through the dark reality of Ari's life. Keep in mind your decisions matter.<br>
<br>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
CONTROLS<br/>
<br/>
Arrow keys to Move<br/>
<br/>
SPACE to Interact<br/>
<br/>
F4 for Full-screen<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
BUGS<br/>
<br/>
Sometimes when it's playing a video the screen will freeze, as of now all I can tell you to close and re-open the game when that happens.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
INSPIRATION<br/>
<br/>
This game is inspired by true crime cases and some of my own experiences in Korea, the dark side of Korea.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charrua Soccer - Mirror Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2726240/Charrua_Soccer__Mirror_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726240/extras/anim7.gif?t=1711210521"><br/>This is CHARRUA SOCCER!, with the same action and adrenaline that you already know from the Pro Edition, in this edition, you can face other players in Mirror Online matches!<br/>Mirror Online? yes! this is something new in football games… two simultaneous matches, one overall score! Control your local team and direct your remote team. The combined goals decide the winner!<br/><br/>A ranked game mode, in which while you directly control your local team, another version of your team, playing as the visitor, faces the opponent on the remote PC, following the strategy you define in advance. Both players will be aware of what happens in the remote match, even being able to view the replays of the best moments from each game.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726240/extras/anim2.gif?t=1711210521"><br/><br/>Create and lead your team to glory, competing in ranked mode or playing with friends.<br/>You can face your rivals alone or if you wish, you can even invite friends to play on the same team, a feature available by connecting locally or through Steam Remote Together.<h2 class="bb_tag">Mirror Online:</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726240/extras/Mirror_Online_Banner2.jpg?t=1711210521"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> An original mode- a new way to play and compete against remote opponents.<br/></li><li> Two Matches Simultaneously- Home and away games, with remote match event alerts!<br/></li><li> Control your home team- you face the rival team under the direction of your opponent.<br/></li><li> Manage your remote team- with your direction, your team will play against the rival.<br/></li><li> Evolve your team- by playing you will get XP to improve your stats.<br/></li><li> Ranked Leagues- start at the bottom and lead your team to compete among the best.<br/></li><li> Ranked Matches- find an opponent with similar skills to play mirror online.<br/></li><li> Friendly Matches- play Mirror Online matches against a friend.<br/></li><li> Cooperative Matches- invite your friends to join your team to face rivals. The connection of these friends can be local or through Remote Play Together. </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Store:</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726240/extras/anim12.gif?t=1711210521"><br/>Earn coins as you play to buy cool items in the store, like custom balls, flags, stadiums, and player cosmetics – think unique hairdos to dog costumes. The possibilities are endless!<h2 class="bb_tag">Link with the PRO Edition:</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726240/extras/ProEdition.jpg?t=1711210521"><br/>Those who already own or plan to purchase the Pro Edition will also benefit from accessing their thematic items, stadiums, balls, etc., in Mirror Edition as well.<br/>The Mirror and Pro versions are linked, the coins earned in both editions are unified, as are the items purchased in either store. That is, if you need coins for an item that you want to buy in the Mirror store, you can also collect coins by playing the various game modes available in the Pro edition.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726240/extras/anim4.gif?t=1711210521"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Intuitive yet challenging gameplay, perfect for all skill levels.<br/></li><li> Dual control modes cater to both casual and seasoned players.<br/></li><li> Customizable assistance – turn it on for help or off for a tougher challenge.<br/></li><li> Realistic soccer elements: fouls, cards, injuries, penalties.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726240/extras/anim6.gif?t=1711210521"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Options for women's, men's, and mixed teams.<br/></li><li> Variety of moves: passes, shots, and specialty skills like Chilean kicks.<br/></li><li> In-depth team management: formation, strategy, substitutions, and more.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726240/extras/anim10.gif?t=1711210521"><br/><br/><strong>The Mirror Edition promises endless entertainment!<br/>Are you prepared to challenge friends or fight for the title of ultimate champion?</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalypse Love Shelter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2782280/Apocalypse_Love_Shelter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a post-apocalyptic adventure/base building game with real actors. You take on the role of a military aficionada who, purely as a hobby, built an entire refugee safehouse. Who would’ve thought that an apocalypse would actually strike? Now, this simple shelter will survive as the first and final line of defense between you and the teeming swarms of zombies.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game features:</h2>·[Pregame: Prior to the apocalypse arriving, you use your personal cash to build up your shelter and perfect it.]<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782280/extras/07.gif?t=1711209709"><br/><br/>·[Arrival: Some people who knew of your hobbies, such as a friend, a coworker, or a neighbor all attempt to enter the shelter. You can choose whether to let them in or not.】<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782280/extras/08.gif?t=1711209709"><br/><br/>·[Shelter Management: Once you’ve built up a team, you need to decide on the best way to allocate food, water, and other resources.]<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782280/extras/09.gif?t=1711209709"><br/><br/>·[Poor Management: Your team will suffer both physically and mentally if you make poor choices – and they may even fall into the eternal slumber of night.】<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782280/extras/04.gif?t=1711209709"><br/><br/>·[Night Events: If you don’t have enough food, everyone’s condition will drastically deteriorate, resulting in all sorts of nighttime events.】<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782280/extras/05.gif?t=1711209709"><br/><br/>·[Affinity &amp; Sidequests: Set your gaze beyond the confines of your shelter. Certain decisions you make in the post-apocalyptic streets will also have a major impact. 】<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782280/extras/10.gif?t=1711209709"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINGULARIUM</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2624410/SINGULARIUM/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624410/extras/GIF1.gif?t=1711265941"><h2 class="bb_tag">Zoom through levels at mach speeds!</h2>At its very core, <strong><i>SINGULARIUM</i></strong> is a game about speed. It's a Fast-Paced 3D platformer, that has you using the various movement mechanics to their fullest, such as wallrunning, bunny hopping, and your ability to create black holes that pull you around, to try to beat each level with a fast time. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624410/extras/GIF2.gif?t=1711265941"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Black Hole Physics</strong> - moving while being pulled will allow you to curve around your black hole, adding a ton of complexity and enriching the movement system for those skilled enough to master it.<br/></li><li> <strong>Hardcore Gameplay</strong> - Quick reactions will be vital if you want to beat these levels while going at breakneck speeds!<br/></li><li> <strong>Tons of Levels</strong> - SINGUALRIUM has 20+ handcrafted levels, with more to come!<br/></li><li> <strong>Level Editor</strong> - Create and share your own custom levels!<br/></li><li> <strong>Complex Movement System</strong> - combining wallrunning, walljumping, swinging, and bunny hopping will allow you to zoom through the levels<br/></li><li> <strong>Builtin Level Timers</strong> - Compare your level times with your friends!</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624410/extras/GIF3.gif?t=1711265941"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number Shoot VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2826100/Number_Shoot_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2826100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Number Shoot VR is a gun shooting VR game that you destroy approaching targets and use the enhancements and weapons you gain to score more points.<br/>The six available weapons have different characteristics, and by using the right weapon you can destroy targets more efficiently.<br/><br/>Play time per session is 4 minutes! <br/>Destroy targets at all costs and aim for a high score!<h2 class="bb_tag">Destroy Targets!</h2>Shoot targets with your weapon anyway! Destroy as many targets as you can and aim for a high score!<br/>The choice of weapon enhancement is the key to a high score.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2826100/extras/確定3_小さい.png?t=1711195330"><h2 class="bb_tag">Destroy targets, enhance weapons!</h2>Enhancement system is introduced for weapons. Destroying a target will enhance the weapon.<br/>Your Weapon will be enhanced Depending on the color of the destroyed target.<br/>　(Red) Firepower<br/>　(Purple) Rate of fire<br/>　(Blue) Magazine ammunition number<br/>　(Green) accuracy.<h2 class="bb_tag">Wipe out targets with explosions!</h2>Explosive weapons or black targets (bombs) can collectively damage a target!<br/>but If you destroy a target with a lot of penalty targets ... around it...!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2826100/extras/確定10_小さい.png?t=1711195330"><h2 class="bb_tag">VRM avatar support!</h2>Unity-Chan VRM avatars are available by built-in!<br/>In addition, external VRM avatars can be loaded from a file!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2826100/extras/確定5.5_小さい.png?t=1711195330"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twizzle Puzzle: Monkeys</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2875920/Twizzle_Puzzle_Monkeys/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2875920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Twizzle Puzzle: Monkeys - is the perfect puzzle game for a fun and rewarding pastime.<br/>Your goal is to assemble a picture of cute monkeys that has been cut into an equal number of pieces.<br/>Rotate the pieces to create the full picture, but think logically about the connections and solve the puzzle. <br/>There are 50 levels to complete, and the challenge becomes increasingly difficult as you progress.<br/>Enjoy a relaxing time connecting the pieces to create a beautiful picture of monkeys<br/><br/>In Twizzle Puzzle: Monkeys:<br/><br/>•50 levels<br/>•Beautiful art<br/>•Simple controls (mouse)<br/>•Achievements<br/>•Relaxing music<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2875920/extras/3.png?t=1711180217"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2875920/extras/1.png?t=1711180217"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2875920/extras/2.png?t=1711180217"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2875920/extras/4.png?t=1711180217"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clean City Project</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2858820/Clean_City_Project/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2858820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Collect, shoot, destroy and collect again.<br>
This is a decontamination shooter game that you can play without worrying about time.<br>
<br>
An experimental city floating on the sea has suddenly turned purple due to a pollution accident.<br>
The player takes on the role of Lavilitta, a rabbit-shaped cleaning robot,<br>
Can you clean up the polluted city and restore the beautiful white city?<br>
<br>
The player has two objectives<br/>
<br/>
Fill all 8 purification facilities with scattered "energy gems".<br/>
To remove all pollution.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
To strengthen the player with the batteries found in each location,<br/>
and collect and remove them more efficiently!<br/>
<br/>
The Story<br/>
<br/>
A pollution accident has occurred in the experimental city of Alpha.<br/>
A large amount of dangerous purple pollutants have been generated and have covered the city.<br/>
All residents appear to have been safely evacuated.<br/>
In order to restore the city, it is necessary to recover the energy scattered throughout the city and fill all eight purification facilities.<br/>
However, the facilities have been shut down and the damage will only continue to grow.<br/>
To solve this problem, the cleaning robot "Lavilitta" was dispatched to remove the contaminants.<br/>
It is equipped with a vacuum cleaner with powerful suction and a special filter.<br/>
And it should be able to destroy contamination by sending energy bullets.<br/>
To reclaim the city, Lavilitta is going to work!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIN-C1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2610970/PRINC1/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An Endless runner with a twist! Play as a dog named <strong>PRIN-C1</strong> who can walk, trot and run but cannot stop. <br/><br/><strong>Go Slow. Go Fast. Speed is your choice</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610970/extras/1_Run.gif?t=1711308907"><br/><br/><strong>Switch views seamlessly</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610970/extras/2_Switch.gif?t=1711308907"><br/><br/><strong>Collect treats. If not.. steal them</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610970/extras/3_Treats.gif?t=1711308907"><br/><br/><strong>Smash them or get punched</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610970/extras/4_Punch.gif?t=1711308907"><br/><br/><strong>Unlock fun costumes by completing score challenges</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610970/extras/5_DressUp.gif?t=1711308907"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living With Sister: Monochrome Fantasy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2429860/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1711168850"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_1__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/>Living in a fantasy world, it's always been your dream to grow up to be a famous adventurer just like your father. Reality proves to be more boring than fiction, however, as your days are mostly spent doing odd jobs for the villagers. With your friends by your side, you enter the Tournament of the Eights and strive for something greater: the chance to become the top guild in the country. Will you realize your ambitions, or will your hopes slip through your fingers and doom you to a life of monochrome monotony?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_2__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/>As a member of your town's Adventurers' Guild, it's your job to protect the townsfolk. Go on hunts, kill dangerous beasts, and hone your abilities to better tackle whatever challenges tomorrow brings.<br/><br/>Once you get home from work, you'll have your sister to attend to. She's a very sickly girl who needs a lot of help. Manage your household finances well, build up your relationship with your sister, and who knows, perhaps you might even be able to solve the mystery behind her illness.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_3__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Big_Brother_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Little_Sister_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Kana_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Yui_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Kasumi_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Yukari_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Akatsuki_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_4__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><strong>Hand-Drawn Monochrome Art</strong><br/>Though it may lack color, this game's world is anything but colorless! The stunning black-and-white art is chock-full of personality and is sure to leave you with plenty of marvelous monochrome memories!<br/><br/><strong>Unique Combat System</strong><br/>With tons of bizarre and ferocious monsters to fight and dozens of unique skills to unlock, your adventures are sure to be full of challenge and excitement!<br/><br/><strong>Charming Characters</strong><br/>Build up your relationships with your guildmates and your sister to learn about what makes them tick and unlock character-specific abilities to further assist you in your quest to become the top guild in the country!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part of You</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1919270/Part_of_You/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1919270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Well shucks, you’ve lost your identity! It’s somewhere in Hacksaw Springs, and everything is pointing you toward the Lost and Found inside… a… Clown Convention?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1919270/extras/PuzzleBanner.png?t=1711164190"><h2 class="bb_tag">Tools</h2>In Part of You, you will have to use a variety of tools in order to solve problems around Hacksaw Springs. Some of the tools you’ll be using include:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>The Flipper:</strong>  The flipper will turn any facial feature upside down. Need somebody to look away? Turn their frown upside down? Make someone look a little goofy, generally speaking? The flipper is for you!<br/><br/></li><li> <strong>The Stamp:</strong> Ever needed someone to have a different person’s mouth? Eyes? … you have? Huh, that’s weird. With the stamp, you can clone facial features and put them onto other people! Want to make someone look like someone else? Make Millard Morawn a chad? Make a clone army? The stamp has you covered!<br/><br/></li><li><strong>The Mask:</strong> Missing your own identity? No problem – just steal someone else’s! Fraud isn’t real, and nobody will come after you. It may not be the best disguise, but… people love talking to familiar faces.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Googly Eyes:</strong> Have you ever taken a pair of googly eyes and put them on your eyelids, trying to balance them and pretend they’re your own eyes? Now you can forcibly stick them onto someone else’s eyes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Hacksaw Springs</h2><br/>Hacksaw Springs is usually a bit of a snoozefest – your average town, your average drama. Now that Funny Business is renting out the convention center for Clown Around 20XX, things have been pretty hectic! The Flea Market is as busy as ever, with new stalls popping up. The Parking Lot is filled with pop-up shops and protests. To top it all off, the incompetent town security is more preoccupied with googly eyes than A BOMB!<h2 class="bb_tag">Characters</h2>Over 100 unique characters fill the streets (and roofs?) of Hacksaw Springs. Help out the friendly townsfolk, and they might just help you in return! A dedicated employee of a three-years-defunct video store, a noseless mechanic in love with his goil, a tumbleweed with a warrant? All that and more as you rediscover who you are…<h2 class="bb_tag">Need a Little Funny HaHa?</h2>The more you play, the more characters you’ll gain access to! Have a field day making the funniest faces Hacksaw Springs has to offer!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1919270/extras/ClownGifDownsample.gif?t=1711164190"><h2 class="bb_tag">Finding your Identity</h2>Part of You is all about finding your identity, as well as us finding ours. This is a game about the absurdity of the world and the silliness we all face every morning when we look at ourselves in the mirror. Part of You and Hacksaw Springs welcomes you, no matter who you are… as long as you don’t have coulrophobia.</img></li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDACTED</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1958850/REDACTED/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1958850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							REDACTED is an action-packed zombie survival game with an emphasis on narrative, unique gameplay experiences, and atmosphere. Anything not nailed down can be used to your advantage as you survive against the zombie horde in this mysterious facility. Check out the merchant to stock up on supplies or buy new weapons. Survive for as long as you can against increasingly difficult waves of undead in survival mode. Try out onslaught mode if you want to test yourself against the ultimate challenge.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snip It!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2849870/Snip_It/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2849870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Snip It! is a line-drawing arcade puzzle game inspired by games like <i>Qix</i>. Your goal is to capture parts of the canvas by drawing shapes and avoiding the enemies. Complete all 25 levels to win!<br/><br/>Controls: WASD/arrow keys or click/touch to navigate &amp; move, ESC to pause, M to mute.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essence Bloom</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2846200/Essence_Bloom/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i>"I will show you a path to happiness."</i></strong><br/><br/>Essence Bloom is a linear story-focused Visual Novel that is centered around the MC (the player) living in a peaceful world where he spends time with friends:<br/><br/><strong>Hikari </strong>- Aka, "The Sunshine Girl," is always smiling and happy. In fact, she seems obsessed with it and wants everyone else to be as happy as she is.<br/><br/><strong>Yuna</strong> - She runs the coffee shop, is number one in her class, and still finds time to take care of her younger sister, Saeko. She's bossy and blunt, but she has a gentle heart deep down.<br/><br/><strong>Saeko</strong> - She is the opposite of her older sister, Yuna, in almost every way. She's clumsy, timid, and very reliant. She also seems confused most of the time and worries everyone, but she is well loved. <br/><br/><strong>Kagome</strong> - She's a well-disciplined martial arts champion who will defend anyone she cares about, no matter the sacrifice. She can also, surprisingly, be a bit bashful.<br/><br/>The friends spend their time in school studying, working at their local coffee shop, and doing fun activities. Everything is peaceful until things start to happen that threaten the serenity of this world...<br/><br/>Features: A story-rich experience with aesthetic visuals, energetic characters, and ~4 hours of dialogue. <br/><br/><strong>This game is meant for 18+ audiences. Some viewers may find the content disturbing or offensive.</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
