<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones: NWO Wars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2487350/Alex_Jones_NWO_Wars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Play the OFFICIAL Alex Jones video game! Save the world from the evil globalists’ plot to turn everyone into bug-eating pod-dwelling libtards! STAY TUNED FOR FUTURE BONUS LEVELS AND CHARACTERS.<br/><br/><strong>Classic Run-and-Gun Gameplay</strong>: Enjoy fast-paced action, intricate animations, and detailed environments as you blast your way through waves of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>Unique Levels</strong>: Battle in various environments like secret underground bases, globalist conferences, and mind control facilities, all inspired by real events. Stay tuned for future levels.<br/><br/><strong>Challenging Boss Fights</strong>: Face off against the elite henchmen of the New World Order, including lizard overlords, secret society leaders, and genetically modified creatures.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Voice Lines</strong>: Featuring iconic and often humorous catchphrases from Alex Jones himself, adding flavor to every combat scenario. Special guest vocals by Ryan Katsu Rivera.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_06.png?t=1704338043"><h2 class="bb_tag">JOIN ALEX AND HIS ALLIES </h2><br/>Every day the deep state sues, lies, defames, and KILLS law-abiding patriots who threaten their power!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_05.png?t=1704338043"><h2 class="bb_tag">DEFEAT BIG TECH CUCKS and MORE</h2><br/>And other anti-American communist bosses throughout this adrenaline-inducing adventure!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_04.png?t=1704338043"><h2 class="bb_tag">PLAY AS ALEX!</h2><br/>For the first time in history, experience the world through Infowars leader Alex Jones’ eyes and see the WAR he fights!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/new_screenshot_03.jpg?t=1704338043"><h2 class="bb_tag">SAVE THE BABIES</h2><br/>It’s no secret the NWO REPTILES are after our children. Play NWO Wars now to help save these innocent victims from these MONSTERS!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_02.png?t=1704338043"><br/><br/>“They’re turning the friggin frogs gay!”<br/><br/>Only Alex Jones can stop this madness and restore balance in the Brain Force!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_01.png?t=1704338043"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milo and the Christmas Gift</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2716140/Milo_and_the_Christmas_Gift/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							After his adventure in Milo and the Magpies, Milo is looking forward to spending a cosy Christmas at home. But a Christmas gift is about to upset his holiday celebrations, especially when said gift disappears after a little misunderstanding! Can you help Milo bring home the lost Gift and save Christmas for Marleen… and himself?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_playing_1.gif?t=1703496663"> <br/><br/>Milo and the Christmas Gift is a free-to-play short and atmospheric point-and-click adventure game created by artist Johan Scherft. The game is a spin-off story following the events in Milo and the Magpies. The game has 5 chapters and a gameplay time of around 30 minutes!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/>■ Relaxing yet stimulating game-play<br/>Join Milo in his home and revisit some of the neighbouring gardens, but this time in a wintery Christmas wonderland! Interact with the festive environment and solve small point-and-click / hidden-object puzzles.<br/><br/>■ Captivating artistic atmosphere<br/>Each hand-painted, interior and snowy garden Milo has to search through has its unique personality, reflecting that of Milo’s owners and next-door neighbours respectively.<br/><br/>■ Atmospheric soundtrack<br/>Each chapter has its own festive theme song composed by Victor Butzelaar.<br/><br/>■ Average playtime: 15-30 minutes<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_snow_1.gif?t=1703496663"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few Nights More: Genesis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713070/Few_Nights_More_Genesis/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Please note: This is a free prologue and it includes act 1, and only 1 playable character and blood school is playable, The maximum heritage gained is limited to 50, and the maximum difficulty can be set to 2. As well only one castle will be available. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Blood3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Conquer castles and claim your birthright!</strong><br/> <br/>The fight to reclaim your place in this world begins. Rebuild lost ruins, make them stronger and defend them against your enemies. After you regain your strength, move on to conquer more territories and eventually claim your birthright.<br/><br/>Few Nights More offers the unique fusing of castle management and turn based rogue-like combat. Fight against humanity, the undisputed masters of this world in your absence. Choose between eight different Vampire Lords, each with their own ambition and history. Find your trinkets, skills and perks along your way. Design your very own castle by placing the right rooms, adding decors that directly contribute to your army and your Vampire Lord. Conquer more castles so your influence and power grow, until you claim your birthright.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Ferocity3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Core Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Design your castle by adding new Rooms, Traps and Minions. Stack up on some buffs with shiny decors to get ready for the invasion screen to defend it to the end of every night!<br/> <br/></li><li> Choose among 7 different Vampire Lords with unique History, Gameplay and Abilities.<br/> <br/></li><li> Master 1 out of 3 Disciplines each time you play, each with 60 unique skills.<br/> <br/></li><li> Acquire new random skills, perks and trinkets to survive the nights.<br/> <br/></li><li> Excel in either being a Prestigious Vampire, a Seductive one, or master a Terrifying presence against your enemies.<br/><br/></li><li> Test the builds you made against a variety of Hunters, Veterans and Unique Bosses in an action packed turn based combat system.<br/> <br/></li><li> Endure three acts across 12 difficulty levels, striving to survive and progress. Accumulate Heritage Points to enhance your lord's starting stats, skills, and unlock new castles and talents unique to each lord.<br/><br/></li><li> Engage in the boundless challenge of Infinity Mode, where you can continuously test your limits without relying on a castle. Each night, you will be presented with three options to advance, growing stronger as you push yourself to see how far you can go.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703868247"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1704314908"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1704314908"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1704314908"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1704314908"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1704314908"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WITCH ON THE HOLY NIGHT</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2052410/WITCH_ON_THE_HOLY_NIGHT/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2052410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2052410/extras/WITCH_ON_THE_HOLY_NIGHT_About_this_game.gif?t=1703737843"><br/><strong>Product Description</strong><br/>TYPE-MOON, known for the wildly popular mobile game "Fate/Grand Order" and the epic visual novel "Tsukihime," is releasing a remaster of the 2012 hit "Witch on the Holy Night. Experience a coming of age story set in the vibrant, bustling 1980s, which follows an innocent young man and two young "witches." Updates added since the original release include long-awaited fully voiced characters as well as visuals remastered in full HD, bringing the experience to life with unparalleled quality and fidelity. Masterful manipulation of visual elements imbues combat scenes with nail-biting tension, but also breathes life into the characters' everyday activities. Animated graphical elements bring an entirely new level of depth to the reading experience as well!<br/><br/><strong>STORY</strong><br/>In the mansion on the hill, there lived two witches...<br/><br/>It is the late 1980s—the twilight of an era of beauty and vigor.<br/>A boy moves to the city, barely missing two witches living in modern times.<br/><br/>The boy leads a completely ordinary life.<br/>She carries herself with gallant pride.<br/>The girl lives a sleepy, hidden life.<br/><br/>Each walks a starlit path.<br/>One would never expect their paths to cross.<br/>The story of how these three disparate people came together is soon to be told.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1703493452"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1703493452"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1703186631"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1703318086"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1703318086"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1702747783"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobalt Core</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2179850/Cobalt_Core/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_1.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>Cobalt Core is a sci-fi roguelike deckbuilder with a unique single-axis combat system that will throw you for a loop. Many loops! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_2.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>Give orders to your crew by playing cards: Will you <strong>raise shields</strong> to protect your ship, <strong>dodge</strong> incoming missiles and cannon fire to avoid damage outright, or <strong>strike</strong> preemptively to disable your enemy’s weapons? Outmaneuver your foes to stay just ahead of impending calamity, and reach the Cobalt Core!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/characters.png?t=1703278835"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fresh new spin on tactics –</strong>  dodge attacks and target weak points in this unique single-axis take on tactics combat. Outwit the enemy in a high stakes game of cat and mouse!<br/></li><li><strong>Customize your deck –</strong> hundreds of cards and split upgrade paths means no two runs will be the same. Find that perfect combo that brings your deck from powerful to overpowered.<br/></li><li><strong>Get to know your crew –</strong> each character comes with a completely unique playstyle and their own personal story. Bring 3 along, mix and match their decks, and see how these little goobers get along with each other.<br/></li><li><strong>Tons of replayability –</strong>  hundreds of different character+ship combinations before you even hit “start run”. Crank up the difficulty and really test your skills!<br/></li><li><strong>Get in the groove –</strong> featuring 90+ minutes of catchy and electrifying original music by <i>Minecraft</i> composer Aaron Cherof!<br/></li><li><strong>Forward momentum –</strong> untangle a narrative and unlock more playstyles as you go. Is there any escape from this time loop?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/grandma_cookies.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>By the makers of <i>Sunshine Heavy Industries</i>, recipient of IGF's <strong>Honorable Mention for Excellence in Design 2022</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658820/Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							10 possible fruits and one goal, reach the Watermelon.<br/>Your job is to combine matching fruits to evolve them to the next one and eventually reach the coveted Watermelon.<br/>To help you, you have 3 different abilities at your disposal. But watch out, using these will cost you some of your points. Be smart about when you use them to get the highest score!<h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLAYER</h2>Measure your fruit skills against another player.<h2 class="bb_tag">GET THE WATERMELON</h2>How many Watermelons can you combine before your basket overflows?<h2 class="bb_tag">USE YOUR ABILITIES</h2>Power, level up and destroy — These abilities will help you reach the Watermelon, using any of those will also allow you to angle your aim.<h2 class="bb_tag">GOLDEN FRUIT</h2>If luck is on your side, you might even see the mysterious Golden Fruit. Find it and witness its effect firsthand.<h2 class="bb_tag">STATISTICS</h2>Track your progress with in-depth statistics. Visit the menu to see the number of fruits you've combined, your ability usage, and much more.<h2 class="bb_tag"></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.codecks.io%2Fwatermelon-game" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/extras/Roadmap_Banner.png?t=1702238677"/></a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EA SPORTS™ WRC</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1849250/EA_SPORTS_WRC/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1849250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build the car of your dreams in our biggest rally game ever, EA SPORTS™ WRC, the all-new official videogame of the FIA World Rally Championship, the first developed by the award-winning team behind the DiRT Rally series.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1849250/extras/WCR_GameFeatures_PostLaunch.jpg?t=1702998175"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For The King II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1676840/For_The_King_II/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/header_alt_assets_7.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_AboutThisGame_Steam_StoreBanner_2_EN.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Once beloved by her people, Queen Rosomon has turned against her subjects, casting them into servitude in the darkness of Fahrul’s mines whilst building alliances with sinister and malevolent forces.<br/><br/>Gather your party in four player co-op or adventure alone through Fahrul as you risk everything to fight the tyrannical queen and bring an end to her oppressive reign.<br/><br/>From the creators of For The King, the much-loved RPG that blends roguelite and tabletop gameplay comes a new chapter in Fahrul’s history, designed on an updated engine bringing innovation and gameplay refinement for returning heroes and new adventurers alike.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading01_Inspired_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>For The King II is easy for anyone to pick up and play, but takes skill, patience, and strategic excellence to master whilst remaining infinitely replayable with a procedurally generated map that ensures no two playthroughs will ever be the same. Unique yet familiar dice roll inspired movement, encounter and combat mechanics add even more spontaneity and variety as your fortunes rise and fall on the roll of the dice.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF01_InspiredByTabletop.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading02_Digestible2_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>For The King II provides a complete campaign with over 30 hours of gameplay, split into 5 separate adventures, each narratively linked. The journey is long and the path is treacherous but fear not, if your party fails you will start stronger and wiser on your next playthrough with better starting items to draft into your loadout.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF02_RogueliteCampaign.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading03_Muster_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Create your party from 12 unique character classes, each with their own unique perks, strengths and playstyles. From the heavy-handed hitter of The Blacksmith, to the wily potion-wielding Alchemist, you choose which characters will take on the fearsome Queensguard and the combat strategies that will ensure success. Introduce new characters to your party with mercenaries and companions that enable you to pluck wild beasts from the forest floor and recruit ruthless mercenaries from local taverns (for a price of course) to bolster your ranks in times of trouble.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF03_MusterYouMight_.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading04_Party_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Traverse Fahrul solo or with up-to three friends in four-player co-op. As a solo player you can control all characters in your party, giving you complete ownership of the campaign map and combat strategy whilst in four-player co-op you must coordinate and negotiate with your party members. Play online multiplayer with your friends controlling your own character(s) or play offline co-op on the same PC. Offline co-op supports multiple controllers; each controller will have input control on everyone’s turn.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF04_PartyofFour.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading05_Evolved_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Inspired by turn-based classics, For The King II adds strategic depth to much-loved combat mechanics with the new Battle Grid, where movement and position provide you and your enemies with strategic buffs and penalties. Defend the back row by equipping a mighty Tower Shield, push enemies into lethal pools of burning fire, or entangle melee troops with dark magic cast with weapons looted from vanquished foes. The choice is yours!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF05_EvolveTurnBased.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading06_Explore_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Fahrul is both beautiful and deadly in equal measure. On your journey you will encounter a wealth of diverse biome environments brought to life in a breathtaking art style. From lush forests, toxic swamps and lava-filled wastelands to pirate (no scratch that!) Merling-infested tropical seas, For The King II transports you deep into the wonders of Fahrul, leading you further than ever before into this stunningly-imagined land of adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF06_ExploreFantastical.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Ffortheking" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTK_Discord_Banner_EN.gif?t=1703284946"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>真三国割草 DynastyKick</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2516310/_DynastyKick/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a 2D survival challenge game, with a story background originating from the Three Kingdoms period in ancient China. During the game, players need to fight independently to eliminate a large influx of monsters. Every 3 to 5 minutes, a boss level monster guarding the level will appear in the game. In the game, players can upgrade and choose appropriate skills to improve their spells and abilities.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weapons Party</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2421290/Weapons_Party/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2421290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Play Weapon Party for Free !<br>
<br>
Gameplay:<br>
-  Create a team or play solo. Participating in the match, players start with their fists. During each certain period of time, the weapon will drop on the map. Players pick up weapons to enhance their character's skills/stats. Each weapon will have a unique index and skill system. Take advantage of it to win.<br>
- Players can buy clothes and hair from the rewards received after each match.<br>
- Win more to increase your rank, compete with other players.<br>
<br/>
Form your team, join the fight. Welcome to "our Party"!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceBoots</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2104390/SpaceBoots/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2104390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							SpaceBoots is a 2D zero gravity shooter.  Players battle each other using a variety of weapons while moving around the arena.  Each player's boots are equipped with a magnet, which can be used to attach to walls and other surfaces, and a thruster for more subtle trajectory adjustments. Fast paced gameplay, customizable weapon selection, and quick local join make this an ideal party game, supporting as many players as you have controllers!<br>
<br>
Several game modes are available:<br>
 - Classic "Deathmatch", where players compete to rack up the most kills to achieve victory.<br>
 - "King of the hill", where players try to remain in a target area for as long as possible, while keeping other players out.<br>
 - "Diamond Hands", where players must capture an artifact and hold onto it as long as possible.<br>
 - "Spaceball", where players attempt to push or shoot the ball into their goal.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton Rebellion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2724130/Skeleton_Rebellion/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ascend the nine levels of the tower in your quest to overthrow the Archmages and create a better society for your fellow undead (and everyone else).<br>
<br>
Recruit a large group of three revolutionaries and equip them with different combinations of Magical Items to cast some of the 62 unique Spells back at the Mages who cast them.<br>
<br>
Disturb the productive working environment with your rebellious presence.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUCKCATCHERS2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2700970/LUCKCATCHERS2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Massive, multiplayer, online, role-playing game in an open world. After choosing a character, go on an adventure. Mine and manufacture resources. Produce materials, engines, weapons and ammo. <br/>Explore the world on airships and aircraft. To move quickly, use the strekolets or jump through the Gate. Live in the cities of the world or build your own settlement.<br/>Open up new possibilities by developing your character's skills. The fate of the world is in your hands!<br/><br/>Many years ago, the Guardians left the world of the Edge of the Inside Out, leaving behind grains of magic, rare objects, and artifacts. The Bastions continue to control the territories. Flocks of dragons burn caravans and settlements caught on their path of fiery migration. The Outcasts seize border towns, shaking the fragile truce between the Empire and the Union. Minions are searching for particles of the Inside Out, bringing the world closer to the apocalypse.<br/><br/><strong>Character</strong><br/>The race you choose affects where you first appear in one of the capitals. Opportunities increase by learning skills.<br/><strong>Travel</strong><br/>Travel only by air using ships, airships, or strekolets. The world is open and without restriction. Instant travel from one point of the world to another is available through the Gate if you have purchased a Sapphire.<br/><strong>Open World</strong><br/>The area of the world is 1,000,000 square kilometers. The world is divided into two continents, several islands and archipelagos. The Navigator will show you the world at a glance.<br/>Each race (faction) has two capitals, located on different parts of the map.<br/><strong>Cities and Settlements</strong><br/>Cities are located along the caravan routes, offering protection, production facilities, and storage for your property. Access to cities directly depends on a character’s reputation.<br/>By purchasing a license, a character can build their own settlement in any vacant and designated place. A settlement differs from a city by providing more opportunities. <br/>Each floating island has a city with unique capabilities. There are cities that sell rare magical items and upgrades.<br/><strong>Aircraft</strong><br/>There are dozens of ships and airships in the game world. They differ in class and characteristics. Yachts are heavy transporters with a large hold capacity. They are distinguished by their speed and maneuverability. Warships with many weapons.<br/>Strekolets can be used for reconnaissance, fast movement, bombing, or a surprise missile and torpedo strike on a target.<br/><strong>Guilds</strong><br/>It isn’t just  player characters that can join guilds, but also NPC. Prominent representatives of NPC guilds: Merchants, Outcasts, Demon Minions, Dragon Flocks.<br/><strong>Events</strong><br/>A bastion is a monumental complex with regeneration capabilities. Each bastion controls one of the world’s territories. A bastion generates rare items and collects taxes from all mined resources in the territory into its warehouse. <br/>Big races are mass start races with no restrictions on the type and modification of strekolets.The use of magic and weapons is allowed.<br/>Bounty hunters destroy the property of outlaw captains for a reward.<br/>War is a battle between the fleets of the border cities.<br/>Migration- four times a year the world comes to a standstill. Thousands of dragons leave their nests to search for better places. During this time, dragons will fly right into your path.<br/>Lottery 6 out of 36 - a chance to hit the jackpot. <br/>Seasonally planned events and activities.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GTH 3033 - Grand Theft Hunter 3033</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2703270/GTH_3033__Grand_Theft_Hunter_3033/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Top down shooter game. About a robot monster hunter.<br>
<br>
Distant future, 3033. There have already been several ends of the world on earth, after which robots and other forms of life live on earth.<br>
<br>
You will play as a robot monster hunter. You can ride motorcycles, cars. Shoot from a machine gun, shotgun, and also chop enemies with a sword.<br>
Your task is to carry out tasks to clear the territories of  robots.<br>
<br>
You can control it using a WASD keyboard and mouse.<br/>
<br/>
The game has achievements and leaderboards.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climb Challenge - Find Items Cyberpunk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2703280/Climb_Challenge__Find_Items_Cyberpunk/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Hidden-object adventure game.<br>
The player needs to run around the location and look for objects in secret places, climbing into them along walls and ledges.<br>
<br>
The player controls the girl using the Wasd keys and the mouse. And jumps around the location.<br>
<br>
When falling from a height, the player's health will be taken away; when it runs out, the player will die and will have to start the passage again.<br>
The game has achievements and a leaderboard.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones: NWO Wars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2487350/Alex_Jones_NWO_Wars/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Play the OFFICIAL Alex Jones video game! Save the world from the evil globalists’ plot to turn everyone into bug-eating pod-dwelling libtards! STAY TUNED FOR FUTURE BONUS LEVELS AND CHARACTERS.<br/><br/><strong>Classic Run-and-Gun Gameplay</strong>: Enjoy fast-paced action, intricate animations, and detailed environments as you blast your way through waves of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>Unique Levels</strong>: Battle in various environments like secret underground bases, globalist conferences, and mind control facilities, all inspired by real events. Stay tuned for future levels.<br/><br/><strong>Challenging Boss Fights</strong>: Face off against the elite henchmen of the New World Order, including lizard overlords, secret society leaders, and genetically modified creatures.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Voice Lines</strong>: Featuring iconic and often humorous catchphrases from Alex Jones himself, adding flavor to every combat scenario. Special guest vocals by Ryan Katsu Rivera.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_06.png?t=1704338043"><h2 class="bb_tag">JOIN ALEX AND HIS ALLIES </h2><br/>Every day the deep state sues, lies, defames, and KILLS law-abiding patriots who threaten their power!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_05.png?t=1704338043"><h2 class="bb_tag">DEFEAT BIG TECH CUCKS and MORE</h2><br/>And other anti-American communist bosses throughout this adrenaline-inducing adventure!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_04.png?t=1704338043"><h2 class="bb_tag">PLAY AS ALEX!</h2><br/>For the first time in history, experience the world through Infowars leader Alex Jones’ eyes and see the WAR he fights!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/new_screenshot_03.jpg?t=1704338043"><h2 class="bb_tag">SAVE THE BABIES</h2><br/>It’s no secret the NWO REPTILES are after our children. Play NWO Wars now to help save these innocent victims from these MONSTERS!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_02.png?t=1704338043"><br/><br/>“They’re turning the friggin frogs gay!”<br/><br/>Only Alex Jones can stop this madness and restore balance in the Brain Force!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_01.png?t=1704338043"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tale of BaGua</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2611590/Tale_of_BaGua/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2611590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2611590/extras/USCGames_AboutThisGame.png?t=1704307703"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2611590/extras/gif_0.gif?t=1704307703"><br/>Tale of BaGua takes players on an extraordinary journey through time and space, enveloping them in a mesmerizing puzzle adventure. As a Chinese teenager on a journey to uncover his family's secrets, you'll wield the mystical power of the BaGua mirrors to travel back in time to the same location, delving into an enigmatic world filled with puzzles, mysteries, and the allure of forgotten lineage. This indie-developed, non-euclidean top-down puzzle game invites you to embark on an emotional odyssey where your decisions shape a compelling story of heritage, sacrifice, and self-discovery.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2611590/extras/USCGames_GameplayFeatures.png?t=1704307703"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2611590/extras/gif_2.gif?t=1704307703"><br/><br/><strong> Time and Space Manipulation</strong><br/>Utilize the unique power of the BaGua mirrors to transcend conventional time and space, solving intricate puzzles and unraveling hidden secrets.<br/><br/><strong>Non-Euclidean Puzzle Solving</strong><br/>Engage with mind-bending puzzles set in non-euclidean spaces, challenging your intellect and creativity as you navigate through complex, interdimensional mazes.<br/><br/><strong>Low-Poly, Minimalistic Art Style</strong><br/>Experience the captivating world of Tale of Bagua through a visually stunning low-poly, minimalistic art style that enhances the game's atmosphere and emphasizes the purity of the storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2611590/extras/USCGames_AboutDevelopment.png?t=1704307703"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2611590/extras/gif_1.gif?t=1704307703"><br/>Tale of Bagua is a labor of love crafted by a dedicated indie development team Offseason Studio, passionate about creating unique and engaging gaming experiences. The non-euclidean gameplay mechanics were meticulously designed to challenge players while keeping them engrossed in the storyline. Every aspect of Tale of Bagua was carefully curated to ensure players embark on an unforgettable adventure, exploring the depths of one's family history, the complexities of time, and the boundless dimensions of human emotions.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving Home(icide)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2720210/Driving_Homeicide/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2720210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Driving Home<i>(icide)</i></strong> is a humorous single-player driving experience as you, the self-driving AI, must deliver your increasingly inebriated and distracting owner for their night on the town.  Complete the story mode (~30min) or endless driving mode, as you survive hilariously annoying distractions, test your reflexes as you dodge through traffic for high scores, and laugh at the hundreds of randomized voice-over lines as your owner jokes, muses, and rambles to you between destinations.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beer Run</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2736910/Beer_Run/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Beer Run is an Indie game created to steal beers from supermarkets. Three guys with a plan to steal more beer after running out, they go into multiple grocery stores to rob beer. Security guards are the enemy while the characters intend to rob from a store. As you progress throughout the game, each level gets harder by improving their security system. Multiple security guards in certain levels that make it tough to steal without being caught. As you collect more beers the character starts to slow down from all the weight being carried, creating another challenge besides evading the security. <br>
<br>
Features include - <br>
Limited carrying supply<br>
Slowed down speed when carrying beers.<br>
Can drop beers to gain speed.<br>
3-star reward system<br/>
Story<br/>
3 different characters						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underground secret</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2747090/Underground_secret/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2747090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a strategy game with a cartoon style square grid that looks very fresh and cute, and the exciting background music is exhilarating. On a limited map, this is a strategic battle, where you need to compete with others for resources and use your skills reasonably in this game. On the one hand, use white balls to attract enemies to gather, and on the other hand, choose the appropriate time to summon your big move - throw a huge bomb at the enemy and knock them down. In this game, you can see a variety of scene designs, as well as different challenges and obstacles, allowing you to continuously experience excitement and fun.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Niels Penguin Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2348380/Niels_Penguin_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2348380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Get ready for an exciting adventure with Nils, the adorable penguin, in a world where friendship and courage unite! In our new game on Steam, you'll meet our main hero, Niels, who decides to become a true hero when his beloved Lisa is kidnapped by the wicked Professor Travis.<br>
<br>
🏔️ Embark on a captivating journey through mysterious locations and incredible worlds filled with secrets and puzzles.<br>
<br>
🦚 Along the way, you'll encounter a variety of interesting characters ready to assist Nils on his mission to save Lisa.<br>
<br>
🔧 Collect various tools and upgrades to defeat enemies and solve puzzles on your path.<br>
<br/>
🏆 Defeat the evil Professor Travis and reclaim Lisa to complete this thrilling adventure.<br/>
<br/>
Grab your controller and get ready for an exciting adventure with Niels. Incredible adventures, captivating puzzles, and an engaging storyline await you. Don't miss the opportunity to play this unique adventure platformer on Steam and save Lisa alongside Niels!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mooselutions</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287140/Mooselutions/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Immerse yourself in a relaxing puzzle adventure set in a forest full of pesky moose who anger easily. You play a lost lumberjack who is a frequent target of angry moose charges and general "shenanigans".<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287140/extras/PlayerTrampled.gif?t=1704292585"><br/><br/>This isn't like real life where you can just move the moose crossing sign to get the moose to leave you alone.<br/><br/>You must navigate your way around the moose (meese?), anger them, and get them to charge where you want them to go. While you're at it, have them charge into other moose and see what happens.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287140/extras/MooseRotate.gif?t=1704292585"><br/><br/>You can hide behind trees and push blocks in front of the moose to stealthily sneak past. You can even load the moose onto rail carts to push them around. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287140/extras/MooseCartLarge.gif?t=1704292585"><br/><br/>Whatever you do, don't get TRAMPLED. The moose aren't mean-spirited. They just don't like you. Mooselutions is a turn-based Sokoban style game, so you get one turn to get away from the moose after you anger them. Don't run into the path of an angry moose!<br/><br/>There are forty nine hand-crafted moose puzzles designed to test your skills, and different areas unlock as you progress. Earn achievements for manipulating the moose to your whims and for being the target of their peskiness.<br/><br/>Who would have thought such simple moose-related rules could lead to so many deep moose puzzles? This is what the moose call psychological pestering.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Stand Delivery</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2585110/Last_Stand_Delivery/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585110/extras/参院指南_EN.png?t=1704293061"><br/>The sanatorium detained rich kinds of patients from Crutched Swordsman to Slime that Sword Stuck in Back.<br/>Even with severe injuries, everyone is still full of passion and wants to continue fighting for their faction. They firmly believe that the only way to Valhalla is to fight to the death.<br/>But you, as an Executor in the sanatorium, should follow their wishes to fight for lost honour by pushing.<br/>Send patients love, wish them well, and mind your own business.————Send them to Valhalla.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585110/extras/商店预览扁平动画预览.gif?t=1704293061"><br/>By the way, the sanatorium now is being overbooked, so it is necessary to send them out.  Help more, do more, earn more. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585110/extras/员工守则_EN.png?t=1704293061"><br/>丨✔️丨Push units from different factions together to make them fight. They won't attack you, only hostile faction units.<br/>丨✔️丨Clear all living creatures on the screen to complete this level (of course, you don't have to die yourself).<br/>丨✔️丨Push equipment onto creatures to strengthen them, gain higher abilities, and then go... die in battle.<br/>丨✔️丨Use conveyors, buttons, and other mechanisms to solve puzzles and find out true.<br/>丨✔️丨 Some extraordinary unknown things wait for you, unlocked with fewer steps.<br/>丨✔️丨Go take a milk and come back to enjoy this game.<br/>丨✔️丨Every chapter comes with stunning visuals, and every level is packed with a barrel of laughs.<br/>丨✔️丨Undo, undo, undo! We now have an unlimited undo button!<br/>丨✔️丨The 'Redo' button is ready to work ! Now, you can press 'Y' to 'Redo' your 'Undo'.<br/><br/>丨❌丨Leaving any units of any faction on the level, They will languish in sorrow, unable to enter Valhalla and eventually perish!<br/>丨❌丨Killing them yourself: You're a staff member, not a murderer! (Mainly, we didn't develop this feature)<br/>丨❌丨Investigating who made them so passionate: Trust me, some things are better left unknown...<br/><br/><br/>It is amazing that someone took the time to read the entire description.<br/> We've prepared a little flower for you here! Thanks for reading!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585110/extras/A_Flower_2.png?t=1704293061"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>runner</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2700470/runner/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"> This is a motion capture game with a focus on parkour. <strong> The player's computer needs to be equipped with a camera </strong> to better experience the game. </h2>           After starting the game, the camera will capture the movements of the human body in real time. Based on the player's body movements, the characters in the game will respond, such as jumping, rolling down, and moving left and right.<br/>          This game belongs to the sports and leisure category, and you don't need to purchase expensive sensory hardware devices to experience the fun of motion capture games at home.<br/>Suggestion:<br/>1. Play in a well lit space so that the camera can accurately capture your movements.<br/>2. The camera is placed in the middle of the game space and adjusted to allow the whole body to capture the image.<br/>3. A computer with a large screen display provides a better gaming experience.<br/>4. If the computer screen is too small, you can connect to a large screen TV for gaming through HDMI.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vent Vipers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2724630/Vent_Vipers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------<br/>Commence your thrilling serpentine journey through atmospheric mazes, where each apple brings you closer to the top of the leader board. Beware of the twisting hallways, and make sure not to wrap around yourself and meet an untimely demise. With each collected apple, you slither closer to unlocking new maps and skins, adding a personalized touch to your adventure. Can you outsmart the mazes and claim the top spot? Dive in now and find out!<br/>----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724630/extras/VVPromoImg1.png?t=1704283172"><br/><br/>----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------<br/>Navigate escalating challenges with each map, where complexity deepens with elements like moving walls and magical portals.<br/>----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724630/extras/VVPromoImg2.png?t=1704283172"><br/><br/>----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------<br/>Compete against friends and players worldwide as you strive for the top spot on the leader board. Unleash your strategic prowess to navigate the ever-intensifying mazes, collecting apples and unlocking unique skins and maps. Are you ready for the ultimate challenge in this 3D serpent showdown?<br/>----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724630/extras/VVPromoImg3.png?t=1704283172"><br/><br/>----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TriviaQuest: Mythic Conquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2737620/TriviaQuest_Mythic_Conquest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2737620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an epic journey with TriviaQuest: Mythic Conquest<br>
Test your wit and battle mythical monsters as you progress through challenging levels.<br>
<br>
Answer true or false to conquer foes, level up, and prove your knowledge in this thrilling adventure. Immerse yourself in a mythical world of trivia challenges, where each question propels you closer to victory. <br>
<br>
Explore the depths of your knowledge and embark on a Mythic Conquest like never before<br>
<br/>
Are you ready for the ultimate conquest of wit and wisdom?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient Warriors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2745680/Ancient_Warriors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745680/extras/Follow.gif?t=1704281151"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745680/extras/gif1.gif?t=1704281151"><br/><strong>Ancient Warriors</strong> -  is an immersive defense game set in a world of ancient magic. Summon unique warriors, strategically deploy traps, and utilize a powerful arsenal to repel waves of diverse enemies. Face epic bosses, adapt your strategy dynamically, and upgrade your defenders to become the legendary savior of the kingdom. Quick thinking and strategic prowess are essential to emerge victorious against the encroaching forces of darkness!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745680/extras/gif2.gif?t=1704281151"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Diverse Warrior Summons: Call forth a variety of mighty warriors, each with unique abilities, to defend your kingdom against the relentless forces of evil.<br/></li><li>Strategic Trap Placement: Strategically place traps on the battlefield to impede and slow down approaching enemies. From underground spikes to explosive bombs, choose the right traps to outsmart your foes.<br/></li><li>Dynamic Enemy Variety: Confront a range of enemy types, each with distinct attack patterns and abilities. Adapt your strategy on the fly to counter diverse challenges, including powerful bosses that test your tactical skills.<br/></li><li>Powerful Arsenal: Wield a potent arsenal, including underground spikes, explosive bombs, and formidable cannons. Choose the right combination of weapons to effectively repel the advancing hordes.<br/></li><li>Heroic Upgrades: Earn experience and resources from successful battles to upgrade your warriors, unlock new traps, and enhance your overall defensive capabilities. Become the kingdom's legendary savior by continuously improving and adapting to the evolving threats.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745680/extras/gif3.gif?t=1704281151"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My evil clones</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743870/My_evil_clones/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							My evil clones is an exhilarating shooter-puzzle game where players find themselves up against aggressive clones that have spiraled out of control. Armed with laser weapons, players navigate through puzzle-like levels, relying on agility and strategic thinking to survive. Encounter various enemy types employing different attacks, requiring players to showcase nimbleness and tactical prowess. The goal is to triumph over these unruly clones, preventing a global calamity.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic Puzzle-Shooter Gameplay: Engage in fast-paced puzzle-shooting action as you navigate through levels filled with aggressive clones. Use your agility and strategic thinking to overcome challenges.<br/></li><li>Varied Enemy Types: Face a diverse range of enemies, each with unique attack patterns. Some may close in for melee attacks, while others unleash long-range gunfire or attempt grenade assaults. Stay on your toes to adapt to different threats.<br/></li><li>Strategic Cover System: Utilize the environment strategically, taking cover from enemy fire and planning your moves wisely. Navigate through mazes, finding optimal positions to defend against various attacks and gain the upper hand.<br/></li><li>Unique Boss Battles: Confront powerful clone bosses with distinct abilities and formidable weapons. Each boss battle presents a unique challenge, testing your skills and requiring adaptive strategies for victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paws Trail</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2726930/Paws_Trail/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Game Description: </strong><br/>In this original adventure game, featuring a charming black cat as the protagonist, players will explore a beautiful forest, uncovering hidden secrets and unlocking mysterious doors. This game combines enchanting storytelling with gameplay that allows players to meet forest friends, and embark on new journeys with the cat.<br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/>1. Enchanting Storyline: Follow the black cat on a mystical journey through the forest, meeting friends along the way.<br/>2. Beautiful Graphics: A fantastical world filled with rich colors, lush forests, and vivid characters.<br/>3. Meet Forest Friends: Interact with various animal friends in the forest to unlock new stories and puzzles.<br/>4. Exploration and Discovery: Uncover hidden secrets as you explore every corner of the forest.<br/><br/><strong>Why It's the Perfect Choice for Players: </strong><br/>"Paws Trail" is suitable for all ages, with beautiful graphics and a captivating storyline that will transport you into a mystical world of the forest. Join the black cat on this adventure to meet new friends and experience an unforgettable journey.<br/>Embark on your forest adventure now with "Paws Trail"!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mannerheim's Saloon Car</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2669080/Mannerheims_Saloon_Car/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Marshal Mannerheim’s Saloon Car is the train carriage that was used by Carl Gustaf Emil Mannerheim and his personnel in 1939-1946. Mannerheim was the commander-in-chief of Finland’s defense forces during World War II, and later he became the president of Finland. During the winter war between Finland and Soviet Union, Mannerheim traveled nearly 79 000 kilometers with the train. This historical train carriage is currently located in Mikkeli, Finland, where it can be visited once a year on June 4th.<br>
<br>
<br>
This application allows its user to visit Mannerheim’s Saloon Car in VR and to explore old items, documents, photo albums, film clips, and even listen to historical radio broadcasts. It is possible to choose from two languages: English or Finnish. The app was developed by Xamk Game Studios at South-Eastern Finland University of Applied Sciences in the ARMikkeli project. The project was partially funded by the South Savo Regional Council from the European Regional Development Fund.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporarily</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2688620/Temporarily/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the mysterious world of Temporarily, an indie horror game that takes you on a chilling journey through time. Assume the role of Jack, who awakens in a peculiar room with no memory of how he got there. As Jack delves into the enigmatic past of himself and his wife, players will uncover a tale shrouded in darkness.<br>
<br>
Players will take on the role of Jack who must progress through various missions to find the truth about himself. The game will have various endings depending on the player's actions.<br>
<br>
Unique to Temporarily is the ability to traverse between two distinct worlds—The Wood and The Room. Each realm unveils a different storyline and gameplay experience. In The Wood, a haunting forest set in the nostalgic 90s, players must navigate through eerie landscapes to unravel the truth. Meanwhile, in The Room, strategic use of abilities is key to aiding Jack's progression through the narrative in The Wood.<br>
<br>
Immerse yourself in a world of old-school graphics reminiscent of the PS2 and PS3 era, capturing the essence of a bygone gaming era. Temporarily offers a compelling indie horror experience with a gripping storyline, atmospheric settings, and unique gameplay mechanics.<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay Features:<br/>
Swap between The Wood and The Room for distinct storylines and gameplay.<br/>
Utilize abilities in The Room to assist Jack's progress in The Wood.<br/>
<br/>
Setting:<br/>
Explore the mysterious forest setting of the 90s, where secrets and horrors await.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whispering Breeze</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732670/Whispering_Breeze/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Playing within the game is not very complicated. The player will be able to read the characters' conversations. try to understand And keep an eye on the characters' emotions.<br/>The main thing players will be able to do is mix drinks for their characters. to get different stories according to the drinks that the players can brew<br/><u><strong>Game Feature</strong></u><br/><u><strong>Single Player talk simulator</strong></u><br/><u><strong>Brewing System</strong></u><br/>   Drinks 10 drinks<br/>   Slime 4 types<br/>   Barrels 3 types<br/><u><strong>Dialogues</strong></u><br/>    7 Days Dialogue<br/><u><strong>Background music</strong></u><br/>   3 Different Songs						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merge Circus</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2739500/Merge_Circus/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Merge small cute animals into bigger cute animals. Measure your skills by playing this puzzle game and achieving the highest score!<br>
<br>
Merge Circus is an adorable physics-based puzzle game where you take the role of a small magician who's trying to fill his magical hat with cute animals. Can you help him achieve his goal of getting the biggest and cutest animal?<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
<br>
🐋 Merge two identical animals into a bigger animal. The bigger the animal the more space it takes up!<br/>
<br/>
🧩 Strategize and use physics to your own advantage. Be creative and methodical while earning points and getting the highest score!<br/>
<br/>
🗺️ The game is full of all kinds of animals from around the world. Land, sea, or air, they're all cute!<br/>
<br/>
🎪 A cozy and comforting environment with nice gameplay that is engaging!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spark of Survival</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2726910/Spark_of_Survival/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Spark of Survival is a top-down 2.5D tower defense strategy game in which you must defend your kingdom against an incoming robot invasion using the five unique elemental towers at your disposal. Place, upgrade, and move towers strategically to form the strongest possible line of defense. Combine the effects of various towers to create elemental reactions that destroy the approaching robot army. Advance through increasingly difficult levels to finally destroy the robot leader once and for all.<br/><br/><strong>Key Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Unique elemental towers<br/></li><li>25 tower upgrades<br/></li><li>Buy, move, and sell towers<br/></li><li>16 types of enemies to destroy<br/></li><li>3 levels</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootlegger's Mafia Racing Story</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2475390/Bootleggers_Mafia_Racing_Story/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step Back in Time and Race Through the Prohibition Era in "Bootlegger's Racing Story.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475390/extras/01.gif?t=1704287009"><br/><br/>Experience the adrenaline-pumping excitement of the 1930s Prohibition era like never before! Immerse yourself in the captivating world of Bootlegger's Racing Story and become the ultimate bootlegger in your quest to save your house and pay off your debts.<br/><br/>The Thrill of the Chase<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475390/extras/02.gif?t=1704287009"><br/><br/>Take on the role of John Hamerton, a retired car engineer and mechanic whose life takes an unexpected turn when he becomes a bootlegger. You'll navigate treacherous roads, hidden paths, and narrow tracks as you race against the clock, evading the relentless pursuit of the police and delivering illicit alcohol to various destinations.<br/><br/>A High-Stakes Tale<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475390/extras/04.gif?t=1704287009"><br/><br/>John's house is at stake, and only by successfully running bootlegging operations can he save his home from foreclosure. You'll need to utilize your racing skills, strategic thinking, and resource management to outsmart the authorities and stay one step ahead of the law.<br/><br/>Upgrade and Customize<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475390/extras/03_2.gif?t=1704287009"><br/><br/>As you progress through the game, you'll have the opportunity to upgrade and customize your car. Enhance its speed, handling, and durability to gain an edge over the competition. Show off your unique style and create a one-of-a-kind bootlegger's ride that strikes fear into the hearts of your rivals.<br/><br/>A Vibrant Setting<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475390/extras/05.gif?t=1704287009"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in the richly detailed world of 1930s America, with small towns, rural landscapes, and secret hideouts as your backdrop. Experience the gritty atmosphere of the Prohibition era, complete with vintage cars, period-appropriate music, and authentic visuals that transport you back in time.<br/><br/>Challenge and Triumph<br/>"Bootlegger's Racing Story" offers a thrilling mix of intense racing, strategic decision-making, and heart-pounding escapes. Can you handle the pressure, outsmart the police, and ensure your bootlegging empire thrives? The fate of John's house and your reputation as a legendary bootlegger rest in your hands.<br/><br/>Get ready to rev your engines and outmaneuver the law! Immerse yourself in an exhilarating journey through the Prohibition era. It's time to leave your mark on history and become the ultimate bootlegger! 🚗						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THERE IS NO SLEEP</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732920/THERE_IS_NO_SLEEP/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							It's just another normal night for you, getting home late and getting ready for bed. But everything changes when you lay down... The Nightmare Demon has taken your mind hostage, and continuously gives you nightmares! To save your dreams and escape your nightmares, you must face down The Nightmare Demon and solve their puzzles! Can you save yourself from a life of insanity... or worse?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732920/extras/SleepBanner2.png?t=1704220395"><br/><br/>This moral-testing adventure/puzzle RPG will give you chills in places you didn't know you could get them! With 10 puzzles, 5 endings, and an intriguing story to boot, you won't want to miss this epic adventure into the world of demons!<br/><br/>Featuring:<br/>-10 unique puzzles<br/>-Intriguing original story<br/>-24 song original soundtrack<br/>-5 different and interesting endings<br/>-Death (There's no way around that one)<br/>-A demon that makes music to cause chaos<br/>-Crystals that may or may not just be a currency<br/>-A young man that has a familiar balding pattern<br/>-Credits! (Which usually means that you've reached the end of the game)						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Pet Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2736570/Super_Pet_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join our heroes in this fast action, pet saving, and traffic dodging game! <br>
    Save your cute furry and scaly friends from the busy crossroad!<br>
    Jump, double jump, and dash to safety!<br>
    Pick up the coins on top of the running cars!<br>
    Unlock 39 amazing characters!<br>
    Multiple levels and variations!<br>
    3 awesome music tracks!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disco Dave</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2736580/Disco_Dave/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Are you ready for some 70s’ disco fever with Dave and the rest of the gang? Disco Dave is a quick fun game with voxel graphics. Test your reflexes in the neon disco environment, stay alive and perform combos to get extra points. Watch the floor tiles change colour, and stay away from the gray ones! Use your coins to unlock new characters with far out style and animations.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats VS Ghosts</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2345080/Cats_VS_Ghosts/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2345080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Tower Defense: Cats are towers, ghosts are enemies and humans are target. You must put the correct cat to destroy the ghosts.<br>
History: Few months ago, something strange began to happen. Civilians reported seeing strange figures wandering the streets, causing chaos and destruction in their wake. Soon it was discovered that they were ghosts who had appeared in the town and seemed to have no friendly intentions.<br>
As the days went by, the ghosts became more and more aggressive, and the humans began to feel helpless in their presence. But there was a group of beings who wouldn't give up so easily: the cats.<br>
The cats, known for their cunning and bravery, began patrolling the streets at night, searching for any signs of the ghosts. When they found one, they pounced on it without fear, clawing, biting and shooting until it disappeared.<br>
The humans couldn't believe what they were seeing. The cats, who normally kept their distance from them, were now protecting them from a supernatural threat.<br>
No one knows for sure why the cats decided to defend humans against the ghosts, but some speculate that they did it out of love for their home and their slaves.<br>
Since then, it's said that the cats are always vigilant, ready to protect their humans from any supernatural danger that may arise.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DraconG VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2591020/DraconG_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a thrilling virtual reality adventure like never before with DraconG, a mesmerizing game that fuses the exhilaration of dragon gliding, the excitement of chasing dragons, the strategic conquest of castles, and the rhythmic beats that guide your every move. As the Dragon Rider, your destiny is to hatch dragon eggs, lead armies, and claim victory in epic battles through a harmonious blend of rhythm and skill.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features:</strong></h2><u><strong>Dragon Gliding:</strong></u><br/>•	Soar through the skies in VR as you control the graceful movements of your dragon.<br/>•	Experience the freedom of gliding through breathtaking landscapes.<br/><br/><u><strong>Chase Challenges:</strong></u><br/>•	Engage in heart-pounding chase sequences, pursuing targets with precision and agility.<br/><br/><u><strong>Rhythmic Gameplay:</strong></u><br/>•	Immerse yourself in a rhythmic world where the beat dictates your actions.<br/>•	Execute flawless maneuvers to the rhythm, unlocking new dragons and enhancing your dragon's prowess in battle.<br/><br/><u><strong>Castle Conquest:</strong></u><br/>•	Lead your army into epic battles to conquer castles scattered across the middle age realm.<br/><br/><u><strong>Dragon Egg Hatching:</strong></u><br/>•	Begin your journey by nurturing and hatching dragon eggs, each with its own characteristics and abilities.<br/>•	Form a powerful bond with your dragon companion, evolving together as you face the challenges that lie ahead.<br/><br/><u><strong>Strategic Army Leadership:</strong></u><br/>•	Make tactical decisions to lead your army to victory.<br/><br/><u><strong>Dynamic VR Environments:</strong></u><br/>•	Immerse yourself in dynamic VR environments that respond to the rhythm of the game.<br/>•	Feel the rush of wind, the heat of the chase, and the intensity of battle in a visually stunning and responsive virtual world.<br/><br/>DraconG invites you to take flight in a realm where rhythm, dragons, and conquest converge. Glide through the skies, chase your destiny, and lead your dragon army to glory. The rhythm of victory beats within you - are you ready to answer the call of DraconG?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lighark</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2619090/Lighark/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619090/extras/跟踪开大.gif?t=1704340362"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619090/extras/激光开大.gif?t=1704340362"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619090/extras/躲避激光.gif?t=1704340362"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619090/extras/闪电链.gif?t=1704340362"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619090/extras/投掷开大.gif?t=1704340362"><br/><br/><strong>Lighark</strong> is a top-down action-adventure game. The secluded protagonist  and their family are brutally murdered, but a man known as the  "Scavenger" clones the protagonist's body and resurrects him. In order  to seek revenge, the protagonist embarks on an adventure, piloting a  spaceship and traveling between various wondrous planets. He collect  the most important Yin and Yang crystals in the galaxy to strengthen his own body, all in order to slay the Emperor of the Holy Light  Empire, who massacred their entire family. Little do they know, they are actually getting entangled in a larger conspiracy.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple Attack Methods</h2><br/>The protagonist's unique physique allows him to merge Yin and Yang  energies to create a new golden energy. This golden energy can further  transform into various elements with different functions. By combining  these elements and energy projection methods, the protagonist can obtain different attack methods.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619090/extras/m技能.jpg?t=1704340362"><h2 class="bb_tag">Balancing between multiple factions</h2><br/>In this galaxy, there are three major factions: local creatures, the  Holy Light Empire, and the Shadow Alliance. The protagonist does not  belong to any of these factions, and different factions can attack each other. Cleverly utilizing the conflicts between factions can enhance the protagonist's survival capabilities on various planets.<h2 class="bb_tag">Mental control enemies</h2><br/>When the protagonist is injured, the golden  energy dropped will be mistakenly absorbed by other creatures as  Yin-Yang energy. When the golden energy exceeds the creature's own  energy, it will be controlled. Controlling a group of creatures to fight together can increase the protagonist's survival rate.<h2 class="bb_tag">Diverse Planets</h2><br/>The galaxy contains over 20 explorable planets, roughly divided into  the galaxy's edge, the Holy Light Empire-controlled area, the Shadow  Empire-controlled area, and the war zone. The difficulty varies  significantly in different regions. Each planet has its own  characteristics, such as different local creatures, terrains, and  special natural phenomena.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619090/extras/地图.png?t=1704340362"><h2 class="bb_tag">Rich Upgrade Options</h2><br/>Attack methods and various parameters of the character can be  upgraded using Yin and Yang crystals obtained in levels. These upgrades  include movement speed, HP, damage, range, cooldown, bullet quantity, revenge rate, and more, providing a wide range of possibilities. Players can choose their own direction of enhancement.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619090/extras/升级选项.png?t=1704340362"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Penguin Horror : Legacy of The pengcasso</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2699930/The_Penguin_Horror__Legacy_of_The_pengcasso/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2699930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2699930/extras/contentimage.png?t=1704199972"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Info</h2>Escape the museum in this horror game where you have to navigate around the area to find and collect all the paintings by Pencasso.<br/>You have to run away from your pursuers and avoid traps.<br/>You can find items by exploring. You can use items to open locked doors and passages, restore health, eliminate traps, and resist pursuers.<br/>There are mazes and puzzle elements.<h2 class="bb_tag">Story information</h2>Penguin, the legendary penguin painter who created many masterpieces, has all his works stolen by humans. His son, Penguin, sneaks into the art museum where the stolen works are displayed, alone, to retrieve them. But as if they knew he was coming, the museum is guarded by guards and set up with many traps. Will Mr. Penguin be able to make it out safely?						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdventureQuest 8-Bit: Dungeons &amp; Doomknights</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2702960/AdventureQuest_8Bit_Dungeons__Doomknights/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2702960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2702960/extras/Dragon.png?t=1704325179"><br/><br/><strong>The young hero Artix,</strong> returning from passing the trials to become a Paladin, finds his home destroyed by an army of the undead... its people gone. He swears to save them and destroy the DoomKnight responsible. <strong>Will you help Artix defeat the evil undead, or become their new master?</strong><br/><br/><strong>AdventureQuest 8-Bit: Dungeons &amp; Doomknights</strong> is more than just a rom in a shiny wrapper! It's packed with other games and goodies to make it the ultimate version of the game! <strong>3 Games, 3 Chaos mods, several color palettes, a CRT filter</strong>, and a dragon in a pear tree! <i>(Okay, last one isn't true.)</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>True 8-Bit Retro Single-Player Adventure</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>500+ screens to explore! (Overworld and Underworld)</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Boss Monsters</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Puzzles</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Inspired palette colors including Game Child and Virtual Child (Green and Red colorings)<br/></li><li>Aspect Ratio Options<br/></li><li>CRT Filter<br/></li><li>Viewable Manual<br/></li><li>The Unofficial Official Pretendo Magazine!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Bonus Games</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>ChronoKnight<br/></li><li>NecroNancy</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Chaos Modes</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dungeons &amp; Daimyo<br/></li><li>Pacadin<br/></li><li>Black &amp; White</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neon Fantasy: Rodents</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2745560/Neon_Fantasy_Rodents/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Neon Fantasy: Rodents is the perfect puzzle game for a fun and rewarding pastime. Collect pictures, develop your attention, and feel like a part of the beautiful neon world.<br/><br/>Neon Fantasy: Rodents is a puzzle game featuring beautiful rodents in a neon style.<br/>Your goal is to assemble a picture of neon rodents that has been cut into an equal number of pieces.<br/><br/>The game features several levels of difficulty, allowing you to choose the optimal level for your experience and mood. Regardless of the difficulty, you can enjoy high-quality images of rodents in bright neon style.<br/><br/>In Neon Fantasy: Rodents:<br/><br/>•50 levels<br/>•Neon art<br/>•Simple controls (mouse)<br/>•Achievements<br/>•Relaxing music<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745560/extras/3.png?t=1704193753"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745560/extras/1.png?t=1704193753"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745560/extras/2.png?t=1704193753"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745560/extras/4.png?t=1704193753"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
