<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Pesticide Not Required</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2479320/Pesticide_Not_Required/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pesticide Not Required combines auto-attacking bullet heaven roguelites with farming game mechanics to create an expansive set of strategies and build combinations. Destroy huge hordes of evil insects, grow tons of crops, create your own build path, and unlock unique characters to play with!<h2 class="bb_tag">Create Overpowered Builds</h2> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/extras/CombatChaosFisher.gif?t=1710767518"><br/>You are the bullet hell! Grow an arsenal of ridiculous weapons and craft your own unique build with a combination of 40+ stats. Additionally, each character has their own unique traits that keep runs fresh.<h2 class="bb_tag">Farm, Fish, and Mine</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/extras/FarmFishMineWinterGif.gif?t=1710767518"><br/>Earn vital gold and experience from growing crops, catching fish, and mining. Expand your plot to harvest huge quantities of crops and build carefully to enhance your farming, fishing, and mining capabilities.<h2 class="bb_tag">Automate Your Farm With Pets</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/extras/PetsGifAutumn.gif?t=1710767518"><br/>Recruit friendly pets that will enhance your farm, collect loot, and kill enemies.<br/><br/>Other Features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Quick ~20-minute play sessions<br/></li><li>Customizable home interior and backyard garden area<br/></li><li>Season-themed map variations with 16 difficulty levels<br/></li><li>20+ unlockable characters with special traits<br/></li><li>Persistent skill tree upgrades<br/></li><li>100+ achievements to unlock<br/></li><li>Compendium with unique fish for each season<br/></li><li>Mouse-only gameplay support<br/></li><li>Gamepad and keyboard support<br/></li><li>Go WUMBO!</li></ul><br/>Pesticide Not Required is inspired by awesome games like Brotato, Vampire Survivors, and Atomicrops.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Park Baseball 25</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384620/Out_of_the_Park_Baseball_25/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_banner_1.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/>We are incredibly excited to announce <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong> - the special 25th Anniversary edition of our award-winning baseball strategy series. Can you believe it's been a quarter of a century? Out of the Park Baseball is not just a game - it's a legacy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_henry.png?t=1710574531"><br/><br/>If it happens in real baseball, it happens in Out of the Park Baseball! Discover new talent, draft the next superstar, negotiate with free agents, enter trade talks with other teams, build your dynasty and guide a franchise into an infinite future! As a manager, dive into the more hands-on management and set your team's lineups, pitching staffs, in-game strategy and call the shots from the dugout. You can oversee your league at a high level, or play out each game in the gorgeous 3D game mode, managing play by play or even pitch by pitch. OOTP has it all covered!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_badge.png?t=1710574531"><br/>Here are just a few of the new features coming to <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong>:<br/><br/><strong>A game-changing new Player Development Lab!</strong><br/><br/>Shape the future of your upcoming stars! You can channel your inner Player Development Director like never before. A modern new Player Development Lab is here for every team that allows you to give players individual programs to work on, developing them how you like. Do you want your hitter to work on improving their baserunning? Bunting? Contact? Would you prefer your pitcher to work on building up their stamina? Developing a new pitch? Velocity? It's all up to you - for each of your upcoming future stars!<br/><br/><strong>Massive Player Ratings and AI Upgrade!</strong><br/><br/>It’s the most comprehensive player ratings upgrade in the 25 year history of Out of the Park Baseball! Batting, Pitching, and Fielding ratings have been painstakingly modified to capture the essence of baseball, with modifications to Contact and Power for hitters, Movement and Stuff for pitchers, the addition of Catcher Framing and Stealing Aggressiveness, and much more. BABIP is now front and center for hitters and hurlers, while new internal ratings updates allow for even more flexibility for Commissioners around the world to adjust the game to their detailed delight. Plus, the AI throughout the game has been improved dramatically to deliver the most challenging OOTP experience ever! <br/><br/><strong>Even More Detailed Player Development Control!</strong><br/><br/>Delegate how each and every player on your team will spend their time day in, day out with coaches at practice. Want your power hitter to worry less about avoiding strikeouts and put that time and effort into working on his home run swing instead? Want your aging starter to spend more time practicing his control instead of spending that time worrying about his stuff? By allocating their time and focus to the areas you want, over time you can influence how players develop, maintain their skillset, and fight the aging curve.<br/><br/><strong>2024 Rosters and Rules!</strong><br/><br/>As always, Out of the Park Baseball features up-to-the-minute 2024 MLB rosters that get updated all season long, with every franchise represented from its big league club all the way down to the low minors, and everywhere in between! Plus, OOTP 25 features officially licensed leagues from South Korea (KBO) and Europe.<br/><br/><strong>Improved Historical MLB Modes!</strong><br/><br/>Set up historical MLB games in an all new streamlined way - and benefit from vastly improved historical player ratings! It’s never been faster or easier to experience the entire history of Major League Baseball, now producing even more realistic outcomes thanks to those comprehensive ratings and simulation engine upgrades.<br/><br/><strong>New Retro Visual Immersion!</strong><br/><br/>Watch games with a variety of experiences, including retro-style black and white, ‘50s-era, and ‘70s-era television presentations. Choose from all of these to play games, watch highlights, or just catch a ballgame from a bygone era!<br/><br/><strong>New Licensed Leagues!</strong><br/><br/>For the first time ever, Out of the Park Baseball features an officially licensed Honkbal Hoofdklasse league from The Netherlands and the British Baseball Federation from the United Kingdom! Look for their official clubs, players, competitions, and more!<br/><br/><strong>For the first time ever - an official partnership with the Baseball Hall of Fame!</strong><br/><br/>What happens when you combine the only game that has the entire history of baseball and the the greatest Hall of Fame in sports? An incredible, year-long journey! Join us as we partner with the Baseball Hall of Fame all season - and beyond. Explore Hall of Fame Plaques, with the official, accurate text for each Hall of Famer. Discover incredible Hall of Fame artifacts, curated and released in fun "exhibits" over the course of the season in concert with the Hall - and more surprises too. It's going to be amazing! <br/><br/><strong>Dozens of upgrades big and small!</strong><br/><br/>--&gt; Updated in-game engine base advancement and camera movements<br/>--&gt; A new manager decision history screen gives you a look back on your best and worst trades and transactions<br/>--&gt; Improved trade packages for prospect packages <br/>--&gt; Updated two-way functionality with injured players<br/>And much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/pt_store_text_banner2.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/><br/><strong>Perfect Team is back - bigger than ever!</strong><br/><br/>It’s an all-new Perfect Team! There’s nothing in the world like the incredible online competitions of Perfect Team. Featuring by far the largest player pool ever, and taking advantage of all the player rating and balance upgrades, this year’s Perfect Team is a whole new ballgame.<br/><br/><strong>Brand New Perfect Team Combinator Series Cards!</strong><br/><br/>Pulled non-live cards have a chance to be a special Combinator Series version of the card! Use other cards that share a link (for example being teammates) with the player to get a chance to boost the raw ratings of the Combinator Series card.<br/><br/><strong>A Perfect Team Tournament Roster Builder!</strong><br/><br/>Want to design rosters for the incredible array of Perfect Team Tournaments - all on your own? For the first time ever, Perfect Team will feature a Tournament Sandbox! You can tinker to your heart's content with varying rosters for every type of tournament, with no pressure. This long-requested feature makes its debut in Out of the Park Baseball 25!<br/><br/>In addition to the brand-new Tournament Roster Builder and Combinator Series, Perfect Team 25 also features:<br/><br/><strong>Team Chemistry</strong> - Players who played together in real life will get extra bonuses when on your roster together. Players gain bonuses for seasons they played together, as well as simply being part of the same team or from the same decades<br/><strong>Perfect Team competitions starting on the first day</strong>, including a huge Opening Weekend of Tournaments with big prizes and Perfect Team Championship Series qualifying from Day One! <br/><strong>New content all season long - and beyond!</strong> All new programs, missions, competitions, and excitement await you every day.<br/><br/>Out of the Park Baseball 25 runs on PC/Mac and features the American League and National League logos, the World Series trophy, official logos and jerseys for all 30 MLB teams and 15 KBO teams, over 150 Minor League Baseball league and team logos, and historical MLB logos.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcast - A New Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1013140/Outcast__A_New_Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							20 years after the award-winning action adventure hit, Outcast, pioneered the genre of non-linear open-world games, the long-awaited sequel sees Cutter Slade return to the spectacular alien world of Adelpha. Resurrected by the almighty Yods, he has returned to find the Talans enslaved, the world stripped of its natural resources, and his own past intertwining with the invading robot forces. It's up to him to go on a mission and save the planet again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/flight_8mb.gif?t=1710511218"><br/><br/>The original team behind Outcast 1 has reunited to create this fascinating world, full of dangerous creatures and home to the Talan people – an ancient culture whose fate has become inextricably linked with earth since the events of the first game. You play as Cutter Slade, ex-Navy SEAL, sporting the same dry wit he had back in the 90s – however, the world around him has changed and eventually, so will he.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/combat01_6mb.gif?t=1710511218"><br/> <br/>To save Adelpha, you will … <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>use your jetpack to jump, air-dash, glide, and quickly traverse the fantastic in-game open world <br/></li><li>combine dozens of different modules to create your own personal weapon for taking down the robot invaders <br/></li><li>have total control to approach the story at your own pace in this non-linear world <br/></li><li>explore the world without boundaries, discover hidden temples and dangerous wildlife <br/></li><li>get familiar with the Talan culture while helping them free their villages and gain access to ancient Talan powers that use forces of nature to destroy your enemies <br/></li><li>experience a beautiful, hand-crafted world accompanied by an epic soundtrack by Outcast's original composer, Lennie Moore </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/combat02.gif?t=1710511218"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skelethrone: The Prey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2139870/Skelethrone_The_Prey/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/Wishlist_Follow_ENG.gif?t=1710431377"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/About_the_Game_628_x_182_bright.gif?t=1710431377"><br/>You're in for a great adventure inspired by games like Castlevania and Dark Souls.  Bloodthirsty monsters, divine creatures and epic boss battles. The game’s story is shaped by  choices that will define your journey.<br/><br/><strong>PROLOGUE KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Metroidvania</strong> - Unlock unique upgrades for movement and combat to expand the world. Maintaining the game's progression requires you to use different relics, items and abilities.<br/></li><li><strong>Challenging bosses</strong> - Test your skills against multiple bosses and other creatures from the Dark Ages. The game will constantly test your patience as you face challenging battles that require their own unique approach..<br/></li><li><strong>Exploration</strong> - The game features a huge world represented by a variety of hand-crafted levels. From fog-shrouded ruins, where undead corpses cling to any living being passing by, and shambling figures emerge. To the Sun-city that hides in the labyrinthine of an ancient tomb where an unspeakable evil lingers, long forgotten by mankind.</li></ul><br/><strong>AVAILABLE IN FULL GAME:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Weapons and Equipment</strong> – Your character can be armed with bows, scythes, longswords, whips, pistols, rifles, and many more traditional weapons. More exotic weapons will also be available to you, so use any means to achieve success.<br/></li><li><strong>Multiple Endings</strong> – Make key decisions along the way to determine Ericona's fate as you progress through the story.<br/></li><li><strong>Non-linear exploration</strong> – Play through levels and bosses, discover side areas with more secrets and enemies to defeat.<br/></li><li><strong>Combat galore</strong> - You must use an ever-expanding arsenal of weapons and equipment to repel  a wide variety of enemies. Put your courage, skills, and resolve on display for them.</li></ul><br/>"Skelethrone: The Prey" is a free prequel to the main game, setting the stage for the events that will unfold throughout Skelethrone's main campaign.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/Story_628_x_182_bright.gif?t=1710431377"><br/>The story takes place a few decades before the events of the game's main campaign. Assume the role of Derek Ericona, a lord who escaped the persecution is now trying to get to the borders of the neighboring kingdom to resist the tyranny of Queen Aurora, but he is being chased and faces an uphill battle. Prepare all your skills to overcome all the obstacles and difficulties prepared for our hero. And now the hunt is on!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F89UKE37PuC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/join_the_comunity_628_x_182_bright.gif?t=1710431377"/></a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Shire: Room One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517850/Toy_Shire_Room_One/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FkhSxB2MSgD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/Toy_Shire_-_Discord_Banner.png?t=1710352808"/></a><br/><br/><br/>Play through the <strong>three levels in Kevin's Room</strong> and defend your room against your old toys. Face Memphis-X in the final level and put a stop to his assault as he crushes your soldiers in an attempt to get to your base.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyVengeance.png?t=1710352808"><br/>You received new toys from your family. Isn't that lovely? Oh, it's for sure... <br/>Your old toys, though, aren't getting along as well. They are no longer cared for and have been forgotten. So what follows next? They're going to join together against you and assault your brand-new toys, so be prepared. But never worry! You're in luck since your brand-new toys are troops of green soldiers. They still require your aid though! Control, strengthen, and defeat the opposing forces! However, focus with care, the enemies you encounter might not be your old playthings!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/InteractiveTowerDefense.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Tower building alone won't be sufficient to repel incoming attackers. Build up your own troops in the best feasible positions, then unleash attacks into enemy territory. Never abandon your towers, and deploy your troops in accordance with the traits of the enemy. First, the attacking forces will attempt to get past your defenses. Build and improve towers to aid your army. By using unique abilities, you can support your troops and towers as well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/EpicBattles.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Safeguard your base against waves of attackers. You need to pick the right troops if you would like to prevail. Clean the paths and guard any open routes. Upgrade your troops and unlock new ones to take down the waves and claim victory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyRealm.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Enter a world and a narrative built around the toys that enriched your youth, including toy soldiers, dinosaur sets, robots, building blocks, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_3.gif?t=1710352808"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dune: Imperium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1689500/Dune_Imperium/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Header.png?t=1710364055"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body0_2.png?t=1710364055"><br/>Experience the ultimate blend of strategy and intrigue as you navigate the treacherous landscapes of Arrakis in the award-winning board game <i>Dune: Imperium</i>!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle online, locally with AI, or against the formidable House Hagal.<br/></li><li>Earn Achievements that showcase your prowess as a leader.<br/></li><li>Embark on more than a dozen Challenges that will test your wit and cunning.<br/></li><li>Compete for badges in the rotating Skirmish Mode where no two games are the same!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body1_2.png?t=1710364055"><br/>Arrakis. Dune. Desert Planet. Raise your banner above the vast wasteland before you. As the Great Houses of the Landsraad marshal their forces and their spies, whom will you influence, and whom will you betray? A tyrannical Emperor. The secretive Bene Gesserit. The shrewd Spacing Guild. The ferocious Fremen of the Deep Desert. The power of the Imperium can be yours, but war is not the only way to claim it.<br/><br/><i>Dune: Imperium</i> blends deck-building and worker placement in a deeply thematic new strategy game where the fate of the Empire hangs on your decisions. Will you seek political allies or rely upon military might? Economic strength or subtle intrigues? A council seat… or a sharpened blade? The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body2_2.png?t=1710364055"><br/>In <i>Dune: Imperium</i>, you'll step into the role of one of the leaders of the Great Houses of the Imperium in a struggle to control the planet Arrakis and the invaluable Spice it provides.<br/><br/>The game plays out in a series of ten rounds, each of which is defined by a new Conflict on the surface of the planet; some award critical resources, and some provide Victory Points that will propel you to dominance. But choose your battles wisely: spread your forces too thin, and you'll find your enemies growing too strong to oppose.<br/><br/>Each round, you'll draw a hand of five cards from your deck, which will get stronger over the course of the game as you acquire new cards. Each card can be played in one of two ways: To send an Agent out into the Imperium to gather resources, or to Reveal at the end of the round to purchase new powerful cards. You must maintain a careful balance to get the most of the resources available to you. How will you find your path?<br/><br/>As your game progresses, you'll vie for Influence with four factions of the Imperium: The Emperor, the economically powerful Spacing Guild, the mysterious Bene Gesserit, and the ferocious Fremen of the deep deserts. Earning Influence among the various groups helps you to earn the Victory Points you need...but will you compete with your rivals for their favor, or abandon alliances to pursue other opportunities?<br/><br/>Many strategies are at your disposal, and many paths to victory. The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Footer.png?t=1710364055"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contra: Operation Galuga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2235020/Contra_Operation_Galuga/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2235020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A new entry in the legendary Contra series is here! Contra: Operation Galuga is a thorough reimagining of the classic run-'n'-gun action game from the '80s, featuring modern graphics and sound, new stages, new enemies and bosses, new play mechanics, an updated weapons system, and explosive co-op combat for up to two players in Story Mode or four players in Arcade Mode!<br>
<br>
When the Red Falcon terrorist group takes over the Galuga Islands off the coast of New Zealand, elite Contra commandos Bill Rizer and Lance Bean springs into action, initiating an all-out war in which the fate of mankind hangs in the balance!<br>
<br>
Run, jump, and shoot your way through eight levels using a devastating arsenal - including the spread shot, laser, and homing missiles - now with stackable upgrades and awesome Overload abilities! The intense action is customizable with three difficulty settings plus a variety of additional challenge options. The true Contra legacy begins now!<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br/>
•The original run-'n'-gun game is back, reimagined and more action-packed than ever!<br/>
•Attack aggressively across eight explosive stages! Infiltrate the jungle, ascend the waterfall, speed through an enemy base on a hovercycle, and more!<br/>
•Multiple playable characters with distinct abilities!<br/>
•Epic, screen-filling boss battles!<br/>
•New and fan-favorite weapons, now with stackable upgrades and incredible Overload abilities!<br/>
•Multiple difficulty options and a wealth of extra content						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals Zero Hour</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732960/Command__Conquer_Generals_Zero_Hour/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals Zero Hour brings you closer to the enemy than ever before. Engage opposing forces at hot spots around the globe as you match strategies and arsenals against the new masterminds of modern war.<br/><br/><strong>Arsenal.</strong> Unleash the next generation of 3D new units and 20 new upgrades including China's ECM Tank, GLA's BattleBus and the USA's Spectre Gunship.<br/><br/><strong>Missions.</strong> Take on 15 new missions and make tomorrow's headlines. Root out a splinter cell in Cairo, steal deadly toxins from a U.S. lab and more.<br/><br/><strong>Generals.</strong> Match strategies and arsenals against 9 enemy commanders with unpredictable personalities and tactics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Tiberian Sun™ and Firestorm™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229880/Command__Conquer_Tiberian_Sun_and_Firestorm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Second Tiberium War begins in this legendary sequel to the original Command &amp; Conquer. <br/><br/>With his forces stronger than ever, arch villain and leader of The Brotherhood of Nod - Kane - is pitched in an epic battle against the world's war machine - the Global Defense Initiative. Now you must orchestrate the fate of mankind.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on Dynamic Battlefields. Nature itself provides tactical opportunities - destroyable and deformable terrain, forest fires, treacherous ice fields and many more surprises that help or hinder your strategies.<br/></li><li>Exciting New Strategies and Units. Jump Jet Infantry, Hover Tanks, Tunneling APCs, Hunter Seekers, Laser Fences, Mechanized Battle Units and many more.<br/></li><li>The "Veterancy" Factor. Units can become faster and stronger as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>New Kinetic Battlefields. Flying shrapnel, shock waves and crashing debris are just a few of the exciting new technologies developed to enhance the in-game experience.<br/></li><li>The mood and attitude of the battlefield comes alive like never before - covert night missions, searchlights and new defenses intensify the thrill and excitement.</li></ul><br/>Then take the battle further in <strong>Firestorm, the official expansion pack for the game</strong>. Includes all-new campaign missions, cinematics, and units to decide the future of mankind.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Renegade™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229890/Command__Conquer_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer gets up close and personal in this classic First Person Shooter for one of the most iconic franchises.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wreak Havoc</strong> - Experience the Command &amp; Conquer universe on foot as Havoc, wise-cracking GDI Commando.<br/></li><li><strong>Make Your Own Rules</strong>  - Take on the evil Brotherhood of Nod using your own mix of brute force, stealth, and strategy.<br/></li><li><strong>Assault at Ground Level</strong>  - Dish out the damage in either first or third person.<br/></li><li><strong>Total Access</strong>  - Sneak inside and explore full-scale structures, like immense Tiberium Refineries and the ominous Hand of Nod.<br/></li><li><strong>Grind the Gears</strong>  - Beef up your arsenal by commandeering lethal vehicles, such as Nod Buggies, Flame Tanks, and Mammoth Tanks.<br/></li><li><strong>Weapons of Mass Destruction</strong>  - Choose from a multitude of weapons, including the Tiberium Auto Rifle, Chemical Sprayer, and the devasting Personal Ion Cannon.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ and The Covert Operations™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229830/Command__Conquer_and_The_Covert_Operations/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The legendary RTS game which started it all. Will you side with the humanistic GDI or bring the world to its knees with Kane and the Brotherhood of Nod. Your adversaries are without mercy. And so are you.  <br/><br/>Includes the <strong>The Covert Operations</strong> expansion pack with a range of challenging new missions.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rental</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2796550/Rental/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796550/extras/Gif_Final__2___1_.gif?t=1709834139"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Great Deal!</strong></h2><br/><i>Perfect cabin for a family of four. Close to the beach with great vibes!<br/>For more information about this rental, contact the caretaker!</i><br/><br/>For summer vacation, Umi's family rents a cabin near the beach. However, Umi soon realizes that the offer was not as grand as promised...<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Explore the summer cabin in this short game reminiscent of classic survival horror games.<br/></li><li> Meet and talk to a quirky cast of characters as you try to piece together the secrets of the cabin. <br/></li><li> Find items that will help you advance and find out what is wrong with this place. </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Controls</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Arrows or WASD to move<br/></li><li> Space to interact</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 March Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2845260/100_March_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🌸🌹 WELCOME TO 100 MARCH CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌷🐈</h2><br/>Join the cutest adventure in the Lovely world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of romantic 8 march themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x200.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 March Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁 DLC List for this game 🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Extra.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867620/100_March_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867640/100_March_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x1.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_15" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit Hole</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2831340/Rabbit_Hole/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/smaller.png?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Remember you will live.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Rabbit Hole is a fast paced, tough-as-nails 2D Platformer-RogueLike-Shooter inspired by popular roguelikes, made with a love for the genre. <br/>You are Disc, someone who was suddenly brought to the Rabbit Hole. <br/>Collect guns, fight foes and meet strange new characters on your descent to the bottom, all in an attempt to find your heart again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/1.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“This place is like its own ecosystem. A big living breathing mess.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Every run is different. Enjoy hours of replayable content through randomly generated floor layouts and 50+ weapons to collect and use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/2.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Hey, hey, hey! How's my favorite anxiety-fueled nutjob!”</i></strong><br/><br/>Unlock new characters with diverse playstyles. Each of the 6 unlockable characters keep gameplay fresh and give a unique perspective on the gameplay loop.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/3.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“There was a blank line, almost as if I had erased it”</i></strong><br/><br/>Discover the truth that lies beneath the surface. Collect books and fill out your library to understand its unseen history. In the end, you may even come to understand yourself?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<br/><br/>※ <i>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</i> is the free-to-play version of <i>Meta-Ghost: The breaking show</i>, to showcase some of the gameplay content.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709870080"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruindog:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802430/RuindogPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 4 are available in the official version.<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 4 in the official version<br/>Weapons: 3 in the prologue, 26 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/11z.jpg?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>A long, long time ago, in a solar system not so far away, alien bugs invaded Earth, but they were soon beaten back home, and by the way, their home planet was blown up. After centuries of being invincible, it became popular for humans to watch live alien hunting shows, participate in alien hunts, save up money, equipment, and use the various loot they found to keep going to new maps and defeating more powerful enemies. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1y.png?t=1710487519"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1z.gif?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>Enemies will come at you from all sides on every level, proceed with caution or you'll be torn to pieces in an instant</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3y.png?t=1710487519"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3z.gif?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>Each character has a different growth path and active skills, utilize these skills and choose the most appropriate item for the current hero to achieve the mission objective</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5y.png?t=1710487519"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5z.gif?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>Earn more resources and achieve various mission objectives to unlock different maps/difficulties and even new map mechanics!<br/>Each map has very different mission objectives and combat mechanics, so choose the one that better suits the current mechanic to win the game</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Epoch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/899770/Last_Epoch/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Epoch combines time travel, exciting dungeon crawling, engrossing character customization and endless replayability to create an Action RPG for veterans and newcomers alike. Travel through the world of Eterra’s past and face dark empires, wrathful gods and untouched wilds – to find a way to save time itself from The Void.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Gameplay.gif?t=1709060046"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>15 Mastery Classes</strong><br/>Embark on your adventure as one of five powerful classes and, through your journey, ascend into a unique Mastery Class that unlocks more specialized abilities and build-options. <br/></li><li><strong>120+ Skill Trees</strong><br/>Every skill has its own augment tree that will allow you to control, alter, and empower your playstyle. Transform your skeletons into archers, your lightning blast into chain lightning, or make your serpent strike summon snakes to fight alongside you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Nodes.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Hunt Rare &amp; Powerful Loot</strong><br/>Fill your arsenal with magic items that you may craft to perfection, change the rules of your build with powerful unique and set items, and always have that next upgrade just on the horizon with Last Epoch's deep and randomized loot system.<br/></li><li><strong>Rewarding Crafting System</strong><br/>The items you wield are yours to forge! Last Epoch’s community-revered crafting system allows you to control your character's power progression, featuring robust and deterministic upgrade mechanics.<br/></li><li><strong>Uncover the Past, Reforge the Future</strong><br/>Travel to different moments of time where you will discover the many factions and secrets that exist within the world of Eterra and fight to set the timeline onto a new path.<br/></li><li><strong>Endless replayability</strong><br/>With a wealth of classes and skills to customize, deep game systems, randomized loot, and continuing development, Last Epoch is a game that will keep you coming back for years to come.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Monolith.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Easy to Learn, Hard to Master</strong><br/>We’re committed to making gameplay approachable for new and veteran players alike by allowing you to jump into the fray quickly and providing many in-game resources. Though don’t be fooled, Eterra has many dangers waiting for you that require a mastery of combat and build-crafting.<br/></li><li><strong>Zero Pay-To-Win</strong><br/>Last Epoch will never offer gameplay advantages by being able to spend real money. We believe in creating a fair environment for all players. </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2379780/Balatro/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Balatro is a poker-inspired roguelike deck builder all about creating powerful synergies and winning big.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Endless_Possibility.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Combine valid poker hands with unique Joker cards in order to create varied synergies and builds. Earn enough chips to beat devious blinds, all while uncovering hidden bonus hands and decks as you progress. You’re going to need every edge you can get in order to reach the boss blind, beat the final ante and secure victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Jokers_Clean_Thin.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The definitive poker roguelike experience.<br/></li><li>Endless possibilities - every pick-up, discard and joker can dramatically alter the course of your run.<br/></li><li>In-depth campaign mode complete with 8 difficulties, as well as challenge, daily and seeded runs. </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Break_The_Game.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Deftly deploy an array of potent tools: different Decks, Jokers, Tarot cards, Planet cards, Spectral cards, and Vouchers. Use these versatile instruments to ignite a combo frenzy and turbocharge your poker hands, crafting electrifying, adrenaline-fueled synergies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro_5_Aces_GIF__HQ_.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 Jokers, each with their own unique abilities<br/></li><li>15 Decks with distinct modifiers to choose from for each run<br/></li><li>5 potential variants of each Joker which add further abilities<br/></li><li>22 Tarot cards variants that can enhance your regular playing cards<br/></li><li>11 Planet cards that help level up your possible poker hands<br/></li><li>32 Voucher cards to help provide permanent buffs for your current run</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Find_Your_Flow.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in Balatro’s distinctive psychedelic world. Let the synthwave soundtrack wash over you -  wind down, escape the daily grind and prepare to enter the ultimate roguelike flow state.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improve your collection and discover new cards and secrets with every single run.<br/></li><li>Make use of the in-depth stats screen to study your best hands, most used Jokers, and more!<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the CRT fuzz and enjoy detailed, hand-crafted pixel art.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Spectral_Pack.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F5mH3dNhjx2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro-join_the_discord.png?t=1710160593"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please, Touch The Artwork 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2600140/Please_Touch_The_Artwork_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Disclaimer:</strong><i> This is a short game made in</i> <strong>6 months</strong><i>. It's</i> <strong>100% FREE</strong><i>(no ads, no dlc's), made by a </i><strong>solo dev</strong><i> in honour of James Ensor’s 75 year remembrance.</i> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/extras/Steam3DRoomGIF_Wide.gif?t=1708975190"><br/><br/>Touch the artwork and help a lost skeleton artist find its way home in a surreal, hand-painted universe. <br/><br/>Collect hidden objects for its quirky inhabitants, solve casual puzzles, and restore cracks in the fabric of the paintings. <br/><br/>This slow paced relaxing adventure was carefully crafted from works by James Ensor, a Belgian pioneer in the world of Modern Art.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Hidden object adventure<br/></li><li>5 unique worlds<br/></li><li>Hints when stuck<br/></li><li>Casual point &amp; click gameplay<br/></li><li>Zoom-in for extra details<br/></li><li>Real hand-painted art<br/></li><li>Atmospheric relaxing sound<br/></li><li>Silly and quirky<br/></li><li>Slow-paced &amp; relaxing<br/></li><li>Fit for ages 12-99</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Small Mazes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2570630/20_Small_Mazes/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2570630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a puzzle game with twenty small mazes. If you solve the mazes, you beat the game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>It's about 1-2 hours long, maybe.<br/></li><li>You need a keyboard and mouse to play it. One person played through the whole game on the Steam Deck, but I tried it and think it's better on PC.<br/></li><li> A few puzzles require knowledge of English. No puzzle requires sound or audio to solve it. No puzzle requires being able to recognize different colors.</li></ul> <br/>I hope you enjoy it. <br/> 						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlazBlue Entropy Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2273430/BlazBlue_Entropy_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/原创声明-英语.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗EN_.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗.gif?t=1710258282"><br/>Charismatic character designs with unique aesthetic styles and dramatic animations create a flamboyant, awesome combat experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快的动作连招EN.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快动作连招.gif?t=1710258282"><br/>Smooth controls, infinite possibilities of combos, and realistic combat feedback. This is the roguelite game with the best action experience yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超多角色豪华制作EN.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/全员图618x346.jpg?t=1710258282"><br/>Ten playable characters with vibrant personalities, unique combat styles, and immersive voice-acting.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式自由定制EN.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式，自由定制en.gif?t=1710258282"><br/>There are hundreds of moves for you to build around, plus countless elemental effects and legacy skills passed between characters. The possibilities are infinite. Time to make the best fighter of your own!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/抉择拯救世界EN.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/GIF-抉择拯救世界EN.gif?t=1710258282"><br/>In the future where the world has been plunged into chaos, people enter a cyberspace called ACE, seeking their last chance to resolve the crisis.<br/>If you are the only person in this world who knows the truth, how will you react?<br/>The ending is also the beginning. Your decision will decide humanity's future.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sputnika Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2730270/Sputnika_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Meet our little friend Sputnik. Help its journey to become the greatest star in the solar system - the Sun!<h2 class="bb_tag">Unique Gameplay With Cosmic Gravity</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730270/extras/MainMech.gif?t=1710427471"><br/>Cosmic gravity is applied to the planet, which makes it different from the classic Suika-style game.<br/>The ability to target the other side of the planets adds much more strategy and depth to the game!<h2 class="bb_tag">Merge Planets</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730270/extras/EvoRing2.png?t=1710427471"><br/>Match two identical planets to create bigger celestial bodies.<br/>Discover 10 dazzling planets, each with its own place in the solar system!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730270/extras/GameOver2.png?t=1710427471"><br/>Watch out for the bubble! If the planet pops out of the bubble, it's game over.<h2 class="bb_tag">Meet the Adorable Planets</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730270/extras/Adorable2.png?t=1710427471"><br/>Our planets aren't just celestial bodies – they're full of life! <br/>Watch them interact – they might greet each other with a smile or gaze curiously at one another. <br/>Get ready for a whole lot of cuteness as you merge your way through the solar system.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1708019001"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal Richards (formerly of Echos)</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1708019001"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about the future of Sheepy, limited edition merch and more.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXIT KUN</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781370/EXIT_KUN/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a game of finding differences and observing. Our game challenges players to carefully observe and spot the distinctions that lead them to the elusive "Exit KUN."<br>
<br>
Game Overview:<br>
<br>
You find yourself trapped in an enigmatic underground labyrinth, and your only goal is to reach "Exit KUN." The journey demands keen observation of your surroundings. Every detail matters, and anomalies could be your key to progress.<br>
<br>
How to Play:<br>
<br/>
Observe Carefully: Scrutinize your surroundings to uncover anomalies that may guide your way or pose a threat.<br/>
Turn Back if Needed: If anomalies are detected, swift decision-making is crucial. Turn back immediately to avoid unforeseen consequences.<br/>
Forward Momentum: Should your observation reveal no anomalies, press forward. <br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Developer Notes:<br/>
This game is inspired by Exit 8. You are free to create, upload, and monetize videos and any other content featuring Game on platforms such as YouTube, Twitch, and other video-sharing websites. The characters, places, and elements involved in the game are fictitious. Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, or events is purely coincidental.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egg</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2784840/Egg/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2784840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><h2 class="bb_tag">About this game!</h2></strong><br/><br/>&gt; <strong>Egg</strong> is an interactive clicker game where you need to click egg to earn more eggs.<br/><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Features!</h2></strong><br/><br/>&gt; This game supports mouse and keyboard.<br/>&gt; This game supports gamepad (use <strong>A</strong> button on joystick to click).<br/>&gt; This game uses best HD quality textures that is possible to create.<br/>&gt; Runs on every hardware. Even on BESM.<br/>&gt; Supports all screen resolutions.<br/>&gt; Supports Windows 10/11 and so on.<br/>&gt; If you don't like the game you can always easily refund it.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mucorales</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2746420/Mucorales/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Mucorales is an immersive interactive horror experience, lasting approximately 30 minutes to an hour, inviting you to delve into a dark reinterpretation of the classic Red Riding Hood fairytale. Explore the twisted narrative and witness how your choices shape the story, unraveling hidden secrets within this captivating RPG Maker tale.<br>
<br>
Embark on a journey with Blanchette, a young girl visiting her grandma. As she discovers unsettling truths about her and the entire forest, you'll be faced with decisions that could lead her down a path of temptation or guide her to escape the ominous woods.<br>
<br>
Engage in conversations with diverse characters, interact with various objects, and witness a chilling story unfold before your eyes. The game offers a unique experience with the opportunity to replay and explore alternative paths, providing fresh perspectives on the narrative each time.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIMP HEROES+</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827180/LIMP_HEROES/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Overview</h2>"LIMP HEROES+" is an action game in which you control a hero who moves with physical behavior and fights against an army of evil villains.<br/>Using attractive characters with a taste of American Comics, players can challenge fierce battles with simple controls that require only jumping and special attacks.<br/>Enjoy the HOT and COOL physical action game "LIMP HEROES+".<h2 class="bb_tag">How to play</h2>Only 2 buttons to use!<br/>Only a brilliant jump and a cool special attack action!<br/>Let's give the villains a hero's action with your heroics!<br/>However……<h2 class="bb_tag">The only weakness of superheroes is their ...... heads! </h2>The only weak point of the heroes with invincible bodies is their heads.<br/>If you can defeat the villain and land a brilliant landing without hitting your head hard, you will win.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Defense</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2235570/Massive_Defense/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2235570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Will you defend your weak ones from the underground Orkish horde and their evil bosses? Deploy upgraded high-tech weaponry on fragile power-supply rings. Fine-tune your tower placement and costs. Incredible journey around the world never ends!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2235570/extras/Massive_Content_001.gif?t=1710808631"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Unique from other TD games are rings!</li></ul>If you lose the ring beneath the tower, the deploying place is also lost. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2235570/extras/Steam_Gif_01a.gif?t=1710808631"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Regular updates!</li></ul>This is a live game and updates are coming regularly.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Long and surprising campaign!</li></ul>40 unique levels with various environments. Endless mode and Hard difficulty.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 7 diverse Towers!</li></ul>Machine Gun, Flame, Tank, Medic, Bank, Tesla and Rocket<br/>3 levels of upgrade. The last upgrade also unlocks the extra functionality of a tower.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 3 Special Weapons!</li></ul>Nuke, Shields, and Sniper.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2235570/extras/Steam_Gif_03a.gif?t=1710808631"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Upgrade Towers and Special Weapons!</li></ul>Based on your performance you earn coins that you use to upgrade weaponry before battle.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 10+ Enemies!</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Bosses! </li></ul>Strong bosses at the end of every world.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Story</li></ul>Follow the story to learn more about the Massive Defense universe.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Play Offline!</li></ul>Single-player game, no need for WiFi.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Have fun!|</li></ul>This game has the appetite to be on top with the best tower defense games. Always polishing and making it better.<br/>Intention it to make it worth your time and do not use fillers, only tasty game juice!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite engineer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2767570/Satellite_engineer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The artificial satellite with interrupted power supply needs repair. Let's navigate the space platform and collect the parts. If possible, challenge the mission with minimal movement to conserve energy.<br>
<br>
There are 49 stages prepared, and clearing the game shouldn't be difficult, but breaking the high score could be challenging.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canyon Rush</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2553690/Canyon_Rush/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2553690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FTRWbhhGtdG" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2553690/extras/Steam_Discord.png?t=1710786779"/></a><br/><br/>Your female protagonist will carefully step onto the dangerous courses in her adrenaline-fueled adventure. Balancing on challenging paths and skillfully evading traps is her sole objective. With each attempt, she will encounter a different map and unique course layouts, striving to overcome these changing challenges. As she navigates through the hazardous terrain and overcomes traps, she will bravely and skillfully battle to reach the end. When she falls, she must contend with the perilous giant sandworms lurking beneath the sandy ground, ready to devour her. Canyon Rush offers a unique thrill with its immersive graphics and addictive gameplay. Join Canyon Rush today to break your own records, climb to the top of the leaderboards, and experience the excitement firsthand!<br/><br/>The game is quite simple: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Avoid falling onto the sandy ground because giant sandworms are ready to devour you, maintain your balance, and steer clear of traps.<br/>These traps can lead you to your demise. <br/></li><li>There's no option to save the game . For Easy Mode ; there are specific checkpoints, while Hard Mode has none. <br/></li><li>After each death, the character returns to the beginning, unless you've reached a checkpoint (only applicable for Easy Mode), from where you can continue. Now, here's the question: Do you think you can complete the game without dying once?</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After the Flood</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2130850/After_the_Flood/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2130850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dive into the heart of a haunted town in 'After the Flood,' a single-player horror adventure. Play as a detective investigating a centuries-old curse, facing roaming dangers and unraveling dark secrets. With no means to fight, you must run and hide to survive. Gather clues, confront the past, and lift the curse before it's too late.<h2 class="bb_tag">Synopsis:</h2><br/>Drawn by rumors of strange occurrences and supernatural phenomena, the detective ventures into the heart of the desolate town, determined to uncover the truth behind its tragic past.<br/><br/>As the detective explores the town's eerie streets and decrepit buildings, they encounter chilling manifestations of the curse, including roaming monsters and malevolent spirits. Armed with only their wits and keen investigative skills, players must navigate treacherous environments, solve puzzles, and gather clues to piece together the dark history of the town and the events that led to its downfall.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2130850/extras/House_flashlight.gif?t=1710781546"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Uncover the Dark Secrets: Step into the shoes of a determined detective bent on unraveling the truth behind the sinister events that befell the town. Unravel the mystery behind the curse that brought the town to ruin, driven by a vengeful witch's wrath. Delve deep into the haunted remains of the town, as whispers of the past guide you toward the truth.<br/><br/></li><li> Survive the Horrors: As a detective caught in the grip of a malevolent force, you cannot fight the creatures lurking within the shadows. Your only means of survival is to run and hide from the relentless lone monster that stalks your every move. But beware of what hides in the darkness of the abandoned buildings. Feel the adrenaline rush as you navigate treacherous environments, seeking sanctuary and evading the nightmarish entities that haunt your path.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lonely Knight - Idle Roguelike RPG</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2757630/Lonely_Knight__Idle_Roguelike_RPG/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Lonely Knight is a game that combines idle and roguelike elements.<br>
<br>
Defeat monsters and embark on a journey to find companions for the lonely knight.<br>
<br>
Experience growth through idle gameplay and test your strength in dungeons!<br>
<br>
*Recommended for:<br/>
<br/>
-Those who want to experience endless growth and fun.<br/>
-Fans of roguelike games.<br/>
-Those who enjoy light deck-building games.<br/>
-Players with limited time to spend on games.<br/>
-Those who want to enjoy games despite having limited time.<br/>
<br/>
*Languages:<br/>
<br/>
-English<br/>
-Korean<br/>
-Japanese						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Street Shuffle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1652670/Street_Shuffle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1652670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Own the streets of Dunkopolis, an urban up-and-coming city, in Street Shuffle, a brand new strategic card deckbuilding game! Join forces with other performers and take on challengers, all while amazing the crowd with your skills.<br>
<br>
Play as a street magician named Ace, busking on the street for extra cash. Along the way, you meet other performers who, after seeing your skills, work together to woo over the crowds with you. However, your skills haven’t gone unnoticed. Your party faces other residents of Dunkopolis who are upset with your sudden boost in popularity (and income). You must battle them to gain the affection of the crowd and control of the streets!<br>
<br>
Features a unique drafting mechanic, character leveling, funky tunes, and a colorful cast of characters that bring the city of Dunkopolis to life.<br>
<br>
Can you perform your way to the top? Play Street Shuffle now!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Vault</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2862850/The_Vault/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2862850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							There's a world far beyond what our eyes comprehend, and luckily, somebody has been documenting it all.<br/><br/>See if you can find a login to use, or what feature the Vault may be hiding. See if you can piece the world back together, and figure out what's under the surface of it all.<br/><br/><br/><i>This game console-based text simulator taking place in its own original world. All information that is accessible requires a decent amount of sluething to discover, but one thread may lead quickly into another.<br/><br/>There are three main windows to take into consideration: the login page, the search page, and the informational pages. <strong>You are not expected to create an account while playing this game.</strong> Rather, you must use the logins of in-world characters in order to gain a higher clearance.<br/><br/>Different information may be hidden from you based on your clearance level, decided at login. Search terms are also very strict, so it's best to know what you're looking for when trying to uncover something new.<br/><br/>For any questions, information, or bugs to report, please tell us in the Discord:<br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Foridont" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/oridont</a></i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlock</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2848850/Unlock/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2848850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"># Notes.</h2>You will not be able to solve all the problems.<br/>This is a nihilistic game.<br/>No hints. You are on your own.<h2 class="bb_tag"># Rules</h2>Select a stage.<br/>Tap to enter the password.<br/>&gt;Tap to enter the password.<br/>When the password you entered is correct, the key will be unlocked.<br/>You can get items by clearing the stage... Extra.<br/><br/>Well, I don't think you can clear it.<h2 class="bb_tag"># Other.</h2>This game is an early release version.<br/>&gt;It will be updated if it is well received. In other words, there will be more hell to pay.<br/><br/>...distribution terms and conditions, etc.<br/>&gt;Nothing in particular. Please use it for chatting!<br/>&gt;However, it is a game of eternal emptiness.<br/><br/>Why did you make this game?<br/>&gt;I got the idea when I saw a lottery ticket...<br/><br/>It's not funny.<br/>&gt;Because it's nihilistic.<br/><br/>Can you clear all the stages?<br/>&gt;I can clear all the stages because there are no bugs. But... What do you mean all the stages?<br/>The odds are astronomical.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game of Life: Time</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2859370/Game_of_Life_Time/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2859370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							See the trajectory of Conway's Game of Life through time in a 3D perspective. Create cells, destroy cells, randomly generate cells, and observe the evolution of cell groups on the timeline!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2859370/extras/GameOfLifeAbout0.png?t=1710771515"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2859370/extras/GameOfLifeAbout1.png?t=1710771515"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pesticide Not Required</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2479320/Pesticide_Not_Required/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pesticide Not Required combines auto-attacking bullet heaven roguelites with farming game mechanics to create an expansive set of strategies and build combinations. Destroy huge hordes of evil insects, grow tons of crops, create your own build path, and unlock unique characters to play with!<h2 class="bb_tag">Create Overpowered Builds</h2> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/extras/CombatChaosFisher.gif?t=1710767518"><br/>You are the bullet hell! Grow an arsenal of ridiculous weapons and craft your own unique build with a combination of 40+ stats. Additionally, each character has their own unique traits that keep runs fresh.<h2 class="bb_tag">Farm, Fish, and Mine</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/extras/FarmFishMineWinterGif.gif?t=1710767518"><br/>Earn vital gold and experience from growing crops, catching fish, and mining. Expand your plot to harvest huge quantities of crops and build carefully to enhance your farming, fishing, and mining capabilities.<h2 class="bb_tag">Automate Your Farm With Pets</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/extras/PetsGifAutumn.gif?t=1710767518"><br/>Recruit friendly pets that will enhance your farm, collect loot, and kill enemies.<br/><br/>Other Features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Quick ~20-minute play sessions<br/></li><li>Customizable home interior and backyard garden area<br/></li><li>Season-themed map variations with 16 difficulty levels<br/></li><li>20+ unlockable characters with special traits<br/></li><li>Persistent skill tree upgrades<br/></li><li>100+ achievements to unlock<br/></li><li>Compendium with unique fish for each season<br/></li><li>Mouse-only gameplay support<br/></li><li>Gamepad and keyboard support<br/></li><li>Go WUMBO!</li></ul><br/>Pesticide Not Required is inspired by awesome games like Brotato, Vampire Survivors, and Atomicrops.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking Bound</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2860420/Breaking_Bound/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2860420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> Breaking the Boundary</strong> is a 2D platform jumping monster development horizontal board game.<br/>--The game atmosphere is simple, relaxed and casual.<br/>--Traditional character development, treasure hunting, monster farming, jumping and breaking through levels.<br/>--Abundant special skill upgrade system.<br/>--Hone your skills in monsters and traps.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2860420/extras/level1-2.gif?t=1710764872"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2860420/extras/level1-4.gif?t=1710764872"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans-Siberian Legends</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2757610/TransSiberian_Legends/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757610/extras/Wishlist_Follow_ENG.gif?t=1710764310"><br/><br/>You are a passenger on a train traveling along the Trans-Siberian Railway. Your goal is to get to the end point.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757610/extras/ezgif-3-071433c2b5.gif?t=1710764310"><br/><br/>The game consists of several stages with an interesting plot.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757610/extras/ezgif-5-7e38fbea84.gif?t=1710764310"><br/><br/>You can walk around cities, look out the window and watch the changes in nature, weather and architecture, listen to the radio and communicate with passengers. You can see forests, fields, mountains, cities and villages.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757610/extras/ezgif-5-d9610f2465.gif?t=1710764310"><br/><br/>The game offers you an exciting journey through Russia by train, full of adventures, discoveries and emotions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757610/extras/ezgif-5-be4fa16fe8.gif?t=1710764310"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galactic Ascendancy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2841730/Galactic_Ascendancy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Galactic Ascendancy is an immersive 2.5D experience that is set in the vast expanse of the Andromeda Galaxy, players will embark on an epic journey to invade and conquer that world.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Destroy enemy fighters and clear the way for the transport ships.<br/></li><li> Collect different powerups to increase your chances of success.<br/></li><li> Collect residue from destroyed enemies to boost your ship's defensive capabilities. </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>EXPLORE A RICH UNIVERSE:</strong></h2>Dive into a meticulously crafted universe filled with different worlds and enemies. Encounter diverse alien civilizations, and unite the galaxies under one banner.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>EPIC SPACE BATTLES:</strong></h2>Engage in intense space battles as you lead your fleet to conquer the Andromeda Galaxy. Witness the grand scale of interstellar warfare.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CONQUER THE GALAXY:</strong></h2>Take on the role of Admiral Preen, a skilled and ambitious strategist and military leader entrusted with a flagship in the human fleet, whose mission is to lead the attack on these creatures. Experience the consequences of war as you strive to fulfill the emperor's vision of galactic conquest.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Immemorial Order</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2856310/The_Immemorial_Order/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2856310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><u>Story</u></strong><br/>It's the first day moving into your new home, located in the small, quiet town of Bricksmore. After living in your new house for a few months, you discover the previous owners have left behind some items that were never meant to be found. You quickly find out that these items are not just any old junk but are connected to a secret, mysterious organization.<br/><br/><strong><u>Gameplay</u></strong><br/>The Immemorial Order is primarily an atmospheric first-person walking simulator with some puzzles, comedy and scares<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2856310/extras/MO+YO9.gif?t=1710781298"><br/><br/><strong><u>Features</u></strong> <br/>- Atmospheric environment<br/>- Jump scares<br/>- Puzzles<br/>- Explore a Grand Lodge of a secret organization<br/>- An English pub with a bartender named Al Mond<br/><br/><strong><u>Mouse and keyboard controls are recommended</u></strong><br/>You can play through the whole game using a controller, but you will not be able to use any menus or run in the game.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turbo Play</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2826820/Turbo_Play/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2826820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							A full-scale Video, Image, Audio and Animation editor and sequencer with AI features, including:<br>
 * 300+ video and image gpu-accelerated effects and transitions<br>
 * H.264/H265/VP9 support, up to 8K rendering, GPU acceleratred, HDR <br>
 * Animation, Automation, Lottie, 360 image and 3D support<br>
 * Advanced audio features (VST 2.x, 3.x, Compression, Equalizer, Modulation, Filter and other known effects)<br>
 * Advanced ASIO support with bundled driver<br>
 * Including 8+GB orchestra<br/>
 * Paid versions include unlimited polymorphic tracks (Free version - 1 track)<br/>
 * Intelligent OpenCV features<br/>
 * OCR features<br/>
 * PDF features<br/>
 * HDR editing features<br/>
 * Artificial Intelligence in Image, Audio and Video editing (using MIT-licensed models).<br/>
 * Multiple interface languages.<br/>
* Steam special version: up to 3 full-featured layers.<br/>
* HDR features						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fruit Mountain</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2753620/Fruit_Mountain/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2753620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Fruit Stacking Puzzle Game<br/>Connect the same types of fruit together to make them grow bigger and bigger!<br/>Stack them up without letting them overflow from the plate, and build your own Fruit Mountain!<br/><br/>[Easy to Play!]<br/>Simply throw fruits and stack them on the plate.<br/>Combine fruits of the same kind to make them bigger!<br/>Game over if the fruits fall off the plate!<br/><br/>[Score Up]<br/>The bigger the fruit, the higher your score!<br/>Make chains for even higher scores!<br/><br/>[Ranking]<br/>Compete with players from all over the world and test your skills.<br/>Aim for a high score and keep challenging yourself!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Commander</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2607310/The_Last_Commander/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Game Goals</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>You are the last remaining commander.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Develop your sector over 50 days and defend it from invading alien spaceships.</li></ul><br/><strong>Game Play</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607310/extras/synergy.gif?t=1710734632"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Construct buildings on hexagon-shaped terrain tiles.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>There are combinations that create synergy between each building.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Use synergy/terrain to build the best combination.</li></ul><br/><strong>Battle</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607310/extras/Battle.gif?t=1710734632"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>17 battles occur over 50 days.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Defend all 17 battles to win the game.</li></ul><br/><strong>Resource Management</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607310/extras/Resource.gif?t=1710734632"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Evaluation resources for hope/administration/education exist.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Manage your evaluation resources by managing complaints.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Consumist Journey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2627770/The_Consumist_Journey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2627770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The Consumist Journey</strong> is a surreal exploration game where you play as a torso-headed character on a quest to explore the capitalist and consumerist paradigms of modern society.<br/><br/>Navigate through bizarre and nonsensical environments, solve puzzles, and interact with eccentric characters to learn more about the world and your place in it.<br/><br/>Along the way, you'll confront challenging questions about the nature of consumerism, capitalism, and the human condition.<br/><strong><br/>Key Features:</strong><br/>Explore a surreal and nonsensical world: The Consumist Journey features a unique and imaginative art style that creates a surreal and thought-provoking world to explore.<br/>Play as a torso-headed character: Your character is a torso with a head, but don't let that stop you from exploring and solving puzzles.<br/>Unravel the mysteries of capitalism and consumerism: Through your interactions with the world and its inhabitants, you'll learn more about the capitalist and consumerist paradigms of modern society.<br/>Confront challenging questions: The Consumist Journey is a game that asks difficult questions about the nature of our world. What is the true cost of our consumerism? What is our place in a capitalist society?<br/>If you're a fan of surreal exploration games, thought-provoking narratives, and challenging questions, then this is the game for you.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eye On The World</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2476760/Eye_On_The_World/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2476760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>【Voxelart ✕ Diorama ✕ Exploration Game】</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2476760/extras/steam_page_01.png?t=1710776607"><br/><br/>Congratulations, you have been appointed as the town's special probation officer!<br/>The story takes place in a town where surveillance cameras have been installed all over the place to maintain security. Suddenly, you are assigned the task of observing the town, and you will use the images from the surveillance cameras to protect the town's safety by searching for lost children, finding lost items, and searching for cats that live in the town.<br/>You will be able to complete your missions smoothly, but you will gradually begin to feel a sense of discomfort with the town and the world,<br/>But you will start to feel something strange about the town and the world, and when you have completed all the missions, you will discover the mystery of this world.<br/><br/>Eye On The World" is an exploration adventure game in which you will find various objects in an exciting world made of voxels.<br/>The game is different from picture books and game books that focus on exploration, as the depth and three-dimensionality of the digital 3D world stimulates surprise, inspiration, and creativity.<br/>Let's challenge everyone to a world of fun exploration!<br/><br/>※ It is recommended to play this game in full screen mode.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RocketJump Cascade</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2082420/RocketJump_Cascade/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2082420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							RocketJumpCascade is an adventure platformer game that will put your movement skills to the test. Embark on an exciting adventure as you explore intricate rifts to uncover new areas and attempt to beat your best times. With fast-paced and fluid gameplay, RocketJumpCascade offers a unique and challenging experience.<h2 class="bb_tag"><u>PLAY THE FULL VERSION FOR FREE THROUGH THE DEMO</u></h2>The demo provides the entire game in its current state to let you try before you buy.<br/>If you want to help support the developer and the game consider purchasing the full game &lt;3<h2 class="bb_tag"><u>About the Game</u></h2>Your goal is to master the RocketJump, and find the quickest path through each level, unlocking new paths and secrets as you progress. You will have to use your reflexes, precision and creativity to discover optimal routes, and master your abilities to jump, blast and surf to beat your best time and reach the top of the leaderboard.<br/><br/>The game features a variety of environments and obstacles, each one more challenging than the last. But don't worry, as you improve, new powers, mechanics and items will be unlocked, making the gameplay more and more fun.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fluid and responsive movement mechanics that focus on rocket jumping and other advanced techniques<br/></li><li>Momentum system based on Source engine games<br/></li><li>Fast-paced gameplay that will put your reflexes and precision to the test<br/></li><li>Power-ups and new areas that can be unlocked as you progress, adding new layers of depth to the gameplay<br/></li><li>Regularly planned updates to improve the game</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waking Tides</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2475480/Waking_Tides/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Delve into a first person adventure game world where <strong>augmented reality</strong> extends your gameplay, seamlessly blurring the lines between reality and fantasy.<h2 class="bb_tag">AR HYBRID GAMEPLAY</h2>Here's a small overview on how the AR companion "hint" app works. The AR is based on native smartphone WebAR technology (Android/Apple AR quicklook technolgy) - no extra app download needed.<br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475480/extras/arExplain.png?t=1710681419"><h2 class="bb_tag">STORY INTRODUCTION</h2>In the murky haze of an unsettling fog, a fateful bond is shattered as your faithful companion vanishes into the watery abyss. When consciousness returns, you find yourself stranded on an enigmatic oil rig, a haunting testament to the unknown. Bizarre and otherworldly objects litter the rig's deck, their unearthly presence mocking the laws of reality. As a pulsating pain grips your skull, an enigmatic and perilous odyssey unfolds, beckoning you to uncover the secrets that lie hidden within this twisted realm.<h2 class="bb_tag">THEMES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Atmospheric Adventure<br/></li><li>Augmented Reality<br/></li><li>Lovecraftian<br/></li><li>Walking Simulator</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZenFire</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2840430/ZenFire/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2840430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Set in a mysterious island paradise, your task is simple, shoot the targets so they land into the bin and earn points, miss and you lose a health point, take a chance on spending those points behind you and take a greater risk playing those minigames to unlock more points, once you defeat the highscore of 20k, you're set free!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OG Puzzlers: Synthwave Boats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2673380/OG_Puzzlers_Synthwave_Boats/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>OG Puzzlers: Synthwave Boats</strong> is an casual puzzel game with stunning images in the synthwave style. You have to assemble a single image from random generated indivdual pieces. <br/>Combine all of the smart singel frames into one big image and unlock the next level.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 12 Levels<br/></li><li> casual puzzle adventure<br/></li><li> auto saving<br/></li><li> simple mouse control<br/></li><li> 100 steam awards</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete Heart - 离散之心</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2617300/Discrete_Heart/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Discrete Heart is an emotion-building game in a 2D pixel style from a top-down perspective. Joy, trust, fear... Each initial emotion corresponds to different initial attributes and props. "Inject" and control the characters to build 8 basic emotions, looking for the answer named "Unintentionaler".<h2 class="bb_tag">Background settings:</h2>In the past, carriages and horses were very slow, and letters were far away. Doves connected the two ends of longing, symbolizing "love and peace";<br/>Nowadays, machines are noisy, people are crowded, and information is expanding. Flying doves symbolizes "betrayal and disputes."<br/>In a certain cyberpunk future world timeline, more and more people in a society where order has collapsed must correctly understand and process the emotions encountered at a faster speed:<br/>The waiter in the restaurant mistakenly captured the mood of the guest, and the office staff failed to understand the leader's thoughts in time, and they lost their jobs...<br/>Those who were greedy for pleasure before their lives were settled, got pregnant before marriage, had no one to take care of their offspring, those affected by the war, their emotions, and where should their future go?<br/>With great anticipation, AlphaMood has developed the first-generation discrete heart emotion module. One of the important functions of this module is to train participants' adaptability to the module through simulated consciousness. This test activity is now recruiting volunteers.<br/>"Everything is becoming faster, and so are emotions," an anonymous person commented. "It is imperative to implant electronic emotional chips."<br/>As a result, one after another emotionally numb characters, who have been beaten to death by life, are planning to participate in emotional module training and become the "Unintentionaler" who knows better about "relaxation", and all their worries will disappear.<br/>We are one step closer to becoming the best tool person who knows how to work without eating or drinking. "This is just a small step for AlphaMood, but it is a giant step for all part-time workers," AlphaMood's CEO said at the press conference.<h2 class="bb_tag">Main target:</h2>None of the above is what the player should care about, the player only needs to complete the game.<br/>The main goal of each game is to find the empathy recipe for empathy within a limited time index(a value used to simulate real time) and become an "Unintentionaler", And you can complete a game by talking to the "Guider".<h2 class="bb_tag">Main features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Emotion-building is the core gameplay, which is inspired by the Plutchik-wheel<br/>    1. Restores the main content of the emotion wheel theory, including basic emotions, combined emotions, etc.<br/>    2. Emotions are set to increase or decrease various abilities. After obtaining the empathy recipe, you can adjust this combination through empathy.<br/>    3. You need to decide for yourself which emotions you should obtain or retain based on the situation you encounter, and...occasionally you may encounter a little accident that breaks your plan.<br/>    4. The guider will only allow complete the game people who is "Unintentionaler".<br/></li><li> There are not many system-level restrictions. Players do not have to play a certain protagonist to save the world in some way. You can deliberately play a certain role, it is up to you.<br/></li><li> Interact with NPCs. The plot includes puzzle elements. There may be connections between various plots, but they do not necessarily have to be connected.<br/></li><li> Simplified ARPG combat system: There are no fancy skills and magic systems, and there are several cold weapons that can be used as combat weapons.<br/></li><li> Mild ROGUE: Tailored RogueLike mechanism.<br/>    1. Players will start activities in a map with limited vision.<br/>    2. Randomly generated sub-maps (generated once per game, different sub-maps will have different terrain and a greater possibility of encountering specific types of units).<br/>    3. Random attribute point rewards.<br/>    4. Encounter randomly generated units in the sub-map and choose possible plots.<br/>    5. All units, including players, can pick up items, have independent archives and will die permanently<br/></li><li> Trading system: You can trade with most NPCs and use currency to exchange for the items you want in their hands.<br/></li><li> Synthesis system: items can be synthesized after obtaining the recipe<br/></li><li> Freely decide the life and death of all NPCs, There are no battles limited by the plot.<br/></li><li> All units have the possibility of actively triggering battles (all units have no camp)<br/></li><li> All units are randomly generated and grow with the growth of the player-controlled character.<br/></li><li> After getting familiar with it, the game time can be controlled within 30 minutes, which is suitable for fragmented time.<br/><br/>Hope you have fun and live a happy life!<br/>The most important thing is: remember to "relax" when you are in a bad mood.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-02-15_洞穴宝箱_all_lan.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-36-44_洞穴中石狮子光影效果_all_lan.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-47-06_生成的副地图中的宝箱_all_lan.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_18-06-05_火焰移情.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_18-25-09.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-13_15-18-56_shadow_out_csve.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-09-20_野怪杀死NPC.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-11-37_野怪拾取情感指示物.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-13_15-16-55_kill_by_moster.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-21-35_野怪冲碎草丛爆金币.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-30-47_交易治疗药水_回血.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-38-40_野怪会首先将攻击它的单位视为索敌目标_勾引野怪互相打斗.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-42-51_NPC击杀野怪.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_17-59-08_宝箱.gif?t=1710598284"/></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mudoku - next Sudoku</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2860250/Mudoku__next_Sudoku/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2860250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Move + Sudoku = Mudoku !!<br>
<br>
Mudoku is addictive puzzle based on Sudoku.<br>
<br>
Move and slide line to complete Sudoku.<br>
The rules are the same as Sudoku.<br>
<br/>
Fill a 9 × 9 grid with digits so that each column, each row, and each of the nine 3 × 3 subgrids that compose the grid contain all of the digits from 1 to 9.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potato Salad</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2855740/Potato_Salad/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Potato Salad is a collection of 7 games across different genres. Each game covers a potato from a different time period and highlights the never ending battle against The King of Spud Town who is always scheming to get his way.<br/><br/><strong>FEATURES</strong><br/>- 7 unique games across different genres.<br/>- Obtain extras from completing challenges.<br/>- Remastered and formatted to HD resolution.<br/>- Designed with the Steam Deck in mind.<br/>- Play the games in any order you wish!<br/><br/><strong>THE LEGENDARY POTATOES</strong><br/>Below you will find information on the potatoes and types of games contained within this collection:<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/extras/Potato0.png?t=1710591807"><br/>Inspector Smith<br/>GENRE: Point and Click<br/>This potato has always found an explanation to every mystery possible. Until now! At the cost of his sanity, he attempts to solve the case of the missing television.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/extras/Potato1.png?t=1710591807"><br/>Potatoman<br/>GENRE: Platformer<br/>An ordinary potato has his life upended when he is magically transported to a new dimension. In this universe, he is the Potatoman and must save the world.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/extras/Potato2.png?t=1710591807"><br/>Beat Hiratio<br/>GENRE: Beat em' Up<br/>The only justice this potato knows is at the end of his fists. Asked to provide food in exchange for monies, he agrees to make the biggest feast in history.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/extras/Potato3.png?t=1710591807"><br/>Boxer Yakuzomo<br/>GENRE: Boxing<br/>A potato determined to become the strongest punchmaster in all the lands. Win all the belts and claim the championship once and for all.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/extras/Potato4.png?t=1710591807"><br/>Spaceace Alexius<br/>GENRE: Shooter<br/>The legendary spaceace is contracted to obtain an item of great power. The grizzled veteran sets off for one last trip; sure to be the deadliest yet.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/extras/Potato5.png?t=1710591807"><br/>Chaos Vasquez<br/>GENRE: Action<br/>Wandering the wasteland without a cause, a hapless king approaches him with a proposal he can't refuse. Everything he's ever known is about to be tested...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/extras/Potato6.png?t=1710591807"><br/>8Bit Potato<br/>GENRE: Arcade Minigame Collection<br/>Trapped in an arcade machine, 8bit potato must beat the high scores to become the ultimate gamer.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Cats in Berlin</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2736480/Hidden_Cats_in_Berlin/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736480/extras/steam_cards_header.gif?t=1710609410"><br/><br/>HALLO! Our cats are now in the awesome city of Berlin! Let's search for them.<br/><strong>A short and pleasant experience in a big and lovely illustration!</strong> Start with a Beautiful monochromatic scenario, relax, and find all the cats to reveal the final colored art.<br/><br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736480/extras/ui-credits-star.png?t=1710609410"><strong>More than 970 hidden objects to find!!!</strong><br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736480/extras/ui-credits-star.png?t=1710609410"><strong>Play through different modes, find special cats, and unlock bonus levels!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736480/extras/modes.png?t=1710609410"><h2 class="bb_tag">NORMAL MODE</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Find 120 cats in fixed positions.<br/></li><li>5 hints.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">ADVANCED MODE</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Find 200 cats in semi-random positions.<br/></li><li> 12 Special cats that unlock Bonus Levels and give hints.<br/></li><li> 20 city people to find and earn hints.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736480/extras/bonus-levels.gif?t=1710609410"><br/><br/>Bonus levels with different sizes and numbers of kittens to find. One use of hint for helping.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Metzgerei:</strong> 50 kittens<br/></li><li><strong>Bäckerei: </strong>50 kittens<br/></li><li><strong>Hauptbanhoff:</strong> 50 kittens<br/></li><li><strong>Berlin Wall:</strong> 75 kittens<br/></li><li><strong>Brauhaus:</strong> 100 kittens<br/></li><li><strong>Tiergarten:</strong> 100 kittens<br/></li><li><strong>Underground Party:</strong> 100 kittens + 100 people</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736480/extras/ui-credits-separator.png?t=1710609410"><h2 class="bb_tag">Accessibility</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dark Mode<br/></li><li>Invert Mouse Zoom<br/></li><li>Mouse Drag Sensibility<br/></li><li>Edge Screen Scrolling<br/></li><li>Color Blindness</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER FURY</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2829060/COMPUTER_FURY/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2829060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							general: Offline For One Player Fighting game like 3rd person challenging fighting game like small computer toys while playing &amp; you can change to you fighter position during fight , special moves , receive score after you win , you can very easily make your any special move or difficult move during fight with any simple keyboard, using keyboard is more fun than x box game pad or pc game pad , but with x box game pad or pc game pad added vibration system , currently there is tow hero characters each character have more than 14 move but soon on new update is coming more characters ,more moves , more enemy &amp; more enemy types<br>
<br>
skills: improve your game skills using keyboard or pc gamepad or x box gamepad , improve your speed , improve your mind memory  <br>
<br>
game play &amp;  story:<br>
when you start play game select start new game , on next scene select your pc game pad or x box game pad or keyboard,  on next scene select your favorite character , on next scene the story is : ( when dark computer team controlled the computers &amp; computer city , so heroes decide to free the computers &amp; computer  city from dark computer team ) , on next scene is map scene for enemy locations the hero should clear all dark computer team from whole computer city so the hero in game chose any plane (randomly) to face dark computer member to fight him on which location should go <br>
<br/>
after loading scene the start actual game scene , start fight dark computer face to face , if you are lose you can continue and no worry about how many time to continue, and if win you will be ready for facing next dark computer member from map scene until facing the boss of dark computer team and facing him , if you win you on boss then you congratulations the computer city is free and cleared from dark computer team.<br/>
<br/>
good luck						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grim Realms</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1522280/Grim_Realms/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1522280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i><strong>A grim world will be generated...</strong></i><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1522280/extras/FlatterDread.gif?t=1710574293"><br/><br/><i><strong>Explore everything from bare deserts...</strong></i><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1522280/extras/FlatterDesert.gif?t=1710574293"><br/><strong><i><br/>... to snow covered mountains.</i></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1522280/extras/FlatterIcetown.gif?t=1710574293"><br/><br/><strong><i>Recruit blacksmiths, brutal pirates, noble intellectuals and everything in between.</i></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1522280/extras/FlatterSmithing.gif?t=1710574293"><br/><br/><strong><i>They will all struggle to survive in a world overrun by the undead...</i></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1522280/extras/FlatterUndead.gif?t=1710574293"><br/><strong><i>... and <u>you</u> will be their guide!</i></strong><br/><br/><strong>A game inspired by Rimworld, Dwarf Fortress and Terraria:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> All humans have unique portraits, different backgrounds and come from distinct cultures. They will develop and age as the seasons change and the years pass.<br/></li><li> They all have different skills and abilities; some will become expert miners, great counsellors, and others master blacksmiths.<br/></li><li> Manage their needs, set their priorities and equip them for war or work. They will eat, sleep, socialize, create art, fight and abandon your faction if pushed too hard. They might return later, but as a friendly visitor or leading an attack? <br/></li><li> Defend your settlement from hordes of undead, bandits, large raiding parties and necromancers.<br/></li><li> Mine for riches deep below the surface, discover ancient shrines and powerful magic.<br/></li><li> Start practicing necromancy, raise the dead and have them work for you - see if you can defend your faction from paladins instead! Or maybe harness the powers of light and try to banish the undead for good!<br/></li><li> Craft a huge variety of weapons, armor and clothes from all kinds of materials.<br/></li><li> Plant crops and later harvest to create food and medicine.<br/></li><li> Hunt animals, or tame them to produce milk and fur.<br/></li><li> Grow your knowledge by plenty of research options. All the way from longbows to muskets and grenades.<br/></li><li> Trade with visiting merchants, convince them to join your settlement or plunder them if you wish!<br/></li><li> Create caravans, travel the world by land or sea; discover new locations and establish new settlements.</li></ul><br/>PS: This game is in the same franchise as Grim Nights. However, <i>this game will focus less on tower defense and much more on your villagers and the management of your growing settlement</i>.<br/>(Also: This game was previously called 'Grim Nights 2'. Long story short: the name was changed because it is too different to easily be considered a sequel.)						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotoko's a Little Weird</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2657710/Kotokos_a_Little_Weird/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2657710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2657710/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1710561616"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2657710/extras/Kotoko_s_a_Little_Weird_Description_1_EN.png?t=1710561616"><br/>Kotoko follows the same routine day after day, trying to be the perfect student and sister. But is that all there is to life? One day, Kotoko decides to spice up her bland routine. Will she end up going back to her old ways, or will she grow into her own person? <br/><br/>Follow Kotoko as she makes new friends and throws herself into some wild situations. Sure, she's a little weird, but that's all part of the fun!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2657710/extras/Kotoko_s_a_Little_Weird_Description_3_EN.png?t=1710561616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2657710/extras/Kotoko_s_a_Little_Weird_Description_01_EN.png?t=1710561616"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blindsighted</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2809170/Blindsighted/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2809170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">A Different Kind of Platformer</h2><strong>Blindsighted</strong> has the player explore levels not by sight but by touch and memory. <strong>Dying is common</strong>, but you'll remember the lay of the land each time. Learn from your mistakes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2>Originally conceived for a <strong>Game Jam</strong> as nothing more than a demo, <strong>Blindsighted</strong> is now a full game!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Lots of unique gameplay mechanics<br/></li><li> Minimalist, but captivating visuals<br/></li><li> Controller support<br/></li><li> 4 original pieces of music<br/></li><li> More than one level! (12 base levels, 3 mastery levels.)<br/></li><li> Level select with best times and best deaths<br/></li><li> Optional timer and death counters<br/></li><li> Accessibility features</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bunny hungry</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667010/bunny_hungry/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							There's only one word that can adequately describe this bunny: hungry. The goal of each puzzle in <i>bunny hungry</i> is to rearrange the terrain so that the bunny has a safe path of grass and dirt to reach the food. Every time you place a piece of terrain, all the tiles interact with their neighbors in consistent ways—but you must discover those ways!<br/><br/>Key features:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 80 original 9-by-9 puzzles<br/></li><li> mouse-based pick-and-place interface<br/></li><li> more than 10 types of terrain to discover<br/></li><li> original music, artwork, and sound effects<br/></li><li> customizable bunny appearance and food types<br/></li><li> unlock-able level editor<br/></li><li> optional move counter<br/></li><li> discord server for community, support, and sharing custom levels</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twilight Manor: Roguelite FPS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2863690/Twilight_Manor_Roguelite_FPS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2863690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2863690/extras/hdsbflkhfdaslkjsfhd.gif?t=1710593138"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fast paced combat! </strong>- Use a wide array of weapons to destroy your enemies! You can even kick enemies and parry their projectiles! <br/></li><li><strong>Advanced Gore System</strong> - Headshot enemies or tear their body to pieces and paint the mansion red! Just better hope it's not your blood being spilled <br/></li><li><strong>Stop time!</strong> - With Twilight Mode, you can use your built up adrenaline to stop time and gain a huge advantage over your foes!  <br/></li><li><strong>Intense boss fights </strong>- Test your skills as you fight through increasingly difficult bosses and uncover the truth about the mansion. <br/></li><li><strong>Upgrade system</strong> - At the end of every boss fight, you get to chose between 1 of 3 upgrades, double damage, 2x reload speed and flight are just some of the abilities you can gain! <br/></li><li><strong>Unlockable difficulties</strong> - Carry over your upgrades and face new difficulty modes you've unlocked!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">STORY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2863690/extras/asdkufygfkajdysgh__1_.gif?t=1710593138"><br/>In Twilight Manor: Roguelite FPS, you play as a woman investigating a mysterious mansion in a futuristic cyberpunk world. As you battle through tough foes, you realize there is more going on here than just some experiments.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloody Hallowfest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1797060/Bloody_Hallowfest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1797060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bloody Hallowfest is a horror game with a retro visual style, inspired by some classic B-series horror films from the 90s.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1797060/extras/BloodyHallowfest_Img1.jpg?t=1710536412"><br/><br/>On the night before Halloween, Maya and her friends gather at the summer camp, eager to set up a special event for the youngsters. Together, they deck out the place and prepare games for Halloween night (kids love hunting for pumpkins and taking a swing at the pinata filled with sweets and candies!). What starts as a fun night takes a horrifying turn when a stranger, wielding a bloodied axe, barges in and snuffs out everyone's lives.<br/><br/>Now, Maya is forced to run for her life. As she unravels the escape plan, she also delves into a sinister secret behind the killer and the motives that led to such a massacre. Will Maya manage to escape the nightmare and confront the truth, or perhaps her blood will mingle with that of her friends on the cold steel of the killer's axe?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1797060/extras/BloodyHallowfest_Gif1.gif?t=1710536412"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Survive the Night: Help Maya navigate through the terrors of the night and escape the bloodbath.<br/></li><li>Unravel the Mystery: Uncover the sinister secret behind the killer and the motives that led to such a massacre.<br/></li><li>Prepare for Halloween: Immerse yourself in the Halloween spirit by helping set up decorations and games for the night.<br/></li><li>Retro Graphics: Experience the nostalgia of classic B-series horror films with the game's retro visual style.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
