<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wartales, Pirates of Belerion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692400/Wartales_Pirates_of_Belerion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/piratesofbelerion_english.png?t=1702564761"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/GIF_Teaser_30fps.gif?t=1702564761"><br/><br/>Since the collapse of the old kingdom of Belerion, the archipelago seemed to have been abandoned. Its population of mostly fishermen quickly turned to piracy, merchants deserted its waters, nothing seemed able to halt the decay of these lands… until the arrival of the Ihrian peoples.<br/><br/>Embark on over +25 hours of new adventures and explore Belerion, a new hostile region far larger than any other part of the continent. Discover a land unlike anything you’ve seen with the first expansion to the world of Wartales! Unravel the secrets of the region's storyline, discover new factions and master the new way to travel: navigation.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/belerionarchipelago_english.png?t=1702564761"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/GIF_Region.gif?t=1702564761"><br/><br/>Despite its apparent tranquility and sun-drenched islands, many sailors refuse to venture into the Belerion archipelago. It is true that there is no shortage of perils for anyone who dares to sail between the islands. Its coasts are lined with sharp reefs, its treacherous winds lose the unwary, scaly beasts roam its beaches, and pirates pillage and sink anything that has the misfortune to cross their path.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/conquertheseas_english.png?t=1702564761"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/GIF_Navigation_02.gif?t=1702564761"><br/><br/>Embark on an awe-inspiring journey through the expansive realm of Belerion, where navigation and exploration take center stage in the thrill of seafaring. Uncover the secrets of wind mastery as you navigate the vast expanse, dock your ship, and explore the islands of the Belerion archipelago. <br/><br/>Craft and upgrade components for your ship, from the shape of your sails to the mighty ballista, ensuring that your vessel is not just a means of travel but a formidable force on the open waters. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/sealord_english.png?t=1702564761"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/GIF_Fight.gif?t=1702564761"><br/><br/>Dominate the perilous waters as you face Guards, lawless pirates, and everything in between. Challenge rivals to duels, a distinctive gameplay feature exclusive to Belerion's maritime conflicts. <br/><br/>Rise through the ranks of the Sea Lords leaderboard by conquering foes, boarding ships, and plundering treasures. With a dynamic battlefield, encounters with new factions, Belerion offers an immersive combat experience where every clash propels you closer to maritime greatness.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1702578551"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1702578551"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1702578551"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1702578551"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1702578551"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WITCH ON THE HOLY NIGHT</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2052410/WITCH_ON_THE_HOLY_NIGHT/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2052410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2052410/extras/WITCH_ON_THE_HOLY_NIGHT_About_this_game.gif?t=1702541165"><br/><strong>Product Description</strong><br/>TYPE-MOON, known for the wildly popular mobile game "Fate/Grand Order" and the epic visual novel "Tsukihime," is releasing a remaster of the 2012 hit "Witch on the Holy Night. Experience a coming of age story set in the vibrant, bustling 1980s, which follows an innocent young man and two young "witches." Updates added since the original release include long-awaited fully voiced characters as well as visuals remastered in full HD, bringing the experience to life with unparalleled quality and fidelity. Masterful manipulation of visual elements imbues combat scenes with nail-biting tension, but also breathes life into the characters' everyday activities. Animated graphical elements bring an entirely new level of depth to the reading experience as well!<br/><br/><strong>STORY</strong><br/>In the mansion on the hill, there lived two witches...<br/><br/>It is the late 1980s—the twilight of an era of beauty and vigor.<br/>A boy moves to the city, barely missing two witches living in modern times.<br/><br/>The boy leads a completely ordinary life.<br/>She carries herself with gallant pride.<br/>The girl lives a sleepy, hidden life.<br/><br/>Each walks a starlit path.<br/>One would never expect their paths to cross.<br/>The story of how these three disparate people came together is soon to be told.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons of Sundaria</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/587520/Dungeons_of_Sundaria/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/587520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">The Dungeons:</h2> <br/>* 8 Huge Dungeons filled with hundreds of fiendish monsters and dozens of diabolical bosses.<br/>* Three Levels of Difficulty: Normal, Hard, and Nightmare.  <br/>* Online single player or co-op up to 4-players.<br/>* Local Split-screen multiplayer co-op up to 4-players (only requires a single game copy).<h2 class="bb_tag">Make your Hero:</h2> <br/>* 7 Races: Human, Dwarf, Elf, Halfling, Orc, Goblin and Drog'al (lizard).<br/>* 5 Classes: Champion, Ranger, Cleric, Wizard, and Rogue. <br/>* Customize the appearance of your Hero.<h2 class="bb_tag">Become a Legend:</h2> <br/>* Collect a huge variety of Weapons, Armor, and Accessories to customize your Hero and grow in power.<br/>* Craft powerful equipment and become a force of reckoning.  Multiple tiers of armor and weapons.<br/>* Embrace the Heroism system, allowing you to continually increase the power of your Hero.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1702562956"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1702562956"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1702000678"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1702000678"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood West</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_steam_text_header.png?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>Weird West legends meet eldritch horror in <strong>BLOOD WEST</strong>, an immersive stealth FPS. Become the Undead Gunslinger, doomed to roam the barren lands until he finds the means to purge their curse and free his soul. No, this isn’t your typical Wild West desperado redemption arc. This is a damnation arc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_episodes_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The Canyons, the Swamp, and the Mountains. Each swarming with abominable monsters and unholy demons, these are open-ended worlds for you to explore freely at your own pace. It will take the player over 20 hours on average to complete all three scenarios, and over 35 if they want to see everything the barren lands have to offer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_stealth_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/><strong>Blood West</strong> is a stealth FPS inspired by the genre classics such as the Thief series (whose fans will be happy to hear the voice of Stephen Russell, the actor voicing the master-thief Garrett, returning here as the protagonist), S.T.A.L.K.E.R. games, or - from the contemporary catalog - Hunt: Showdown. The gameplay rewards the careful approach: scouting the area, stalking your enemies, and striking from the shadows. Can you figure out a way to clear a fort full of ghouls and monsters without raising an alarm?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_horror_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The Barren Lands present the player with a nightmarish, twisted vision of the Wild West legends. The curse that has befallen the realm has corrupted every living thing, defiled the land itself, while summoning restless spirits and dark entities. In this mixture of gunslinger pulp and Lovecraftian horror, dark occult magick presents just as much of a threat as sudden lead poisoning.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_characters_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>In <strong>Blood West</strong> you will meet many colorful, yet strangely twisted, fully-voiced NPCs. Just as much prisoners of the Barren Lands as you are, they will sometimes share their unusual stories and send you on various missions. Play nice and they might reward you or become your allies. Cross them and risk their wrath.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_secrets_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The game won’t hold your hand. You’ll have to explore the land for yourself (buying a map from a vendor might prove useful!), and figure out your own way to approach quests. As you poke around the three expansive maps, keep an eye out for hidden places and secret stashes. There’s gold in the mountains! Fair warning - it’s probably cursed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_brutal_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>If sneaking around isn’t exactly your thing, or you feel that you have a power advantage over your enemies, you can always take the head-on approach and meet your enemies guns blazing. <strong>Blood West</strong> comes from the creators of the fan-favorite boomer shooter <strong>POSTAL: Brain Damaged</strong>, so much gratuitous fantasy violence and pixelated blood splatter is to be expected!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_inventory_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>One man’s hell might be another hoarder’s paradise! From simple one-use items like bandages, through medical tinctures, explosives and incendiaries, straight to arcane artifacts that - once slotted - can change the way you play the game, the Barren Lands are just filled with STUFF. There are tons of useful items to discover, and there’s a special player’s stash crate for all those super-rare potions that you’ll hoard and never use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_weapons_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>A gunslinger without a gun would be just a regular slinger. Where’s the fun in that? <strong>Blood West</strong> makes sure you’ll have plenty of weapons to choose from. Revolvers, rifles, shotguns, carabines - a great variety of firearms, from standard army-issue to those infused with powerful magic, or straight-up possessed. And if you prefer not to cause a ruckus, there’s a wide selection of hand-to-hand combat weapons and archery weapons to pick your favorites from.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_skills_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The RPG-like perk-based progression system in <strong>Blood West</strong> will allow you to highly customize the gameplay experience to your liking. Become a stealthy hunter, a revolver-fanning gunman or a relentless berserker. You will gain experience and progress through the skill tree, while discovering new artifacts in each of the scenarios that will bestow on you additional abilities. Combining skills and load-out creates more possible playstyles than you’d normally be able to explore in one playthrough.<h2 class="bb_tag">Are you ready to take back the frontier from the dark forces of demonic corruption and earn the right to move on to a better world? The Barren Lands call you, Gunslinger!</h2><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1702394215"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1702394215"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1702394215"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1702203824"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1702203824"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinball M</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2337640/Pinball_M/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-1.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-2.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free<br/>- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage<br/>- Thrilling competition<br/>- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation<h2 class="bb_tag">Sink your teeth into these tables as purchasable DLC: </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">- Chucky's Killer Pinball:</h2> Step into a twisted realm where the innocent becomes sinister, and the playful turns menacing. Navigate through an eerie playfield where Chucky lurks in the shadows, ready to pounce.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Dead by Daylight™️ Pinball:</h2> Become the hunter or even the hunted in a thrilling fusion of classic pinball and the excitement of one of the most popular horror games ever created.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Duke Nukem's Big Shot Pinball:</h2> Enjoy the biggest, grooviest, most BADASS pinball table ever made packed with guns and babes. Push start and play with balls of steel!<h2 class="bb_tag">- The Thing Pinball: </h2>Use your pinball skills and battle against the shape-shifting alien through the arctic chill of U.S. Outpost #31. Can you trust anyone, even yourself?<br/>- Even more coming...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-4.png?t=1701703297"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn back immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Option</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.<br/>If you are easily intoxicated, changing the following settings may help.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera shake】</strong><br/>The camera shakes when you walk or run, but if you set the value to 0.0, the camera will not shake.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Acceleration】</strong><br/>If you set the maximum value to 30.0, the camera will move without delay.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Sensitivity】</strong><br/>If the sensitivity is high, the camera will move significantly when the mouse is moved. <br/>Adjust the value if you find it difficult to operate the camera with the default value of 1.<br/><br/><strong>【Motion Blur】</strong><br/>Afterimages will appear when the camera is moved. Recommended to disable at 30FPS<br/><br/><strong>【Preset】</strong><br/>Set the overall graphic settings.<br/>If you do not have sufficient specs, it is better to set it to "Low" to avoid sickness.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1701808865"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1701948634"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1701948634"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1701948634"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little Goody Two Shoes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1812370/Little_Goody_Two_Shoes/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/DIVIDER_grapes_616.png?t=1702566240"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/Dive_into_the_FairytaleEN.png?t=1702566240"><br/>There once was Elise , a vibrant and ambitious young lass with a big dream – becoming filthy rich. In spite of this, the stars didn’t seem to have reserved our protagonist much fortune in life. Elise, who came from humble beginnings, had no choice but to spend her days away assisting her fellow neighbours with menial tasks to make a living.<br/>One day, Elise discovers a pair of beautiful shiny red shoes buried in her backyard – what a surprise! Bewitched, Elise embarks on a fearful journey that pulls her closer and closer into the heart of the mysterious Woods!<br/>Will Elise risk it all for the sake of a dream come true, or settle for her humble day-to-day life? The ending of this tale is yours to write…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/Steam_Page_GIF_02.gif?t=1702566240"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/Venture_into_the_WoodsEN.png?t=1702566240"><br/>Little Goody Two Shoes is a horror narrative adventure game, set in a hand-painted fairy tale environment. There are 10 possible endings to fit your choices and actions in the game.<br/><br/>But there’s more than meets the eye here, as you must also manage multiple aspects of Elise’s life in the village to stay alive. Remember, all decisions matter in this story!<br/><br/>During the day, you will need to strengthen Elise’s bonds with her fellow villagers and work to make a living by playing fun minigames.<br/><br/>But once the moon rises, make sure to keep Elise fed, healthy and sane in the multiple encounters with deadly foes as she makes her way further into the Woods.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/Steam_Page_GIF_01.gif?t=1702566240"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/EN_-_Key_Features.png?t=1702566240"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Kieferberg is a small and devout village, which means Elise will need to carefully navigate her relationships with the villagers to avoid arousing suspicion of witchcraft and be left to die in the Woods as punishment. <br/></li><li>At night, Elise can roam around the Woodlands, a mystical and phantasmagorical  realm where enigmas and deadly enemies await as she tries to uncover its secrets.<br/></li><li>Through a limited day and night cycle Elise will need to carefully manage her needs if she wants to stay alive to finish her tale.<br/></li><li>Get struck by Cupid’s arrow and fall in love with the charming bachelorettes of Kieferberg. In this all-female cast of romanceable characters, unlock dreamy date scenes and storylines for each of them.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/HEADER_SteamDeck_616.png?t=1702566240"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/DIVIDER_grapes_616.png?t=1702566240"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658820/Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							10 possible fruits and one goal, reach the Watermelon.<br/>Your job is to combine matching fruits to evolve them to the next one and eventually reach the coveted Watermelon.<br/>To help you, you have 3 different abilities at your disposal. But watch out, using these will cost you some of your points. Be smart about when you use them to get the highest score!<h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLAYER</h2>Measure your fruit skills against another player.<h2 class="bb_tag">GET THE WATERMELON</h2>How many Watermelons can you combine before your basket overflows?<h2 class="bb_tag">USE YOUR ABILITIES</h2>Power, level up and destroy — These abilities will help you reach the Watermelon, using any of those will also allow you to angle your aim.<h2 class="bb_tag">GOLDEN FRUIT</h2>If luck is on your side, you might even see the mysterious Golden Fruit. Find it and witness its effect firsthand.<h2 class="bb_tag">STATISTICS</h2>Track your progress with in-depth statistics. Visit the menu to see the number of fruits you've combined, your ability usage, and much more.<h2 class="bb_tag"></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.codecks.io%2Fwatermelon-game" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/extras/Roadmap_Banner.png?t=1702238677"/></a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football Manager 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2252570/Football_Manager_2024/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2252570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a real boss and write your own football story in Football Manager 2024, the most complete edition in the series yet. <br/><br/>Whether you’re a manager who likes to build from the bottom or prefers to chase immediate glory, the perfect challenge awaits. The arrival of the new Meiji Yasuda Insurance Ltd J. League licence unlocks J1 League, J2 League, J3 League for the first time ever, giving you the opportunity to explore new horizons in Japan.<br/><br/>Wherever you manage, it's up to you to build a team capable of competing with the world's elite.<br/><br/><strong>Game Description </strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Continue your relentless journey to the top of the footballing world by using the new ability to import your existing career from Football Manager 2023.<br/></li><li>Craft a winning tactical approach, incorporating modern football’s most popular systems and cutting-edge positional innovations to deliver victories on the pitch. <br/></li><li>Master the transfer market, using new ways to shape your side to cultivate a squad capable of achieving your goals. <br/></li><li>Level up your players on the training field, developing the mentality and teamwork needed to transform contenders into champions. <br/></li><li>See your tactical vision come to life on Matchdays, with every game elevated by improvements to ball and player movements.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">NEW FOR THIS SEASON</h2><br/><br/><strong>TRUER FOOTBALL MOTION</strong><br/><br/>Enhancements to player animations, ball physics and lighting deliver the most immersive Match Engine in Football Manager history. Move to the cutting edge of football by using the new Inverted Full-Back player role, while more intelligent player rotational movements add more fluidity to every highlight. <br/><br/><strong>DOMINATE FROM SET PIECES</strong><br/><br/>Make an impact at both ends of the pitch with an overhauled Set Piece Creator. Lean on the expertise of brand-new Set Piece Coaches to develop winning routines in every scenario that will help you to outsmart your rivals. <br/><br/><strong>BRACE FOR TRANSFER BATTLES</strong><br/><br/>Showcase your squad-building skills in our most refined transfer market yet. You’ll face a trickier battle for talent as your rival opposition managers are now more strategic than ever in their recruitment decision-making. <br/><br/><strong>NEW AGENTS TO BUILD A DREAM SQUAD</strong><br/><br/>Better shape your perfect squad with the introduction of new Intermediaries that will help you offload surplus players for a cut of the final transfer fee. Additional functionality for existing Agents and the debut of TransferRoom, a football marketplace for transfers in real life, gives you more real-world powered tools than ever to build an elite team and dominate the competition.<br/><br/><strong>ELEVATE PERFORMANCES WITH TARGETS</strong><br/><br/>Motivate your team to achieve more on and off the field by setting them individual Targets. Whether you’re focusing on goals scored in a season or average training performances, challenge your star players and top prospects to maximise their ability. <br/><br/><strong>A HOST MORE ADDITIONS</strong><br/><br/>Enjoy greater variety in every career with the arrival of two new game modes. Real World mirrors when players actually joined your club. Your World sets club squads and budgets at the day your career starts, meaning that only players who joined before that date will be in your squad, giving you the opportunity to rewrite your team’s transfer window.<br/><br/>Elsewhere, you can look to dominate international management and plan for your country's future with a revamped National Pool that gives you a better overview of the talent at your disposal. Match preparation and briefing meetings deliver you winning insights before each fixture. <br/><br/>That’s not all though, with many more changes waiting for you to discover in every career.<br/><br/><i>This version contains information that is still under approval process by rights holders and may contain data that does not, at this time, accurately reflect real world data. For context, some club and player assets may be absent during this version.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPIN UP</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684090/SPIN_UP/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Story</strong><br/>SPIN UP is a climbing action game set on a planet.<br/>After falling to an unknown planet, players aim for the top in order to return to their friends.<br/><br/><strong>Overview</strong><br/>The game is controlled with the left and right keys, and the player climbs by "grabbing" and "spinning".<br/><br/>Pressing the key allows the player to grab onto any object,<br/>While grabbing an object, the player rotates while accelerating.<br/>The moment you release the key, it will fly away by the rotational force.<br/><br/>Where it flies depends on the rotation force and the timing of releasing the key.<br/><br/>Don't give up.<br/>We are waiting for you at the top!<br/><br/><br/><strong>About video distribution</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Both individuals and corporations can distribute their videos.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video sharing site.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racket Club</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2407910/Racket_Club/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2407910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							If you’re a fan of racket sports - from tennis to pickleball or padel to ping-pong - Racket Club is for you! Hit the courts in this all-new sport created for VR that combines the best of these sports and allows players to immerse themselves into a fully-social experience of a real racket club. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>REAL FUN </strong>-  Play in singles or doubles multiplayer, or go for single-player glory in Career Mode. <br/></li><li><strong>REAL MOVEMENT</strong> - A new sport that captures the authentic feel of play with real movement (no virtual locomotion!), Racket Club employs physics and interactions as close to real life racket sports as you can imagine, all within a space that fits in your home.<br/></li><li><strong>REAL(LY) SOCIAL</strong> - Step onto the court in an authentic club experience! Meet new players and reconnect with old friends, on and off the court, as you partner up for doubles, compete in singles,  or spectate courtside together.<br/></li><li><strong>REAL GOOD AI BOTS</strong> - Take on AI bots up through the highest competitive level or just use them to warm up and hone your skills.  </li></ul><br/>Coming December 14, 2023. Wishlist today!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starfend</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2540820/Starfend/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Place defenses strategically, upgrade and combine them. <strong>Starfend</strong> is a 3D tower defense game set in a vast space universe where you will take command of a powerful fleet of advanced spaceships. Your mission is to protect the orbit of inhabited planets against a relentless horde of malevolent meteors that threaten to destroy.<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540820/extras/placeShip.gif?t=1702586543"><br/>Get ready to face an endless succession of challenges, as the game has endless levels, each one more intense and exciting than the last. At each level, you'll be confronted with different models of meteors, each with a different type of protection to try to break through your defenses.<br/><br/>Your arsenal of space defenses includes 10 types of ships with 10 levels, each equipped with futuristic weapons and special abilities. Carefully plan your tactics, place ships in strategic locations around the meteor paths, upgrade your turrets and combine them to get strongger and meet the ever-increasing challenges the hostile universe presents.<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540820/extras/upgradeShip.gif?t=1702586543"><br/>In addition, the 3D gameplay brings an immersive and dynamic experience, allowing you to freely explore, rotate the view and get a complete perspective of space combat.<br/><br/>CameraControls: Hold mouse right click and drag to look around.<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540820/extras/lookAround.gif?t=1702586543"><br/>W - move forward, S - move backward, A - move left, D - move right, Q - move down, E - move up or Hold mouse left click and drag to move the camera. hold shift to increase camera speed.F - Change to free camera. R - reset free camera position. use arrows to switch beteween static cameras, use mouse scroll to zoom in and out.Use mouse left click for interactions.<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540820/extras/cameraMovement.gif?t=1702586543"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ordinary Day</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2240220/Ordinary_Day/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2240220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ordinary Day takes place in a fictional town run by The Church. Founded by the early members and quickly swept in darkness as they uncovered the horror contained nearby, clouded and driven by an external force the church enforced their own rules upon the town, driven to rebirth the darkness. You are bound from birth to fufil a singular purpose, it awaits the day your soul is weakened.<br/><br/>⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2240220/extras/seperator-2.png?t=1702586442"><br/><br/>You return from a party running late in to the night, exhausted with a long drive ahead you set off home. A decision that changed your life and kicked in motion the ever growing darkness lingering in your soul, enter this not so ordinary horror and uncover the shroud of mysteries.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2240220/extras/characters.png?t=1702586442"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBM Studio's Gettysburg</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2492030/RBM_Studios_Gettysburg/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2492030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In RBM Studio's Gettysburg, take command of either the Confederate or Union forces for the Battle of Gettysburg, the single bloodiest battle of the U.S. Civil War.  Each side has an historically accurate order of battle that details when and where reinforcements will arrive, letting the player attempt to outdo the generals of history.  As the Confederate commander Lee, it's your task to either crush the Union forces or secure a safe route for your continued invasion of the North.  As the Union commander Meade, you must at least match the losses inflicted by the Confederates while also securing the roads leaving Gettysburg towards D.C.<br/><br/>RBM Studio's Gettysburg features gameplay based on the historical wargaming boardgames of the 70's and 80's.  Players maneuver markers that represent their units on a hexagonal map that mimics the gameboard and cardboard counters of traditional boardgames.  Turns are completed in an "I go, you go" style, wherein players alternate their turns with their opponent until one player passes.  Once that happens, a random number of unopposed actions are given to their opponent.  Pass too early and you risk giving your opponent the opportunity to maneuver completely around your forces.  Combat is resolved through die rolls modified by terrain, battle line factors, and the use of artillery support.  Attackers benefit from flanking defenders.  Defenders benefit from being in defensible terrain.  <br/><br/>Artillery support is a finite resource, so think carefully about when to use it.  If both players use artillery in an engagement, an artillery duel is conducted in which at most one player will receive the bonus but both players risk losing additional artillery support if their opponent's cannon manage to hit their own.<br/><br/>The Confederates begin the game with less artillery support but ultimately receive more units and benefit from a greater area of influence generated by General Lee.  Only the Union player can deploy a special sharpshooter unit that protects a single hex from the Confederate advance.  Careful placement of this unit can help block a Confederate advance farther into the North.<br/><br/><strong>Key Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Command your units in an historically accurate representation of the real Battle of Gettysburg.<br/></li><li>Maneuver to try and pin your opponent's forces, while keeping your own free to act.<br/></li><li>Manage your artillery usage to avoid being overrun late in the game if your opponent still has resources left.<br/></li><li>Choose your fights carefully - losing artillery and men attempting to capture a well-defended hex without adequate preparation is a sure path to defeat.<br/></li><li>Solo play as both sides to explore the rules and potential strategies.<br/></li><li>Online multiplayer play against a human opponent.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cave Runner</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2616490/Cave_Runner/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2616490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Run at blinding speeds using wire anchors,<br>
and escape from the cave in time.<br>
<br>
The game has no heavy story, no tedious material collection, no complicated synthesis, <br>
and no moving encounters and goodbyes.<br>
<br>
We just keep on running.<br>
Faster, faster, faster, faster<br/>
<br/>
There are two ways to play: escape mode and time attack mode.<br/>
In escape mode, the objective is to escape from the cave within a set time.<br/>
In Time Attack mode, you can choose any course and compete for the time from start to finish.<br/>
Once you have a satisfactory time, upload your score and participate in the ranking.<br/>
Players' replay data can also be saved as ghosts and downloaded from the leaderboard.<br/>
(They can also be exchanged directly between users.)						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Cutter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1924430/Cookie_Cutter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Void. The Matter. The Megastructure. A dystopian world with an egomaniac leader determined to unveil the secrets of the universe. INFONET promised a utopia built on the backs of tireless androids called Denzels. It was a lie. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/Cherry.gif?t=1702589263"><br/><br/>200 years later the planet is decaying and the mysterious Red Seed has been stolen. Raz, a renegade mechanic, searches a hidden lab and discovers the Denzel Cherry, butchered and left for dead, clinging to life by sheer will alone. Her creator—and the love of her life, Doctor Shinji Fallon—has been taken by a demented sicko and Cherry intends to make him—and anybody or anything who gets in her way—pay.<br/><br/>Fueled by love and powered by rage, join Cherry on a blood-soaked quest for revenge as she explores the massive Megastructure and eviscerates the armies of INFONET in an unforgettable over-the-top 2D platformer that breaks tropes and bones.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Subversive_Metroidvania.png?t=1702589263"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Subversive_Metroidvania.gif?t=1702589263"><br/>Cookie Cutter is unabashedly irreverent, violent, and risqué. Become Cherry, a badass android on a rage-filled and love-driven quest. To save her beloved creator she’ll explore and fight her way through a unique illustrated sci-fi dystopian world as she chainsaw-murders anybody who stands in her way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Hand-drawn_Action.png?t=1702589263"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Hand-Drawn_Action.gif?t=1702589263"><br/>Every frame of this immersive experience is drawn by hand with copious amounts of love. That means epic, fall-out-of-your-chair visuals. Grotesque bugs and menacing robots. Gargantuan bosses. Ridiculous weapons, special moves, and brutal gory finishers. All of it brought to life with benchmark 2D animation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Epic_Combat_Abilities.png?t=1702589263"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC__Epic_Combat_Abilities.gif?t=1702589263"><br/>Whether you’re ripping the wings off overgrown mosquitos, impaling mini-bosses, crushing robots on Cherry’s motorcycle, or kick-punch-uppercut-stomping waves of foes with complex combos, you won’t find a better fighting experience with responsiveness and all the flair you could ask for in a Metroidvania.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Rage-Filled_Spectacle.png?t=1702589263"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Rage-Filled_Spectacle.gif?t=1702589263"><br/>Far future dystopia? Check. An android companion turned rage-filled killer? Check. Over-the-top characters and enemies? Check. Buckets of blood? Of course. Experience our bizarre tale, inspired by Japanese manga and Quentin Tarantino films, through 10 huge zones, each weirder than the next.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Square Logic</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2614980/Square_Logic/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614980/extras/GIF_Logic_Puzzles.gif?t=1702578784"><br/>Square Logic is a logical puzzle game. The rules of the game are simple, but its solutions will challenge your mind.<br/><strong>Your goal is to fill the entire grid by drawing squares and/or rectangles.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614980/extras/GIF_Gameplay.gif?t=1702578784"><h2 class="bb_tag">To solve the puzzle, two rules need to be respected:</h2><br/><strong>Each piece to be colored must contain only one number.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614980/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1702578784"><br/><br/><strong>This number indicates what size the piece will be.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614980/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1702578784"><br/><br/>Elabore your strategy to solve more and more puzzles!<br/><strong>Square Logic</strong> is a game inspired by Japanese puzzles.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614980/extras/GIF_Features.gif?t=1702578784"><br/>🔳 <strong>200 brain-teasing puzzles.</strong> Divided into grids 5x5, 7x7, 10x10 and 15x15.<br/>🔳 <strong>Minimalist design.</strong> No score, timer or pressure. Solve the puzzle in your time and enjoy the game experience!<br/>🔳 <strong>Want more challange?</strong> Try disabling the errors highlight available in the game.<br/>🔳 <strong>Beautiful and relaxing.</strong> Choose between the 3 color palettes available in the game, plus dark mode.<br/>🔳 <strong>Autosave.</strong> Take a break and continue later if you want.<br/>🔳 <strong>Steam Cloud support.</strong><br/>🔳 <strong>Keyboard, mouse and controller support.</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topple Tactics Official Soundtrack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2652840/Topple_Tactics_Official_Soundtrack/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2652840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							This is the original Topple Tactics soundtrack. It includes all 8 tracks in mp3 and flac format. <br>
<br>
This is a great way to support Tim Haywood, the composer of the soundtrack!						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Death Focal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2689820/The_Death_Focal/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2689820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							There is an incoming danger threatening to the ANNIHILATION of the human race and humans are gathering their most skilled warriors to fight the incoming battle and so you must prove<br>
Are you a skilled warrior ? do you have the necessary fighting skills it take to fight the battle that will decide weather the human race survives or DIES ?<br>
You will prove if you are qualified by surviving 10 level of simulated zombie apocalypse, each level has 3 zombies waves and their main mission is to KILL you  and each level is harder than the one before and all you got is a Rifle with limited ammo so you must be smart and shoot carefully.<br>
So the question is CAN YOU PROVE YOURSELF WORTHY FOR THE NEXT BATTLE ?						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Defender</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2686350/Home_Defender/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Home Defender: A Holiday-inspired Adventure, a nostalgic journey back to the 90s with references to classic movies and games. <br>
In this unique game, you'll take on the role of a home defender.<br>
<br>
When your family go out, they forgot one very important thing... You!<br>
<br>
Now you can play as nine-year-old boy. Your goal is to protect your home from two burglars who are trying to get you. You need to explore the house and find items that you can use to make traps and find weapons. You can also encounter side quests and enemies in different areas of the house, such as the basement, the attic and the backyard. Armed with imagination and a BB-Gun, you can create a wealth of clever contraptions.<br>
<br/>
You have 7 minutes before burglars enter your house. Try to beat your basement and attic nightmares first to find weapons and secret keys to unlock more traps.<br/>
When you defeat the bandits, you will be able to call the police to take them away.<br/>
<br/>
To win you must know that:<br/>
<br/>
Your every mistake costs your life <br/>
(then you lose everything you have collected in the inventory and you have to start the game again)<br/>
<br/>
Save bullets, stones and water for later (the traps may be destroyed and then weapons and ammunition may be the only way to survive)<br/>
<br/>
Patience and perseverance are the key to victory<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Are you ready to defend your home from invasion? Get ready for an exciting game where your skills will be put to the test. Be the hero of your own Home Defender story!<br/>
<br/>
Have fun playing and good luck defending your home!<br/>
<br/>
!!! FREE DLC COMING SOON !!!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Word Warrior: Zombie Typocalypse</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391830/Word_Warrior_Zombie_Typocalypse/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for a hilariously unique gaming experience in "Word Warrior: Zombie Typocalypse," the ultimate typing-based rail shooter extravaganza!<h2 class="bb_tag">Unleash Your Imagination:</h2>In a post-apocalyptic world overrun by zombies, you have the power of Anything World™ at your fingertips. Type anything you can think of, and watch in awe as your summoned objects become your creative weapons against waves of relentless undead. From giant rubber chickens to flying toasters, the possibilities are endless, and the results are always entertaining.<h2 class="bb_tag">Epic Adventures Await:</h2>Embark on an epic journey through 5 multi-path levels, each offering a unique set of challenges and surprises. Test your typing skills and creativity in 5 unforgettable boss battles, where only the most inventive summoners will emerge victorious.<h2 class="bb_tag">Customize and Conquer:</h2>Upgrade your arsenal with weapon enhancements, making your summoned creations even more formidable. "Word Warrior: Zombie Typocalypse" offers three game modes of varying difficulties, suitable for both casual players and seasoned pros.<h2 class="bb_tag">Compete Globally:</h2>Face off against players worldwide on Steam leaderboards as you strive to secure the number one position in this whimsical, score-chasing adventure. Elevate your score multiplier with the replay feature, but be cautious - as you replay levels, the zombies grow more formidable, and the rewards become increasingly valuable.<h2 class="bb_tag">Silliness Meets Apocalypse:</h2>Immerse yourself in a quirky and lighthearted post-apocalyptic world filled with humorous characters and absurd situations. Uncover the story behind the main character and learn their horrible truth.<h2 class="bb_tag">Collect and Achieve:</h2>Track your collection of summoned objects in the in-game "Summonography" and earn achievements as you master the art of summoning and conquer in-game challenges.<br/><br/>"Word Warrior: Zombie Typocalypse" is a game that celebrates creativity, humor, and the joy of outlandish mayhem in a post-apocalyptic setting. It's a fresh take on the rail shooter genre that's perfect for players of all ages.<br/><br/>Get ready to type your way to victory and join the ranks of the most imaginative zombie hunters in the world!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCKED</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2664910/LOCKED/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2664910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of Debbie, a young woman ensnared by the clutches of a merciless serial killer. Trapped in a harrowing ordeal, you'll be challenged to solve intricate puzzles within a highly detailed 2D environment, all while evading the relentless pursuit of your abductor. Your objective? To escape the oppressive confines of the basement and unlock the path to freedom within your captor's lair.<br/><br/>LOCKED is a gripping and compact 2D horror-themed side-scrolling game that draws inspiration from the iconic horror games of the PS1 and PS2 era, as well as classic cinematic gems like 'The Texas Chainsaw Massacre' and 'Golden Glove.' Are you ready to unravel the mysteries that lie within and confront the chilling terror that awaits?<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><br/><strong>Short Horror-Themed Experience</strong><br/>Immerse yourself in a bite-sized horror adventure inspired by the VHS era of horror movies, offering a thrilling and intense gameplay experience.<br/><br/><strong>High-Resolution 2D Graphics</strong><br/>Explore a world brought to life with highly detailed hand-drawn graphics, showcasing a unique and visually captivating style.<br/><br/><strong>Classic Survival Horror Meets Side-Scroller</strong><br/>Navigate an open, interactive environment with classic 2D side-scrolling controls, all while solving intricate puzzles to progress. However, tread carefully as the ruthless serial killer lurks, ready to hunt you down anywhere in the house.<br/><br/><strong>Tense Hide and Seek Gameplay</strong><br/>Feel the adrenaline as you hide from your abductor, using your wits to outsmart a relentless foe and uncover the secrets of your captor's lair.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Djikstra's Enigmatic Puzzle Cube</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2697640/Djikstras_Enigmatic_Puzzle_Cube/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2697640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Djikstra's Enigmatic Puzzle Cube is a puzzle game inspired by 2048 and Rubik's Cubes.<br/><br/>Combine adjacent elements together: you can merge them upward, downward, leftward, or rightward on the front face of the cube. Standard combinations can be merged if the elements are the same and their scores are equal. Special combinations can be merged by combining together two elements of the same tier. Find the special combinations by playing and experimenting! Discover rare combinations requiring unique arrangements of cubes!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>FEATURES</strong></h2><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Leaderboards</strong></h2>Play to achieve a high score on our leaderboards, each leaderboard for different cube arrangements!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Cube Sizes</strong></h2>Choose your cube size and hit the reset button to restart the game with a smaller or larger cube! You can go from 4x4x4 to 8x8x8.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Achievements</strong></h2>Unlock achievements spanning from simple discoveries to elaborate chains or unique rare combinations, demonstrating your geometric puzzle skills!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Regular Updates</strong></h2>Check in frequently for new content updates, including: alternate game modes, seasonal graphic sets, and new special cube combinations!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hibernation Day</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2331870/Hibernation_Day/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Hibernation Day</strong> is about family and the problems we face trying to keep it afloat. Our small team combined life experiences to compose a new-year-esk story you can relate to and spiced it up with some humor, so you wouldn't fall asleep listening to a calming soundtrack. The game features no saves but can be finished in around 20 very satisfying minutes, it's also slightly non-linear – try again and choose differently if you want more of them crisp wintery dialogs.<h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2>It is almost the end of <strong>Hibernation Day</strong>, a holiday of the last day before a long winter slumber. However, the celebration isn't going well and everybody's on edge. Your cool older sister isn't happy to be stuck at home, your silly younger brother is nowhere to be found, and the parents are fighting (as they often do). Help your family get along and find peace in the last day before winter hibernation.<h2 class="bb_tag">Creators</h2>Developer and game designer: Serezhka Korneevskii<br/>Artist: Nastasia Viatkina<br/>Writer: Aleksandr Korneevskii<br/>You must be aware that this game is our love-child, and if you treat it poorly, you should expect us to visit your parents for the explanations.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Match Solitaire Winterscapes 2 - Collector's Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2655010/Jewel_Match_Solitaire_Winterscapes_2__Collectors_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2655010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take a break from the holiday hubbub, and lose yourself in the snowy serenity of Jewel Match Solitaire Winterscapes 2. Play more than 1000 frosty levels and clear the icy tableaus. Unlock classic and new solitaire variants such as Genghis Khan, Lullaby, or Mammoth! Escape to a picturesque winter wonderland with enchanting backgrounds that change as you build fantasy locations throughout the game. From a cozy cottage to a snow-covered palace, every scene is a visual delight.<br/><br/>Embark on festive quests, collecting exclusive winter decorations to bring frozen scenes alive and enhance their beauty. Select game-changing power-ups across four unique game modes: Standard, Challenging, Relaxed, and Timed. No matter your preferred playstyle, prepare to be enchanted by a soothing holiday soundtrack, captivating winter visuals, and a mesmerizing gaming experience.<br/><br/>Don't miss out on the most delightful Solitaire experience of the year. Let the snowflakes guide your cards to victory with Jewel Match Solitaire Winterscapes 2!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2655010/extras/JMSW2_Steam_3_cards_600px.png?t=1702571145"><br/>- More than 1000 levels!<br/>- 6 classical Solitaire games including Klondike, Spider and Freecell.<br/>- 18 additional Solitaire variants including Somerset and Council.<br/>- 120 replayable bonus Mahjong levels!<br/>- 10 snowy fantasy locations to build.<br/>- Play 4 different game modes: Normal, Hard, Relaxed and Timed.<br/>- Play supersize, challenge, sliding and match-2 bonus level.<br/>- Accomplish quests.<br/>- Choose between multiple card decks to play with.<br/>- Unlock stunning wallpapers for your desktop.<br/>- Relish a soothing festive soundtrack.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeaOrama: World of Shipping</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2002570/SeaOrama_World_of_Shipping/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2002570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In Seaorama: World of Shipping, you'll have access to a fleet of over 17 types of ships and 90 port locations. But getting goods from one port to another is just the beginning…<br/><br/><strong>Start Your Own Shipping Company</strong><br/><br/>Embark on a thrilling entrepreneurial journey as you establish and nurture your very own shipping company in Seaorama: World of Shipping. Begin with a single vessel and transform it into a maritime empire. Strategize, invest wisely, and watch your company grow from humble beginnings to a dominant force in the global trade arena.<br/><br/><strong>Plan Trade Routes Between 90 Port Locations</strong><br/><br/>Create your own trade routes across an expansive world map featuring 90 port locations. Each destination offers unique challenges and opportunities. Analyze market trends, factor in geopolitical events, and master the art of logistics to optimize your routes for maximum profitability and efficiency.<br/><br/><strong>Manage Your Ships &amp; Contracts</strong><br/><br/>Take control of a versatile fleet comprising 17 types of vessels. From cargo vessels to container ships, ensure that your fleet is well-maintained and equipped. Strike lucrative contracts with clients and meticulously oversee every aspect of your shipping operations. Adapt to unforeseen challenges and keep your cargo moving, no matter what obstacles arise.<br/><br/><strong>And Rise as the Shipping Industry's Next Kingpin!</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>River Tails: Stronger Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1851610/River_Tails_Stronger_Together/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1851610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1851610/extras/rivertailgif1.gif?t=1702569292"><br/><br/><strong>River Tails: Stronger Together</strong> is a <strong>3D co-op adventure platformer</strong> with a colourful cartoon aesthetic. Teammates must work together to defeat end-of-level bosses and solve puzzles across a range of natural-world environments. <br/><br/>Play either as <strong>Furple</strong>, the curious and excitable purple kitten, or <strong>Finn</strong>, the independent fish with a bit of an attitude problem. You’ll embark upstream with these unexpected allies, towards the icy mountain where Furple’s family are in mortal danger. Can you save them in time? <br/><br/><strong>* River Tails: Stronger Together requires a controller in order to play. *</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Immerse yourself in visually stunning natural-world environments</h2><br/>In River Tails, you’ll embark on an epic and visually stunning journey across land and water. Explore the flora of uncharted rainforests, immerse yourself in the magical atmosphere of river caves, cross the treacherous swamp (if you can!). Only then will you get back to the icy mountain. On your way, you’ll encounter a wide range of local wildlife - but be sure to work out which are your friends and which are your enemies before it's too late! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1851610/extras/rivertailsgif2.gif?t=1702569292"><h2 class="bb_tag">Innovative and constantly evolving gameplay</h2><br/>Your journey will be filled with innovative and fun river-themed challenges. The further you travel, the more mechanics and puzzles you’ll face. To succeed, working with your partner is absolutely vital. You know that saying about teamwork making the dream work? It’s a little cliché, but totally true when playing River Tails.<h2 class="bb_tag">Nail-biting boss fights</h2><br/>They can be pretty scary, but having mastered the key co-op mechanics earlier in the game you will have all necessary skills to defeat these angry enemies. Just keep calm and work together. Bosses aren’t evil, but they do have some anger issues for which they should really seek professional help. They are very protective of their turf and aren’t best pleased when a lively kitten and a cool-guy fish get too close.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1851610/extras/rivertailsgif3.gif?t=1702569292"><h2 class="bb_tag">Play a co-op game in a challenging single-player mode!</h2><br/>River Tails is designed specifically for two players, but we didn't like the idea of a game that can only be played in one way. That's why we added the LoneWolf mode. We have added a special control mode that allows you to play as both characters using one controller. The coordination becomes between one part of your brain and the other!<br/>This single-player mode is a whole new kind of challenge.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1851610/extras/rivertailsgif4.gif?t=1702569292"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Da Vinci Cryptex 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2717780/The_Da_Vinci_Cryptex_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717780/extras/h1.png?t=1702568910"><br/>The genial inventor is back with new logical enigmas written in a book!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717780/extras/img1.png?t=1702568910"><br/><br/>Find the answers, unlock the Cryptex, and see what awaits you in the next level!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717780/extras/h2.png?t=1702568910"><br/><strong>The Da Vinci Cryptex 2</strong> is a brainteasing game with 50 unique riddles. The more you solve them, the harder the puzzles become<br/><br/><strong>Warning</strong>: this IQ game may be addictive!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717780/extras/h3.png?t=1702568910"><br/>- 50 unique handcrafted puzzles<br/>- Hints available (click the bulb button to get a hint)<br/>- Astonishing graphics<br/>- Captivating background music<br/><br/>If you're a fan of puzzles, word games, brain thinking, mind games, IQ logic riddles, and enigmas, <strong>The Da Vinci Cryptex</strong> is the game for you, have fun in your spare time!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717780/extras/xslogo.png?t=1702568910"><br/><strong>XSGames</strong> is a solo indie game developer from Italy. I self-published the first Mystery Box chapter on the app stores in 2021 and got amazed by the awesome success it had with mobile game players.<br/>Such results changed my life, so I hope you'll enjoy playing the Mystery Box escape room adventures as much as I love making them!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aztec Tiki Talisman</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2645150/Aztec_Tiki_Talisman/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645150/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for an exhilarating and challenging journey into the heart of the ancient Aztec jungle in ""Aztec Tiki Talisman."" This vibrant 3D platformer promises a unique and action-packed experience that will transport you to a world brimming with mystery and danger. Dive into a beautifully designed adventure that combines challenging platforming, thrilling combat encounters, and mind-bending puzzles.<br/><br/>In ""Aztec Tiki Talisman,"" you play as a courageous hero who must navigate a treacherous Aztec jungle. The game is divided into 5 distinct chapters offering a total of 50 levels to explore. Your adventure unfolds in a visually stunning and dense jungle environment that immerses you in the mysteries of the Aztec civilization.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2></strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>50 levels to explore<br/></li><li>An Epic Journey Through the Jungle<br/></li><li>Platforming, Puzzles, and Combat<br/></li><li>Epic Boss Battles<br/></li><li>Classic 3D Platforming Revived<br/></li><li>Uncover hidden objects, and crack complex puzzles.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eredia 2: The Great War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2468490/Eredia_2_The_Great_War/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2468490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/>- The sequel to Eredia: The Diary of Heroes, packed with over 50 hours of gameplay.<br/><br/>- More than 70 contracts to complete, most of which can be completed in multiple ways. How you choose to do your job matters. <br/><br/>- Engaging, thought-provoking story, which picks up right where its predecessor ends.<br/><br/>- CTB Battle System with unique trait, combo and finisher mechanisms.<br/><br/>- A brand new Divination system which can make each playthrough a unique experience.<br/><br/>- Hidden karma system keeps track of your every action and how you perform them.<br/><br/>- With over 500 different types of enemies, 400+ Skills, 500+ Weapons and Armor, the possibilities are endless!<br/><br/>- Pick fights at your local inn, hang out with monks who have taken a vow of silence, or take your stoicism to the next level by learning to meditate on skulls. (Purely optional... or is it?)<br/><br/>- A particular kind of mushroom enables you to talk to cats.<br/><br/>NOTE - Although it is not mandatory to do so, the two games are designed to be experienced one after the other. And players who have finished the first game are recommended to export their saves to Eredia 2. Please check out the latest announcement for details on how to export saves.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bahnsen Knights</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1933190/Bahnsen_Knights/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1933190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In a world of religious fanaticism, F5 tornadoes and Ford Sierras you are Boulder, an undercover agent. Your assignment sees you infiltrate the <i>Bahnsen Knights</i>, a deadly, supercharged cult with an enigmatic leader. In this murky and dangerous world you must keep your wits about you and stay alive to unravel the mystery behind an old friend’s disappearance.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1933190/extras/WHO_ARE_THE_BK__1_.gif?t=1702568359"><br/><br/><strong>Who are the Bahnsen Knights?</strong><br/>The Bahnsen Knights are the fastest cult in the land. Powered by religious fanaticism and supercharged Sierras they follow their charismatic leader Toni as they unleash hell upon earth. What are their aims? Why are they performing ‘route exorcisms’ and babbling about 'miracles on the road'? And adding to the enigma: Why are they holding paranormal investigator Lou Hill captive in a trunk?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1933190/extras/ABOUT_THIS_GAME__1_.gif?t=1702568359"><br/><br/><strong>An enigmatic leader </strong><br/>The Bahnsen Knights’ highest authority, Toni, is an ex-car salesman preaching that Hell is not below but above us all. He was being investigated by agent Cupra, one of your oldest friends in the Agency. But now Cupra’s gone. Does Toni have something to do with his disappearance?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1933190/extras/AN_ENIGMATIC_LEADER.gif?t=1702568359"><br/><br/><strong>An undercover agent</strong><br/>You thought you had seen everything in all your years working for the Agency, but this assignment is something else, something personal, something darker… and it scares you. Will you be able to keep it together for long enough to uncover what happened to Cupra and take down Toni and the Bahnsen Knights once and for all? Danger lies around every corner and every conversation. You just need to stay alive!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1933190/extras/AN_UNDERCOVER_AGENT.gif?t=1702568359"><br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Immerse yourself in the story with its rich, branching narratives and evocative illustrations<br/></li><li>Decide the fate of characters in ‘Choose Your Own Adventure’ style gameplay<br/></li><li>Earn the trust of the Bahnsen Knights to survive the investigation<br/></li><li>Piece together more of the interconnected world of Pixel Pulps<br/></li><li>Accessible, brain-tickling puzzles throughout the story… including the return of solitaire!</li></ul><br/><strong>A Pixel Pulps adventure</strong><br/><i>Bahnsen Knights</i> is a standalone experience and the third in the Pixel Pulps series of interactive adventures. Created by novelist Nico Saraintaris and artist Fernando Martinez Ruppel, Pixel Pulps fuse exceptional writing and stunning illustration, inspired by mid-20th century pulp fiction and 80s home computer graphics. The first volume comprises three games: Mothmen 1966, Varney Lake, and Bahnsen Knights.<br/><br/><i>Bahnsen Knights</i>, like all the Pixel Pulps, is made to be played by anyone who enjoys fine storytelling.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Japanese RPG: Hiragana Forbidden Speech</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114950/Learn_Japanese_RPG_Hiragana_Forbidden_Speech/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114950/extras/banner_free_demo.png?t=1702562805"><h2 class="bb_tag">Play the free demo!</h2>If you like the demo, buy the full game and continue from your last save point!<h2 class="bb_tag">Learning should be an adventure</h2>Dialogue changes from English to Japanese as you learn and progress in this comedic RPG backed by professional Japanese voice acting.  <br/><br/><br/><strong>Learn Japanese RPG: Hiragana Forbidden Speech</strong> is aimed at <strong>anime fans</strong> with little to no Japanese ability, but any beginner may enjoy and benefit, even those who have studied Japanese and hiragana before. This is a full introductory Japanese course and adventure all in one. We've made the game we wanted to play when we were first learning Japanese.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114950/extras/dalon_meet.gif?t=1702562805"><h2 class="bb_tag">What will I learn?</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>How to read, write, and pronounce hiragana<br/>Hiragana is a set of characters used to write Japanese words. <br/></li><li>Over 240 common Japanese words used in anime<br/></li><li>Enough grammar to understand basic Japanese sentences	</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">How will I learn?</h2><strong>Mild Immersion</strong><br/>Our frustration with other Japanese learning games is that while they teach hiragana and words, they rarely (if ever) use these learnings in actual conversations. Almost everything is out of context.  A random character, word, or sentence here or there. On the other hand, trying to learn Japanese by watching anime or reading manga is overwhelming (for a beginner).<br/><br/>We try to strike a balance between these two worlds.  This game strives for <strong>“Mild Immersion.”</strong>  We want to immerse you in Japanese as much as possible, but only beginner Japanese. We want you to feel confident that any Japanese that comes your way is something you’ve been taught and are capable of understanding at a basic level.<br/><br/><strong>Small Step Immersion</strong><br/>This game also strives for <strong>“Small Step Immersion.”</strong> We want to immerse you in Japanese one small step at a time. After learning a new hiragana, you will soon learn words spelled with that hiragana and immediately start seeing and hearing those words in dialogue and battle.  Slowly, but surely, your vocabulary and reading ability will grow as the game gently immerses you, more and more. <br/><br/>We believe context, immersion, and fun are key to effective learning. This game isn't just an RPG with Japanese flashcard-type battles. It is much more.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FVkgM3zUgmw" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114950/extras/banner_join_our_discord.png?t=1702562805"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">The Adaptive Dialogue System and how it helps you learn</h2><br/>The Adaptive Dialogue System helps you learn by doing. It determines whether to show dialogue in Japanese or English based on your current knowledge.  The more Japanese words and grammar you learn, the more dialogue will appear in Japanese!<br/><br/>For example, consider the following sentence: "doko iku?"  (Where are we going?)  <br/><br/>If you don't know one of the words "doko" (where) or "iku" (go, going), then this sentence will be shown in English.  This is to avoid frustrating you with content you haven't yet learned.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114950/extras/doko_iku_englih.png?t=1702562805"><br/><br/>However, if you know both words, it will be written in Japanese hiragana.<br/><br/>Pressing a button displays the "roumaji" of the sentence. Roumaji uses the English alphabet to describe Japanese sounds.  A second press displays the English translation.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114950/extras/doku_iku_anim.gif?t=1702562805"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Professional Japanese voice acting (Over 4000 lines of spoken dialogue)<br/></li><li>Teaches Japanese starting from zero<br/></li><li>Teaches all the most common hiragana<br/></li><li>Teaches over 240+ Japanese words commonly used in anime<br/></li><li>Teaches word usage and Japanese grammar (over 50 tutorials)<br/></li><li>Adaptive Dialogue System gets you reading Japanese fast without being overwhelmed<br/></li><li>Real-time battles and humorous dialogue make learning fast and fun<br/></li><li>Gradual Reveal Dialogue System lets you conveniently check your reading comprehension<br/></li><li>All Hiragana Mode lets advanced adventurers immerse themselves instantly in a deeper Japanese experience<br/></li><li>Battle drills can be disabled at any time<br/></li><li>Level up controls allow you to adjust the pace of your learning<br/></li><li>Disable automatic voice over to practice reading comprehension easily<br/></li><li>16-20 hours of gameplay</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tremendous replay value. Game adjusts Japanese content to your level from the very beginning</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban Massacre</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2714730/Urban_Massacre/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2714730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the last survivor in this night city. It was completely occupied by the walking dead. Your goal is to collect all the necessary supplies to leave this damned place. Armed with one pistol, you have to fight your way through crowds of zombies and collect things from the list. Show courage and tactics to survive and complete the combat mission.<br>
<br>
Urban Massacre is a zombie horror shooter where you collect items scattered throughout the town. Be careful because there is only one life and in case of death you will have to start over.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
- Zombie survival<br>
- One life<br/>
- Search for objects						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRUNDER</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713860/GRUNDER/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							GRUNDER - You are a young and ambitious student of the master. For a long time you studied your craft under the strict guidance of your mentor. The time has come when it is time to go to complete difficult tests, which are considered the duty of every student.<br>
<br>
You will have to go through a series of dangerous locations, each of which presents a new test and challenge for your skills. On your journey you will encounter treacherous enemies. Use your fighting skills to overcome your challenge!<br>
<br>
The game is a 2D platformer with puzzle elements. Destroy enemies in the location and advance along the storyline.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br/>
- Nice pixel graphics<br/>
- Various enemies<br/>
- Good soundtrack						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compass of Destiny: Istanbul</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2302840/Compass_of_Destiny_Istanbul/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302840/extras/ABOUT_THE_GAME_EN.png?t=1702559668"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Face Your Past, Shape Your Future!</strong></h2>Play as a Venetian in the 17th century Ottoman Empire and face the darkness of his past. Try to solve the problems in your past and deal with the impossibilities of your future!<br/>Customize your hero, choose wisely in challenges, and solve mysteries of The Compass in your quests for adventure and truth!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302840/extras/REAL_STORY_EN.png?t=1702559668"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Mysterious Look into a True Story!</strong></h2>Many of the stories told in Compass of Destiny are based on true events. The Chief Magistrate Ahmed Dede, who sent the hero to the expeditions, the Cretan War, the Venetian-Ottoman relationship and all the features of Istanbul were formed as a result of a detailed research.<br/>The events that took place in the Ottoman Empire of the 17th century and in the world were researched, and these historically true stories were blended with fantastic elements.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302840/extras/Gif_02_EN.gif?t=1702559668"><br/><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Between Two Worlds (Fîtrat)</h2></strong><br/>Spend time in this place where destiny and creation are intertwined, where you can sometimes see the lifeline of a merchant and sometimes a king!<br/>Find people and events that can move into the Fîtrat Realm to improve your skills while exploring Istanbul. Solve puzzles, defeat your enemies and get your rewards at the end of Fîtrat to see memories of the past of your character!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302840/extras/Gif_03_EN.gif?t=1702559668"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Making Way to Truth!</h2></strong><br/>Follow the Compass that fate has forced into your hands. Find the Fîtrat Realm, people, quests and direction with it! <br/>Find your way to the Fîtrat Realm using your Compass. Examine every item, person or event that the Compass reacts to! Trust your compass and never refuse its help!<br/>Remember that you hold the direction of destiny, truth, past, future and everything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302840/extras/Gif_01_EN.gif?t=1702559668"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Discover Your Abilities!</h2></strong><br/>Access your skill scrolls and improve yourself when you complete every discovery in the Fîtrat Realm. Defend yourself better inside and outside the Fîtrat Realm and subdue your enemies!<br/>Swords, Bows, Shields or Fist! Access four different skill trees in four different variants. Improve yourself in any attack position you want! Survive with different types of attacks!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Quests Based on True Stories!</h2></strong><br/>Dive into historical and fact-based stories from the 17th-century Ottoman Empire!<br/><br/>Meet the most famous people of the 17th century such as Müneccim Ahmed Dede and Mehmed IV, listen to the real history from them and successfully fulfill their quests! Guide the story of the protagonist while witnessing the Venetian-Ottoman relationship closely!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1702578551"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1702578551"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1702578551"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1702578551"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1702578551"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The King In Yellow - Escape Room</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2599930/The_King_In_Yellow__Escape_Room/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2599930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2599930/extras/Wishlist.gif?t=1702557584"><br/><br/><i>You have been sent to investigate what happened in a strange spaceship, will you be able to uncover the mystery?</i><br/><br/>The King In Yellow is an escape room game where you will have to solve different puzzles to advance through the ship and try to understand what is the strange entity that is mentioned.<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Different types of puzzles.<br/></li><li>Different rooms that you will have to go through.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Caped Crusader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2706340/The_Caped_Crusader/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is an exciting medieval adventure in which the hero, The Caped Crusader, takes on the King's Guard in an effort to give back to the poor the gold coins the King has unfairly collected from poor tenants.   During the game,  one and then increasingly more members of the King's Guard are seen travelling through the medieval forest with the bags of gold they have collected from the poor tenants.  The Caped Crusader is watching their advances in the distance.  When the King's Guard stop to rest at their various campfires, they place a bag of gold on the ground beside the open fire.   This is when The Caped Crusader must advance and grab the bag of gold that is on the ground at the guard's feet.  But The Caped Crusader needs to be careful in his advance.  If he is seen by members of the King's Guard, the guards will attack and potentially seriously injure The Caped Crusader.  If The Caped Crusader is seriously injured he is forced to retreat  and recommence the game at another time.   What level The Caped Crusader can recommence depends upon how many bags of gold he has successfully collected before being seriously injured. The total number of bags of gold that The Caped Crusader was able to collect appears on the screen when The Caped Crusader is seriously injured.  The Caped Crusader's goal in each game is to take as many bags of gold as he can from the King's Guard so that they can be given back to the poor tenants.  To collect a bag of gold, The Caped Crusader merely needs to step over it.  Each time The Caped Crusader is successful in getting a bag of gold The Caped Crusader must return to his original campsite. The bag of gold will drop automatically when The Caped Crusader approaches his tent.  The Caped Crusader must drop his gold before going out into the woods again to get more gold.   This is how bags of gold are tallied.   The player can only advance to the next level when the necessary number of bags of gold have been collected by The Caped Crusader and been placed by him in the tent at the original campsite.<br>
Français: <br>
Il s'agit d'une aventure médiévale passionnante dans laquelle le héros, le chevalier à  la cape, affronte la garde du roi dans le but de rendre aux pauvres les pièces d'or que le roi a injustement collectées auprès des locataires pauvres.   Au cours du jeu, on voit un, puis de plus en plus de membres de la garde du roi se déplacer dans la forêt avec les sacs d'or qu'ils ont collectés auprès des pauvres paysans.  Le chevalier observe leurs avancées au loin.  Lorsque les gardes du roi s'arrêtent pour se reposer à leurs différents feux de camp, ils déposent un sac d'or sur le sol, à côté du feu.   C'est à ce moment-là que le chevalier doit avancer et s'emparer du sac d'or qui se trouve par terre aux pieds des gardes.  Mais le chevalier doit être prudent dans son avancée.  S'il est vu par des membres de la garde du roi, les gardes l'attaqueront et risqueront de le blesser gravement.  Si le chevalier est gravement blessé, il est contraint de battre en retraite et de reprendre le jeu à un autre moment.   Le niveau auquel le chevalier peut reprendre le jeu dépend du nombre de sacs d'or qu'il a réussi à collecter avant d'être gravement blessé. Le nombre total de sacs d'or que le chevalier a pu collecter apparaît à l'écran lorsque qu'il est est gravement blessé.  L'objectif du chevalier dans chaque partie est de prendre le plus grand nombre de sacs d'or possible à la garde du roi afin de les rendre aux pauvres.  Pour récupérer un sac d'or, le chevalier n'a qu'à l'enjamber.  Chaque fois que le chevalier réussit à obtenir un sac d'or, il doit retourner à son campement d'origine. Le sac d'or tombera automatiquement lorsque le chevalier s'approchera de sa tente.  Le chevalier doit déposer son or avant de repartir dans les bois pour en récupérer d'autres. C'est ainsi que les sacs d'or sont comptabilisés.   Le joueur ne peut passer au niveau suivant que lorsque le nombre nécessaire de sacs d'or a été collecté par le chevalier et placé par lui dans la tente du campement d'origine.<br>
<br>
Deutch: Dies ist ein spannendes mittelalterliches Abenteuer, in dem der Held, der Kreuzritter mit Umhang, gegen die königliche Garde antritt, um den Armen die Goldmünzen zurückzugeben, die der König zu Unrecht von den armen Mietern einkassiert hat.   Im Laufe des Spiels sieht man erst ein und dann immer mehr Mitglieder der königlichen Garde mit den Säcken voller Gold, die sie von den armen Mietern eingesammelt haben, durch den mittelalterlichen Wald ziehen.  Der Kreuzritter mit dem Umhang beobachtet ihr Vorankommen in der Ferne.  Wenn die königliche Garde an ihren verschiedenen Lagerfeuern rastet, legen sie einen Beutel mit Gold auf den Boden neben dem offenen Feuer.   In diesem Moment muss der Kreuzritter mit den Kapuzen vorrücken und sich den Beutel mit dem Gold schnappen, der vor den Füßen der Wache auf dem Boden liegt.  Aber der Kreuzritter mit dem Umhang muss bei seinem Vormarsch vorsichtig sein.  Wenn er von Mitgliedern der königlichen Garde gesehen wird, greifen die Wachen an und verletzen den Kreuzritter mit Kapuze möglicherweise schwer.  Wenn der Kreuzritter mit Kapuze schwer verletzt wird, muss er sich zurückziehen und das Spiel zu einem anderen Zeitpunkt wieder aufnehmen.   Welches Level der Kreuzritter mit Kapuze neu beginnen kann, hängt davon ab, wie viele Goldsäcke er erfolgreich gesammelt hat, bevor er schwer verletzt wurde. Die Gesamtzahl der Goldsäcke, die der Caped Crusader sammeln konnte, wird auf dem Bildschirm angezeigt, wenn der Caped Crusader schwer verletzt ist.  Das Ziel des Kreuzritters ist es, in jedem Spiel so viele Goldsäcke wie möglich von der königlichen Garde zu erbeuten, damit sie an die armen Pächter zurückgegeben werden können.  Um einen Goldsack einzusammeln, muss der Caped Crusader nur über ihn steigen.  Jedes Mal, wenn der Kreuzritter mit dem Kapuzenpulli einen Sack Gold ergattert hat, muss er zu seinem ursprünglichen Lagerplatz zurückkehren. Der Goldsack wird automatisch fallen gelassen, wenn der Kreuzritter mit Kapuze sich seinem Zelt nähert.  Der Kreuzritter mit dem Umhang muss sein Gold fallen lassen, bevor er wieder in den Wald geht, um weiteres Gold zu holen.   Auf diese Weise werden die Goldsäcke gezählt.   Der Spieler kann erst dann in den nächsten Level aufsteigen, wenn er die erforderliche Anzahl von Goldsäcken gesammelt und in das Zelt am ursprünglichen Lagerplatz gelegt hat.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harmony in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2700090/Harmony_in_the_Wild/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700090/extras/Hitw_logo_Final_2.png?t=1702558135"><br/><br/>Welcome to an enchanting world of <strong>Harmony in the Wild</strong>. As a young fox, you'll roam a captivating open world through forest, arctic and ocean while mending the delicate balance of dying nature. During the adventure you learn new abilities and a power of transformation to help you restore harmony back to your new home. <br/><br/>This game is a product of 6 game production students at Jamk during a 3,5 month period with the help of composer <strong>Kai Tuominen</strong> and voice actor <strong>Matti Mali</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag"><u><strong>Features: </strong></u></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Transforming fox​:</strong> Adapt to your surroundings by transforming into either an arctic fox or a red fox. <br/></li><li><strong>Open-world exploration:</strong> Explore vibrant forests, navigate icy terrains, swim through vast ocean and unravel the secrets of a fading ecosystem. <br/></li><li><strong>Various Main &amp; Side Quests​:</strong> Embark on a compelling journey with various main and side quests, each revealing new abilities for you to use. <br/></li><li><strong>Unique abilities​ such as:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Gliding <br/></li><li>Swimming <br/></li><li>Charged Jump <br/></li><li>Freezing <br/></li><li>Telegrab <br/></li><li>Rock Smashing</li></ul><br/></li><li><strong>Adventurous Companions:</strong>Befriend a diverse cast of animal companions, each offering unique insights and assistance on your quest. <br/></li><li><strong>Harmonious Gameplay:</strong> Enjoy a harmonious experience through a blend of exploration and narrative-driven gameplay, providing a peaceful yet engaging experience. </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><u><strong>Credits: </strong></u></h2><br/>Made by <strong>Lumo Creations:</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700090/extras/LumoCreations_logo2.png?t=1702558135"><br/><br/><strong>Valtteri Yli-Olli</strong> – Product Owner, Audio, Business <br/><br/><strong>Zsombor Faragó</strong> – Scrum Master, Programming, Publishing <br/><br/><strong>Jutta Mujunen</strong> – Programming, Implementation, World Building <br/><br/><strong>Sannina Salin</strong> – 2D Art, UI Design <br/><br/><strong>Saara Kämäräinen</strong> – 3D Art &amp; Implementation, Tech Art <br/><br/><strong>Aaron Wirenius</strong> – Design, Testing						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Minute Shopping</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2700100/Last_Minute_Shopping/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome customers, to [REDACTED] furniture store! We’re thrilled that you’ve chosen to silence your inner shopping demons by becoming our customer! Feel free to explore our store to your heart’s content! <br/><br/>Check out the upstairs area to find inspiration for your interior decorating journey, pick the product you wish to purchase, and check its price tag for the warehouse location! Then head downstairs, pick up a few loose items on the way, and finish your shopping spree at the self-serve warehouse! <br/><br/>After you’re done, be sure to come again! Our store will always offer you a fresh experience, with a new combination of products to buy with each shopping spree! The more you spend, the more we’ll earn! Win-win! <br/><br/>Just make sure not to leave your shopping till the very last minute! Shopping takes time, patience, and a calm mind, and doing this under time pressure is no simple task!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features </h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Immersive shopping experience! Feels just like the real thing!<br/></li><li>200+ products to purchase, each with its own ridiculous names and gags!<br/></li><li>Physics! Blow off some steam and cause as much mess as you want!<br/></li><li>Procedurally generated furniture stores! Just like the real thing!<br/></li><li>Tons of replayability!<br/></li><li>Swedish!<br/></li><li>Many jabs at capitalism and consumerism!<br/></li><li>It’s free! Your money is no good here! </li></ul><br/><strong>NOTE:</strong> Last Minute Shopping is a parody game! The game is not affiliated with any real-life company or property that isn’t listed in the credits!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liam FitzRoy kills everyone The game Part Zero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2704290/Liam_FitzRoy_kills_everyone_The_game_Part_Zero/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Liam FitzRoy kills everyone The game Part Zero is a 2d shooter inspired by old 3d shooters, it has encounters and dialogues with characters that will help or hinder each one in a different way during the course of the story, the idea here is basically to shoot everything We have to see and read the dialogues to try to understand the situation of the protagonist who lost his memories.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escape from Grustovia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2068980/Escape_from_Grustovia/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2068980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are an ordinary guy living amidst the apartment buildings of the country of Grustovia, but now the moment has come that will determine how fast you can run. You've received a draft notice, and an incredible adventure begins, one that will be remembered for a lifetime if you're not quick enough. You need to run or hide. For planned repositioning, you have several unique paths available: escape through the garages and attempt to cross the border or seek refuge in the metro catacombs. Which mode of transportation will be most suitable for the terrible roads of Grustovia, which border to cross is better, where to hide in the metro, and much more awaits you in the game "Escape from Grustovia"<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>You can steal a tractor<br/></li><li>Numerous diverse escape routes<br/></li><li>Multiple endings<br/></li><li>Underground apartments and a camouflaged gold reserve</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dirt And Flo</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2526070/Dirt_And_Flo/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2526070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In Dirt and Flo you can control one or other of these character wich have their own capacities to resolve puzzle and regain your spaceship.Dirt can move some object and throw a ball of dirt and Flo can glide , blow an allergenic pollen cloud and open the locks wich blocks your progression.<br>
<br>
Be careful of the lifeform of this planet ! they all want to beat you or eat you. To avoid that you can use the advantage of your biologic body to hide yourself and get invisible from their eyes !						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
