<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Bulwark: Falconeer Chronicles</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/290100/Bulwark_Falconeer_Chronicles/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/titleBannerDescr.png?t=1711475617"><br/>Bulwark: Falconeer Chronicles is an open world builder with freedom and expression at its core, allowing players to build sprawling towns, spires, and fortresses that become hubs for trade, or rallying grounds for conquests. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/building.gif?t=1711475617"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_2-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Reforge a world shattered by the decisions of those who came before you, tower by tower, wall by wall, sculpting from the daunting cliffs and perilous waters of an unforgiving landscape that refuses to be tamed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_3-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Devastated by the aftermath of a war 40 years prior, you are in command of creating the last great settlement upon the Great Ursee - a vast, fantastical oceanic world filled with lost myths, breath-taking vistas and danger. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_4-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Starting with humble docks and wooden jetties, you will scavenge resources and grow your settlement as your population and creations grow ever grander, sculpting monumental stone towers and battlements that scrape the skies, where airships and giant warbirds rule.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_5-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Create trade routes and strike alliances with other factions scattered across the waves, acquiring powerful Captains and Commanders to protect your creations and utilise their aid in exploration -  or muster your own battlegroup to strike at them, waging war upon your ancient enemies. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_6-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>This world and its choices are yours to make - what legacy will you leave behind? What creations will bear your name?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/combat.gif?t=1711475617"><h2 class="bb_tag">Rediscover The Great Ursee </h2>The next instalment in the series which started with the award-winning 2020 aerial combat game, ‘The Falconeer’, taken into a completely new genre.<h2 class="bb_tag">A World of History and Violence </h2>An open world, full of opportunity. Explore the widest reaches of the Ursee in search of resources and engage with splintered factions - allying with them to acquire their aid, or sending your own warband to raid their settlements.<h2 class="bb_tag">Defend Your Bulwark </h2>Recruit powerful Captains and Commanders, used to provide powerful units, shore up your defences and adorn your settlement with their own architecture and style.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build Without Limits</h2>Enjoy a cosy ‘Freebuild Mode’, devoid of the conflict and challenges present in standard play, you can build without the need for resources or upgrades.<h2 class="bb_tag">Chaotic Creativity </h2>Immerse yourself in building mechanics inspired by 3D modelling software and kitbashing, for a building experience that focuses on experimentation.<h2 class="bb_tag">Transcendental Soundtrack </h2>Award-winning composer Benedict Nichols returns to craft an eclectic soundtrack like no other, sculpting the audible landscape of the Ursee along with your creations.<h2 class="bb_tag">Share Your Creations </h2>Utilise an intuitive, flexible camera mode and time lapse replay feature to watch your unique creations grow brick by brick, then share them with the world<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Ffalconeer" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/Bulwark-Discord.png?t=1711475617"/></a><br/><br/>Secret Code -&gt; 20TSFCBW24AW						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1268590/Millennia/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fmillennia" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/616x152.png?t=1711472688"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Store_Page_City_Growth_animation_Steam-Loop.gif?t=1711472688"><br/>Create your own nation in Millennia, a historical turn-based 4X game that challenges your strategic prowess across 10,000 years of history, from the dawn of humanity to our possible futures.  Set the course of history and experience different timelines in every playthrough as you write an epic story through your actions.  Lead your people through times of crisis and ages of discovery, face great challenges and opportunities, and build a civilization that prospers through the ages.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Guide_Your_Nation.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Dictate the course of history across ten ages, from the first cities to space travel.  Accomplish certain objectives and you can move time into a Variant Age - an alternate history with new rules, new technologies, and new units.  But beware Crisis Ages; following a path of chaos and disorder may plunge the world into a future filled with war, sickness or ignorance.  Then again, a wise ruler can always turn a crisis into an opportunity....  Choose the path with care, as the ages you pass through will have a lasting impact on your people and the world.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Choose_What_You.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Customize your nation by adopting unique Nations Spirits over the course of your game.  Will you be a nation of warriors or explorers?  Are your people lead by a Great Khan or a builder of monuments?  Are you known for defining  pop culture or for dominating global finance?  What parts of your culture will reverberate across history?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Master_a_Deep.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Manage your economy with care and create a juggernaut of growth and construction.  Start with basic resources to gain food, wealth, and production.  As your advance, decide how to best convert these simple goods into more valuable products through research and improvements.  Specialize your regions, turning iron into weapons or tools, wood into paper or lumber, gold into coin or jewelry.  Ship surplus goods where they are needed, allowing the breadbasket of your empire to feed far-flung colonies or your industrial heartland to supply troops near your enemy.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Unlock_Technologies.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Pursue knowledge to research scientific and cultural advances, unlocking new units, buildings, and improvements to grow your cities or strengthen your armies.  Research Defense to train the first archers, Smelting to master iron production, or Guilds for making wine.  Variant and Crisis Ages feature unique alternatives, introducing everything from Cloud Estates in the Age of Aether to underwater cities in the Age of Utopia.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Achieve_Victory.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Achieve your ultimate success through a Victory Age.  Toward the end of the game (or earlier if your strategy is sound), dominance allows a nation to dictate the winning conditions.  The rest of the world must decide if they will struggle to achieve victory before the leader ... or oppose the leader's attempt.  Risk everything to take victory in the Renaissance or carefully plan for triumph in the modern era.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Millennia: Premium Edition includes the following content:</h2><br/><strong>Wolfpack Warband &amp; Eagle Archers cosmetics</strong><br/>Elevate the presence of your units in Millennia with the exclusive Wolfpack Warband and Eagle Archers clothings. Available instantly with the Premium Edition, this clothes pack unlocks unique wolf skin clothing for your Warband. Your Archer Unit receives eagle-inspired clothes, symbolizing their precision and keen sight.<br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Ancient Worlds</strong><br/>Take your first uncertain steps in a new era for humanity in Millennia: Ancient Worlds. Take control of your people before their first settlement, while they still wander as nomads.  Includes a new nomadic game start option, a new National Spirit, a new economic Good, and new Nation starting bonuses. <br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Atomic Ambitions</strong><br/>Unlock the mysteries of the atom and change the world forever in Millennia: Atomic Ambitions. The Premium edition adds ways to harness the power of the atom for the good of all humankind, but, there are also ways to turn the planet into a fallout-filled wasteland if you aren’t careful. Includes two new Ages, a new National Spirit, and nuclear options for the Strategic Warfare System.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1268590/Millennia/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fmillennia" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/616x152.png?t=1711472688"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Store_Page_City_Growth_animation_Steam-Loop.gif?t=1711472688"><br/>Create your own nation in Millennia, a historical turn-based 4X game that challenges your strategic prowess across 10,000 years of history, from the dawn of humanity to our possible futures.  Set the course of history and experience different timelines in every playthrough as you write an epic story through your actions.  Lead your people through times of crisis and ages of discovery, face great challenges and opportunities, and build a civilization that prospers through the ages.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Guide_Your_Nation.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Dictate the course of history across ten ages, from the first cities to space travel.  Accomplish certain objectives and you can move time into a Variant Age - an alternate history with new rules, new technologies, and new units.  But beware Crisis Ages; following a path of chaos and disorder may plunge the world into a future filled with war, sickness or ignorance.  Then again, a wise ruler can always turn a crisis into an opportunity....  Choose the path with care, as the ages you pass through will have a lasting impact on your people and the world.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Choose_What_You.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Customize your nation by adopting unique Nations Spirits over the course of your game.  Will you be a nation of warriors or explorers?  Are your people lead by a Great Khan or a builder of monuments?  Are you known for defining  pop culture or for dominating global finance?  What parts of your culture will reverberate across history?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Master_a_Deep.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Manage your economy with care and create a juggernaut of growth and construction.  Start with basic resources to gain food, wealth, and production.  As your advance, decide how to best convert these simple goods into more valuable products through research and improvements.  Specialize your regions, turning iron into weapons or tools, wood into paper or lumber, gold into coin or jewelry.  Ship surplus goods where they are needed, allowing the breadbasket of your empire to feed far-flung colonies or your industrial heartland to supply troops near your enemy.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Unlock_Technologies.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Pursue knowledge to research scientific and cultural advances, unlocking new units, buildings, and improvements to grow your cities or strengthen your armies.  Research Defense to train the first archers, Smelting to master iron production, or Guilds for making wine.  Variant and Crisis Ages feature unique alternatives, introducing everything from Cloud Estates in the Age of Aether to underwater cities in the Age of Utopia.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Achieve_Victory.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Achieve your ultimate success through a Victory Age.  Toward the end of the game (or earlier if your strategy is sound), dominance allows a nation to dictate the winning conditions.  The rest of the world must decide if they will struggle to achieve victory before the leader ... or oppose the leader's attempt.  Risk everything to take victory in the Renaissance or carefully plan for triumph in the modern era.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Millennia: Premium Edition includes the following content:</h2><br/><strong>Wolfpack Warband &amp; Eagle Archers cosmetics</strong><br/>Elevate the presence of your units in Millennia with the exclusive Wolfpack Warband and Eagle Archers clothings. Available instantly with the Premium Edition, this clothes pack unlocks unique wolf skin clothing for your Warband. Your Archer Unit receives eagle-inspired clothes, symbolizing their precision and keen sight.<br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Ancient Worlds</strong><br/>Take your first uncertain steps in a new era for humanity in Millennia: Ancient Worlds. Take control of your people before their first settlement, while they still wander as nomads.  Includes a new nomadic game start option, a new National Spirit, a new economic Good, and new Nation starting bonuses. <br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Atomic Ambitions</strong><br/>Unlock the mysteries of the atom and change the world forever in Millennia: Atomic Ambitions. The Premium edition adds ways to harness the power of the atom for the good of all humankind, but, there are also ways to turn the planet into a fallout-filled wasteland if you aren’t careful. Includes two new Ages, a new National Spirit, and nuclear options for the Strategic Warfare System.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outpost: Infinity Siege</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1566690/Outpost_Infinity_Siege/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1566690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1566690/extras/ENGIF.gif?t=1711468695"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Outpost Building</strong></h2>Explore the world, gather resources, merge and upgrade outpost units to build your own outpost.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Unique Weapon</strong></h2>Fully exploit the value of the unique XEN Firearm with different protoslag attributes, and utilize ammunition with diverse performance.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Loot &amp; Farm</strong></h2>Enjoy the abundant difficulty levels, diverse gameplay features, and distinctive maps of the exploration mode. Venture deep into the brand new zones full of hazards and opportunities, and harvest powerful outpost units.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Feature</strong></h2>Fight alongside friends on Recovery Day, or strive together to survive infinite waves of monsters in Endless mode till the last moment.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arma 3 Creator DLC: Reaction Forces</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2647760/Arma_3_Creator_DLC_Reaction_Forces/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647760/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">More From Rotators Collective</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1681170/Arma_3_Creator_DLC_Western_Sahara/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1681170/Arma_3_Creator_DLC_Western_Sahara/</a><br/><br/>Fight fires from above in the Cougar medium utility helicopter or swerve from the beaten track in the MOOSE pickup truck to take on tier-1 operations with new weapons and equipment, from pistols and rifles to remote-controlled mortars and micro-drones. <br/><br/>Reaction Forces Creator DLC is the ultimate response to any situation on the battlefield.<h2 class="bb_tag">HOW TO LAUNCH</h2><br/>Once released, the Arma 3 Creator DLC: Reaction Forces will be optional to install and load. To play Arma 3 with this DLC enabled, please visit the DLC section in the Arma 3 Launcher, make sure Reaction Forces are owned and loaded, then launch the game by clicking the PLAY button.<h2 class="bb_tag">KEY FEATURES</h2><br/><strong>Cougar Helicopter</strong><br/>The Cougar is a four-blade, twin-engine, medium-sized, utility helicopter that has seen extensive military and civilian use over the years. In its civilian role, it is primarily used for transportation and offshore support, as well as public service missions, such as search and rescue. Some variants even come equipped with an emergency flotation device, which mitigates the risks of ditching at sea.<br/><br/>For military use, the Cougar comes with variable pylon mounts for external weaponry. Some variants are fitted with a 20 mm chin-gun, vastly increasing its striking power and versatility as a gunship.<br/><br/>Take advantage of extensive customization options featuring different pylon loadouts and over 30 skins, which allow you to outfit the helicopter for every imaginable mission.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647760/extras/banner_heli_v5.gif?t=1711461889"><br/><br/><strong>MOOSE Pickup</strong><br/>The MOOSE pickup is a light-duty vehicle with a wide range of configurations, serving military and civilian sectors worldwide. It is often used as a means of short-range transportation, or simply as a dependable weapons platform for special forces and non-state actors. <br/><br/>With 40 available texture variants, as well as a plethora of visual customization options and multiple different weapons modules, you can tailor your MOOSE to stand out amidst the chaos of battle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647760/extras/banner_pickups_v3.gif?t=1711461889"><br/><br/><strong>120 mm Twin Mortar and Commando Mortar</strong><br/>The 120 mm Twin Mortar is a container-sized emplacement that can launch HE, smoke, or laser-guided rounds accurately at incredible distances across the battlefield. The Commando Mortar is a lightweight one-man mortar that can be easily assembled in the field.<br/><br/><strong>RC-40 Micro-UAV</strong><br/>Keep an eye and an ear to the skies - although if you hear one of these drones, it is probably too late! This incredibly compact UAV can be equipped with explosive or smoke charges, which can be detonated remotely or via impact with a target. A scout variant can laser designate targets while maintaining a low profile.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647760/extras/banner_mortars_v2.gif?t=1711461889"><br/><br/><strong>Two Rifles, Two Handguns, and Four Aircraft Weapon Pods</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Mk26 L5</strong> - An American-made, semi-automatic pistol chambered in .50AE popularized through 80s action movies - and yes, a gold plated version is available!<br/></li><li><strong>HADES H6</strong> - Manufactured in Germany, the H6 is a modern, ultra-lightweight and easy-to-handle 5.56 mm bolt rifle.<br/></li><li><strong>Veles</strong>  - Russian-developed dedicated CQB bullpup rifle with a high stopping power.<br/></li><li><strong>G19</strong> - Often used by military and police, a full-automatic capable pistol, designed and produced in Austria.</li></ul><br/>Additionally, this CDLC features new suppressors, optics, and special 5.56 mm armor-piercing ammunition are available for extra firepower!<br/><br/>There is also a lethal selection of heavy-duty weapons for aircraft mounts, capable of turning an innocuous transport helicopter into a devastatingly effective gunship:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>12.7 mm machine gun weapon pod<br/></li><li>20 mm cannon weapon pod<br/></li><li>DAR/DAGR x19 missile pod<br/></li><li>Tratnyr HE/AP x16 missile pod</li></ul><br/><strong>Equipment</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Leather Jacket outfit<br/></li><li>Shape Breaker helmet variants for AAF, CSAT, and NATO<br/></li><li>Heavy Combat Helmet<br/></li><li>New sleek and lightweight Heli Pilot Helmet and Coveralls<br/></li><li>Wildland Firefighter Fatigues<br/></li><li>Full Brim Hard Hat to offer maximum protection in exposed environments<br/></li><li>Duffle Bag - spacious and with iconic Armaverse branding!<br/></li><li>TNVG-B night-vision goggles with color-enhanced thermal imaging and a special filter for low-light conditions<br/></li><li>Carrier Lite Rig and Tactical Vest Rig variants<br/></li><li>Colored steerable parachutes and backpacks for civilians and parachute display teams</li></ul><br/><strong>Modules and Mechanics</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hit Indicator effects module<br/></li><li>Wildfire mechanics module<br/></li><li>Water bombing waypoint types (collect and drop water for AI)<br/></li><li>The Advanced Helicopter Flight Model HUD gauges can be enabled in standard mode (Options &gt; Game &gt; Difficulty &gt; Category: Reaction Forces)</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647760/extras/banner_weapons_v1.gif?t=1711461889"><br/><br/><strong>Open-World Campaign Scenario: "Air Control"</strong><br/><br/>Take part in a combined arms offensive! Prioritize your tasks, transport special forces, and fly logistics as a helicopter pilot, influencing battles below from above in this vast, multi-hour open-world campaign scenario playable solo or in up to 12-players in multiplayer .<br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer Scenarios: Training Day and FireSeason</strong><br/><br/>Familiarize yourself with the Cougar helicopter, learn how to use a helicopter bucket, and take part in water bombing drills on Malden. Once trained, you can go on duty and help protect the island during the current fire season.<br/><br/><strong>COOP and Singleplayer Scenario: "QRF"</strong><br/><br/>Respond to an emergency call and protect the HVT until reinforcements arrive! As a Quick Reaction Force (QRF), defend against waves of enemies and fight for your life against overwhelming odds in this new co-op game mode. Conserve your ammo and pick your targets carefully while working closely with a team of up to six people.<br/><br/><strong>Multiplayer Mode: "Cashpoint"</strong><br/><br/>A series of cashpoint robberies are happening all across Malden and Tanoa — will you stop the criminals responsible, or are you one of them? This is a Team Deathmatch scenario for up to 12 players in two uneven teams.<br/><br/><strong>Additional Content</strong><br/><br/>Rounding out the Reaction Forces package, comes a set of additional items including new static props, as well as over 1 hour of newly composed ambient music tracks.<br/><br/>Included with the download is a specifically curated soundtrack in high-quality digital format. The soundtrack includes 11 tracks with a total duration of 38 minutes, curated from the Reaction Forces ingame ambient music for the best possible listening experience outside of the game.<h2 class="bb_tag">ABOUT THE DEVELOPERS</h2><br/>This DLC is published by Bohemia Interactive and developed by the Rotators Collective - a small group of like-minded developers loosely assembled from all around Europe with over a decade of experience in making mods for a wide variety of games, including the top-rated Arma 3 mini-campaigns Callsign Minotaur and Dunes, as well as their previous project, the highly praised Western Sahara Creator DLC.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTH PARK: SNOW DAY!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1214650/SOUTH_PARK_SNOW_DAY/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1214650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From South Park Digital Studios, the studio that brought you South Park: The Stick of Truth, South Park: The Fractured but Whole, and South Park: Phone Destroyer comes the next chapter in the journey of the New Kid.<br/><br/>Join Cartman, Stan, Kyle, and Kenny, in three-dimensional glory, to celebrate the most magical day in any young child’s life - a snow day! A massive blizzard has thrown the town into chaos and, more importantly, canceled school.<br/><br/>Play with up to three friends, use matchmaking, or solo the game with ally bots and battle through the snow-piled town of South Park. Engage in frenetic, action-packed combat against warring factions in an all-new story where you make the rules. Equip unique weapons and deploy devastating, upgradable special abilities on a new adventure to save the world and enjoy a day without school.<h2 class="bb_tag">It’s a snow day, dude!</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle your way through the snow-covered town of South Park in this all-new 3D co-op game.<br/></li><li>A blizzard of epic proportions has blanketed the town of South Park and it’s up to Cartman, Stan, Kenny, Kyle, and you, as the New Kid, to save the town from an endless winter.<br/></li><li>Experience cooperative gameplay for the first time ever in a South Park game with up to three friends or ally bots - unleashing powerful, coordinated attacks on your foes.<br/></li><li>Equip and upgrade devastating melee and ranged weapons. Deploy special abilities and powers that will bring hordes of enemies and epic bosses to their knees.<br/></li><li>Use a wide range of iconic cosmetics and customize your New Kid with endless possible combinations from beanies to Cheesy Poof T-shirts to chin balls.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DORONKO WANKO</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2512840/DORONKO_WANKO/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							『DORONKO WANKO』 is a <strong>DORONKO Action</strong> Game.<br/>In this game, you can become a cute, innocent pomeranian.<br/>And you can make your master's home messy and dirty.<br/>Let's explore this beautiful house and make it dirty and muddy at will!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Action_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Action.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>Pomeranian can get muddy by "rubbing"  against the "mud" spread on the floor.<br/>Spread out the mud with "splash"!<br/>Let's make the whole area muddy and messy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Goal_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Goal.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>Sometimes you can find "hidden pome" when you are spreading mud all over the house.<br/>When you find all the "hidden pome", the "Good Smell Room" 's door will open.<br/>(Let's go inside quietly before others notice!)<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Damage_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Damage.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>More mud, more damage!<br/>You can check the total amount of damage you have caused from the ending “Receipt”.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Present_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Present.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>When you cause enough damage, you will receive a “gift”?!<br/>They will help Pome’s exploration by making it easier to splash mud and obtain key items.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Gimmick_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Gimmick.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>A little action can cause a huge damage?<br/>Use personal appliances and toys to get even muddier.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Badge_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Badge_EN.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>The Pomeranian's adventures will remain as a "badge of memory".<br/>A random move may get an unexpected badge.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Customize_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Customize.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>"Put on" the "Goods" and make your Pomeranian more pretty.<br/>Don't forget the special goods that can release mud!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GGST Additional Character 12 - A.B.A</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2524050/GGST_Additional_Character_12__ABA/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2524050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							This allows the character "A.B.A" to be used in-game.<br>
<br>
※This product is also included in a bundle. Please be careful not to make duplicate purchases.<br>
※The main game (sold separately) is required to use this product.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2510720/Artifact_Seeker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/DS.png?t=1711367082"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/11y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>The unique “Artifacts sharing code function” allows you to share the Artifacts you collect with your friends! !<br/>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/1y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/1z.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/2y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/gif1.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/3y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/3y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/4y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/4y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/5y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/5y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/6y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/6y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living With Sister: Monochrome Fantasy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2429860/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1711168850"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_1__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/>Living in a fantasy world, it's always been your dream to grow up to be a famous adventurer just like your father. Reality proves to be more boring than fiction, however, as your days are mostly spent doing odd jobs for the villagers. With your friends by your side, you enter the Tournament of the Eights and strive for something greater: the chance to become the top guild in the country. Will you realize your ambitions, or will your hopes slip through your fingers and doom you to a life of monochrome monotony?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_2__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/>As a member of your town's Adventurers' Guild, it's your job to protect the townsfolk. Go on hunts, kill dangerous beasts, and hone your abilities to better tackle whatever challenges tomorrow brings.<br/><br/>Once you get home from work, you'll have your sister to attend to. She's a very sickly girl who needs a lot of help. Manage your household finances well, build up your relationship with your sister, and who knows, perhaps you might even be able to solve the mystery behind her illness.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_3__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Big_Brother_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Little_Sister_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Kana_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Yui_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Kasumi_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Yukari_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Akatsuki_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_4__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><strong>Hand-Drawn Monochrome Art</strong><br/>Though it may lack color, this game's world is anything but colorless! The stunning black-and-white art is chock-full of personality and is sure to leave you with plenty of marvelous monochrome memories!<br/><br/><strong>Unique Combat System</strong><br/>With tons of bizarre and ferocious monsters to fight and dozens of unique skills to unlock, your adventures are sure to be full of challenge and excitement!<br/><br/><strong>Charming Characters</strong><br/>Build up your relationships with your guildmates and your sister to learn about what makes them tick and unlock character-specific abilities to further assist you in your quest to become the top guild in the country!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Chilla's Art] Shinkansen 0 | 新幹線 0号</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2793370/Chillas_Art_Shinkansen_0___0/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2793370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Shinkansen 0 | 新幹線 0号 is a game set in Japan where players are tasked with finding anomalies in the Shinkansen. (Japanese bullet train)<br/><br/><i><strong>Supporter content can be turned on and off at the title screen. (It is on by default) </strong></i><br/><br/><i><strong>Motion Blur and Headbob is turned off by default.</strong></i><br/><br/><strong>Controls:<br/><br/>WASD - Move<br/>Left Click - Interact　<br/>Right Click - Zoom<br/>Shift - Run<br/>ESC - Options</strong><br/><br/>Easy mode - There is an easy mode in the mainmenu available for everyone to enjoy<br/><br/>Auto-save: auto-save for each chapter<br/><br/>Endings: There are two endings<br/><br/><strong><i>If you encounter any technical issues, do the following:<br/><br/>-Update GPU driver<br/>-Lower the Graphics settings/Screen resolution<br/>-Update Windows OS<br/>-Check if your anti-virus software is blocking the game or its save data. (Save Data location: C:\Users\[YOURUSERNAME]\AppData\LocalLow\Chilla's Art, LLC\Shinkansen0)<br/>-Delete save, then try again (Save Data location: C:\Users\[YOURUSERNAME]\AppData\LocalLow\Chilla's Art, LLC\Shinkansen0)<br/>-Check if your PC meets the system requirements</i></strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2054970/Dragons_Dogma_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Note: There are other sets that include this item.<br/><br/>Set forth on your grand adventure, Arisen!<br/><br/>Dragon’s Dogma is a single player, narrative driven action-RPG series that challenges the players to choose their own experience – from the appearance of their Arisen, their vocation, their party, how to approach different situations and more. Now, in this long-awaited sequel, the deep, explorable fantasy world of Dragon’s Dogma 2 awaits.<br/><br/>On your journey, you’ll be joined by Pawns, mysterious otherworldly beings, in an adventure so unique you will feel as if accompanied by other players while on your own adventure.<br/><br/>All of these elements are elevated further through physics technology, artificial intelligence (AI) and the latest in graphics, to create a truly immersive fantasy world in Dragon’s Dogma 2.<br/><br/><br/><strong><u>Action that challenges your creativity </u></strong> <br/><br/>Wield swords, bows, and chant magick.<br/>The vocations in Dragon's Dogma 2 give you the ability to approach combat the way you want.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_01.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Company in your single-player experience </u></strong> <br/><br/>Players can customize their own main Pawn, who will always accompany your Arisen, <br/>and enter a covenant with up to 2 additional Pawns from other players through the network. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_02.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Facing the monsters in this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Beyond the town borders, you will encounter diverse monsters that inhabit the lands. <br/>You will need to decide between engaging in battles or finding alternatives; <br/>so be aware of your party’s setup, the terrain around you, and the monsters you face.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_03.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Inhabitants of this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Travelers, merchants, soldiers and other folk go about their daily lives. <br/>Preoccupied by their own objectives and motives, they all exhibit different emotions.<br/>At times, they may lead you to a quest by approaching you and asking for a favor. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_04.gif?t=1711067553"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cureocity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2612680/Cureocity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							We are "Bread On Board," a collective of independent game developers spread across four countries, united by our passion and meeting during a GameJam. <br/>Our game demo was born in the "BOOOM CHALLENGE", a GameJam by GCORES. With only 21 days, we created a game based on a given theme. After the competition, we even won the "Most Popular Game" award at an Online Game Trial Event.<br/>The full playthrough of our game will take about an hour. We hope to give you a short, but super heartwarming and loving adventure❤️.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/1.奇幻而治愈（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>A rookie adventurer fresh on the scene and a former mercenary who was transferred into an adventurer due to injury. Two protagonists with contrasting personalities will embark on an adventure of fantasy and healing together. In the mysterious ruins of an underground dungeon that lies in the depth of a jungle, what awaits them will be...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/2.两位冒险者（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>According to the tavern's adventurer logs, the team heading into the dungeon features a rookie adventurer and an ex-mercenary who is now working as a healer. The adventurer looks as charming as a doll, and the enthusiasm never disappears; the healer is cool and a bit traditional, acting as a guiding figure for their adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/>What stories have unfolded between these two contrasting characters, and what challenges will they face together in this adventure? The continuation of this adventurous story is yours to discover.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/3.注重手法的回合制解谜（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>"People think battles need powerful weapons, but strategy at hand is key." <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_3_en.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/>In "Cureocity," the power of your strategy is materialized as the numerical values of your hands in combat. You can swap different weapons or items held in your left and right hands to alter your character's attack and defense stats. You may also change "gestures" to focus attacks or land heavy blows on specific enemies.As you delve deeper into the dungeon, you will take the unique traits of monsters into consideration and discuss strategies with your allies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/4.你的选择决定冒险归途（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>In this adventure, you'll discover not only the secrets hidden within the dungeon, but also the truths about the world and the  characters themselves. When faced with contaminated monsters, you can choose to either fight them or attempt to purify them. Of course, you also have the option to let things take their own course.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_4_en.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/>With each decision,the fate of the protagonists may change. The end of this adventure... is yours to decide.<h2 class="bb_tag">About the Publisher</h2>GCORES PUBLISHING is an independent game publishing venture formed by GCORES, committed to bringing you more outstanding indie games from the BOOOM CHALLENGE.<br/>Feel free to follow our <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/44750639" rel="" target="_blank">publisher webpage</a> for future updates.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midnight Ghost Hunt</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/915810/Midnight_Ghost_Hunt/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/915810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>MIDNIGHT GHOST HUNT IS A <i>PETRIFYING</i> PROP HAUNT GAME TO PLAY WITH PALS! </strong><br/><br/>Lying in wait across a series of cursed locations, relentless spirits stalk the halls. Assigned to eliminate them are the Ghost Hunters, armed to the teeth with the ghoul-busting tech to banish them to another realm! Play both Ghost and Hunter in a chaotic 4v4 struggle between the living and the dead.<br/><br/><strong>TONGUE-IN-CHEEK HIDE-AND-SEEK</strong><br/>As a Ghost, conceal yourself inside seemingly harmless pieces of furniture to evade preying Hunters… but when their backs are turned, turn the environment against them with telekinetic bombardment. No chair, lamp, or grandfather clock is innocent in this hijinks-heavy frenzy.<br/><br/><strong>MIDNIGHT MAYHEM</strong><br/>The fun isn’t over yet...when the clock strikes twelve, the witching hour begins, and the Hunters become the Hunted. The tables turn and Ghosts become supercharged, giving Hunters a limited amount of time to survive their vengeful wrath.<br/><br/><strong>MURDEROUS 4v4 MULTIPLAYER</strong><br/>Play together and communicate with your team and ensure a triumphant victory, giving each other pointers on the paths enemies tend to tread. Create synergies with your team's abilities to outthink and outwit your opponents.<br/><br/><strong>HARNESS SUPERNATURAL ABILITIES</strong><br/>The restrictions of reality don’t apply to Ghosts, of course. Claim your supernatural powers, which include turning invisible, causing furniture to float, and conjuring a dangerous Ghostly miasma. Ghosts can even hide in plain sight by masquerading as a Hunter’s doppelgänger!<br/><br/>Ghostly Perks include dramatically increasing your weight, extending your possessing range, the ability to see nearby Hunters through walls, and much more. <br/><br/><strong>ARMED AND READY</strong><br/>Hunters must choose their weapons from a full range of hi-tech gadgets designed to cast out Ghosts from our plane of existence. Detect ghostly presences with the Spectrophone, Radar and Pathfinder, capture them with a Trap, and suck up their spectral remains with the Vacuum – or just blast them to smithereens with the Spectral Cannon, sledgehammers, harpoons, salt-spewing shotguns, and more.<br/><br/>Hunters can also select Perks to give them a special boost. Choose from an extra burst of speed, health-replenishing capabilities and a host of other powers to get ahead of the game.<br/><br/><strong>A BEVY OF BLOOD-CURDLING MAPS </strong><br/>Explore ten unsettling locations, including an abandoned theatre, eerie mansion and cursed carnival. Each map brings with it different tactical considerations and items to throw about… as well as plenty of opportunities to play tricks on the enemy.<br/><br/><strong>FRIGHTENING NEW FEATURES</strong> <br/>As it crept through Steam Early Access, Midnight Ghost Hunt picked up a gaggle of game-changing features, built on the feedback of its community of Ghosts and Hunters.<br/><br/>Dedicated servers and host migration support make setting up matches a breeze, while the Progression Tier and Challenge systems bring added competition to the hunt. Looking for less of the silly and more of the scary? The Experimental Darkness game mode lends a chill to the chaos. Not to mention crossplay, full controller support, and even the GhostMaster minigame to pass the time during the van ride to your next match!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horizon Forbidden West™ Complete Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420110/Horizon_Forbidden_West_Complete_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/extras/horizon_forbidden_west_cinemagraph_610x610.gif?t=1711473066"><br/><br/>Join Aloy as she braves a majestic but dangerous new frontier that holds mysterious new threats. This Complete Edition allows you to enjoy the critically acclaimed Horizon Forbidden West on PC in its entirety with bonus content, including the Burning Shores story expansion that picks up after the main game.<br/><br/>Explore distant lands, fight bigger and more awe-inspiring machines, and encounter astonishing new tribes as you return to the far-future, post-apocalyptic world of Horizon.<br/><br/>The land is dying. Vicious storms and an unstoppable blight ravage the scattered remnants of humanity while fearsome new machines prowl their borders, and life on Earth is hurtling toward another extinction.<br/><br/>It's up to Aloy to uncover the secrets behind these threats and restore order and balance to the world. Along the way, she must reunite with old friends, forge alliances with warring new factions and unravel the legacy of the ancient past.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>See every gameplay detail with Ultrawide 21:9 and Super Ultrawide 32:9 resolutions, as well as 48:9 triple monitor support.*<br/></li><li>Witness the Forbidden West coming to life, with NVIDIA DLSS 3 upscaling and frame generation, image enhancing NVIDIA DLAA and latency reducing NVIDIA Reflex. AMD FSR and Intel XeSS are also supported.**<br/></li><li>Customize graphic settings to your preference, with the potential for unlocked frame rates.**<br/></li><li>Take control with full support for the DualSense™ controller, including haptic feedback and adaptive trigger functionality.*** </li></ul><br/>* Compatible PC and 4K display device required. <br/>** Compatible PC required. <br/>*** Wired connection required to experience the full range of in-game controller features.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age of Water: The First Voyage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2841350/Age_of_Water_The_First_Voyage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The First Voyage is the very beginning of your Age of Water experience. Jump right into the intense naval combat, craft your first boats, explore the waterworld and get a good idea of what Age of Water is about. Don’t forget to wishlist the full game now!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_ship_anim.gif?t=1711025025"><br/><br/>Become a sea captain on a post-apocalyptic Earth completely covered in water and go on an adventure in a huge open world. Sail through storms, fight and trade, capture other people's boats or build your own, extract resources from the bottom of the ocean, reveal the secrets of the Age of Water world.<br/><br/><strong>Water post-apocalypse</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_1.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>The ocean destroyed a once great civilization, but people survived and adapted. They built settlements on the roofs of tall buildings and the tops of other man-made structures. People travel across the ocean in tiny boats and huge combat vessels. The ocean provides everything they need, including extractable resources on the seabed. And yet, the dream of real land is still alive.<br/><br/><strong>True open world</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_2.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Explore the world at your own pace, discover new settlements and meet their inhabitants. Complete tasks, search for and extract valuable resources from the bottom of the ocean, earn money on trade or simply sell the artifacts you have obtained, and when you get the idea of how this world works, build your own base.<br/><br/><strong>Hundreds of unique ships</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_3.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Build boats from scratch or modify existing ones. Players have access to dozens of hulls and hundreds of parts, from which they can assemble anything ranging from a small boat to a hefty vessel 30 meters long, and then install equipment, armor and weapons. It’s important not to forget to gather a team of good crewmembers so that there is someone to stand behind machine guns and cannons or do other work on board.<br/><br/><strong>Fierce naval battles</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_4.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Pirates are always waiting for you at sea, and in some cases more aggressive players even start to chase you, so do not forget to install enough guns on your deck.  You can destroy an enemy vessel, or you can capture it in battle and take it for yourself forever. Adventures might also get you into storming enemy fortresses and defending allied settlements!<br/><br/><strong>Personal naval base</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_5.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>This shelter is reliably protected from enemies, and it allows a player to organize the production of everything that the captain may need on it. Build factories for the production of equipment, weapons, hulls for boats of all sizes, as well as the necessary resources.<br/><br/><strong>Flexible balance between PvE and PvP</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_6.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>At first, you will only meet computer opponents, but later you can challenge other players if you are confident enough in your skills and gear. Always be on the lookout: if your task is to transport illegal goods, then other players may well take the quest to hunt smugglers. In Age of Water, everyone decides for themself who they are today - a peaceful traveler or a bloodthirsty pirate.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slice &amp; Dice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1775490/Slice__Dice/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1775490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Slice &amp; Dice is a tactical dice battle roguelike.<br/><br/>Take control of 5 heroes, each with their own unique dice. Fight your way through 20 levels of monsters and try to take on the final boss. If you lose a single fight you have to start over so be careful/lucky!<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/>- 3D dice physics, choose which dice to reroll<br/>- Simple turn-based combat<br/>- Level up a hero or gain an item after each fight<br/>- Randomly-generated encounters<br/>- Ridiculous combos<br/>- Undo actions as much as you like<br/>- Each turn is like a mini-puzzle<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/>- 128 hero classes (+99999?)<br/>- 73 monsters<br/>- 473 items<br/>- Too many modes<br/>- ∞ curses<br/>- Weird modding<br/>- Online leaderboards<br/><br/><strong>Credits</strong><br/>- Created by tann (it took ~7 years)<br/>- Pixel art by a3um<br/>- Music by Ziggurath, Aleksander Zabłocki, Louigi Verona, Cold Sanctum, Ro'sø, Andrew Goodwin<br/>- Trailer by Everdraed<br/><br/>I plan to not participate in any sales/deals/bundles. No AI was used to make this game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone in the Dark</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1310410/Alone_in_the_Dark/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Alone in the Dark weaves a chilling tapestry of psychological horror and Southern Gothic charm, reimagining the iconic game that set the benchmark for the genre. We invite you to join us on a journey into madness, where each encounter could be your last. With each step you take closer to unravelling Derceto's mystery, the eyes that watch from the darkness grow hungrier. Every bullet means the difference between survival and an unthinkable end. The next door you unlock could lead to a nightmarish realm offering nothing but slashing claws, grasping tentacles, and frayed sanity.  Journey to interbellum Louisiana, where an era of decadence hides a darker tale - of escape from past traumas and an intolerant society, into the waiting grasp of something darker, something that has patiently lurked for impossible eons. This is Alone in the Dark as you've never seen it - a skillfully-woven narrative of Southern Gothic elegance and eldritch madness that pays homage to its legendary origins while taking the next step forward in survival horror storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_VIPIntro_2.gif?t=1711356992"><h2 class="bb_tag">A Haunting Tale of Mystery and Madness</h2>Step inside Derceto Manor, an asylum shrouded in intrigue, guarding a terrible secret. Client Emily Hartwood and private investigator Edward Carnby embark on a harrowing quest for answers; Emily to the mystery of her missing uncle, Edward to the toughest case he will ever face, and both to questions they dare not ask themselves. This re-envisioned classic invites you to explore an unforgettable single player adventure rich with suspense, frights, and revelations that will test the limits of your imagination.<h2 class="bb_tag">Featuring Hollywood Talent</h2>Experience some of the greatest acting survival horror has ever seen through the performances of award-winning actors Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow) in their first videogame roles. Jodie and David’s immaculately captured likenesses breathe life into Emily Hartwood and Edward Carnby, lending a deeply personal aspect to Alone in the Dark’s story that demands it be played twice to get the full experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Tribute to Horror Pioneers</h2>Rediscover the essence of psychological horror in a game that respectfully nods to its 1992 origin, the game that established the survival horror genre. Alone in the Dark is your gateway to an experience steeped in the atmospheric dread of classic horror, with next-generation storytelling and gameplay. A must-play for fans of twisted tales, nerve-wracking exploration, and desperate combat.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Story That Challenges Reality</h2>Envisioned by Mikael Hedberg, acclaimed writer behind modern horror classics “SOMA” and “Amnesia”, Alone in the Dark’s intricate web of mystery delves into themes of trauma, faith, evil, and abandonment. Whether you choose to brave the nightmare as Emily or Edward, you will uncover secrets that defy everything you thought about videogame storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Atrmo_2.gif?t=1711356992"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore Derceto Manor in this reimagination of Alone in the Dark, a love letter to the 90’s cult classic horror game.<br/></li><li>Return to the roots of psychological horror and experience an atmospheric journey worthy of the game that started the genre.<br/></li><li>Dive into a world full of sounds that make your skin crawl with a haunting, yet mesmerizing doom jazz soundtrack.<br/></li><li>Enjoy the thrill of desperate survival in a world where reality starts to crumble, evil lurks in every shadow and ammunition is scarce.<br/></li><li>Experience this nightmare from either Emily Hartwood’s or Edward Carnby’s perspective and unearth the dark secrets of a gothic mansion.<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in a deep psychological story that goes beyond the realms of the imaginable, by Mikael Hedberg, cult horror writer of SOMA and Amnesia.<br/></li><li>See Emily and Edward brought to live by the Hollywood talent of Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow), who lend their voices, their appearance, and their formidable acting skills to the protagonists.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Riddles_2.gif?t=1711356992"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Park Baseball 25</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384620/Out_of_the_Park_Baseball_25/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_banner_1.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/>We are incredibly excited to announce <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong> - the special 25th Anniversary edition of our award-winning baseball strategy series. Can you believe it's been a quarter of a century? Out of the Park Baseball is not just a game - it's a legacy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_henry.png?t=1710574531"><br/><br/>If it happens in real baseball, it happens in Out of the Park Baseball! Discover new talent, draft the next superstar, negotiate with free agents, enter trade talks with other teams, build your dynasty and guide a franchise into an infinite future! As a manager, dive into the more hands-on management and set your team's lineups, pitching staffs, in-game strategy and call the shots from the dugout. You can oversee your league at a high level, or play out each game in the gorgeous 3D game mode, managing play by play or even pitch by pitch. OOTP has it all covered!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_badge.png?t=1710574531"><br/>Here are just a few of the new features coming to <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong>:<br/><br/><strong>A game-changing new Player Development Lab!</strong><br/><br/>Shape the future of your upcoming stars! You can channel your inner Player Development Director like never before. A modern new Player Development Lab is here for every team that allows you to give players individual programs to work on, developing them how you like. Do you want your hitter to work on improving their baserunning? Bunting? Contact? Would you prefer your pitcher to work on building up their stamina? Developing a new pitch? Velocity? It's all up to you - for each of your upcoming future stars!<br/><br/><strong>Massive Player Ratings and AI Upgrade!</strong><br/><br/>It’s the most comprehensive player ratings upgrade in the 25 year history of Out of the Park Baseball! Batting, Pitching, and Fielding ratings have been painstakingly modified to capture the essence of baseball, with modifications to Contact and Power for hitters, Movement and Stuff for pitchers, the addition of Catcher Framing and Stealing Aggressiveness, and much more. BABIP is now front and center for hitters and hurlers, while new internal ratings updates allow for even more flexibility for Commissioners around the world to adjust the game to their detailed delight. Plus, the AI throughout the game has been improved dramatically to deliver the most challenging OOTP experience ever! <br/><br/><strong>Even More Detailed Player Development Control!</strong><br/><br/>Delegate how each and every player on your team will spend their time day in, day out with coaches at practice. Want your power hitter to worry less about avoiding strikeouts and put that time and effort into working on his home run swing instead? Want your aging starter to spend more time practicing his control instead of spending that time worrying about his stuff? By allocating their time and focus to the areas you want, over time you can influence how players develop, maintain their skillset, and fight the aging curve.<br/><br/><strong>2024 Rosters and Rules!</strong><br/><br/>As always, Out of the Park Baseball features up-to-the-minute 2024 MLB rosters that get updated all season long, with every franchise represented from its big league club all the way down to the low minors, and everywhere in between! Plus, OOTP 25 features officially licensed leagues from South Korea (KBO) and Europe.<br/><br/><strong>Improved Historical MLB Modes!</strong><br/><br/>Set up historical MLB games in an all new streamlined way - and benefit from vastly improved historical player ratings! It’s never been faster or easier to experience the entire history of Major League Baseball, now producing even more realistic outcomes thanks to those comprehensive ratings and simulation engine upgrades.<br/><br/><strong>New Retro Visual Immersion!</strong><br/><br/>Watch games with a variety of experiences, including retro-style black and white, ‘50s-era, and ‘70s-era television presentations. Choose from all of these to play games, watch highlights, or just catch a ballgame from a bygone era!<br/><br/><strong>New Licensed Leagues!</strong><br/><br/>For the first time ever, Out of the Park Baseball features an officially licensed Honkbal Hoofdklasse league from The Netherlands and the British Baseball Federation from the United Kingdom! Look for their official clubs, players, competitions, and more!<br/><br/><strong>For the first time ever - an official partnership with the Baseball Hall of Fame!</strong><br/><br/>What happens when you combine the only game that has the entire history of baseball and the the greatest Hall of Fame in sports? An incredible, year-long journey! Join us as we partner with the Baseball Hall of Fame all season - and beyond. Explore Hall of Fame Plaques, with the official, accurate text for each Hall of Famer. Discover incredible Hall of Fame artifacts, curated and released in fun "exhibits" over the course of the season in concert with the Hall - and more surprises too. It's going to be amazing! <br/><br/><strong>Dozens of upgrades big and small!</strong><br/><br/>--&gt; Updated in-game engine base advancement and camera movements<br/>--&gt; A new manager decision history screen gives you a look back on your best and worst trades and transactions<br/>--&gt; Improved trade packages for prospect packages <br/>--&gt; Updated two-way functionality with injured players<br/>And much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/pt_store_text_banner2.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/><br/><strong>Perfect Team is back - bigger than ever!</strong><br/><br/>It’s an all-new Perfect Team! There’s nothing in the world like the incredible online competitions of Perfect Team. Featuring by far the largest player pool ever, and taking advantage of all the player rating and balance upgrades, this year’s Perfect Team is a whole new ballgame.<br/><br/><strong>Brand New Perfect Team Combinator Series Cards!</strong><br/><br/>Pulled non-live cards have a chance to be a special Combinator Series version of the card! Use other cards that share a link (for example being teammates) with the player to get a chance to boost the raw ratings of the Combinator Series card.<br/><br/><strong>A Perfect Team Tournament Roster Builder!</strong><br/><br/>Want to design rosters for the incredible array of Perfect Team Tournaments - all on your own? For the first time ever, Perfect Team will feature a Tournament Sandbox! You can tinker to your heart's content with varying rosters for every type of tournament, with no pressure. This long-requested feature makes its debut in Out of the Park Baseball 25!<br/><br/>In addition to the brand-new Tournament Roster Builder and Combinator Series, Perfect Team 25 also features:<br/><br/><strong>Team Chemistry</strong> - Players who played together in real life will get extra bonuses when on your roster together. Players gain bonuses for seasons they played together, as well as simply being part of the same team or from the same decades<br/><strong>Perfect Team competitions starting on the first day</strong>, including a huge Opening Weekend of Tournaments with big prizes and Perfect Team Championship Series qualifying from Day One! <br/><strong>New content all season long - and beyond!</strong> All new programs, missions, competitions, and excitement await you every day.<br/><br/>Out of the Park Baseball 25 runs on PC/Mac and features the American League and National League logos, the World Series trophy, official logos and jerseys for all 30 MLB teams and 15 KBO teams, over 150 Minor League Baseball league and team logos, and historical MLB logos.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Shire: Room One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517850/Toy_Shire_Room_One/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FkhSxB2MSgD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/Toy_Shire_-_Discord_Banner.png?t=1710352808"/></a><br/><br/><br/>Play through the <strong>three levels in Kevin's Room</strong> and defend your room against your old toys. Face Memphis-X in the final level and put a stop to his assault as he crushes your soldiers in an attempt to get to your base.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyVengeance.png?t=1710352808"><br/>You received new toys from your family. Isn't that lovely? Oh, it's for sure... <br/>Your old toys, though, aren't getting along as well. They are no longer cared for and have been forgotten. So what follows next? They're going to join together against you and assault your brand-new toys, so be prepared. But never worry! You're in luck since your brand-new toys are troops of green soldiers. They still require your aid though! Control, strengthen, and defeat the opposing forces! However, focus with care, the enemies you encounter might not be your old playthings!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/InteractiveTowerDefense.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Tower building alone won't be sufficient to repel incoming attackers. Build up your own troops in the best feasible positions, then unleash attacks into enemy territory. Never abandon your towers, and deploy your troops in accordance with the traits of the enemy. First, the attacking forces will attempt to get past your defenses. Build and improve towers to aid your army. By using unique abilities, you can support your troops and towers as well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/EpicBattles.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Safeguard your base against waves of attackers. You need to pick the right troops if you would like to prevail. Clean the paths and guard any open routes. Upgrade your troops and unlock new ones to take down the waves and claim victory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyRealm.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Enter a world and a narrative built around the toys that enriched your youth, including toy soldiers, dinosaur sets, robots, building blocks, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_3.gif?t=1710352808"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dune: Imperium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1689500/Dune_Imperium/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Header.png?t=1710955211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body0_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Experience the ultimate blend of strategy and intrigue as you navigate the treacherous landscapes of Arrakis in the award-winning board game <i>Dune: Imperium</i>!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle online, locally with AI, or against the formidable House Hagal.<br/></li><li>Earn Achievements that showcase your prowess as a leader.<br/></li><li>Embark on more than a dozen Challenges that will test your wit and cunning.<br/></li><li>Compete for badges in the rotating Skirmish Mode where no two games are the same!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body1_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Arrakis. Dune. Desert Planet. Raise your banner above the vast wasteland before you. As the Great Houses of the Landsraad marshal their forces and their spies, whom will you influence, and whom will you betray? A tyrannical Emperor. The secretive Bene Gesserit. The shrewd Spacing Guild. The ferocious Fremen of the Deep Desert. The power of the Imperium can be yours, but war is not the only way to claim it.<br/><br/><i>Dune: Imperium</i> blends deck-building and worker placement in a deeply thematic new strategy game where the fate of the Empire hangs on your decisions. Will you seek political allies or rely upon military might? Economic strength or subtle intrigues? A council seat… or a sharpened blade? The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body2_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>In <i>Dune: Imperium</i>, you'll step into the role of one of the leaders of the Great Houses of the Imperium in a struggle to control the planet Arrakis and the invaluable Spice it provides.<br/><br/>The game plays out in a series of ten rounds, each of which is defined by a new Conflict on the surface of the planet; some award critical resources, and some provide Victory Points that will propel you to dominance. But choose your battles wisely: spread your forces too thin, and you'll find your enemies growing too strong to oppose.<br/><br/>Each round, you'll draw a hand of five cards from your deck, which will get stronger over the course of the game as you acquire new cards. Each card can be played in one of two ways: To send an Agent out into the Imperium to gather resources, or to Reveal at the end of the round to purchase new powerful cards. You must maintain a careful balance to get the most of the resources available to you. How will you find your path?<br/><br/>As your game progresses, you'll vie for Influence with four factions of the Imperium: The Emperor, the economically powerful Spacing Guild, the mysterious Bene Gesserit, and the ferocious Fremen of the deep deserts. Earning Influence among the various groups helps you to earn the Victory Points you need...but will you compete with your rivals for their favor, or abandon alliances to pursue other opportunities?<br/><br/>Many strategies are at your disposal, and many paths to victory. The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Footer.png?t=1710955211"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Realm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1330000/Stolen_Realm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/GreenDragon.gif?t=1710442130"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TURN-BASED STRATEGY MEETS ACTION RPG IN THIS DUNGEON CRAWLING LOOTER</strong></h2><br/><br/>Stolen Realm is a <strong>simultaneous turn-based tactical dungeon crawling looter with action RPG elements</strong> where you control up to <strong>6 heroes, solo or through online co-op</strong>, venturing forth in adventures set in a high-fantasy, low-poly world. <br/><br/>Stolen Realm features an <strong>innovative turn-based combat system</strong> where <strong>simultaneous turns</strong> allow every team to take their actions at once, creating quick combat encounters that blend the tactical depth of titles like Divinity: Original Sin with the thrill of a fast-paced action RPG. Every battle scales based on the number of players involved, so you can easily jump in and out of the game even in the same playthrough!<br/> <br/>With a <strong>highly customisable class system</strong>, Stolen Realm allows you to create traditional RPG classes or break the mold to forge a unique champion of your own as you draw from a pool of hundreds of possible skills. Make a spell-slinging assassin, a priest born of frost, or a shadow-infused knight. Further customize your build by earning and reforging <strong>loot that truly changes the way you play</strong>: wield Abbadon the Soul Crusher, a mythic mace that raises slain enemies as skeletal warriors to fight for you, or unsheath the Bloodletter, a cursed sword that grants additional power at the cost of your lifeblood. D&amp;D-like events where attribute-based rolls will have permanent effects on your character add yet another layer to building a character that is truly your own. Anything is possible in this title that keeps compelling choices at the forefront of your experience.  <br/><br/>Keeping the core appeal of RPGs at its forefront, Stolen Realm ensures you spend all your time, fighting, building your characters and making compelling choices that determine your immediate path or effect your character, rather than getting bogged down in side quests and other RPG-bloat.   After each battle, pick your path between story events, resource gathering, shops and treasure rooms, until you get to the final boss of each <strong>procedurally generated adventure.</strong> If you’re up to a challenge, crank the difficulty up with <strong>6 different difficulty levels</strong> – or pick <strong>Hardcore Mode with permadeath</strong>, where every battle can be the last!<br/><br/>Also features <strong>Roguelike Mode</strong>, a fast paced version of the game where you can mix and match builds that are simply not possible in the traditional campaign!<br/><br/>Carve a place in history with your sword and magic. Rise to honor and glory in the battlefield. <strong>Recover the Stolen Realm.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/CycloneKick.gif?t=1710442130"><h2 class="bb_tag">PRAISE FOR STOLEN REALM</h2><br/>“The tactical depth of Divinity: Original Sin” - GamesRadar+<br/><br/>“we’re losing our evenings to… Stolen Realm” - TheXboxHub<br/><br/>“A gorgeous looking game” - PC Gamer<br/><br/>“You can be a fire warrior. You can be a healing necromancer. You can do all sorts of weird s**t.” - <strong>Sacriel</strong><br/><br/>“What I like about this game is it’s straight to the point. You just go in, you’re building your character, you’re getting items…and you just fight. There’s no bulls**t.” - <strong>Shroud</strong><br/><br/>“It’s rad” - <strong>Sequisha</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/Dwarven_Warmachine.gif?t=1710442130"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>KEY FEATURES</strong></h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play solo or with friends in up to 6 player online co-op, allowing you and your friends to wreak havoc amongst your foes<br/></li><li>Experience thrilling and fast-paced turn-based battles thanks to a simultaneous team turn system<br/></li><li>Full story campaign, roguelike mode and streamer mode<br/></li><li>Use over 300 skills in 10 distinct skill trees allowing for complete and flexible character customization<br/></li><li>Navigate hex-based battlefields where positioning is key due to battle shrines with special effects, exploding barrels and movable crates<br/></li><li>Find and loot over 700 unique items, fully customizable with modifiers, as you explore a wonderful world full of magic, secrets and unexpected dangers<br/></li><li>Co-op focused design keeps gameplay fast paced and strategic for up to 6 players <br/></li><li>Easy drop-in, drop-out design and automatic scaling that allows you to join or drop out mid-quest <br/></li><li>D&amp;D-like attribute-based rolls in special events that have permanent character effects<br/></li><li>Fight against over 200 types of enemies in battles that will be different every time: thanks to the Enemy Modifications feature, every creature you face on the battlefield will be unique<br/></li><li>A world that changes on each expedition, from frosty peaks guarded by the elusive Blue Dragon to overgrown jungles where the rock giants roam. <br/></li><li>Pick your path between battles, choosing where to go between story events, resource gathering, shops, fights, and treasure rooms until you get to the final boss of each adventure<br/></li><li>6 different difficulty levels<br/></li><li>Choose between Normal Mode and Hardcore Mode with permadeath if you want a real challenge!</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals Zero Hour</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732960/Command__Conquer_Generals_Zero_Hour/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals Zero Hour brings you closer to the enemy than ever before. Engage opposing forces at hot spots around the globe as you match strategies and arsenals against the new masterminds of modern war.<br/><br/><strong>Arsenal.</strong> Unleash the next generation of 3D new units and 20 new upgrades including China's ECM Tank, GLA's BattleBus and the USA's Spectre Gunship.<br/><br/><strong>Missions.</strong> Take on 15 new missions and make tomorrow's headlines. Root out a splinter cell in Cairo, steal deadly toxins from a U.S. lab and more.<br/><br/><strong>Generals.</strong> Match strategies and arsenals against 9 enemy commanders with unpredictable personalities and tactics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Tiberian Sun™ and Firestorm™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229880/Command__Conquer_Tiberian_Sun_and_Firestorm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Second Tiberium War begins in this legendary sequel to the original Command &amp; Conquer. <br/><br/>With his forces stronger than ever, arch villain and leader of The Brotherhood of Nod - Kane - is pitched in an epic battle against the world's war machine - the Global Defense Initiative. Now you must orchestrate the fate of mankind.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on Dynamic Battlefields. Nature itself provides tactical opportunities - destroyable and deformable terrain, forest fires, treacherous ice fields and many more surprises that help or hinder your strategies.<br/></li><li>Exciting New Strategies and Units. Jump Jet Infantry, Hover Tanks, Tunneling APCs, Hunter Seekers, Laser Fences, Mechanized Battle Units and many more.<br/></li><li>The "Veterancy" Factor. Units can become faster and stronger as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>New Kinetic Battlefields. Flying shrapnel, shock waves and crashing debris are just a few of the exciting new technologies developed to enhance the in-game experience.<br/></li><li>The mood and attitude of the battlefield comes alive like never before - covert night missions, searchlights and new defenses intensify the thrill and excitement.</li></ul><br/>Then take the battle further in <strong>Firestorm, the official expansion pack for the game</strong>. Includes all-new campaign missions, cinematics, and units to decide the future of mankind.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Renegade™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229890/Command__Conquer_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer gets up close and personal in this classic First Person Shooter for one of the most iconic franchises.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wreak Havoc</strong> - Experience the Command &amp; Conquer universe on foot as Havoc, wise-cracking GDI Commando.<br/></li><li><strong>Make Your Own Rules</strong>  - Take on the evil Brotherhood of Nod using your own mix of brute force, stealth, and strategy.<br/></li><li><strong>Assault at Ground Level</strong>  - Dish out the damage in either first or third person.<br/></li><li><strong>Total Access</strong>  - Sneak inside and explore full-scale structures, like immense Tiberium Refineries and the ominous Hand of Nod.<br/></li><li><strong>Grind the Gears</strong>  - Beef up your arsenal by commandeering lethal vehicles, such as Nod Buggies, Flame Tanks, and Mammoth Tanks.<br/></li><li><strong>Weapons of Mass Destruction</strong>  - Choose from a multitude of weapons, including the Tiberium Auto Rifle, Chemical Sprayer, and the devasting Personal Ion Cannon.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™, Counterstrike™ and The Aftermath™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229840/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_Counterstrike_and_The_Aftermath/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert</strong> pushed the envelope for the RTS genre in the mid-1990s and became one of the most iconic strategy games of all time. <br/><br/><strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert</strong>  gives you the opportunity to be more devious, cunning, and ruthless than ever before. Red Alert puts the fate of the world in your hands!<br/><br/><strong>Counterstrike</strong>, the exciting expansion pack to Red Alert, is full of clandestine activity, experimental technologies, and disavowed tactics. Includes 16 all-new missions, where you decide the ultimate fate of the struggle between the Allies and Soviets.<br/><br/><strong>In The Aftermath expansion pack</strong>, prepare for guerilla tactics, insidious strategies, and forbidden weapons. Includes 18 all-new missions and multiple units in a showdown that will test your mettle.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ and The Covert Operations™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229830/Command__Conquer_and_The_Covert_Operations/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The legendary RTS game which started it all. Will you side with the humanistic GDI or bring the world to its knees with Kane and the Brotherhood of Nod. Your adversaries are without mercy. And so are you.  <br/><br/>Includes the <strong>The Covert Operations</strong> expansion pack with a range of challenging new missions.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit Hole</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2831340/Rabbit_Hole/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/smaller.png?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Remember you will live.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Rabbit Hole is a fast paced, tough-as-nails 2D Platformer-RogueLike-Shooter inspired by popular roguelikes, made with a love for the genre. <br/>You are Disc, someone who was suddenly brought to the Rabbit Hole. <br/>Collect guns, fight foes and meet strange new characters on your descent to the bottom, all in an attempt to find your heart again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/1.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“This place is like its own ecosystem. A big living breathing mess.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Every run is different. Enjoy hours of replayable content through randomly generated floor layouts and 50+ weapons to collect and use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/2.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Hey, hey, hey! How's my favorite anxiety-fueled nutjob!”</i></strong><br/><br/>Unlock new characters with diverse playstyles. Each of the 6 unlockable characters keep gameplay fresh and give a unique perspective on the gameplay loop.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/3.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“There was a blank line, almost as if I had erased it”</i></strong><br/><br/>Discover the truth that lies beneath the surface. Collect books and fill out your library to understand its unseen history. In the end, you may even come to understand yourself?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<br/><br/>※ <i>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</i> is the free-to-play version of <i>Meta-Ghost: The breaking show</i>, to showcase some of the gameplay content.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709870080"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hide for Cat - all for the best -</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2607760/Hide_for_Cat__all_for_the_best/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>[A talented cat hides "floors and walls"]</strong><br/><br/>This game is a 2D puzzle action game where you aim to clear the world in a world where the terrain changes exactly as you see it by hiding floors and walls so that they are no longer visible. In order to reach its owner, the cat, the main character, progresses through seemingly impossible stages by hiding and erasing walls and floors.<br/><br/>The appeal of this game is that you can change the terrain and carve your own path to the goal.<br/><br/><strong>[Simple operation method]</strong><br/>In addition to basic movement and jumping, you will use "black boxes" to hide walls and floors to conquer the game. A "black box" appears while you click the mouse, and by hiding the terrain, it is treated as if the terrain does not exist at that location and you can pass through it. You will conquer various stages with this intuitive operation.<br/><br/><strong>[Two different modes]</strong><br/>This game has two modes: a ``puzzle'' mode where you can have fun and have casual fun, and an ``action'' mode where you use gimmicks to reach the goal.Even with the same ``hiding floors and walls'' element, you can have different fun.<br/><br/><strong>【Stage】</strong><br/>There are over 50 stages in total! A variety of stages await you, from easy ones to highly difficult ones to ones with a few quirks!<br/><br/><strong>[Story]</strong><br/>The main character, a cat named ``Hyde,'' goes into an impossible labyrinth in order to find his owner who disappeared one day. She uses her research on ``the power to block out existence and make it impossible to even touch'' to advance through a labyrinth that seems impossible to conquer, with walls and doors buried.<br/><br/><strong>[Distribution guidelines]</strong><br/><br/>Game distribution/live commentary: OK for individuals and corporations<br/>Spoiler: OK<br/>Monetization: OK<br/>Distribution platform: No particular restrictions<br/><br/>・If you would like to broadcast or provide live commentary, we would appreciate it if you could write the following information!<br/>Steam URL						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crystal Guard TD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2846100/Crystal_Guard_TD/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Introducing Crystal Guard TD, a dynamic twist on tower defense!<br/><br/>Make strategic choices in a shop where you're presented with three randomly selected tower options. Spend wisely and combine three identical towers to level them up.<br/><br/>Features <ul class="bb_ul"><li> 20 different towers to try<br/></li><li> 25+ different Power ups<br/></li><li> Pixel graphics<br/></li><li> In-game tutorial slides<br/></li><li> 6 Levels to complete</li></ul><br/>Your mission? Defend your crystal shrine against 20 waves of relentless robots. Can you outwit your enemies and emerge victorious?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELECTROBASIS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2766540/ELECTROBASIS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766540/extras/SteamGif.gif?t=1711490550"><br/><br/><br/>Hundreds, if not <strong>THOUSANDS</strong> of years ago, a Biblical rapture fell upon the Earth, leading for angels to walk beside man, in effort to make humankind more holy living by example. Which, nowadays, isn’t all that sacred of a concept - <strong>angels are everywhere!</strong> THEY’ve integrated human characteristics into their own culture, rather than vice versa.<br/><br/>                              <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766540/extras/SteamPageLore.gif?t=1711490550"><br/><br/>Made up of pure electricity, cherubs take up object heads to anthropomorphize their form. They own businesses, live in casinos, and are free to gamble their heart away. <strong>YOU</strong>, as a fallen angel, crashland <strong>SMACKdab</strong> in the center of a casino in Vegas - LITERALLY crashland. By playing this game you agree to clean-up duty*, fixing up the spark inside! Start with fixing up the casino herself by turning back on the power, and then expand into the happiness of the residents in the rooms upstairs.<br/><br/>                              <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766540/extras/SteamPageGifIntro.gif?t=1711490550"><br/><br/><br/><strong>INCLUDES:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A casino and hotel to explore!<br/></li><li>Five different residents that have something wrong with them!<br/></li><li>Exposition dump in text form for YOUR, yes your, eyeballs to scan over!<br/></li><li>2010s dance party ending!<br/></li><li>At least one rat<br/></li><li>Music from famous musician VEN! You know Ven, don’t you?</li></ul><br/><i>katabasis</i> (n.) <br/>a mytheme or trope in which the hero embarks on a journey to the underworld<br/>any journey downwards or fall						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOG® – The dog takes the hindmost</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2512010/DOG__The_dog_takes_the_hindmost/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The dog takes the hindmost! </strong><br/>Looks like Ludo, but it's DOG®. In this game, you also have to safely bring your four game pieces into your home area. The difference is that they are moved using cards that have a few surprises in store for you. Team spirit is important, because you can only win together.<br/><br/>Highlights:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Different game modes <br/></li><li>For uo to 6 players<br/></li><li>Game boards with different looks</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yatzi</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2512040/Yatzi/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Skillful combination is half the battle!</strong><br/>It's quite tricky to roll a YATZI: Roll five dice with the same number in three tries. This classic dice game thrills players thanks to its simple game rules and exciting gameplay. You can’t be sure who has the most points until the very end.<h2 class="bb_tag">Highlights:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Different game modes <br/></li><li>Game boards with different looks</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal Kart Racer 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2649820/Animal_Kart_Racer_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2649820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Three, two, one - STEP ON IT!</h2>Anything goes in these races: Risky overtaking manoeuvres, shameless crashes and insane pile-ups. Hurtle through deep gorges, glittering diamond caves, icy polar regions and yawning canyons. Dodge obstacles at full speed, catapult your vehicle over jumps and fire items at your opponents.<br/>Give it your all, achieve your best time and win the trophy!<br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>20 fun characters with cool vehicles<br/></li><li>6 action-packed cups with 24 fast-paced race tracks<br/></li><li>Single race or tournament<br/></li><li>Multiplayer mode for daredevil players <br/></li><li>Even more action, even more power, even more stunts!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backgammon + Checkers + Mills</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2673570/Backgammon__Checkers__Mills/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover three exciting board games!</h2><br/>Backgammon, checkers and mills are among the oldest strategic games in the world and are played around the globe. They require concentration, strategic thinking and a bit of luck with the dice. Lovingly designed game boards and the option of adapting the rules to your own habits ensure fun and variety. <br/>The popular board game classics for two players are ideal for grey rainy days, cosy game evenings or simply as a pastime. If you don't have a game partner, you can play challenging games against artificial intelligence. An entertaining collection of games for all ages!<br/><br/>• Game boards with different looks<br/>• Customisable rules<br/>• In pairs or alone against the AI						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood Midnight Blossom</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2503260/Blood_Midnight_Blossom/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2503260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The main character is an ordinary girl named Annihilation, who lives in a small town A. She inherits a huge debt from her father and is desperate to find a way out. On the street, she meets a stranger in a raincoat, called Catharsis, who offers a demonic part-time job for a week.<br/><br/>Catharsis is a vampire who lives in a world hidden from the eyes of ordinary people. For hundreds of years she has been looking after this city and does not mind lending a helping hand to it’s inhabitant. But there is one problem – the existence of Catharsis is coming to an end, her soul is decaying and in a week she will die in case she cannot ascend to her ancestors. To do this, she needs a human guide who will extract demonic energy for the ritual. Annihilation finds their agreement fair and agrees. <br/>But there is a nuance.<br/><br/>Will the girl manage her task? Why does she have an ability to collect demonic energy? And where did her father’s debt come from? All this secrets will reveal the Blood Midnight Blossom.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>High-Quality anime style graphics<br/></li><li>Dark atmosphere<br/></li><li>Full HD 1080p screen resolution</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragons Legacy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2520410/Dragons_Legacy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2520410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dragons Legacy is an online dragon survival sandbox game set in a large, beautiful, open world with day/night cycles. Rule the world as one of several dragon species such as the Flame Stalker Dragon, Shadow Scale Dragon, or the Acid Spitter Drake.<br/><br/><strong>Features Include:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>    Survive! You come into the world as a hatchling and must eat, drink, survive, and grow to become an adult.<br/></li><li>    Online Steam Multiplayer. Play with other people. Some creatures are players, some are AI. It all takes place on a Dedicated server that you or someone  else is hosting.<br/></li><li>    Huge 16x16km Map. The world is huge and beautiful with forests, grasslands, lakes, canyons, and swamps.<br/></li><li>    Clans. Join your friends or start your own clan complete with clan chat, clan leadership, and other clan features.<br/></li><li>    Special abilities! Some dragons can fly, breath fire, spit acid, and even turn invisible!<br/></li><li>    Growth. Your dragon grows over time. You need to eat and drink to survive to the adult stage. <br/></li><li>    Movement. Dragons can fly, they can swim, they can walk, run, trot, and even sleep! Some can even swim under water!<br/></li><li>    Physics-Based Flight. Experience realistic, physics-based flight that is easy to learn and difficult to master.<br/></li><li>    Fire! Dragons can breathe fire, some spit acid, some shoot plasma. Each dragon species is different and has different stats.<br/></li><li>    Nesting. Dragons can lay eggs which can then be hatched by players, each egg inherits stats from each parent. Or you can spawn into the game with randomly assigned stats. Each dragon will have slightly different stats within the range of its species.<br/></li><li>    End game. The game is more than just growing and surviving. After reaching adult, you can unravel the mystery that will allow your dragon to grow stronger, even larger, becoming an Elder dragon of your species.<br/></li><li>    Friends. Dragons Legacy is a social game where players are able to chat and form groups and clans together.<br/></li><li>    Compatibility. Dragons Legacy runs on Windows and Linux, Laptops and the Steam Deck using older gen hardware.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCP: Blackout</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/963400/SCP_Blackout/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/963400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>READ THIS!</strong><br/>SCP: Blackout is no longer being developed, that is why it is now free! The hard drive that had the project got corrupted, so I no longer have the project or any backups to be able to work on it!<br/><br/>The game is fully playable, though VR will likely slowly go out of date. I'm sorry if you run into bugs or small issues, I won't be able to fix them, I'm sorry.<br/><br/><br/><strong>Overview:</strong><br/>      SCP: Blackout is a Desktop/VR game. It is a surreal horror game with a branching narrative. As a new D-Class transferred to Site-50, you must decide what you want to do as you navigate through the facility trying to survive various malicious SCP entities, determining what choices to make, and collecting pieces of the story to truly understand what is going on. <br/><br/><br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>VR (Vive and Oculus) OR normal desktop.<br/></li><li>An immersive horror atmosphere.<br/></li><li>Branching narrative with semi-rouge-like features to ensure every play through is different.<br/></li><li>Different story lines resulting in eight different endings.<br/></li><li>Choices that impact the game world itself, rewarding or punishing the player for their actions.<br/></li><li>Over 10 SCP monsters to learn and evade.<br/></li><li>Different back stories on SCPs to collect and learn about through written, audio, and computer logs. <br/></li><li>Secondary story arcs and mysteries to uncover about the site, the true motives of Dr. Slate and Dr. Millar, and more.<br/></li><li>Multiple gamemodes.<br/></li><li>Tons of secrets to uncover and keep you busy and guessing.</li></ul><br/>-Licensing-<br/>Content relating to the SCP Foundation, including the original SCP Foundation logo, is licensed under Creative Commons ShareAlike 3.0 – the base concept originates from the SCP Wiki and its authors. SCP: Blackout, being derived from this content, is released under Creative Commons ShareAlike 3.0 The source files of Unreal Engine 4 and all other third party software are the properties of their respective owners and not released under CC-BY SA. In addition, certain third-party and first-party assets are the properties of their creators and not released under CC-BY SA						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limb From Limb</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2866710/Limb_From_Limb/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2866710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The Raymond Mitchell Association Welcomes You </strong> <br/>Limb From Limb is a card roulette game about surviving encounters against a monster with your fingers as a sacrifice for losing. Between encounters, navigate your way across a board of randomized events that forces you to consider what path you take out of this accursed experiment. <br/><br/><strong>Fighting Patient Zero</strong><br/>Engage with a patient in a lethal card game of chance. Draw from a deck of 52 cards, some of which will cost you a finger to proceed. <br/><br/><strong>Collect Items</strong><br/>Gather from a pool of 10 different items, each with its own personality and effect. Choose which items you want to take into the encounters, but be meticulous, as once-used items are gone forever.<br/><br/><strong>Escape</strong><br/>Traverse through the hospital using a game board and your innate strategy to succeed in the RMA program. Each attempt brings a series of mixed events to define a new experience for every patient.<br/><br/><strong>Content Warning</strong><br/>This game may potentially trigger seizures for people with photosensitive epilepsy. Player discretion is advised.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armored War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1631530/Armored_War/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1631530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Armored War is a realistic tactical first-person shooter set in the realities of modern conflict. Take part in ground battles using a full arsenal of weapons and equipment.</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Features:</strong></h2><li><strong>Realistic battles</strong><br/><br/></li><li><strong>Variety of different locations</strong><br/><br/></li><li><strong>Several game modes</strong><br/><br/></li><li><strong>Weapons with customization and attachments</strong><br/><br/></li><li><strong>Character customization with camouflages</strong><br/><br/></li><li><strong>Air vehicles for support</strong></li></ul><br/>Game in Beta stage, you may notice bugs and shortcomings. There is only one developer						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roll the Ball</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2641460/Roll_the_Ball/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2641460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a thrilling journey with <strong>Roll the Ball</strong>, a captivating casual game that promises hours of excitement! Dive into vibrant visuals across three unique biomes as you race against the clock to reach the finish line. Choose from three engaging game modes, including a story mode! With over 60 meticulously crafted levels to explore, Roll the Ball offers endless fun for players of all skill levels. Immerse yourself in physics-driven gameplay, mastering ball control to overcome each challenge. Collect coins, unlock hidden trophies, and customize your ball with over 30 unique skins. With no checkpoints to hold you back, every twist and turn presents a new opportunity to test your skills. Enjoy a dynamic soundtrack and immersive voice-over narration as you conquer each level. Prepare for the ultimate challenge with Speed Run mode, where even the most skilled players will face their toughest test yet. <br/><br/><strong>Roll the Ball—where excitement meets endless possibilities. Are you ready to roll?</strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TIME RUSH</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2641460/extras/RollTheBall_TimeRushGIF_v4.gif?t=1711479137"><br/><br/>Time Rush Mode thrusts players into a whirlwind of excitement as they navigate each level against the relentless ticking of the clock. As players traverse the levels, they may encounter Timur, who subtly reveals morsels of the game's backstory, enriching the journey with layers of depth and intrigue.<br/>But it's not just about speed – players must also keep their eyes peeled for valuable coins scattered throughout the levels. These coins open the door to a treasure trove of customization options, allowing players to deck out their ball in a dazzling array of skins. And with the number of coins collected directly influencing the coveted star rating awarded at the end of each level, every coin becomes a stepping stone to glory.<br/>But the adventure doesn't end there. In their quest for mastery, players will uncover hidden trophies tucked away in the farthest corners of the game world. These elusive prizes serve as badges of honor, adding an extra layer of challenge and reward to the already exhilarating gameplay.<br/>With 30 pulse-pounding levels to conquer and an additional 6 bonus levels nestled within three distinct biomes, Time Rush Mode promises an epic odyssey through a world brimming with excitement and discovery.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHALLENGE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2641460/extras/RollTheBall_ChallengeGIF_v1.gif?t=1711479137"><br/><br/>In Challenge Mode, players must endure for a set duration to advance to subsequent levels. This mode introduces the ability to jump and activate slow motion, though the latter impacts the potential star rating at level completion. Each use of slow motion deducts one star from the achievable total, with a maximum of three stars per level. Prepare to face an array of challenges, including confrontations with frenzied balls, snowmen, and dynamic platforms. With 20 core levels and 4 bonus stages, a variety of tests awaits eager players.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SPEED RUN</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2641460/extras/RollTheBall_SpeedRunGIF_v1.gif?t=1711479137"><br/><br/>Embark on a speed run like no other, where time is but a measure of your mastery. No strict time limits constrain you; instead, your journey's duration is the ultimate gauge of your skill. Conquering the heights of this world demands precision, perseverance, and the willingness to confront numerous obstacles strewn along the path. With the finish line set at a formidable 1000 meters, expect a challenging ascent filled with traps and trials. As you navigate this arduous terrain, Timur will offer guidance and companionship to Sparky, the intrepid ball at the heart of the adventure.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>STORY</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2641460/extras/RollTheBall_StoryGIF_v1.gif?t=1711479137"><br/><br/>In the Prelude mode, players embark on a singular journey orchestrated by Timur to test the mettle of Sparky, a creation born from the ingenuity of Timur and his grandfather. However, as the journey climaxes, an unexpected twist sends Sparky on an unforeseen path, setting the stage for a tale of resilience and redemption. Beyond this introductory chapter, Sparky's encounters with Alex will continue to shape the unfolding saga across various game modes.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2></strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Immersive physics-driven gameplay that brings every movement to life, offering a dynamic and engaging experience.<br/></li><li>Embark on an exhilarating journey through four distinct game modes, each offering its own unique challenges and thrills.<br/></li><li>Collect coins and strive for star perfection, unlocking a plethora of rewards and bonuses as you progress.<br/></li><li>Discover hidden trophies scattered throughout the game world, adding an extra layer of excitement and achievement to your adventure.<br/></li><li>Customize your experience with a selection of 30 visually stunning skins, allowing you to personalize your gameplay and stand out from the crowd.<br/></li><li>Test your skills and determination in a game without checkpoints, offering a true test of endurance and perseverance.<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the rich auditory landscape of the game with a diverse range of captivating soundtracks, enhancing every moment of your gameplay.<br/></li><li>Harness the power of slow motion to navigate tricky obstacles and conquer challenging levels with precision and finesse.<br/></li><li>Uncover the gripping backstory behind the game's universe, adding depth and intrigue to your journey as you unravel its secrets.<br/></li><li>Master a variety of different Steam achievements, rewarding your skill and dedication as you conquer each challenge and milestone.<br/></li><li>Enjoy seamless immersion with localization available in 10 diverse languages, ensuring players from around the world can fully experience the game's captivating narrative and gameplay.<br/></li><li>Dive deeper into the story with immersive voice-over narration.</li></ul><br/>Powered by Unreal Engine!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zerko</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2862990/Zerko/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2862990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Some call it reverse sudoku, while others call it a nullification game, but it's Zerko - a puzzle game filled with shapes, numbers, and a straightforward goal: make every number zero.<br>
<br>
To achieve this, you need to strategically place blocks of various shapes and values so that the numbers on the board effectively "remove up" to zero.<br>
<br>
Like all my games, this one too is about relaxation... Just chill. There are no points, no time pressure, no data collection, no in-app purchases, no ads, no nonsense ;) My only hope is that you'll enjoy it and that I'll be able to add new content and levels for you in the future.<br>
<br>
Relaxing audio by: Marek Koszczyński						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loop Theory</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2787960/Loop_Theory/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Immerse yourself in the game created on the Unreal Engine 5. Solve puzzles, make your way through various rooms, use objects and find out more about the fate of the main character. <br/><br/><strong><i>Average time to complete the game: 45 minutes</i></strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787960/extras/banner.png?t=1711476459"><br/><br/>This is a story-oriented horror game. Take part in the mysterious investigation of the crimes of the most ordinary family. The narrative in the game does not provide direct answers related to the paranormal story of the main character, so you will have to collect the missing pieces of the puzzle yourself. Will you be able to get answers to questions about your character's past and present? During the passage of the plot, you will come across notes and inscriptions, study them!<br/><br/><strong>Waiting for you:</strong><br/>- A mysteriously changing house<br/>- Riddles<br/>- An ambiguous plot<br/><br/><strong>ATTENTION:</strong> The game contains images of violent scenes that can have a negative impact on the psyche.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulwark: Falconeer Chronicles</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/290100/Bulwark_Falconeer_Chronicles/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/titleBannerDescr.png?t=1711475617"><br/>Bulwark: Falconeer Chronicles is an open world builder with freedom and expression at its core, allowing players to build sprawling towns, spires, and fortresses that become hubs for trade, or rallying grounds for conquests. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/building.gif?t=1711475617"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_2-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Reforge a world shattered by the decisions of those who came before you, tower by tower, wall by wall, sculpting from the daunting cliffs and perilous waters of an unforgiving landscape that refuses to be tamed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_3-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Devastated by the aftermath of a war 40 years prior, you are in command of creating the last great settlement upon the Great Ursee - a vast, fantastical oceanic world filled with lost myths, breath-taking vistas and danger. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_4-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Starting with humble docks and wooden jetties, you will scavenge resources and grow your settlement as your population and creations grow ever grander, sculpting monumental stone towers and battlements that scrape the skies, where airships and giant warbirds rule.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_5-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Create trade routes and strike alliances with other factions scattered across the waves, acquiring powerful Captains and Commanders to protect your creations and utilise their aid in exploration -  or muster your own battlegroup to strike at them, waging war upon your ancient enemies. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_6-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>This world and its choices are yours to make - what legacy will you leave behind? What creations will bear your name?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/combat.gif?t=1711475617"><h2 class="bb_tag">Rediscover The Great Ursee </h2>The next instalment in the series which started with the award-winning 2020 aerial combat game, ‘The Falconeer’, taken into a completely new genre.<h2 class="bb_tag">A World of History and Violence </h2>An open world, full of opportunity. Explore the widest reaches of the Ursee in search of resources and engage with splintered factions - allying with them to acquire their aid, or sending your own warband to raid their settlements.<h2 class="bb_tag">Defend Your Bulwark </h2>Recruit powerful Captains and Commanders, used to provide powerful units, shore up your defences and adorn your settlement with their own architecture and style.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build Without Limits</h2>Enjoy a cosy ‘Freebuild Mode’, devoid of the conflict and challenges present in standard play, you can build without the need for resources or upgrades.<h2 class="bb_tag">Chaotic Creativity </h2>Immerse yourself in building mechanics inspired by 3D modelling software and kitbashing, for a building experience that focuses on experimentation.<h2 class="bb_tag">Transcendental Soundtrack </h2>Award-winning composer Benedict Nichols returns to craft an eclectic soundtrack like no other, sculpting the audible landscape of the Ursee along with your creations.<h2 class="bb_tag">Share Your Creations </h2>Utilise an intuitive, flexible camera mode and time lapse replay feature to watch your unique creations grow brick by brick, then share them with the world<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Ffalconeer" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/Bulwark-Discord.png?t=1711475617"/></a><br/><br/>Secret Code -&gt; 20TSFCBW24AW						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polda</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2762710/Polda/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2762710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Investigate a mysterious kidnapping in the town of Lupany in this classic point and click old school adventure game. You got your uniform and your gun and you’re certainly no angel, so you take the law into your own hands. This detective parody full of comedy is fully dubbed in English. The game features loads of characters, an unusual amount of details, detailed animations, logical plot twists, more than 250 quality sound effects, a story full of authentic and peculiar humour…<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>45 interactive characters<br/></li><li>35 game locations in different settings<br/></li><li>outstanding and stylish graphic design<br/></li><li>lots of game items<br/></li><li>interesting detective plot<br/></li><li>logical puzzle tasks<br/></li><li>quality music and sound effects</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asterball</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2837470/Asterball/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Asterball is an online third-person sports game where you play as a Sportsman on one of two teams in a game of gridiron, with a unique twist.<h2 class="bb_tag">Levels</h2>Asterball contains multiple different levels, each with their own unique gameplay elements. Battle it out in the classic Starfield, which takes you back to the basics. Or compete in the Warpgate, which challenges the players with limited platforms and portals.<h2 class="bb_tag">Items</h2>Each Sportsman can gain points during gameplay from various tasks, such as scoring touchdowns or tackling other players. These points ca be used to gain advantageous items to help. Items only last for the round, but can help gain an edge on the opponent in different ways. The Sportsman can purchase the electrifying Lightning Rod to gain a huge increase in speed, or can play on the offensive with the Pulse Bomb, causing targets to be knocked back.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Settlers: New Allies</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2750080/The_Settlers_New_Allies/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2750080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Settlers®: New Allies is a strategy game with an in-depth build-up experience and real-time strategic battles.<br>
<br>
- Fully reimagined from the ground up, with stunning graphics and detailed animations.<br>
- Choose among three factions: the Elari, the Maru, and the Jorn. Each has a unique look, playstyle, and background story.<br>
- Experience a story-driven campaign set in the world of The Settlers, or go for the special Hardcore mode and its additional challenges.<br>
- Play online with up to eight players in thrilling skirmish battles against other players or AI for long-lasting fun.<br>
<br>
Get the most out of your game experience with the The Settlers®: New Allies Deluxe Edition, including the game, the Deluxe Pack, and the Explorer Pack.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Settlers: New Allies</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2750080/The_Settlers_New_Allies/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2750080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Settlers®: New Allies is a strategy game with an in-depth build-up experience and real-time strategic battles.<br>
<br>
- Fully reimagined from the ground up, with stunning graphics and detailed animations.<br>
- Choose among three factions: the Elari, the Maru, and the Jorn. Each has a unique look, playstyle, and background story.<br>
- Experience a story-driven campaign set in the world of The Settlers, or go for the special Hardcore mode and its additional challenges.<br>
- Play online with up to eight players in thrilling skirmish battles against other players or AI for long-lasting fun.<br>
<br>
Get the most out of your game experience with the The Settlers®: New Allies Deluxe Edition, including the game, the Deluxe Pack, and the Explorer Pack.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1268590/Millennia/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fmillennia" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/616x152.png?t=1711472688"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Store_Page_City_Growth_animation_Steam-Loop.gif?t=1711472688"><br/>Create your own nation in Millennia, a historical turn-based 4X game that challenges your strategic prowess across 10,000 years of history, from the dawn of humanity to our possible futures.  Set the course of history and experience different timelines in every playthrough as you write an epic story through your actions.  Lead your people through times of crisis and ages of discovery, face great challenges and opportunities, and build a civilization that prospers through the ages.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Guide_Your_Nation.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Dictate the course of history across ten ages, from the first cities to space travel.  Accomplish certain objectives and you can move time into a Variant Age - an alternate history with new rules, new technologies, and new units.  But beware Crisis Ages; following a path of chaos and disorder may plunge the world into a future filled with war, sickness or ignorance.  Then again, a wise ruler can always turn a crisis into an opportunity....  Choose the path with care, as the ages you pass through will have a lasting impact on your people and the world.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Choose_What_You.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Customize your nation by adopting unique Nations Spirits over the course of your game.  Will you be a nation of warriors or explorers?  Are your people lead by a Great Khan or a builder of monuments?  Are you known for defining  pop culture or for dominating global finance?  What parts of your culture will reverberate across history?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Master_a_Deep.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Manage your economy with care and create a juggernaut of growth and construction.  Start with basic resources to gain food, wealth, and production.  As your advance, decide how to best convert these simple goods into more valuable products through research and improvements.  Specialize your regions, turning iron into weapons or tools, wood into paper or lumber, gold into coin or jewelry.  Ship surplus goods where they are needed, allowing the breadbasket of your empire to feed far-flung colonies or your industrial heartland to supply troops near your enemy.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Unlock_Technologies.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Pursue knowledge to research scientific and cultural advances, unlocking new units, buildings, and improvements to grow your cities or strengthen your armies.  Research Defense to train the first archers, Smelting to master iron production, or Guilds for making wine.  Variant and Crisis Ages feature unique alternatives, introducing everything from Cloud Estates in the Age of Aether to underwater cities in the Age of Utopia.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Achieve_Victory.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Achieve your ultimate success through a Victory Age.  Toward the end of the game (or earlier if your strategy is sound), dominance allows a nation to dictate the winning conditions.  The rest of the world must decide if they will struggle to achieve victory before the leader ... or oppose the leader's attempt.  Risk everything to take victory in the Renaissance or carefully plan for triumph in the modern era.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Millennia: Premium Edition includes the following content:</h2><br/><strong>Wolfpack Warband &amp; Eagle Archers cosmetics</strong><br/>Elevate the presence of your units in Millennia with the exclusive Wolfpack Warband and Eagle Archers clothings. Available instantly with the Premium Edition, this clothes pack unlocks unique wolf skin clothing for your Warband. Your Archer Unit receives eagle-inspired clothes, symbolizing their precision and keen sight.<br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Ancient Worlds</strong><br/>Take your first uncertain steps in a new era for humanity in Millennia: Ancient Worlds. Take control of your people before their first settlement, while they still wander as nomads.  Includes a new nomadic game start option, a new National Spirit, a new economic Good, and new Nation starting bonuses. <br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Atomic Ambitions</strong><br/>Unlock the mysteries of the atom and change the world forever in Millennia: Atomic Ambitions. The Premium edition adds ways to harness the power of the atom for the good of all humankind, but, there are also ways to turn the planet into a fallout-filled wasteland if you aren’t careful. Includes two new Ages, a new National Spirit, and nuclear options for the Strategic Warfare System.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1268590/Millennia/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fmillennia" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/616x152.png?t=1711472688"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Store_Page_City_Growth_animation_Steam-Loop.gif?t=1711472688"><br/>Create your own nation in Millennia, a historical turn-based 4X game that challenges your strategic prowess across 10,000 years of history, from the dawn of humanity to our possible futures.  Set the course of history and experience different timelines in every playthrough as you write an epic story through your actions.  Lead your people through times of crisis and ages of discovery, face great challenges and opportunities, and build a civilization that prospers through the ages.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Guide_Your_Nation.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Dictate the course of history across ten ages, from the first cities to space travel.  Accomplish certain objectives and you can move time into a Variant Age - an alternate history with new rules, new technologies, and new units.  But beware Crisis Ages; following a path of chaos and disorder may plunge the world into a future filled with war, sickness or ignorance.  Then again, a wise ruler can always turn a crisis into an opportunity....  Choose the path with care, as the ages you pass through will have a lasting impact on your people and the world.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Choose_What_You.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Customize your nation by adopting unique Nations Spirits over the course of your game.  Will you be a nation of warriors or explorers?  Are your people lead by a Great Khan or a builder of monuments?  Are you known for defining  pop culture or for dominating global finance?  What parts of your culture will reverberate across history?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Master_a_Deep.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Manage your economy with care and create a juggernaut of growth and construction.  Start with basic resources to gain food, wealth, and production.  As your advance, decide how to best convert these simple goods into more valuable products through research and improvements.  Specialize your regions, turning iron into weapons or tools, wood into paper or lumber, gold into coin or jewelry.  Ship surplus goods where they are needed, allowing the breadbasket of your empire to feed far-flung colonies or your industrial heartland to supply troops near your enemy.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Unlock_Technologies.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Pursue knowledge to research scientific and cultural advances, unlocking new units, buildings, and improvements to grow your cities or strengthen your armies.  Research Defense to train the first archers, Smelting to master iron production, or Guilds for making wine.  Variant and Crisis Ages feature unique alternatives, introducing everything from Cloud Estates in the Age of Aether to underwater cities in the Age of Utopia.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Achieve_Victory.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Achieve your ultimate success through a Victory Age.  Toward the end of the game (or earlier if your strategy is sound), dominance allows a nation to dictate the winning conditions.  The rest of the world must decide if they will struggle to achieve victory before the leader ... or oppose the leader's attempt.  Risk everything to take victory in the Renaissance or carefully plan for triumph in the modern era.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Millennia: Premium Edition includes the following content:</h2><br/><strong>Wolfpack Warband &amp; Eagle Archers cosmetics</strong><br/>Elevate the presence of your units in Millennia with the exclusive Wolfpack Warband and Eagle Archers clothings. Available instantly with the Premium Edition, this clothes pack unlocks unique wolf skin clothing for your Warband. Your Archer Unit receives eagle-inspired clothes, symbolizing their precision and keen sight.<br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Ancient Worlds</strong><br/>Take your first uncertain steps in a new era for humanity in Millennia: Ancient Worlds. Take control of your people before their first settlement, while they still wander as nomads.  Includes a new nomadic game start option, a new National Spirit, a new economic Good, and new Nation starting bonuses. <br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Atomic Ambitions</strong><br/>Unlock the mysteries of the atom and change the world forever in Millennia: Atomic Ambitions. The Premium edition adds ways to harness the power of the atom for the good of all humankind, but, there are also ways to turn the planet into a fallout-filled wasteland if you aren’t careful. Includes two new Ages, a new National Spirit, and nuclear options for the Strategic Warfare System.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineered To Purpose</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2199780/Engineered_To_Purpose/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2199780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Engineered To Purpose is a narratively-driven sci-fi tower defence game which allows players to design their own towers, customising attacks, targeting schemes, and more. As pressure mounts, plan out and optimise your defences in order to defeat hordes of enemies!<br/><br/><strong>Tower Design</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2199780/extras/resized-design-towers.gif?t=1711468859"><br/><br/>Our design system is based on combining sets of components and then assigning modifiers to the attack to customise each tower into a unique form and effect. The system allows you to use your unlocked components to build and experiment, adding a new layer of strategy to the tower defence formula.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2199780/extras/defending-towers.gif?t=1711468859"><br/><br/>Designing a tower can be done mid-level if you have enough room, or between levels in our workshop, where towers can be tested against any enemy you have encountered, and you can see the effect of your choices in real-time. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2199780/extras/3.png?t=1711468859"><br/><br/><strong>Key Demo Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Design your towers!<br/></li><li>Face hordes of unique and challenging enemies!<br/></li><li>Test your towers in the Workshop to prepare for missions!<br/></li><li>The first chapter of our story-driven campaign!</li></ul><br/><strong>Coming Soon!</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Three more worlds: more story, more enemy types, more tower components, and more maps!<br/></li><li>Over 100 enemy types!<br/></li><li>Gameplay Modifiers, allowing you to customise the challenges you face per level and adding deep replay options for even the simplest map! <br/></li><li>Post-game advancement - Once the campaign is complete, continue to collect new components and upgrade your collection!</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outpost: Infinity Siege</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1566690/Outpost_Infinity_Siege/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1566690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1566690/extras/ENGIF.gif?t=1711468695"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Outpost Building</strong></h2>Explore the world, gather resources, merge and upgrade outpost units to build your own outpost.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Unique Weapon</strong></h2>Fully exploit the value of the unique XEN Firearm with different protoslag attributes, and utilize ammunition with diverse performance.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Loot &amp; Farm</strong></h2>Enjoy the abundant difficulty levels, diverse gameplay features, and distinctive maps of the exploration mode. Venture deep into the brand new zones full of hazards and opportunities, and harvest powerful outpost units.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Feature</strong></h2>Fight alongside friends on Recovery Day, or strive together to survive infinite waves of monsters in Endless mode till the last moment.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appetit MR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2835050/Appetit_MR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2835050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
<u>Bon Appetit!</u><br/><br/>Appetit is your ultimate Mixed Reality virtual cooking assistant to help you in all your culinary ventures, small or large! Have recipes suggested to you, search for and create custom recipes that fit your needs and preferences, order ingredients online, adjust the recipe's difficulty and complexity and more! Appetit has your back in the kitchen.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nine Lives Ninja: Explore!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2848390/Nine_Lives_Ninja_Explore/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2848390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Nine Lives Ninja: Explore lets you take control of a cat (who also happens to be a ninja) as they explore an ancient cave system searching for the Fountain of Kitty Youth - the only way to restore their lost lives. How did the cat become a ninja? Aren't all their lost lives directly due to the dangers of the cave? Fantastic questions! For now let us simply join the intrepid ninja (who also happens to be a cat) and help them reach their goal.<br>
<br>
Nine Lives Ninja: Explore is a platformer with metroidvania elements. It features multiple game modes, retro-pixel graphics, tight controls, collectibles, and achievements to uncover.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero's black dungeon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2865900/Heros_black_dungeon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2865900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Hero's black dungeon is a 2D action roguelike. Take control of a young adventurer who travels to the Mediterranean lands in search of adventure and glory. On your way you will meet quite a few enemies and interesting characters. Arm yourself with magical blades and chop down enemies on your way! Complete tasks, collect resources and go deeper and deeper through the floors!<br>
<br>
In the game you have to clear locations from enemies, complete your goals and go deeper into the dungeon.<br>
<br>
Are you ready to become a real hero and explore dark dungeons while fighting the forces of evil? Then go on a journey with a young adventurer and test yourself!<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br/>
- Pixel graphics<br/>
- Various enemies<br/>
- Good soundtrack						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exit: Left or Right</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2874660/Exit_Left_or_Right/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2874660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You've entered liminal space. It's a strange, empty world outside of our reality. Sometimes, some people end up here, and you are one of them. Now, you need to find a way out. There will always be two different paths in front of you, left or right. One of the paths will lead you to the exit, and the other will lead you to death. You have to scrutinize your surroundings to choose the right path.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2><br/>Exit Left or Right is a short walking simulator inspired by liminal spaces. There is no fast-paced action or pathos story in this game. All you need is just to choose the right way to go. You need to scrutinize your surroundings, because you can always notice something strange in front of the wrong door...<br/><br/><strong>Keep an eye on your surroundings, don't overlook any oddities.</strong><br/><br/><strong>If you find anomalies, turn back immediately.</strong><br/><br/><strong>If you don't find any anomalies, go forward.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Your goal is to get to the exit.</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTH PARK: SNOW DAY!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1214650/SOUTH_PARK_SNOW_DAY/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1214650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From South Park Digital Studios, the studio that brought you South Park: The Stick of Truth, South Park: The Fractured but Whole, and South Park: Phone Destroyer comes the next chapter in the journey of the New Kid.<br/><br/>Join Cartman, Stan, Kyle, and Kenny, in three-dimensional glory, to celebrate the most magical day in any young child’s life - a snow day! A massive blizzard has thrown the town into chaos and, more importantly, canceled school.<br/><br/>Play with up to three friends, use matchmaking, or solo the game with ally bots and battle through the snow-piled town of South Park. Engage in frenetic, action-packed combat against warring factions in an all-new story where you make the rules. Equip unique weapons and deploy devastating, upgradable special abilities on a new adventure to save the world and enjoy a day without school.<h2 class="bb_tag">It’s a snow day, dude!</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle your way through the snow-covered town of South Park in this all-new 3D co-op game.<br/></li><li>A blizzard of epic proportions has blanketed the town of South Park and it’s up to Cartman, Stan, Kenny, Kyle, and you, as the New Kid, to save the town from an endless winter.<br/></li><li>Experience cooperative gameplay for the first time ever in a South Park game with up to three friends or ally bots - unleashing powerful, coordinated attacks on your foes.<br/></li><li>Equip and upgrade devastating melee and ranged weapons. Deploy special abilities and powers that will bring hordes of enemies and epic bosses to their knees.<br/></li><li>Use a wide range of iconic cosmetics and customize your New Kid with endless possible combinations from beanies to Cheesy Poof T-shirts to chin balls.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrestling Cardboard Championship</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1663320/Wrestling_Cardboard_Championship/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1663320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A game experience inspired by wrestling, making use of simulated physics, cardboard boxes with unique skills and movements, fight in large arenas based on arenas that have marked wrestling, such as Madison Square Garden, Arena México and Tokyo Dome.<br/><br/>A new wrestling company has been born, offering a unique show around the world, different fighting styles and extremely skilled fighters ready to give it their all in the ring. The Wrestling Cardboard Championship gives all kinds of cardboard boxes the opportunity to show that they are the strongest and that they have the talent to entertain the people.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1663320/extras/LocalMultiplayer_english.png?t=1711465968"><br/>Experience different game modes for up to 4 players: 1 vs 1, 2 vs 2, 3 vs 1 and All vs All<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1663320/extras/CareerMode_english.png?t=1711465968"><br/>The Normal Box is in its last days of useful life, after knowing what its cruel destiny would be, being crushed and recycled, it decides to change it for wrestling, arriving at the WCC in search of an opportunity and showing that his passion can take him to the top, although you will soon realize that being a professional wrestler is not an easy thing.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1663320/extras/VariedRoster_english.png?t=1711465968"><br/>12 unique boxes with varied fighting styles, inspired by well-known brands and professional wrestlers. Each Box has its own theme song and its own personality. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1663320/extras/KnownScenarios_english.png?t=1711465968"><br/>Inspired by real settings such as Madison Square Garden, Hammerstein Ballroom, Arena Mexico and Tokyo Dome. (Adding more post launch scenarios via DLC)						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamburg: 'Neue Burg' VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2769660/Hamburg_Neue_Burg_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2769660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Immerse yourself in over 1000 years of Hamburg's history and experience the beginnings of the city in 1024! The 'Neue Burg' - the nucleus of Hamburg's early 'New Town' - has been reconstructed in great detail in collaboration with archaeologists. This immersive Virtual Reality experience offers 22 interactive stations that invite you to discover and understand the history of Hamburg.<br>
<br>
Climb the castle walls and ship masts, jump back in time and compare then and now, collect parts of a painting to create a portrait of the Duke of the castle and explore models that visualize the 1000-year urban development of this place. You can follow the fully audio-guided tour or explore the entire area freely.<br>
<br>
'Hamburg: Neue Burg VR' was developed as part of a PhD project and aims to use the potential of VR to convey history in a playful way.<br>
<br>
VR hardware necessary! Tested on HTC Vive Pro, Valve Index, Oculus Quest 2 &amp; Pico 4						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Chess Q14</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2077200/3D_Chess_Q14/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2077200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Extended Chess Game with additional optional figures.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The user can play on Boards with 6-by-6 to 16-by-16 fields.<br/></li><li> Up to 3 new Figures: Wizard, Gamma and Keeper<br/></li><li> More than 70 play modes: Single Layer, 3D Stacked Game, Random Attack Games, and Tower Challenge.<br/></li><li> 3D view 2D projection.<br/></li><li> Play on the same computer, online with your friends or against the AI.<br/></li><li> Anti-Chess support for all single-level games<br/></li><li> 3D Stacked: Play on several levels: Each hit figure will be your trophy on the next level. Since a level is done (check or draw), the game continues on the next level.<br/></li><li> Tower Mode: Play several sized games. The best player wins.<br/></li><li> Online: Play against other online users<br/></li><li> Quick Game: Attach to a random online game.<br/></li><li> Snapshots: Create a game snapshot and replay any time.<br/></li><li> Switch between different visualizations. Board Style, Darkmode, Fullsized Windows, hint fields</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go Fight Fantastic</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1183530/Go_Fight_Fantastic/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1183530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Go Fight Fantastic</strong> is a 1-3 player hack n’ slash starring a crew of interstellar smugglers, led by their space-dog captain Bowie. When they stumble into an invasion during a mission to Bird Planet, they become the only hope of this once peaceful world. <br/><br/>Team up in<strong> co-op </strong>(local and online) or switch between the different characters on-the-fly in <strong>solo play.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1183530/extras/1_new_gif.gif?t=1711454743"><h2 class="bb_tag">Story Mode</h2>Fast-paced. Light-hearted. Vibrantly hand-drawn. Fight across treacherous marshlands, steep summits and picturesque settlements and meet an imaginative cast of friends and foes along the way. A unique touch is added to each playthrough by a degree of randomized level composition, enemy encounters, and upgrade drops.<h2 class="bb_tag">Horde Mode</h2>Fire up captain Bowie’s combat simulator and plow through an endless alien assault to climb the online leaderboards! Use the strengths of all your characters to prevail, pick powerups between the waves, and repeat. The longer you stay alive, the more challenging it gets.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1183530/extras/2_new_gif.gif?t=1711454743"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Crew</h2>Play as four different characters, each representing their own playstyle, and tailor them with persistent <strong>Meteorite</strong> upgrades found throughout the game. Want a Healer who can deal some serious damage? Or a Striker with poisonous blades? Have at it!<h2 class="bb_tag">Join the Community</h2>Join our official Discord Server and let us know what you think of the game! Come hang out, join contests and get the latest news about the development.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FGoFightFantastic%2F" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/GoFightFantastic/</a> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OG Puzzlers: Synthwave Monsters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2872770/OG_Puzzlers_Synthwave_Monsters/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2872770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>OG Puzzlers: Synthwave Monsters</strong> is an puzzel game with scary monsters in an stunning synthwave style. You have to assemble a single image from random generated indivdual pieces. <br/>Combine all of the smart singel frames into one big image and unlock the next level.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 11 Levels<br/></li><li> puzzle adventure<br/></li><li> auto saving<br/></li><li> simple mouse control<br/></li><li> 100 steam awards</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2839430/Room/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2839430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I thought it was just an ordinary day, but I accidentally entered this endless cycle of rooms.<br>
Among the countless terrifying and anomalous things, there is a girl who seems like she shouldn't exist here.<br>
--------------------------<br>
This game is a Galgame that focuses on finding anomalies and inferring the plot. The game time is about one hour, and the entire game is dubbed in Chinese.<br>
--------------------------<br>
All characters appearing in the game are adults. The characters, stories, places, plots, worlds and other manifestations involved are fictional and have no connection with any characters or events in reality.						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BouncingBalls</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2868580/BouncingBalls/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2868580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is an aim trainer implemented in a playful way.<br>
You find yourself in a kind of laboratory box where balls fall from the sky and bounce off walls and fly around the room unpredictably and these balls have to be shot.<br>
 However, it won't be easy, so get started and set an incredible high score!						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
