<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>20 Small Mazes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2570630/20_Small_Mazes/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2570630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a puzzle game with twenty small mazes. If you solve the mazes, you beat the game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>It's about 1-2 hours long, maybe.<br/></li><li>You need a keyboard and mouse to play it. One person played through the whole game on the Steam Deck, but I tried it and think it's better on PC.<br/></li><li> A few puzzles require knowledge of English. No puzzle requires sound or audio to solve it. No puzzle requires being able to recognize different colors.</li></ul> <br/>I hope you enjoy it. <br/> 						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAIL VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/801550/VAIL_VR/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/801550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/801550/extras/VAIL_GameplayFeatures.gif?t=1708040999"><br/><br/>VAIL is a multiplayer VR shooter delivering unparalleled combat.<br/><br/><strong>Explore 12 maps with 30+ variations custom-made for each game mode</strong><br/>● Warm-up in classic Team Deathmatch and Free-For-All<br/>● Team up in Artifact for our take on Search and Destroy<br/>● Take control of the Hardpoint and defend it from enemies<br/>● Capture the Orb and return it safely in Capture the Flag<br/>● Experience low-gravity chaos with only snipers and knives in ScoutzKnivez<br/>● Duel in 1v1 variations of all the maps<br/>● Hang out and chill on any map with our Picnic mode<br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES</strong><br/>● Immersive weapon interactions to reload, change the fire rate, and control recoil<br/>● Physics-based knife with immersive stabbing, slashing, and throwing<br/>● Accurate and satisfying throwing for grenades and utilities<br/>● Climb ladders, vault over obstacles, ride zip lines, and defy gravity on jump pads<br/>● Finely tuned spatial audio both vertically and horizontally for footsteps, gunshots and other sound effects<br/>● Customizable and realistic sights and scopes that bend and distort light<br/>● Level up to unlock weapons, sights, in-game currency, gun skins, character skins, and more<br/>● Track your stats and see if you can top the daily, weekly, and all-time leaderboards<br/>● Add friends and party up for matchmaking<br/>● Cross-play and cross-platform account linking so you always have access to the same friends list, in-game items, and progress on every platform<br/><br/><strong>FIGHT FOR HUMANITY'S LEGACY</strong><br/>On a blighted Earth, the claim to the human legacy is diverging. Many have chosen to move to the colonies orbiting Earth, while those left behind swore to rebuild civilization under REYAB Corporation’s protection. The Colonists believe in a future in the cosmos, but they must return to Earth to retrieve sensitive data from the Artifact nodes protected by the REYAB who fight to maintain power over the populace. As the war between these factions evolves, humanity’s future remains uncertain…<br/><br/>Experience unparalleled combat						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caribbean Legend</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2230980/Caribbean_Legend/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i><strong>Based on Sea Dogs series and inspired by Sid Meier's Pirates!</strong></i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/История_EN.gif?t=1708179484"><br/><br/>Welcome to the Caribbean in 1654 AD, a place teeming with opportunities and mysteries. Assume the role of Charles de Maure, a young French noble who embarked on a journey to the New World to assist his brother. What initially appeared to be a simple family matter quickly evolves into a lifelong adventure.<br/>Immerse yourself in the tale of a noble brat who rises to become the most influential figure in the Caribbean. <strong>Riches, titles, power, and romance – the ultimate booty awaits, and it's up to you to seize it all.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/steamchar.jpg?t=1708179484"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Embark on a 200-hour-long journey.<br/></li><li>Undertake hundreds of quests.<br/></li><li>Freeplay, rush through the story, or combine both - you're the Captain, and your ship will sail where you command.<br/></li><li>Experience a historical narrative with a touch of mystique.<br/></li><li>Explore romantic interests and companions.<br/></li><li>Choose from various career options, from general-governor to pirate baron.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/Мир_EN.gif?t=1708179484"><br/><br/>The Caribbean Sea – a realm of dozens of islands and cities, a grand archipelago shrouded in mystery and secrets. From the summits of Indian pyramids to the ocean depths, unique rewards, quests, and curiosities await. <strong>This open world is your sandbox, you are free to explore it and shape your legend as you see fit. </strong>Your decisions determine where to go, what to do, and who to take with you. Subdue the New World or it will destroy you!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Discover dozens of islands and settlements.<br/></li><li>Build your very own colony.<br/></li><li>Explore caves, pyramids, jungles, Indian tribes, and lost cities.<br/></li><li>Visit taverns, brothels, shipyards, churches, forts, and many other points of interest.<br/></li><li>Engage in treasure hunting and gambling.<br/></li><li>Experience dynamic weather and the serene turquoise sea.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/Море_EN.gif?t=1708179484"><br/><br/><strong>Owning a warship is a privilege, a symbol of status and luxury. </strong>You are among the very few who can afford such grandeur. Begin your journey with a simple sloop and work your way up to commanding a ship of the line or even a fleet of these formidable vessels, ready to plunder cities at your whim. No one will stand in your way. Tired from leading massive armadas and the responsibility? Take command of a fast Frigate or Corvette and just free roam the Caribbean. In moments of tranquility at sea, relish the stunning views, embrace the sense of exploration, or navigate in the heart of a storm.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/valciria3_копия.png?t=1708179484"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Command dozens of ships representing the glory of the Age of Sail.<br/></li><li>Customize, paint, upgrade, and repair your vessel.<br/></li><li>Engage in unforgiving yet enjoyable naval combat.<br/></li><li>Experience intense boarding action, from the upper deck to the captain's cabin.<br/></li><li>Collect unique vessels to rule the seas.<br/></li><li>Manage booty distribution, morale, and the threat of mutinies.<br/></li><li>Assemble a formidable team of officers.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/боевка_EN.gif?t=1708179484"><br/><br/>Captains are most vulnerable when they set foot on land. Surviving naval combat can be challenging, but at least you won't die alone – your crew will stand with you till the very end. Land battles are different: dishonest, ruthless and risky for you and those who you hold dear. <strong>Bring your companions with you, poison your weapons, study the terrain, craft deadly items, and confront thugs, soldiers, pirates, and rivals head-on.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/face_201_копия.png?t=1708179484"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tailor your character's build – become a heavy swordsman, a nimble rogue, a master sharpshooter, or a silver-tongued diplomat.<br/></li><li>Equip yourself and your companions with a wide array of swords, axes, rapiers, armor, muskets, and pistols.<br/></li><li>Craft amulets, ammo, potions, and always be prepared for battle.<br/></li><li>Seek out challenges – the more you fight, the stronger both you and your character become.<br/></li><li>Command military operations from raiding to sieges.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708005696"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708005696"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smalland: Survive the Wilds</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/768200/Smalland_Survive_the_Wilds/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>"Before the time of the giants, we lived freely under the Sun and Moon. Centuries have passed, but those stories of the surface world have been passed down through the generations. Now the giants are gone, and you, Vanguard, must venture out into the wilds once more, on an urgent mission. Be brave, and do not falter…"</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/TreeLookingup.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the vast “Land of the Small" </h2>Traverse lake sized puddles, scale skyscraper sized trees, scramble through cavernous cracks in roads, as you experience a huge open world from a new perspective. Explore dense forests, hazardous swamps and strange ruins left over from the time before. Uncover lore and knowledge from hidden NPCs scattered throughout the world and learn to survive in this vast wilderness. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Land_of_Small.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Tame and ride creatures</h2>Uncover recipes that will let you tame and ride an array of critters. Leap huge distances on the back of a Grasshopper, zoom around on a Damselfly, scurry from place-to-place on a Spider. This world and its inhabitants are yours to conquer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Mounts.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive together</h2>Play alongside friends with support for up to 10 players in multiplayer. Explore together, fight together, build together and survive the wilds as a team.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Together.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build encampments on the ground or amongst the trees</h2>Scavenge or refine resources to build your encampment with multiple material tiers, from leaves and twigs to sturdy stone. Pick your favourite spot in the world and build, or scale vast trees and claim your own settlement at the top.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Housing.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Craft powerful armour sets</h2>Collect powerful armours that provide you with resistances and abilities and mix them up to personalise your appearance. Glide through the skies in winged armour, swing from tree to tree with the grappling hook and many more. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Armors.gif?t=1708077077"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive the Wilds</h2>Most of the creatures you encounter will see you as lower on the food chain – Ants, Cockroaches, Beetles, Wasps, and Spiders all view you as a potential meal. Weather conditions and seasons are in constant flux so if you want to survive for another day, preparation is key.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Survive_the_Wilds.gif?t=1708077077"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider I-III Remastered Starring Lara Croft</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2478970/Tomb_Raider_IIII_Remastered_Starring_Lara_Croft/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2478970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover Lara Croft’s Original Adventures, Lovingly Restored</h2> <br/>Play the Original Three Tomb Raider Adventures: For the first time ever, play the complete experience with all expansions and secret levels on modern platforms in this definitive collection.<h2 class="bb_tag">Included Game Titles</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tomb Raider I + Unfinished Business<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider II + Golden Mask<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider III + The Lost Artifact</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><strong>Solve Ancient Mysteries</strong>: Uncover treasures of the ancient world by solving puzzles and unraveling mysteries lost to the ravages of time.<br/><br/><strong>Globe-trotting Adventure</strong>: Follow Lara Croft around the world and face off against deadly foes and dangerous myths.<br/><br/><strong>Lovingly Restored</strong>: Experience the classics boasting upgraded graphics, with the option to switch to the original polygon look at any time.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islands of Insight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2071500/Islands_of_Insight/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Islands of Insight: a sublime shared-world puzzle game set in a fantasy realm of ancient wonders and natural beauty. Brimming with mysterious puzzles to solve, secrets to uncover, and vibrant landscapes to explore, this peaceful world of floating islands is the perfect place to unwind. Embark on a puzzle adventure of your choice, all at your own pace.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_1-Title-Journey_EN.png?t=1708109878">‎‎‏‏‎<br/>Play as a Seeker on a peaceful journey rich in exploration and puzzle-solving. Embark on the Path of Discovery and let your curiosity guide you through a breathtaking open world where the answer is always in sight.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_Gifs_Journey_HD.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_2-Title-Puzzles_EN.png?t=1708109878"><br/>Seek out and solve an unparalleled collection of over 10,000 puzzles divided across 24 puzzle types. Every corner of the world holds a new eureka moment for you to discover. From enigmas of perspective to logic problems, environmental challenges and more, the puzzles you’ll encounter vary in difficulty and have been crafted by some of the best minds in puzzle design to create an engaging experience for both newcomers and seasoned puzzle fans.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_Gifs_Puzzles_HD.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_3-Title-Exploration_EN.png?t=1708109878"><br/>Freely explore the main island’s expansive open world where most of the puzzles and secrets are found. Wander the vibrant landscapes and architecture of its 5 distinct biomes or spread your wings to glide above them. Navigate the environment’s verticality and take your game to new heights. Unlock puzzle types and new areas in the campaign by completing 20+ Enclaves housing curated puzzle challenges. Go where you want. Solve what you want. The only path here is the one you make.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/3.IOI_Steam_Gif_Exploration___Discovery_2.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_5-Title-Experience_EN.png?t=1708109878"><br/>Customize your character. Increase your puzzle masteries to level them up while earning sparks to unlock new abilities. Complete daily quests. Seamlessly interact with other players in our shared world to gain or offer a bit of guidance, or choose to figure things out entirely on your own. With puzzles that refresh over time, a new discovery awaits with every visit to the islands.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/4.IOI_Steam_Gif_An_Evergreen_Experience_2.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/>Age restrictions may apply to access this game.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultros</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2386310/Ultros/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You wake up stranded, after seemingly crashing your ship on The Sarcophagus — a giant, space-drifting, cosmic uterus holding an ancient demonic being known as ULTROS. Trapped in the eternal loop of a black hole, you will have to explore The Sarcophagus and meet its inhabitants to understand the part you play. <br/><br/>Are you the gruesome breaker of this cycle, or can you become a link from destruction to rebirth? <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat1.png?t=1708088745"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat1.gif?t=1708088745"><br/>ULTROS is set in a multifaceted realm - a vast alien landscape teeming with life. Grounded in science fiction, ULTROS comes wrapped in an eccentric art style and a mystical soundtrack from the visionary El Huervo, renowned for his work on Hotline Miami. ULTROS explores meta-themes of mental health, life, death, and karmic cycles through deep lore and environmental storytelling.       <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat2.png?t=1708088745"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat2.gif?t=1708088745"><br/>Experience brutal, intimate, close-quarter combat with cosmic lifeforms, driven by a sense of urgency – where precision is paramount and every cut of your blade counts. Yet this intense combat is juxtaposed with cultivating the greenery and tending to plant life in The Sarcophagus, providing precious moments of contemplation and peace. In turn, this grants deeper access to obscured paths.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat3.png?t=1708088745"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat3.gif?t=1708088745"><br/>The rich world of ULTROS holds many secrets for those curious enough — and fearless enough — to seek them out. A unique loop-based mechanic will allow you to start over at key moments in the story, providing opportunities to unfold such secrets, unlock different areas of the world and new abilities on a branching skill tree. Experiment with and master your own specific fighting style as you explore the world of ULTROS. Each loop brings you closer to the truth...						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Will:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802530/Space_WillPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 10 in the prologue, 59 in the official version<br/>Galaxy: 2 in the prologue, 6 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><strong>Sixty basic cores, hundreds of base station equipment, and thousands of chips, you can freely cooperate and shoot through the dual-angle joystick operation in a survival Roguelike game! Explore the sci-fi space and build your strongest battleship!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Step 1: Choose a "core" as your basic role<br/>Step 2: Choose a "crew" as your initial weapon<br/>Step 3: Select a galaxy for exploration</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game will continuously collect new "units" or "chips" during the exploration process<br/>Using "crew" can expand weapons and enhance combat effectiveness for your warship<br/>Using "chips" can enhance various abilities of your warship</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Each "core" or "unit" has a maximum of 4 interfaces. When the interfaces are used up, you cannot equip more parts, but you can also infinitely increase the number of your interfaces!<br/>Each "crew" can use the right mouse button to rotate and adjust the optimal angle for combat</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game features dual joystick shooting, with the keyboard moving and the mouse aiming at the enemy. Of course, there are many weapons that can automatically attack or be placed in the scene as traps for use~</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_TITLE_FULLSCREEN.gif?t=1708080818"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_1.png?t=1708080818"><br/> <br/>In New Eden, 1695, communities of settlers are plagued by a dreadful curse. As Banishers, step into their lives, investigate the source of evil, unravel chilling mysteries, explore diverse landscapes, and interact with unforgettable characters whose fate lies in your hands.<br/><br/>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden is an all-new title crafted by renowned studio DON'T NOD, known for their acclaimed titles such as Life is Strange and Vampyr. Immerse yourself in an intimate narrative Action-RPG, taking you on an exhilarating journey between life, death, love and sacrifices.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_2.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_FANTASY.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Play as a couple of Banishers, Red and Antea, experienced spirit hunters entrusted with the daunting task of dispelling a malevolent curse through powerful rituals. Protect the living from the threat of lingering ghosts and specters, and become a beacon of hope in a world consumed by darkness.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_3.png?t=1708080818"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_NARATION_LOVE.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Experience a heart-wrenching love story between Antea Duarte and Red mac Raith. When Antea is killed and turned into a spirit, you find yourself facing a choice. Will you uphold your oath and ascend her soul, or will you sacrifice the living in the hope of bringing her back? Your decisions will shape the fate of New Eden’s inhabitants - may they be living or dead, and determine the end of your journey.<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>BLAME</strong> the living and sacrifice their lives, holding them responsible for their actions<br/></li><li><strong>BANISH</strong> souls of the departed, condemning them to eternal suffering<br/></li><li><strong>ASCEND</strong> souls, liberating them from eternal sorrow and granting them serenity</li></ul><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_4.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_COMBAT.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Banishers are specialized in combat against undead creatures, such as specters or ghosts. Combine Red's physical arsenal with Antea's supernatural powers in a dynamic combat system. Find your own style by mixing weapon attacks and spiritual abilities. Powerful synergies will lead you to defeat New Eden’s most dangerous enemies and bosses.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_6.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_SKILL.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Unleash the full power of the Banishers by unlocking new gear and supernatural abilities. By exploring New Eden, you will find ancient artifacts, trinkets and valuable resources to enhance your equipment in preparation of future fights. In addition to your arsenal, progress in Antea’s skill trees to upgrade her devastating spectral powers and unseal new combos.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_5.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_EXPLORATION.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Investigate haunting cases in a mystical world full of dark secrets. Discover New Eden, a North America settlement marked by terrible stories and secrets of its tormented inhabitants. Understanding each resident’s motivations will be essential to guide your decisions throughout the game.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_7.png?t=1708080818"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Ninja Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_9" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🥋🐾 WELCOME TO 100 NINJA CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🗡️</h2>🗡️Join the cutest adventure in the Ninja world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of ninja themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game.<br/>😊Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x200.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Ninja Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Extra.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816000/100_Ninja_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815980/100_Ninja_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Artbook.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x1.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_10" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_11" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III - BlackCell (Season 2)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731840/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III__BlackCell_Season_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Get Call of Duty® Points* and in-game content for Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III and Call of Duty®: Warzone™.<br>
<br>
Offering includes:<br>
<br/>
- Battle Pass for Season 2<br/>
- 20 Battle Token Tier Skips<br/>
<br/>
Exclusive BlackCell Sector on the Battle Map:<br/>
<br/>
- 1100 Call of Duty® Points<br/>
- BlackCell Operator<br/>
- Assault Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Battle Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Finishing Move<br/>
<br/>
- BlackCell Bonus Topper with 11 additional reactive Operator skin alternatives and 6 Weapon Blueprints with Tracers.<br/>
<br/>
Activision may update, replace, or remove this in-game content at any time.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1708019001"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal Richards (formerly of Echos)</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1708019001"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about the future of Sheepy, limited edition merch and more.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXIT KUN</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781370/EXIT_KUN/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a game of finding differences and observing. Our game challenges players to carefully observe and spot the distinctions that lead them to the elusive "Exit KUN."<br>
<br>
Game Overview:<br>
<br>
You find yourself trapped in an enigmatic underground labyrinth, and your only goal is to reach "Exit KUN." The journey demands keen observation of your surroundings. Every detail matters, and anomalies could be your key to progress.<br>
<br>
How to Play:<br>
<br/>
Observe Carefully: Scrutinize your surroundings to uncover anomalies that may guide your way or pose a threat.<br/>
Turn Back if Needed: If anomalies are detected, swift decision-making is crucial. Turn back immediately to avoid unforeseen consequences.<br/>
Forward Momentum: Should your observation reveal no anomalies, press forward. <br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Developer Notes:<br/>
This game is inspired by Exit 8. You are free to create, upload, and monetize videos and any other content featuring Game on platforms such as YouTube, Twitch, and other video-sharing websites. The characters, places, and elements involved in the game are fictitious. Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, or events is purely coincidental.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soak &amp; Splash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2051500/Soak__Splash/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2051500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the Soak &amp; Splash! Get ready to sweat, socialize, and have a blast with your friends in this unique game that combines the best of traditional sauna culture with modern party fun.<br>
<br>
First, step into the steamy sauna and feel the heat and humidity envelop your body.<br>
<br>
Once everyone is inside, it's time to start the fun. You can start by whisking each other with broom.<br>
<br>
Feeling competitive? You can also fight with other players with sauna equipment. Or you can simply relax and enjoy the company of your friends, chatting, singing, or telling jokes.<br>
<br/>
Finally, when you've had enough of the sauna, you can cool off in the nearby pool or shower.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, this game is all about having fun, bonding with your friends, and experiencing the unique benefits of sauna culture. So why wait? Download game and get ready to sweat, laugh, and enjoy life to the fullest!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/315210/Suicide_Squad_Kill_the_Justice_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Rocksteady Studios, the creators of the Batman: Arkham series, Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is a genre-defying third-person action shooter where the ultimate band of misfits must do the impossible to save the world: Kill the Justice League.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/SSKTJL_Intro.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Join the newly “recruited” members of Amanda Waller’s infamous Task Force X (aka the Suicide Squad), Harley Quinn, Deadshot, Captain Boomerang and King Shark, as they set out on an impossible mission to Kill the Justice League. Drop into an expansive and dynamic open-world Metropolis ravaged by Brainiac’s invasion and terrorized by the heroes who once protected it. <br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/Traversal_2.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Each Squad member brings their own traversal mechanics to help them navigate a sprawling and battle-torn Metropolis, combining free-roaming exploration and combat verticality for an unforgettable experience. Players are free to experiment with a variety of different play styles to unleash maximum damage on their enemies. Whether in single player or online with up to three of your friends, players can take on this suicide mission their own way.<br/><br/>Post-launch, players can expect a continuously evolving Metropolis with free new playable villains, environments, weapons, in-game events, and more, all included with purchase of the base game.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788630/Nothing_Together/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play together. Maybe.<br/><br/>Just do Nothing as the timer goes up and climb the leaderboards. If you do Something, you lose.<br/><br/>Play in <strong>Together </strong>mode, where up to 20 players unite to do Nothing, or compete with other players in <strong>Battle Royale</strong> to find out who's the best at doing Nothing!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161700/Persona_3_Reload/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a transfer student thrust into an unexpected fate when entering the hour "hidden" between one day and the next. Awaken an incredible power and chase the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fight for your friends, and leave a mark on their memories forever. <br/><br/>Persona 3 Reload is a captivating reimagining of the genre-defining RPG, reborn for the modern era.<br/><br/>Key Features: <br/>- Experience the pivotal game of the Persona series faithfully remade with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, and signature stylish UI. <br/><br/>-Fully immerse yourself in an emotional, gripping journey with new scenes, character interactions, and additional voiceover.<br/><br/>- Choose how to meaningfully spend each day through various activities, from exploring the Port Island to forging genuine bonds with beloved characters.<br/><br/>- Build and command your optimal team to take down otherworldly Shadows and climb closer to the truth.<br/><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Deluxe Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook: Filled with 64 pages of character art, concept art, backgrounds and other illustrations from the game!<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack: Listen to newly arranged tracks from the original Persona 3 plus all-new tracks from Persona 3 Reload, presented by the Atlus sound team for a total of 60 new songs.</li></ul><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Premium Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack<br/></li><li>Persona 3 Reload DLC Pack:  P5R Phantom Thieves Costume Set, P5R Shujin Academy Costume Set, P5R Persona Set 1, P5R Persona Set 2 , P5R BGM Set, P4G Yasogami High Costume Set, P4G Persona Set</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1131620/Dominion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Expand a small kingdom to a mighty Dominion!  <br/><br/>Play the Spiel des Jahres winning boardgame beloved by millions around the world. This is the officially licensed implementation.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Reigning.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Discover the game that defined a genre, Dominion was first to popularize deck-building and remains a staple of tabletop. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/GrowYourKingdom.png?t=1707010484">Collect as many Victory Points as you can by building a powerful deck. Your deck starts out a small sad set of Estates and Coppers, but you hope that by the end of the game it will be brimming with Gold, Provinces, and the inhabitants and structures of your kingdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/BuildEngine.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Choose wisely among the 10 cards available in the tableau to create the strongest combos to dominate your opponent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CollectAllExpansions.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Make your games more exciting with additional cards and rules from up to 15 expansions including the recent Plunder expansion! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/NearInfiniteVariety.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Over one hundred thirty-two septillion possible Kingdom combinations, 500+ cards, 15 and counting expansions, and ongoing promo packs make Dominion one of the most extensive and replayable boardgames in the hobby. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CompeteComputer.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Sharpen your skills with solitaire style solo play against a robust AI, with four levels of difficulty. Our innovative AI learns through self-play. Earn Achievements and win in Recommended Sets against each AI level. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/PlayWithFriends.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Join up to 6 players online through your device or pass and play among your friends. Play ranked or unranked matchmaking, with realtime and asynchronous modes. Set up a private table for a family game, challenge a stranger in the lobby, or invite a friend!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Daily.png?t=1707010484"><br/>A daily ritual to relax with over a cup of coffee. Try the Daily Dominion, a free puzzle level available to players around the world. Practice your strategy to keep up a winning streak and climb the leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CrossPlatform.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Play from any supported device, whenever you want, after verifying your email in-game. Join games with opponents on platforms other than your own to enjoy the largest possible multiplayer pool and speedy matchmaking. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/JoinCommunity.png?t=1707010484"><br/>With an active Discord and online community, make new friends or challenge new people to a game. Export and share kingdoms and game summaries to compare strategies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/FreeToPlay.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Download the game that started it all for free! The base set of Dominion is available at no charge. Try the rotation of expansion cards in the Daily at no cost once per day. Jump into a lobby game with expansions enabled to try before you buy. Only the host needs to own the expansions.    <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Intro.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Learn the ropes in this easy to pick-up, hard to master title. Play one of the most highly regarded strategy tabletop games of all time through our simple tutorial.  The core loop is easy to follow, but offers a wealth of strategy to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>1-6 player</strong> support<br/></li><li><strong>500 </strong> plus <strong>cards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Solo play</strong> against four AI difficulties<br/></li><li><strong>Async </strong>&amp; <strong>real-time</strong> multiplayer<br/></li><li><strong>Ranked</strong> &amp; <strong>unranked</strong> matchmaking<br/></li><li><strong>Lobby</strong> &amp; <strong>Private game</strong> tables<br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform multiplayer</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform purchases</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Daily challenge</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Challenging AI</strong> that learns through self-play<br/></li><li><strong>Recommended Sets</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Customize</strong>, save &amp; share <strong>Kingdoms</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Achievements</strong>, <strong>Stats </strong>&amp; <strong>Leaderboards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Pass &amp; Play</strong> mode<br/></li><li>Automated <strong>score-keeping</strong> &amp; hints<br/></li><li><strong>Smart-play</strong> options to streamline gameplay<br/></li><li><strong>Jumbo mode</strong> for readability on phones<br/></li><li><strong>Turbo mode</strong> to zoom through games quickly<br/></li><li><strong>Tutorial</strong> &amp; <strong>Rules</strong><br/></li><li><strong>4 languages</strong>: English, Japanese, German, French<br/></li><li><strong>15 expansions</strong> plus three promo packs </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Awards for the Boardgame</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Awards.png?t=1707010484"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/881020/Granblue_Fantasy_Relink/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/881020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Story<br/>
Granblue Fantasy takes place in the Sky Realm, a world where myriad islands float in a great blue expanse. Take your role as captain of a skyfaring crew, joined by a scrappy little dragon named Vyrn and a young girl with mysterious powers named Lyria. Together you sail with a colorful cast of crewmates, including kings and misfits alike, for Estalucia, a fabled island beyond the end of the skies.<br/>
<br/>
In the Zegagrande Skydom, islands are guarded by powerful creatures known as primal beasts and winds carry tales of a secretive organization known as the Church of Avia. Unveil a web of intrigue reaching far beyond the borders of Zegagrande and engage in a battle for the fate of the Sky Realm itself.<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay<br/>
Engage in real-time combat with a party of four in this character action RPG—choose from a diverse roster of skyfarers, each with their own unique weapons, skills, and combat styles. Teamwork makes the dream work with party-based mechanics such as Link Attacks and Chain Bursts to help you crush foes in spectacular fashion. Tackle quests solo or with the help of others for up to 4-player co-op and take down treacherous foes to score rare loot to further enhance your gear. Every enemy and party formation has its own strengths and weaknesses—the key to victory lies in working out how these pieces fit together.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced combat not your thing? Assist modes can provide accessibility for gamers of all skill levels. Toggle on Full Assist to have all actions performed automatically during battle!<br/>
<br/>
The Sky Realm is rich in lore and history. Browse Lyria's journal at any point during the game to access a trove of writings on the world's peoples, places, and more. In addition to the wealth of side quests available, Fate Episodes allow you to delve into the backstories of each member of your crew!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlazBlue Entropy Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2273430/BlazBlue_Entropy_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/原创声明-英语.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗EN_.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>Charismatic character designs with unique aesthetic styles and dramatic animations create a flamboyant, awesome combat experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快的动作连招EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快动作连招.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>Smooth controls, infinite possibilities of combos, and realistic combat feedback. This is the roguelite game with the best action experience yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超多角色豪华制作EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/全员图618x346.jpg?t=1707811616"><br/>Ten playable characters with vibrant personalities, unique combat styles, and immersive voice-acting.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式自由定制EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式，自由定制en.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>There are hundreds of moves for you to build around, plus countless elemental effects and legacy skills passed between characters. The possibilities are infinite. Time to make the best fighter of your own!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/抉择拯救世界EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/GIF-抉择拯救世界EN.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>In the future where the world has been plunged into chaos, people enter a cyberspace called ACE, seeking their last chance to resolve the crisis.<br/>If you are the only person in this world who knows the truth, how will you react?<br/>The ending is also the beginning. Your decision will decide humanity's future.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poppy Playtime - Chapter 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2555190/Poppy_Playtime__Chapter_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2555190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							A decrepit orphanage known as Playcare sits beneath the once magical toy factory. You must make your way through this haunted place, solving new puzzles and avoiding the nightmares that lurk within the dark. Answers lie between the blood-stained bedsheets and screaming echoes... If you can survive.<br/><br/><strong>This is Poppy Playtime's biggest and most terrifying chapter yet. More lies ahead than you might expect...</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>New monsters await, and they're much more than just simple toys.<br/></li><li>Playcare is Playtime's own massive, fantastical orphanage. And you get to explore it.<br/></li><li>The GrabPack gets an upgrade!<br/></li><li>New hands permit new and creative ways to explore.<br/></li><li>A Gas Mask is the only way to safely explore through the red smoke that fills the air.<br/></li><li>Answers will finally be revealed. Lies can only stay buried for so long...</li></ul><br/>There is so much more to see, with further details coming very soon. <br/><br/>Much awaits you in the chapter ahead... a bit of playtime never hurt anyone, right?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2772560/Supermarket_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This Prologue is a limited version of the full game to stop waiting and jump into running your supermarket already. Don't forget to wishlist the full game to continue your most fun supermarket experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Design your store, optimizing for efficiency and aesthetics. Determine where products are displayed, manage your aisles, and ensure a smooth shopping experience for your customers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Order stock using an in-game computer and anticipate the arrival of your next delivery. Unpack goods, organize them in your storage room and display them on shelves, fridges, and freezers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Read product barcodes, handle cash and credit card transactions, and ensure customers leave satisfied with their shopping and checkout experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier_Raw.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Navigate the complexities of a real-time market. Buy products when prices dip and determine the best-selling prices to balance customer satisfaction with profit margins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><br/>Wishlist the full game "Supermarket Simulator" where every decision matters. Will you rise to the occasion, transforming a modest establishment into a retail powerhouse, all while balancing customer satisfaction, finances, and mafia expectations?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Lily - Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2220360/Paper_Lily__Chapter_1/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Something terrible has happened. You can’t bear to think about it - but you can’t live like this anymore. You stopped attending school, you haven’t left your house in months, you have no reason to get out of bed anymore. There are no choices left.<br/><br/>No choice except... that strange golden letter.<br/><br/>It’s time to get your life back together. <br/><br/>One last try.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/divider.png?t=1706724298"><br/><br/>Paper Lily is a story-driven, psychological horror RPG where each puzzle has multiple solutions and outcomes. <strong>There is always another way.</strong><br/>Follow Lacie's story as you explore a dangerous hidden world, solve puzzles in multiple different ways, and face strange enemies. The game is playable in about 4 hours and contains multiple endings depending on your actions.<br/><br/>Paper Lily - Chapter 1 is the continuation to the prologue, <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1698960" rel="" target="_blank">Project Kat</a>, but it can also  be enjoyed without having played it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/lacie_sai_walk.gif?t=1706724298"><h2 class="bb_tag">Out of Context Features</h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple ways of solving puzzles!<br/></li><li>Touch grass, and trees<br/></li><li>Minigames where you press buttons and push boxes around<br/></li><li>Call your mother<br/></li><li>Harmless Snack™<br/></li><li>Various things made of paper<br/></li><li>Bunnies (or whatever those things are)<br/></li><li>Demons<br/></li><li>Fast demons<br/></li><li>Social anxiety simulation<br/></li><li>Table salt<br/></li><li>...Is that Kat? Nah, probably not<br/></li><li>Bathroom etiquette<br/></li><li>Death</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2072450/Like_a_Dragon_Infinite_Wealth/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/Accolades_616.png?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>EPIC EMOTIONAL DRAMA</strong><br/>Two larger-than-life heroes brought together by the hand of fate, or perhaps something more sinister…<br/><br/>Ichiban Kasuga, an unstoppable underdog who’s no stranger to crawling up from rock bottom, and Kazuma Kiryu, a broken man facing down his last days.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/2_Epic_Emotional_Drama.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>BEST-IN-CLASS RPG ACTION</strong><br/>Experience one-of-a-kind combat with dynamic, fast-paced RPG battles where the battlefield becomes your weapon, and anything goes. Adapt your party’s skills to the situation with outlandish jobs and customizations to strategically subdue enemies with over-the-top moves. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/3_Best_In_Class_RPG_Action.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>INFINITE ADVENTURE</strong><br/>Live it up in Japan and explore all that Hawaii has to offer in an adventure so big it spans the Pacific. Unforgettable moments await at every step of the journey with a unique mix of quests and activities to enjoy at your leisure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/4_Infinite_Adventure.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Deluxe Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Ultimate Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/>- Assorted Outfit Bundle: Customize your party's look with outfits &amp; swimwear<br/>- Sujimon &amp; Resort Bundle: Get legendary Sujimon, resort guests and special boosters<br/>- Yakuza CD Collection Set: Increase your in-game playlist with classic karaoke tracks						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summon Masters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2100140/Summon_Masters/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2100140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a card and board game with the following features:<br>
<br>
Deck Building: Players can build their own decks to battle with. Depending on different strategies and opponents, players can choose different cards to counter.<br>
<br>
Tactical Gameplay: The game uses a 3x10 chessboard, and players can freely place cards to fight. Players need to develop tactics and arrange card positions and usage order within limited space.<br>
<br>
Different Professions: Players can choose freely from four professions - swordsman, mage, monk, and archer. Each profession has different characteristics and skills, and players can choose according to their preferences and tactical needs.<br/>
<br/>
Competitive Battles: Players can battle with other players after building their decks, and it is fun to fight with other people. Through battles with other players, players can improve their strength and tactical skills.<br/>
<br/>
Team Dungeons: In addition to fighting against other players, players can also team up with others to challenge high-difficulty dungeons. Players need to defeat powerful bosses through cooperation and strategy to get more rewards and cards.<br/>
<br/>
Special Challenges: Players can participate in special rules challenges and use their intelligence to defeat other players. These special rules make the game more interesting and challenging, and players need to constantly think and try new strategies.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced: Each game is fast-paced (within 5 minutes), and can be played in short fragments of time. The fast pace of the game allows players to enjoy the game in a short time, while also being able to play at any time and anywhere.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2248950/TransSiberian_Railway_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take the helm of a classic Russian locomotive, discover the raw beauty and wildness of Siberia and try to survive on the longest railway line in the world. This is the Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator. A game for real adventurers!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/drinking1.gif?t=1707824452"><br/><br/>Complete the tutorial and the first kilometers of the route for free.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/explosion_gif.gif?t=1707824452"><br/><br/>The Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator offers amazing rail and survival challenges on real Russian dangerous routes. Feel what it is like to put your hands at the helm of a powerful freight locomotive and explore the untouched natural landscape that is sure to delight you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/shooting_gif.gif?t=1707824452"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Prologue features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Detailed simulation of driving a VL10 locomotive - the locomotive control is slightly simplified.<br/></li><li> Locomotive repair system - Manage and replace locomotive parts that are constantly wearing out.<br/></li><li> Train traffic simulation - Follow rail signs and signals to avoid derailment or damage to a part of the locomotive.<br/></li><li> Work system - Earn by completing transport orders. <br/></li><li> Game modes (Survival) and (Simulator). It is recommended to play in the (Survival) mode. This is the leading game mode that is constantly being developed. <br/>For players who are not interested in survival mechanics, a simple Simulator mode is available. <br/></li><li> Mafia system - Complete missions for the mafia to earn extra money.<br/></li><li> Survival system with statistics of hunger, thirst, alcohol, hangover, disease and hypothermia - Eat and drink to avoid death. <br/>Keep the right temperature so you don't freeze.<br/></li><li> Shooting system - Use your weapons for hunting and self-defense.<br/></li><li> Purchase and sales system - Buy various items, food, tools, weapons and ammunition.<br/></li><li> Locomotive inspection mode - Inspect the condition of locomotive parts and replace them in time to avoid damage.<br/></li><li> Dynamic weather system with day and night cycle - Survive extreme weather conditions.<br/></li><li> Route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Novosibirsk-Main) - scale 1:1. Buy the full version with the route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Krasnoyarsk).<br/></li><li> Police system - A corrupt militia watches over your movements.<br/></li><li> Much more to discover.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Universim</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/352720/The_Universim/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>WHAT WOULD YOU DO WITH THE POWER?</strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Play God!</strong> </h2>Guide your fledgling sentient species (lovingly called “nuggets”) from Stone Age cave painters to star-faring explorers.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-1-2d869427c7.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Wield godly power</strong></h2>Command more than 15 godly powers to guide, protect — or discipline — your followers. Create devastating tornadoes, smite naughty followers with lightning bolts, or shake and sunder the very earth. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-1-998341a4ac.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Watch your Nuggets grow and thrive</strong></h2>Observe Nuggets' every move as they work and fight to survive. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-537928a55b.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Evolve and advance through the ages</strong></h2>Research more than 200 technological and societal advancements. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-daca04b5ec.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Expand your power and colonize the galaxy</strong></h2>Discover and colonize a galaxy of procedurally generated planets, each with  unique ecosystems and challenges to conquer.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-be2f66969b.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Manage delicate ecosystems</strong></h2>Manage the delicate balance of planetary ecosystems to help nuggets thrive. Your decisions and your followers’ ' actions influence global climates and have real environmental consequences. (Try not to kill them in an ecological disaster — well, unless you want to, of course.)<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-0095b39c11.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Delve into the deeper mystery of your existence</strong></h2>Unravel the layers of a deeper cosmic story that challenges your perception of who and what you are — and reveals unexpected twists!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-4830f44913.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>About This Game:</strong></h2><br/>The Universim is a strategy city builder game with “God” elements where you guide a civilization (Nuggets) from the Stone Age to the Space Age. Manage resources, dynamic challenges, and ensure your Nuggets can survive, thrive, and spread to the stars. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Animated_Planet_3.png?t=1705993770"><br/><br/>The Universim  features more than  200 research perks that will help you to shape your civilization. Be as benevolent or malevolent as you like to drive nuggets to evolve, advance, and expand. (Even the best civilizations need an occasional smiting).  <br/>Every planet in The Universim is procedurally generated and offers unique characteristics  and challenges, ensuring  that every world and every game is unique and engaging.  Ecological balance and resource management are critical to success. Nuggets have their own needs and behaviors you must attend to. Your guidance will shape how they deal with conflicts, natural disasters, alien creatures, and other civilizations. Their growth and evolution depends on you!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FSymAzCGWsk" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Crytivo_Discord.png?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FgUt5N68" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Discord_join.jpg?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://twitter.com/crytivo" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Twitter.png?t=1705993770"/></a> <br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Feepurl.com%2FbKnqM1" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/News.png?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><br/>This game published by <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/franchise/Crytivo" rel="" target="_blank">Crytivo</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Capitalist Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743080/100_Capitalist_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779640/100_Capitalist_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_6" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779640/100_Capitalist_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱💼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 CAPITALIST CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆💰💵</h2>🤑 Join the cutest adventure in the Wall Street, New York, heart of capitalism! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/600x200.png?t=1706062420"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level of Wall Street location<br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Capitalist Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779640/100_Capitalist_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100CapitalistCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Extra.png?t=1706062420"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779660/100_Capitalist_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100CapitalistCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1706062420"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779650/100_Capitalist_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=100CapitalistCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Artbook.png?t=1706062420"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/600x1.png?t=1706062420"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1706062420"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot" id="dynamiclink_7" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743080/100_Capitalist_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot" id="dynamiclink_8" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743080/100_Capitalist_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intravenous 2: Mercenarism</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2651330/Intravenous_2_Mercenarism/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Wishlist_Game.png?t=1705699394"><br/><br/>Step into the shoes of Gideon, a ruthless mercenary who cares about nothing but his wealth. Set two months before the events of Intravenous 2, you will take on seemingly simple jobs, the effects of which will ripple out and affect the main game's protagonist. But why should Gideon care? He's just in it for the money.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Stealth_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Stealth or Firepower:</strong> the choice is yours. Sneak through shadows, turn off the lights, pick doors, or unleash a hail of bullets. The game will adapt to your play style.<br/></li><li> <strong>Customize Your Skills:</strong> develop your skills the way you want to, whether it's mastering the art of stealth or becoming a gunslinging virtuoso.<br/></li><li> <strong>Bullet Time:</strong> Gideon is no stranger to stimulants that enhance his cognitive abilities - bending time to give him the edge in tense situations.<br/></li><li> <strong>Vast Arsenal:</strong> choose from firearms, gadgets, and a variety of ammo types to creatively tackle the challenge<br/></li><li> <strong>Weapon Modification:</strong> personalize each firearm with suppressors, laser sights, and more, tailoring your arsenal to the task at hand.<br/></li><li> <strong>Responsive AI:</strong> engage in intense combat with enemies that react to your actions, take cover, use tactics and call for backup.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Action_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2744170/Artifact_SeekerPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/DS.png?t=1706492908"/></a><br/>The difference between the prologue version and the official version<br/>There is a special artifact in the prologue<br/>Characters: 2 in the prologue, at least 5 in the official version<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 3 in the final version.<br/>Systems: Tavern, Marketplace, and Endless Mode will be added to the game.<br/>Artifacts: More artifacts will be added to the game.<br/>Skills: More skills will be added in the official version.<br/>Affixes: More Affixes will be added in the official version.<br/>Events: There will be more interesting Events in the official version.<br/>Progress: No need to worry, all progress will be carry into the official version.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/11y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1z.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/2y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/gif1.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong>[/b]<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><strong><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </img></img></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saving Clicklandia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2725030/Saving_Clicklandia/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">HISTORY:</h2><br/>An ancient evil has awoken in the Kingdom of Clicklandia and chaos now reigns. The Legendary Dragon has attacked, unleashing terror and disorder upon the once-tranquil realm. The fate of the kingdom and its people hangs in the balance, and only a true hero can stand against the impending disaster.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725030/extras/Banner_0.gif?t=1708313956"><br/><br/>Do you have what it takes to step into the shoes of this valiant hero? Embark on an epic journey to restore peace and order in Clicklandia. Navigate through treacherous landscapes, confront formidable foes, and unlock your true potential. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725030/extras/Banner_1.png?t=1708313956"><br/><br/>As you progress, you'll uncover many abilities, develop beneficial relationships with shopkeepers and witches alike and earn plenty of gold to help you on your journey.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725030/extras/Banner_2.png?t=1708313956"><br/><br/>Venture forth, for the Kingdom of Clicklandia relies on your courage and heroism. Will you rise to the challenge and save this world from its darkest hour? Find out and embark on a legendary adventure with Saving Clicklandia today!<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features:</h2><br/>Saving Clicklandia is a game in the genre of "match-three" in which you will have to pass numerous tests and fight with formidable bosses. This game is a classic "match-three" with role-playing elements, you can change the appearance of the character, equip the hero in different armor and craft numerous items that will help in battle and give an advantage.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725030/extras/Banner_4.gif?t=1708313956"><br/> <br/>The game features are battles with unique bosses that diversify the gameplay and change the approach to passing.<br/> <br/>In addition to battles you can buy useful ingredients to create potions and other auxiliary items.<br/> <br/>As you progress through the game, the levels will appear new game elements that develop the gameplay and complicate the passage.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725030/extras/Banner_3.png?t=1708313956"><br/><br/>Complete 200 levels<br/>Catchy downloadable Original Soundtrack<br/>Beautiful desktop wallpapers<br/>Earn dozens of achievements<br/>Defeat the formidable bosses<br/>Find new equipment for the character						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backrooms:Rebirth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2791030/BackroomsRebirth/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a horror puzzle type game based on the theme of the Backrooms, find an exit in each level to escape here, before you have to keep dodging the pursuit of monsters that are entities, and then open the door through various methods to find props to clear the game, cheer the wanderers.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation Save the Girl: Code X</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2717000/Operation_Save_the_Girl_Code_X/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An abandoned medieval military base is infested with mutated zombies, and your female boss accidentally enters it while on a mission. Because the zombies are so bad, your female boss is infected by them. You must go and save her. The new boss has given you an order that the female boss must come out smoothly. Are you ready?<br>
<br>
This is a first-person shooter game, there are a lot of zombies and props in the game, you need to use these smoothly to rescue the female boss. This is your mission.You need to complete a total of 11 tasks in order to save the female boss.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
♦ Female zombies in bikinis, and lots of blood-pumping effects.<br>
♦ Excellent first-person controller, smooth operation.<br>
♦ 3AAA level scene construction, friendly interaction and sound effects.<br/>
♦ Wonderful mission, a link link.<br/>
♦ Conscientious pricing, can meet your requirements for FPS games.<br/>
<br/>
Game play:<br/>
♦ WSAD move character, mouse control perspective.<br/>
♦ F Open doors or pick up weapons and supplies.<br/>
♦ TAB key can change the language.<br/>
♦ 12345 Switch weapon,T shot.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Math Problem Killer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2479160/The_Math_Problem_Killer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INCREDIBLY DARK AND DISTURBING DESCRIPTIONS OF VIOLENCE</strong></h2><br/>WARNING!!!<br/><br/>The Math Problem Killer is incredibly dark and disturbing. You must listen to recordings made by the Serial Killer. These recordings describe violence against men, women, and children.  Only the most courageous Special Agents should attempt to enter the dungeons of the Math Problem Killer.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>ENTER DISTUBRING DUNGEONS AND SOLVE THE KILLER'S CREEPY MATH</strong></h2><br/>The main gameplay mechanic of The Math Problem Killer is walking through dungeons and listening to the recordings of a sadistic serial killer recount how he stalked, abducted and tortured his victims., and ultimately solving a math problem based on those disturbing stories.  The ultimate goal of each level is to rescue an individual hostage that his being held at the end of the dungeon.  <br/><br/>As you walk through the dungeons, the killer will tell you stories about how he abducted or tortured a victim. In his stories there will be facts, such as when he abducted a victim, or how long he followed them, or how long he tortured them, or how long it took them to die.  He will then form a math question based on the facts from his stories.  Such as...<br/><br/><strong><i></i>"I want you to start with Andrea's age, then multiply that by the number of nails I hammered into her husband. Then add the number of minutes I made her hang in my dungeon. Then multiply this number by the number of minutes I tortured Andrea's neighbor."<i></i> </strong><br/><br/>You will need to listen to all of the recordings in the room in order to gather all of the information required to solve the question.  When you do have your answer, you must enter it into the keypad on the door to the next room. If your answer is correct, the door will open and you will repeat the process until you reach the last room with the hostage. If your answer is wrong, then the hostage dies immediately and you must start over. <br/><br/>At its core, The Math Problem Killer is a tense, slow paced, story centric, crime thriller, walking simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A CRIME THRILLER STORY</strong></h2><br/>The Math Problem Killer is a crime thriller. A sadistic serial killer, known as the Math Problem killer has been murdering people in the city of New Columbia. At the request of the mayor and state governor, a federal Serial Killer Task Force arrives to hunt down the Serial Killer. Within days of arrival, the Task Force recieves a communication from the illusive and dangerous killer.  He has taken a hostage named Bethany Morgan. He tells the Task Force the hostage location, but he also informs the task force that they may only send one agent inside, and that agent may not have any communication with the outside world. <br/><br/>You are the Task Force Special Agent that is chosen to enter the facility and attempt a rescue of Bethany Morgan. The game takes place over the course of 11 weeks, and follows the Serial Killer Task Force as it attempts to find and apprehend the Math Problem killer. Each week is a new dungeon that must be entered, and a new hostage that must be rescued.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479160/extras/hanging_nails.gif?t=1708278496"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>THE KILLER WILL TELL YOU DISTURBING STORIES</strong></h2><br/>The Math Problem Killer is a sadistic and violent monster. He enjoys stalking, and torturing his victims. He also enjoys bragging about his exploits even more. Throughout each dungeon you will find recordings left by the killer. In each recording, he will recount with delight the various methods he employed to capture and torture his victims. You must be prepared to listen to unsettling and disturbing accountings of murder and violence towards, men, women and children. But remember, you are a special agent in the Serial Killer Task Force, and it is your job to rescue the hostage being held in the dungeons. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479160/extras/keypad.gif?t=1708278496"><br/><br/>The Math Problem Killer has placed multiple recordings of pieces of a fact pattern and an accompanying complicated multi-part word problem in each room. The player must listen to the recordings and solve the math word problem that is presented. The answer to the math problem is the door code for the locked door. However, if the player enters a wrong answer the hostage will be immediately killed.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>ONE MISTAKE AND THE HOSTAGE DIES</strong></h2><br/><strong>I wont kill the hostage...you will.</strong><br/><br/>The Math Problem Killer does not give you second chances. You must be accurate, or the hostage will die. In each room of each dungeon, you must solve a simple math word problem, and then enter your answer into the keypad on the locked door. If you enter an incorrect code, the hostage you are trying to rescue will be burned alive by hyrdoflouric acid. Think carefully special agent. There is zero margin for error. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479160/extras/crate.gif?t=1708278496"><br/><br/>A single mistake will kill the hostage and cause the player to fail the level. <i>The Math Problem Killer</i> is a high consequence game in which one mistake will have dire consequences. So think carefully Special Agent.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>YOU WILL NEED A PENCIL AND PAPER</strong></h2><br/>In each room of each level, you will need to solve a math word problem, and use the answer as the code to open the locked door to the next room and ultimately the locked box that contains the hostage. The math word problems are not difficult, but you will need to gather the numbers from the disturbing stories told by the killer.  Essentially you must gather clues and piece them together in order to figure out the answer. The only way to successfully solve these math problems is utilize a pencil and piece of paper.  The player will need to write things down. Because one math mistake, and the hostage dies.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>protoViolence - Definitive Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2675850/protoViolence__Definitive_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2675850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2675850/extras/angiemove2.gif?t=1708278336"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Can a scientist save a test subject from her life’s work?</strong></h2><br/>A sci-fi/drama visual novel, and a prequel to <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2403570/malViolence__Definitive_Edition/" rel="" target="_blank"><i>malViolence.</i></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2675850/extras/phonecall.gif?t=1708278336"><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>About:</u></h2>For over 20 years, <strong>Dr. Deidre Destrange </strong>produced groundbreaking research on cybernetics under STOP: a world-renowned security organization.<br/><br/>However, her work has led to the birth of STOP’s Youth Training and Development Initiative (YTDI): an unethical program that turns children into powerful cyborg soldiers. <br/><br/>Since Deidre’s legacy founded the YTDI, she believes she has the power to end it.<br/><br/><i>Will her upcoming case study save STOP from itself?</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2675850/extras/angiemove.gif?t=1708278336"><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>This visual novel features:</u></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>~2 hours of reading time</strong><br/></li><li><strong>High-quality sprites and CGs:</strong> with blinking, speaking and dynamic camera movements<br/></li><li><strong>Interactive records to explore</strong><br/></li><li><strong>An original, immersive soundtrack</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Partial voice acting</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Accessibility options</strong> such as image captions, sound captions, and text legibility functions<br/></li><li><strong>One ending</strong></li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grow a Carrot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2794860/Grow_a_Carrot/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2794860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2794860/extras/BunnySitting1gif.gif?t=1708256359"><br/><br/>Ever dreamed about <strong>growing carrots</strong>? Me neither, however - For a <strong>cheap</strong> price I present you an indie game where you can <strong>plant and harvest carrots</strong>, get them <strong>from a tree</strong>, <strong>fight</strong> with the <strong>carrots slimes</strong> and <strong>dig</strong> carrots out of the <strong>Mine</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2794860/extras/GameplayGif.gif?t=1708256359"><br/><br/><br/><br/>Make sure to meet all of the bunnies - Some of them are more useful than you could expect<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2794860/extras/MeetThem.gif?t=1708256359"><br/><br/>I recommend playing this game on the second screen - as a time killer. Just open Youtube or Twitch, relax, and grow a carrots on the second screen!<br/><br/><br/><br/>"Grow a Carrot" powered by Clickteam Fusion 2.5						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pigmenta</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2812720/Pigmenta/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2812720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pigmenta is an ambient logic puzzle game, where you mix different colored lines to solve puzzles.<br/><br/>The game includes:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 48 handcrafted campaign puzzles<br/></li><li> Time trial mode for those seeking extra challenges<br/></li><li> Infinite puzzle generator to keep on playing</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seraphim</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594690/Seraphim/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594690/extras/Title.gif?t=1708254463"><br/>A fast-faced speedrunning platformer where you undermine the righteous angel's unrighteous past. Break through the cute, charming aesthetic to find its sinister undertones. Seraphim was built with a religious fervour for player feel. That means the jump is fine-tuned, the run is tight, and the wings should feel like an extension of your thoughts. Just a warning: this is a DIFFICULT game for platforming veterans! Know what you're getting into!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594690/extras/tricks.gif?t=1708254463"><br/>Master the tricks and the tech in a judgment-free zone. Or, turn on "mock me" mode to be insulted when you mess up! Tame your wings and learn to manoeuvre around traps, steel yourself against brambles, dodge and weave around sinister bosses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594690/extras/Bosses.gif?t=1708254463"> <br/>They're sinister. But also the perfect level of cute so you feel bad about hurting them.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594690/extras/Features.gif?t=1708254463"> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Forty plus unique, hand-crafted levels<br/></li><li>An accessible yet engaging narrative<br/></li><li>Five core areas<br/></li><li>Secrets and extras (hunt for them if you dare!)<br/></li><li>A willingness to sacrifice all my artistic principles for a funny joke <br/></li><li>A bona fide title screen (that's right)<br/></li><li>An extensive soundtrack to get your blood pumping<br/></li><li>Many, many spikes and brambles and explosions and occasionally pits<br/></li><li>Skeletons<br/></li><li>Closets<br/></li><li>Skeletons in closets<br/></li><li>A real pause menu for you pro gamers<br/></li><li>Configurable settings<br/></li><li>A writer who doesn't know how to end a list<br/></li><li>Compromising poses<br/></li><li>And more!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594690/extras/Ending.gif?t=1708254463"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road Engineer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2785810/Road_Engineer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are a Road Engineer. Build roads and bridges to lead vehicles to destination.<br>
<br>
Different vehicles (car, van, moto, truck, bus), different roads (normal, large, bridge).<br>
Avoid traffic jams, stay under limited cost, optimize time or speed, reach a distance.<br>
<br>
Every level is a specific challenge depending on available features, board size, and objectives.<br>
80 levels with progressive difficulty.<br>
A leaderboard by level to compare to best Road Engineers !						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hamster's Journey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2609800/The_Hamsters_Journey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2609800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Hamster's Journey is a roguelite platformer about combining hats and pants to overcome the obstacles that get in your way, while being chased by the ominous Hamster's Nightmare.<br/><br/>Throughout the levels, you can unlock and pick up a variety of <strong>pants</strong>, such as the pogo pants and the skateboard pants, which affect how you move and how you jump. You'll also find <strong>hats</strong>. These are your actions: Equip the grapple hook hat to swing from the scenery or the dash hat for a quick horizontal burst of speed. There are dozens of unique pairings of hats and pants, and finding a winning combination - or making the most of a bad one - is what The Hamster's Journey is all about!<br/><br/>This is a game about variety of movement, and finding the right tool for the job. But then again, using the worst combinations can sometimes help you find unexpected secrets!<br/><br/>If you make it far enough - and fast enough - you can make it all the way to the end of a world, and unlock the door to the next one. In the end, perhaps the intrepid hamster really can escape and see what's out there in the real world.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>幸存者幻想曲 Survivor Fantasia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2717050/_Survivor_Fantasia/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Introduction</h2>"Survivor's Fantasia" is a vampire-themed game that combines elements of light tower defense. In the game, players can choose from over 10 survivor characters and utilize a combination of more than 50 cards, 20+ consumables, and various combat professions to fend off approaching hordes of monsters, while also challenging powerful bosses and striving to survive.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2>Diverse Gameplay: The game combines elements of light tower defense, RPG, and more, offering players a diverse range of strategies and tactical experiences.<br/>Traps/Terrain: The game includes various traps and terrain that players can utilize to hinder monster advances, adding strategic depth to the gameplay.<br/>Active Items: Players can use active items such as walls, bushes, magic books, bombs, etc., to alter the terrain or enhance their own abilities, thereby changing the course of the battle.<br/>Boss Battles: Boss fights in the game test players' ability to use items effectively, requiring them to cleverly utilize various items and combat strategies to defeat powerful bosses.<br/>Career Choices: The game offers five career options, including warrior, assassin, mage, archer, and summoner. The choice of career affects the effects of certain cards, adding diversity to the combat strategies.<br/>Fast-paced: Game sessions have a duration of 15 minutes.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead end Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2780270/Dead_end_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2780270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2780270/extras/Exit_8_550x55_en.png?t=1708245884"><h2 class="bb_tag">Ghost hits the wall</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Have you heard of this term? Or have you experienced it yourself?<br/></li><li>You are trapped in an infinite loop from which you may never escape.<br/></li><li>Hospital! Synonymous with a scary place. There are all kinds of equipment and medicines, and nurses keep appearing.<br/></li><li>Check everything in the scene carefully to see if it is the same as in your memory.<br/></li><li>Once you find something is wrong, turn back immediately! Maybe it's not too late.<br/></li><li>After reaching the eighth floor, you will be able to leave this terrible place<br/></li><li>Maybe. . . .</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">This is a game that is very suitable for interacting with fans and barrages</h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Maybe your fans are better than your eyes? </h2><h2 class="bb_tag"> When the number of positive reviews reaches 200, we will update the second scene, which is also centered around the nightmare scene in our hearts. </h2><h2 class="bb_tag"> The game supports VR mode. Press ESC on the main interface and select VR mode to enter. </h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Before selecting, please make sure you have and connected the VR device.<br/></li><li>Before choosing, please make sure you have the possibility to take off your VR device.<br/></li><li>After selecting, you may not be able to take off the VR device.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeskPet</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2778280/DeskPet/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Desk pet, now available<br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2778280" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2778280</a><br/><br/>1. Music playback function, let the gentle cat lady maid play those exciting melodies for you!<br/><br/>2. Search information support. Help you search for the information you need with just one click.<br/><br/>3. The interactive experience has been upgraded! Feedback when the mouse moves across different areas, and corresponding content is obtained after clicking.<br/><br/>4. Time display function makes your date display more gorgeous.<br/><br/>5. The divination function, combined with the finger-pinch divination method of the ancient Zhouyi algorithm, provides the experience of instant divination and customized time divination. For entertainment purposes only.<br/><br/>6. Customize the picture function to create a table pet that you are satisfied with. Choose the look you like. You can customize the table pet that accompanies you.<br/><br/>7. Supported languages: Traditional Chinese, Chinese, Japanese, English<br/>Come and make this cat lady maid an indispensable companion on your desktop!<br/><br/>Q group: 955269108<br/><br/><br/><strong>Cat Lady Maid, your new desktop companion</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUIQ: Demons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2719610/PUIQ_Demons/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2719610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							PUIQ: Demons is a game where you must survive several waves of demons and bosses for 25 minutes to win. Gain powers, passives and combine them to get buffs, as well as buy turrets, and other equipment to improve your train to help you on this journey. Win the game to compete for the ranking of the best in the world at killing demons and earn rare achievements to show who the real exorcist is.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2719610/extras/gif_test.gif?t=1708203223"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparSpecial</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2767970/SparSpecial/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A group of high skilled former martial artists get together and spar for fun to keep up with their old practice. The main character Lushi tends to seek out his old adversaries for a few more rounds of sparring. There are different maps based in different places and environments all over! The first playable characters will meet and uncover new players (playable characters) through Story mode where you will spar and unlock them once it is released(coming Soon!). In Sparring choose a character and match them up with who you want in the menu (some characters will be locked!). Sparring mode does not feature any health bars, you will see your enemy defeated once they turn red or a different color and can no longer be hit!<br>
<br>
<br>
- This game is a first release version there will be updates where more features and assets will be dropped and added(monthly).<br>
<br>
- Features original scene, and screen sounds Soundtracks and OFX.						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bigfoot Quest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2798250/Bigfoot_Quest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2798250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Many books have been written, many blurry photos have been taken, but has anyone really found Bigfoot? Discover beautiful landscapes, find clues, and solve puzzles along the way in this point-and-click style puzzle adventure game.<br>
<br>
Your Uncle Henry has set up camp deep in the forest of the Pacific Northwest in search of the mysterious Bigfoot. He asks for your help as he is close to discovering the location of Bigfoot’s den. Will you find Bigfoot?<br>
<br>
Your Uncle Henry has been renowned for discovering lost treasures for as long as you can remember. His legendary stories of adventure excited your imagination as you were a child growing up. Now with your newly acquired archeology skills, he has been reaching out from time to time for your help in tracking down some of these difficult to find treasures.<br>
<br>
This captivating adventure game has:<br/>
- Custom designed beautiful HD graphics!<br/>
- Custom composed soundtrack and sound effects!<br/>
- A dynamic map to show the screens you have visited and current location<br/>
- A camera that takes photos of clues and symbols as you discover them<br/>
- Dozens of puzzles, clues, and items<br/>
- Auto saves your progress<br/>
- Available for phones and tablets!<br/>
- Instantly move around the map reducing travel time with Fast-travel<br/>
- Get helpful text hints that nudge you in the right direction and complete walkthrough videos for each hint and puzzle<br/>
<br/>
Visit our website to sign up for our newsletter and learn about upcoming games!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescue the Enchanter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2798240/Rescue_the_Enchanter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2798240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Search for the enchanter who has been trapped for years within the enchanted world of the last book you discovered! Find clues, solve puzzles, and uncover tools along the way needed to unlock and explore vast, exotic worlds and rescue the enchanter.<br>
<br>
Uncle Henry has started to search for the enchanter within the book, but was unsuccessful so he is leaving this important task to you. He left clues in the enchanted world within the book to help you on your journey.<br>
<br>
Your Uncle Henry has been renowned for discovering lost treasures for as long as you can remember. His legendary stories of adventure excited your imagination as you were a child growing up. Now with your newly acquired archeology skills, he has been reaching out from time to time for your help in tracking down some of these difficult to find treasures.<br>
<br>
This captivating adventure game has:<br/>
- Custom designed beautiful HD graphics!<br/>
- Custom composed soundtrack and sound effects!<br/>
- A dynamic map to show the screens you have visited and current location<br/>
- A camera that takes photos of clues and symbols as you discover them<br/>
- Dozens of puzzles, clues, and items<br/>
- Auto saves your progress<br/>
- Available for phones and tablets!<br/>
- Instantly move around the map reducing travel time with Fast-travel<br/>
- Get helpful text hints that nudge you in the right direction and complete walkthrough videos for each hint and puzzle<br/>
<br/>
Visit our website to sign up for our newsletter and learn about upcoming games!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Enchanted Worlds 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2798230/The_Enchanted_Worlds_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2798230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dear Adventurer, Once again your Uncle Henry is in need of your expertise to help locate a missing amulet that unlocks the 4th enchanted book you discovered. Over his travels he also discovered three enchanted books that transport you to the worlds written on their pages when using a special amulet for each. Use your skills to find clues and solve puzzles that unravel the mystery of this adventure story.<br>
<br>
Your Uncle Henry has been renowned for discovering lost treasures for as long as you can remember. His legendary stories of adventure excited your imagination as you were a child growing up. Now with your newly acquired archeology skills, he has been reaching out from time to time for your help in tracking down some of these difficult to find treasures.<br>
<br>
This captivating adventure game has:<br>
- Custom designed beautiful HD graphics!<br>
- Custom composed soundtrack and sound effects!<br/>
- A dynamic map to show the screens you have visited and current location<br/>
- A camera that takes photos of clues and symbols as you discover them<br/>
- Dozens of puzzles, clues, and items<br/>
- Auto saves your progress<br/>
- Available for phones and tablets!<br/>
- Instantly move around the map reducing travel time with Fast-travel<br/>
- Get helpful text hints that nudge you in the right direction and complete walkthrough videos for each hint and puzzle<br/>
<br/>
Visit our website to sign up for our newsletter and learn about upcoming games!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Enchanted Worlds</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2798220/The_Enchanted_Worlds/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2798220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this latest adventure with Uncle Henry, he has had a secret kept for many years that he now wishes to share with you. Over his travels he has discovered three enchanted books that transport you to the worlds written on their pages when using a special amulet for each. He has just learned that there is a fourth book hidden within one of these worlds! He asks for your help in search of this fourth book. You must go to his house and use the clues and puzzles he has placed to locate and explore the three books that are hidden away in his library.<br>
<br>
Your Uncle Henry has been renowned for discovering lost treasures for as long as you can remember. His legendary stories of adventure excited your imagination as you were a child growing up. Now with your newly acquired archeology skills, he has been reaching out from time to time for your help in tracking down some of these difficult to find treasures.<br>
<br>
This captivating adventure game has:<br>
- Custom designed beautiful HD graphics!<br>
- Custom composed soundtrack and sound effects!<br/>
- A dynamic map to show the screens you have visited and current location<br/>
- A camera that takes photos of clues and symbols as you discover them<br/>
- Dozens of puzzles, clues, and items<br/>
- Auto saves your progress<br/>
- Available for phones and tablets!<br/>
- Instantly move around the map reducing travel time with Fast-travel<br/>
- Get helpful text hints that nudge you in the right direction and complete walkthrough videos for each hint and puzzle<br/>
<br/>
Visit our website to sign up for our newsletter and learn about upcoming games!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mystery of Blackthorn Castle 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2798210/The_Mystery_of_Blackthorn_Castle_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2798210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on your own quest in this beautifully designed classic point and click adventure puzzle game. Explore an all but forgotten 14th century Blackthorn Castle, surrounding dark forest and structures. Discover hidden passageways, clues and puzzles along the way!<br>
<br>
Uncle Henry has been hunting lost treasures for as long as you can remember. His legendary stories of adventure excited your imagination as you were a child growing up. Now with your newly acquired archeology skills, he has been reaching out from time to time for your help in tracking down some of these difficult to find treasures.<br>
<br>
This captivating adventure game has:<br>
- Custom designed beautiful HD graphics!<br>
- Custom composed soundtrack and sound effects!<br/>
- A dynamic map to show the screens you have visited and current location<br/>
- A camera that takes photos of clues and symbols as you discover them<br/>
- Dozens of puzzles, clues, and items<br/>
- Instantly move around the map reducing travel time with Fast-travel<br/>
- Get helpful text hints that nudge you in the right direction and complete walkthrough videos for each hint and puzzle<br/>
- Auto saves your progress<br/>
- Available for phones and tablets!<br/>
<br/>
Visit our website to sign up for our newsletter and learn about upcoming games!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mystery of Blackthorn Castle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2798200/The_Mystery_of_Blackthorn_Castle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2798200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Once again your Uncle Henry has asked for your help in the search for a mysterious artifact. Embark on your own quest in this beautifully designed classic point and click adventure puzzle game. <br>
<br>
Uncle Henry has been hunting lost treasures for as long as you can remember. His legendary stories of adventure excited your imagination as you were a child growing up. Now with your newly acquired archeology skills, he has been reaching out from time to time for your help in tracking down some of these difficult to find treasures.<br>
<br>
In his latest quest, he has been hunting for a mysterious artifact last known to be at Castle Blackthorn in England. As the tale goes, centuries ago a wizard once lived in this castle and stole a valuable artifact from a local watch maker and hid it away somewhere in the depths of the castle.<br>
<br>
You must hurry and help him on this amazing adventure before anyone else finds the mysterious artifact!<br/>
<br/>
This captivating adventure game has:<br/>
- Custom designed beautiful HD graphics!<br/>
- Custom composed soundtrack and sound effects!<br/>
- A dynamic map to show the screens you have visited and current location<br/>
- A camera that takes photos of clues and symbols as you discover them<br/>
- Dozens of puzzles, clues, and items<br/>
- Auto saves your progress<br/>
- Available for phones and tablets!<br/>
- Instantly move around the map reducing travel time with Fast-travel<br/>
- Get helpful text hints that nudge you in the right direction and complete walkthrough videos for each hint and puzzle<br/>
<br/>
Visit our website to sign up for our newsletter and learn about upcoming games!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hunt for the Lost Treasure 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2798190/The_Hunt_for_the_Lost_Treasure_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2798190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Imagine the roar of cannon fire from tall wooden sailing ships as you hunt for pirate treasure in this beautifully designed classic point and click adventure puzzle game. Explore 89 game map scenes as you travel across multiple islands. Follow trails, discover ancient temples, and structures of past tree dwelling inhabitants.<br>
<br>
Get lost in a vast desert as you search for temples, get trapped in an ancient underground labyrinth. Discover hidden passageways, clues and puzzles along the way!<br>
<br>
Uncle Henry has been hunting lost treasures for as long as you can remember. His legendary stories of adventure excited your imagination as you were a child growing up. Now with your newly acquired archeology skills, he has been reaching out from time to time for your help in tracking down some of these difficult to find treasures.<br>
<br>
This captivating adventure game has:<br/>
- Custom designed beautiful HD graphics!<br/>
- Custom composed soundtrack and sound effects!<br/>
- A dynamic map to show the screens you have visited and current location<br/>
- A camera that takes photos of clues and symbols as you discover them<br/>
- Dozens of puzzles, clues, and items<br/>
- Auto saves your progress<br/>
- Available for phones and tablets!<br/>
- Instantly move around the map reducing travel time with Fast-travel<br/>
- Get helpful text hints that nudge you in the right direction<br/>
- Complete walkthrough videos for each hint and puzzle available as In App Purchase<br/>
<br/>
Visit our website to sign up for our newsletter and learn about upcoming games!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hunt for the Lost Treasure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2798180/The_Hunt_for_the_Lost_Treasure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2798180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Continue the adventure of the The Lost Ship in this longer quest as you hunt for the pirate’s lost treasure in this beautifully designed classic point and click adventure puzzle game. <br>
<br>
Uncle Henry has been hunting lost treasures for as long as you can remember. His legendary stories of adventure excited your imagination as you were a child growing up. Now with your newly acquired archeology skills, he has been reaching out from time to time for your help in tracking down some of these difficult to find treasures.<br>
<br>
In his latest quest, he has used the map you discovered in the lost ship and tracked down the location of the pirate’s cove. You must explore the island, find clues, and solve puzzles left behind by the pirates to discover the location of the lost treasure!<br>
<br>
This captivating adventure game has:<br/>
- Custom designed beautiful HD graphics!<br/>
- Custom composed soundtrack and sound effects!<br/>
- A dynamic map to show the screens you have visited and current location<br/>
- A camera that takes photos of clues and symbols as you discover them<br/>
- Dozens of puzzles, clues, and items<br/>
- Auto saves your progress<br/>
- Available for phones and tablets!<br/>
- Instantly move around the map reducing travel time with Fast-travel<br/>
- Get helpful text hints that nudge you in the right direction and complete walkthrough videos for each hint and puzzle<br/>
<br/>
Visit our website to sign up for our newsletter and learn about upcoming games!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hunt for the Lost Ship</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2796880/The_Hunt_for_the_Lost_Ship/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Uncle Henry has been hunting lost treasures for as long as you can remember. His stories of adventure excited your imagination as you were a child growing up. Now with your newly acquired archeology skills, he has been reaching out from time to time for your help in tracking down some of these difficult to find treasures.<br>
<br>
In his latest quest, he has been hunting for the treasure map known to be in the lost pirate ship "Queen Anne's Revenge". Thought to have sunk off the coast of the American shores, Uncle Henry has discovered new information that the ship was really blown on to an island when it was caught in a hurricane while sailing through Caribbean waters.<br>
<br>
You must hurry and help him on this amazing adventure before anyone else finds the location of the lost ship!<br>
<br>
This captivating adventure game has:<br/>
- Custom designed beautiful HD graphics!<br/>
- Custom composed soundtrack and sound effects!<br/>
- A dynamic map to show the screens you have visited and current location<br/>
- A camera that takes photos of clues and symbols as you discover them<br/>
- Dozens of puzzles, clues, and items<br/>
- Auto saves your progress<br/>
- Available for phones and tablets!<br/>
- Instantly move around the map reducing travel time with Fast-travel<br/>
- Get helpful text hints that nudge you in the right direction and complete walkthrough videos for each hint and puzzle<br/>
<br/>
Visit our website to sign up for our newsletter and learn about upcoming games!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle Clash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2785480/Battle_Clash/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Battle Clash is a medieval multiplayer PVP game. On spawn, each player is randomly assigned a medieval class and forced to battle against other players. Reach a kill streak to unlock your class's ultimate attack, and dominate the battlefield. When the timer ends, the player with the most kills wins!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785480/extras/gif1-ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter.gif?t=1708185307"><br/><br/>There are 8 medieval classes in the game, and they each have <strong>their own unique set of skills:</strong><br/><br/>Knight<br/>Primary: Sword slash<br/>Secondary: Defensive Shield Block<br/>Ultimate: Blitz (faster movement, and attack speed)<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785480/extras/knighticon.png?t=1708185307"><br/><br/>Heavy<br/>Primary: Battleaxe Bludgeon<br/>Secondary: Quick Dash<br/>Ultimate: Rage (increased damage, and movement speed)<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785480/extras/heavyicon.png?t=1708185307"><br/><br/>Archer<br/>Primary: Bow &amp; Arrow Shot<br/>Secondary: Bow Shove<br/>Ultimate: Ruthless (sees through walls, and increased arrow damage)<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785480/extras/archericon.png?t=1708185307"><br/><br/>Wizard<br/>Primary: Spell Cast<br/>Secondary: Staff Shove<br/>Ultimate: Fireball (well, it's a fireball. A deadly fireball)<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785480/extras/wizardicon.png?t=1708185307"><br/><br/>Spearman<br/>Primary: Spear Thrust<br/>Secondary: Defensive Spear Spin<br/>Ultimate: Impale (throws spear at enemy, typically one-shotting anyone)<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785480/extras/spearmanicon.png?t=1708185307"><br/><br/>Assassin<br/>Primary: Single Dagger Slice<br/>Secondary: Double Dagger Slash<br/>Ultimate: Cloak (invisible, but footsteps still visible)<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785480/extras/assassinicon.png?t=1708185307"><br/><br/>Swordmaster<br/>Primary: Katana Slash<br/>Secondary: Katana Thrust<br/>Ultimate: Barrage (super quick consecutive attacks)<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785480/extras/swordmastericon.png?t=1708185307"><br/><br/>Arbalist<br/>Primary: Crossbow Bolt Shot<br/>Secondary: Crossbow Shove<br/>Ultimate: Surge (rapid fire crossbow. pretty much a medieval gun)<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785480/extras/arbalisticon.png?t=1708185307"><br/><br/>Play against your friends in a private lobby, or play against randoms in a public lobby. No one to play with? No problem.<strong> Play against bots/AI!</strong><br/><br/>So what are you waiting for? Battle in the Clash right now!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focus Tower</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2818020/Focus_Tower/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2818020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							For centuries the tower has stood in the center of the world. It is rumoured a ancient power lives on top. Many lives have been lost trying to climb the tower and fall to their demise, never to tell their tale. <br>
<br>
Jacob, a villager who lives on the nearby village of Destiny takes it upon himself to journey and climb the tower and climb the power for his own. Equipped with the mystical dragon claw, he must grapple and make his way towards the heavens and climb the deadly tower. <br>
<br>
With traps, pitfalls and puzzles to solve, Focus Tower will require all of your focus and patience as you make your way to the very top. Are you brave enough to climb the Focus Tower?<br>
<br>
Game Features<br/>
-Platform and jump using the grapple to avoid spikes and cannon balls<br/>
-Solve puzzles by using the string of the dragon claw to open doors<br/>
-Presented in HD graphics with a great sound track<br/>
-Timed gameplay that keeps your high score with replay ability						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We'reWolves</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2564770/WereWolves/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Slay the hordes and survive in this journey through a wild and untamed world filled with friendly characters and dangerously relentless foes. In this bullet heaven inspired by games like Vampire Survivors and Halls of Torment, you'll use a wide range of melee and ranged weapons to stay safe while you duck and dodge through massive waves of enemies. Collect gems to level up, cash to progress your builds, and moon stone fragments to become the werewolf you always knew you were. <br/><br/>With over <strong>5600 cosmetic items</strong> to choose from (and absolutely no microtransactions), <strong>100+ build options</strong>, and an expanding set of dungeons, you'll find the look and playstyle that is just right for you. Can you make it through the masses of evil and learn what turned this once peaceful world into a rabid nightmare?<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564770/extras/Chaos-3.gif?t=1708171170"><br/><br/><table> <tr> <td> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564770/extras/Trainer.png?t=1708171170"><br/> </img></td> <td> <strong>Dynamic Enemy Encounters</strong>: Face off against crazed fauna, resurrected skeletons, trolls, ogres, and more. Utilize strategy, skill, and your werewolf abilities to prevail.<br/> </td> </tr></table><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564770/extras/Chaos-5.gif?t=1708171170"><br/><br/><table> <tr> <td> <strong>Choose Your Path</strong>: Select from a diverse set of starting classes like the precise Cutthroat, the explosive Stormbringer, the balanced Bladeguard, and the "handy" Monk. Each class offers unique starting abilities and tactical opportunities to fit your playstyle. Don't worry, <strong>every class can use every weapon!</strong><br/> </td> <td> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564770/extras/MenderFlipped.png?t=1708171170"><br/> </img></td> </tr></table><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564770/extras/Classes.gif?t=1708171170"><br/><br/><table> <br/> <tr> <td> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564770/extras/Blacksmith.png?t=1708171170"><br/> </img></td> <td> <strong>Epic Environments</strong>: Traverse the frenzied Fields, navigate the mysterious Forest, and conquer the nightmarish Castle. Each area offers new challenges, enemies, and dangers to overcome. Expect to see many more levels show up throughout major updates and DLC!<br/> </td> </tr></table><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564770/extras/Classes-2.gif?t=1708171170"><br/><br/><table> <tr> <td> <strong>Intriguing Characters</strong>: Interact with the diverse inhabitants of the jungle fortress, Beasthaven Stronghold, to permanently enhance your Hero and their abilities. Select from thousands of cosmetics, included with the base game. <strong>NO MICROTRANSACTIONS HERE!</strong><br/> </td> <td> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564770/extras/Cosmologist.png?t=1708171170"><br/> </img></td> </tr></table><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564770/extras/Classes-3.gif?t=1708171170"><br/><br/><table> <tr> <td> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564770/extras/Apothecary.png?t=1708171170"><br/> </img></td> <td> <strong>Progressive Difficulty</strong>: As the game duration increases, so does the challenge. Waves of enemies spawn as you duck and weave, engaging in thrilling, tactical combat. Weapons automatically attack so you can focus on the best path forward. Build your character up to survive through the night!<br/> </td> </tr></table><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564770/extras/Classes-1.gif?t=1708171170"><br/><br/>Join the Adventure!<br/><br/>Unleash your inner beast and delve into a world filled with intrigue, danger, and excitement. With engaging gameplay, simple storytelling, and endless exploration, this dungeon-crawling adventure promises a thrilling and unforgettable gaming experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564770/extras/Classes-5.gif?t=1708171170"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark spirit</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748150/Dark_spirit/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748150/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dark spirit is an exciting game where you will find yourself in the role of a vengeful ghost imprisoned in an ancient castle. Terrible secrets, dark corners and encounters with enemies - all this awaits you in this exciting adventure. Are you ready to reveal all the secrets of the castle and free your dark soul? Prepare for deadly battles, journeys through dark dungeons and encounters with ancient villains. Your revenge will be ruthless and terrifying - are you ready to become a ghost, ready to end everything with your enemies?<br>
<br>
The game is a 2D platformer with puzzle elements. Explore the levels, destroy enemies and move on to the next levels.<br>
<br>
After the last enemy falls at your feet, the castle will be free and you will become a free ghost, ready to start a new life in the spirit world.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUNKER PROTECTION</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748120/BUNKER_PROTECTION/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are one of the newest soldiers sent on a mission to save humanity. In the future, humanity is struck by a terrible and rapidly spreading disease that turns people into zombies. Scientists invented a serum against the virus, but did not have time to spray it before they were destroyed by the zombie invasion.<br>
<br>
You are sent to a dangerous bunker, where the last hope of humanity is located - a serum against the virus. Your main goal is to do everything possible to extract the serum and bring it to the surface to save the survivors from the terrible fate of the zombies.<br>
<br>
The game is a 2D platformer. You need to destroy enemies and go through stage by stage.<br>
<br>
Can you overcome all the obstacles, find the serum and return to the surface to save the world from complete destruction?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carrot Rescue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748130/Carrot_Rescue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Carrot Rescue - you play the role of a farmer who must harvest his carrot crop before winter comes. However, there are various obstacles on your way: wild animals that are trying to eat your crops and evil farmers who want to steal it.<br>
<br>
Your task is to protect your crops using throwing weapons. And also give selection to your enemies and wild animals.<br>
<br>
Will you be able to protect your harvest from beasts and evil farmers and harvest all the carrots on time? Head to your farm and take on the challenge of protecting your carrot harvest!<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br/>
- Nice pixel graphics<br/>
- Various levels<br/>
- Good soundtrack						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move Blocks</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2758820/Move_Blocks/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A calming game about a cat inside a box.<br>
Control with the mouse, click on the desired object and use the direction of the mouse to push them in the directions you need. You need to clear the way for the cat in the box so that she can escape!<br>
<br>
Move Blocks - A game in which the player controls the mouse and by clicking the mouse moves objects and clears the way for the cat inside the box.<br>
<br>
Control:<br>
Left mouse button - move objects<br/>
<br/>
Game Features:<br/>
- Visual style<br/>
- Relaxing Game<br/>
- Difficulty						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HellSpheres</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2758830/HellSpheres/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this game, you control a clot of energy that feeds on the energy of other balls, collecting and storing it in yourself, dodging red balls that take away your energy. Be careful and don't touch the walls!<br>
<br>
Hell Spheres - A game in the Top Down Shooter genre, where the player controls a spherical clot of energy, which must collect other spheres with energy and increase in size, increasing which the player becomes cramped within the level.<br>
<br>
Control:<br>
WASD - walking<br>
<br/>
Game Features:<br/>
- Visual style<br/>
- Unique Levels<br/>
- Difficulty						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chick Road Rage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2758840/Chick_Road_Rage/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The farmer has lost all his chickens, but they remember the way home and are ready to return, however, their path is full of difficulties and obstacles. Rivers with floating logs and cars flying past. The most important rule is that everyone must survive!<br>
<br>
ChickRoadRage is a Top Down game where the player controls a bunch of chickens one at a time, moving them across the road, floating on logs, and dodging cars.<br>
<br>
Control:<br>
WASD - walking<br>
<br/>
Game Features:<br/>
- Visual style<br/>
- Music<br/>
- Difficulty						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bomber Chaos</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2758850/Bomber_Chaos/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A fighter finds himself in the jungle with a bomb strapped to his body, he needs to collect pieces of other falling bombs in order to hold out time and survive as long as possible. Play together and survive as long as possible before the whole earth disappears from under your feet!<br>
<br>
Bomber Chaos is a platformer where the player controls a character who cannot stand still for long, because when the timer expires, an explosion will occur. It is necessary to collect falling explosive barrels and replenish the timer.<br>
<br>
Control:<br>
WASD - walking for Player 1<br>
Arrows - walking for Player 2<br/>
<br/>
Game Features:<br/>
- Visual style<br/>
- Game for two<br/>
- Difficulty						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boom-Shaka-Laka!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2745720/BoomShakaLaka/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You find yourself behind enemy lines. Arena made of steel structures and destructible boxes. You are a miner. The weapons that matter are bombs. Enemy soldiers are patrolling around. Some will persistently follow you and may interrupt your game. The main task is to destroy all enemies and find the key to move to the next level.<br>
<br>
Boom-Shaka-Laka! - is a modern arena-game with a classic twist. Place bombs with a timer. Collect upgrades. Look for a move to the next level.<br>
<br>
Game features:<br>
- Maze-like maps<br>
- Soundtrack<br/>
- Upgrades system						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivor's Day</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2746530/Survivors_Day/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You play as a scientist in a semi-abandoned area and your task is to keep the area clean. Every day you receive tasks in your diary, such as cleaning the area, repairing mechanisms, or collecting laboratory tests. Each task has a time limit and you must do it in time, otherwise the game will be over. Many tasks consist of several subtasks, so you will have to do a bit of scrambling.<br>
<br>
Survivor's Day is a time management adventure game in a post-apocalyptic open world setting.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
- Many interesting tasks for every day<br>
- Route calculation tactics<br/>
- Minimalistic graphics<br/>
- Calm soundtrack						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
