<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Trinity Fusion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1911360/Trinity_Fusion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take control of your parallel selves on a mission to save the dying multiverse. Explore dark, sci-fi worlds and engage in fast-paced, smooth and precise combat.<h2 class="bb_tag">A rogue-lite journey through the multiverse</h2>The various branches of the multiverse are always changing. Fight through a combination of procedurally-generated levels as well as hand-crafted challenges and arenas that will put your skills to the test. Levels with 3D graphics are seamlessly constructed out of hundreds of custom-made rooms.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/extras/Ranger_Factory.gif?t=1702635042"><h2 class="bb_tag">High-intensity combat</h2>With weapons and attack systems that leverage our previous experience working on fighting games. You’ll slide, dash and dodge between enemy attacks and strike back with an arsenal of satisfying special weapons and abilities.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/extras/Ranger_City_Walls_GIF_Cleanup.gif?t=1702635042"><h2 class="bb_tag">Three characters, three universes to explore</h2>Each of your parallel selves has their own world with multiple biomes to explore, as well as their own sets of unique abilities and weapons. Travel through a universe of desolate wastes and caverns roamed by mutant creatures, escape the endless forges and labs of a world ruled by machines, and survive the dangerous sky cities of a post-human society.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/extras/Player_Running_Cleanup.gif?t=1702635042"><h2 class="bb_tag">Constant Progression</h2>Unlock permanent upgrades in the Hub and discover new starting points for your run as you reclaim major locations in each universe. Finding yourself getting stuck in one area? Start your next run in a different one! No matter where you die, or which starting point you pick, you're making progress somewhere.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1911360/Trinity_Fusion/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1911360/Trinity_Fusion/</a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Cutter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1924430/Cookie_Cutter/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Void. The Matter. The Megastructure. A dystopian world with an egomaniac leader determined to unveil the secrets of the universe. INFONET promised a utopia built on the backs of tireless androids called Denzels. It was a lie. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/Cherry.gif?t=1702589263"><br/><br/>200 years later the planet is decaying and the mysterious Red Seed has been stolen. Raz, a renegade mechanic, searches a hidden lab and discovers the Denzel Cherry, butchered and left for dead, clinging to life by sheer will alone. Her creator—and the love of her life, Doctor Shinji Fallon—has been taken by a demented sicko and Cherry intends to make him—and anybody or anything who gets in her way—pay.<br/><br/>Fueled by love and powered by rage, join Cherry on a blood-soaked quest for revenge as she explores the massive Megastructure and eviscerates the armies of INFONET in an unforgettable over-the-top 2D platformer that breaks tropes and bones.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Subversive_Metroidvania.png?t=1702589263"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Subversive_Metroidvania.gif?t=1702589263"><br/>Cookie Cutter is unabashedly irreverent, violent, and risqué. Become Cherry, a badass android on a rage-filled and love-driven quest. To save her beloved creator she’ll explore and fight her way through a unique illustrated sci-fi dystopian world as she chainsaw-murders anybody who stands in her way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Hand-drawn_Action.png?t=1702589263"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Hand-Drawn_Action.gif?t=1702589263"><br/>Every frame of this immersive experience is drawn by hand with copious amounts of love. That means epic, fall-out-of-your-chair visuals. Grotesque bugs and menacing robots. Gargantuan bosses. Ridiculous weapons, special moves, and brutal gory finishers. All of it brought to life with benchmark 2D animation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Epic_Combat_Abilities.png?t=1702589263"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC__Epic_Combat_Abilities.gif?t=1702589263"><br/>Whether you’re ripping the wings off overgrown mosquitos, impaling mini-bosses, crushing robots on Cherry’s motorcycle, or kick-punch-uppercut-stomping waves of foes with complex combos, you won’t find a better fighting experience with responsiveness and all the flair you could ask for in a Metroidvania.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Rage-Filled_Spectacle.png?t=1702589263"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Rage-Filled_Spectacle.gif?t=1702589263"><br/>Far future dystopia? Check. An android companion turned rage-filled killer? Check. Over-the-top characters and enemies? Check. Buckets of blood? Of course. Experience our bizarre tale, inspired by Japanese manga and Quentin Tarantino films, through 10 huge zones, each weirder than the next.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wartales, Pirates of Belerion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692400/Wartales_Pirates_of_Belerion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/piratesofbelerion_english.png?t=1702564761"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/GIF_Teaser_30fps.gif?t=1702564761"><br/><br/>Since the collapse of the old kingdom of Belerion, the archipelago seemed to have been abandoned. Its population of mostly fishermen quickly turned to piracy, merchants deserted its waters, nothing seemed able to halt the decay of these lands… until the arrival of the Ihrian peoples.<br/><br/>Embark on over +25 hours of new adventures and explore Belerion, a new hostile region far larger than any other part of the continent. Discover a land unlike anything you’ve seen with the first expansion to the world of Wartales! Unravel the secrets of the region's storyline, discover new factions and master the new way to travel: navigation.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/belerionarchipelago_english.png?t=1702564761"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/GIF_Region.gif?t=1702564761"><br/><br/>Despite its apparent tranquility and sun-drenched islands, many sailors refuse to venture into the Belerion archipelago. It is true that there is no shortage of perils for anyone who dares to sail between the islands. Its coasts are lined with sharp reefs, its treacherous winds lose the unwary, scaly beasts roam its beaches, and pirates pillage and sink anything that has the misfortune to cross their path.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/conquertheseas_english.png?t=1702564761"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/GIF_Navigation_02.gif?t=1702564761"><br/><br/>Embark on an awe-inspiring journey through the expansive realm of Belerion, where navigation and exploration take center stage in the thrill of seafaring. Uncover the secrets of wind mastery as you navigate the vast expanse, dock your ship, and explore the islands of the Belerion archipelago. <br/><br/>Craft and upgrade components for your ship, from the shape of your sails to the mighty ballista, ensuring that your vessel is not just a means of travel but a formidable force on the open waters. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/sealord_english.png?t=1702564761"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692400/extras/GIF_Fight.gif?t=1702564761"><br/><br/>Dominate the perilous waters as you face Guards, lawless pirates, and everything in between. Challenge rivals to duels, a distinctive gameplay feature exclusive to Belerion's maritime conflicts. <br/><br/>Rise through the ranks of the Sea Lords leaderboard by conquering foes, boarding ships, and plundering treasures. With a dynamic battlefield, encounters with new factions, Belerion offers an immersive combat experience where every clash propels you closer to maritime greatness.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1702578551"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1702578551"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1702578551"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1702578551"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1702578551"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WITCH ON THE HOLY NIGHT</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2052410/WITCH_ON_THE_HOLY_NIGHT/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2052410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2052410/extras/WITCH_ON_THE_HOLY_NIGHT_About_this_game.gif?t=1702631006"><br/><strong>Product Description</strong><br/>TYPE-MOON, known for the wildly popular mobile game "Fate/Grand Order" and the epic visual novel "Tsukihime," is releasing a remaster of the 2012 hit "Witch on the Holy Night. Experience a coming of age story set in the vibrant, bustling 1980s, which follows an innocent young man and two young "witches." Updates added since the original release include long-awaited fully voiced characters as well as visuals remastered in full HD, bringing the experience to life with unparalleled quality and fidelity. Masterful manipulation of visual elements imbues combat scenes with nail-biting tension, but also breathes life into the characters' everyday activities. Animated graphical elements bring an entirely new level of depth to the reading experience as well!<br/><br/><strong>STORY</strong><br/>In the mansion on the hill, there lived two witches...<br/><br/>It is the late 1980s—the twilight of an era of beauty and vigor.<br/>A boy moves to the city, barely missing two witches living in modern times.<br/><br/>The boy leads a completely ordinary life.<br/>She carries herself with gallant pride.<br/>The girl lives a sleepy, hidden life.<br/><br/>Each walks a starlit path.<br/>One would never expect their paths to cross.<br/>The story of how these three disparate people came together is soon to be told.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons of Sundaria</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/587520/Dungeons_of_Sundaria/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/587520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">The Dungeons:</h2> <br/>* 8 Huge Dungeons filled with hundreds of fiendish monsters and dozens of diabolical bosses.<br/>* Three Levels of Difficulty: Normal, Hard, and Nightmare.  <br/>* Online single player or co-op up to 4-players.<br/>* Local Split-screen multiplayer co-op up to 4-players (only requires a single game copy).<h2 class="bb_tag">Make your Hero:</h2> <br/>* 7 Races: Human, Dwarf, Elf, Halfling, Orc, Goblin and Drog'al (lizard).<br/>* 5 Classes: Champion, Ranger, Cleric, Wizard, and Rogue. <br/>* Customize the appearance of your Hero.<h2 class="bb_tag">Become a Legend:</h2> <br/>* Collect a huge variety of Weapons, Armor, and Accessories to customize your Hero and grow in power.<br/>* Craft powerful equipment and become a force of reckoning.  Multiple tiers of armor and weapons.<br/>* Embrace the Heroism system, allowing you to continually increase the power of your Hero.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1702562956"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1702562956"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1702000678"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1702000678"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood West</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_steam_text_header.png?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>Weird West legends meet eldritch horror in <strong>BLOOD WEST</strong>, an immersive stealth FPS. Become the Undead Gunslinger, doomed to roam the barren lands until he finds the means to purge their curse and free his soul. No, this isn’t your typical Wild West desperado redemption arc. This is a damnation arc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_episodes_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The Canyons, the Swamp, and the Mountains. Each swarming with abominable monsters and unholy demons, these are open-ended worlds for you to explore freely at your own pace. It will take the player over 20 hours on average to complete all three scenarios, and over 35 if they want to see everything the barren lands have to offer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_stealth_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/><strong>Blood West</strong> is a stealth FPS inspired by the genre classics such as the Thief series (whose fans will be happy to hear the voice of Stephen Russell, the actor voicing the master-thief Garrett, returning here as the protagonist), S.T.A.L.K.E.R. games, or - from the contemporary catalog - Hunt: Showdown. The gameplay rewards the careful approach: scouting the area, stalking your enemies, and striking from the shadows. Can you figure out a way to clear a fort full of ghouls and monsters without raising an alarm?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_horror_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The Barren Lands present the player with a nightmarish, twisted vision of the Wild West legends. The curse that has befallen the realm has corrupted every living thing, defiled the land itself, while summoning restless spirits and dark entities. In this mixture of gunslinger pulp and Lovecraftian horror, dark occult magick presents just as much of a threat as sudden lead poisoning.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_characters_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>In <strong>Blood West</strong> you will meet many colorful, yet strangely twisted, fully-voiced NPCs. Just as much prisoners of the Barren Lands as you are, they will sometimes share their unusual stories and send you on various missions. Play nice and they might reward you or become your allies. Cross them and risk their wrath.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_secrets_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The game won’t hold your hand. You’ll have to explore the land for yourself (buying a map from a vendor might prove useful!), and figure out your own way to approach quests. As you poke around the three expansive maps, keep an eye out for hidden places and secret stashes. There’s gold in the mountains! Fair warning - it’s probably cursed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_brutal_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>If sneaking around isn’t exactly your thing, or you feel that you have a power advantage over your enemies, you can always take the head-on approach and meet your enemies guns blazing. <strong>Blood West</strong> comes from the creators of the fan-favorite boomer shooter <strong>POSTAL: Brain Damaged</strong>, so much gratuitous fantasy violence and pixelated blood splatter is to be expected!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_inventory_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>One man’s hell might be another hoarder’s paradise! From simple one-use items like bandages, through medical tinctures, explosives and incendiaries, straight to arcane artifacts that - once slotted - can change the way you play the game, the Barren Lands are just filled with STUFF. There are tons of useful items to discover, and there’s a special player’s stash crate for all those super-rare potions that you’ll hoard and never use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_weapons_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>A gunslinger without a gun would be just a regular slinger. Where’s the fun in that? <strong>Blood West</strong> makes sure you’ll have plenty of weapons to choose from. Revolvers, rifles, shotguns, carabines - a great variety of firearms, from standard army-issue to those infused with powerful magic, or straight-up possessed. And if you prefer not to cause a ruckus, there’s a wide selection of hand-to-hand combat weapons and archery weapons to pick your favorites from.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_skills_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The RPG-like perk-based progression system in <strong>Blood West</strong> will allow you to highly customize the gameplay experience to your liking. Become a stealthy hunter, a revolver-fanning gunman or a relentless berserker. You will gain experience and progress through the skill tree, while discovering new artifacts in each of the scenarios that will bestow on you additional abilities. Combining skills and load-out creates more possible playstyles than you’d normally be able to explore in one playthrough.<h2 class="bb_tag">Are you ready to take back the frontier from the dark forces of demonic corruption and earn the right to move on to a better world? The Barren Lands call you, Gunslinger!</h2><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1702394215"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1702394215"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1702394215"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1702620270"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1702620270"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn back immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Option</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.<br/>If you are easily intoxicated, changing the following settings may help.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera shake】</strong><br/>The camera shakes when you walk or run, but if you set the value to 0.0, the camera will not shake.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Acceleration】</strong><br/>If you set the maximum value to 30.0, the camera will move without delay.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Sensitivity】</strong><br/>If the sensitivity is high, the camera will move significantly when the mouse is moved. <br/>Adjust the value if you find it difficult to operate the camera with the default value of 1.<br/><br/><strong>【Motion Blur】</strong><br/>Afterimages will appear when the camera is moved. Recommended to disable at 30FPS<br/><br/><strong>【Preset】</strong><br/>Set the overall graphic settings.<br/>If you do not have sufficient specs, it is better to set it to "Low" to avoid sickness.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1701808865"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons 4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1643310/Dungeons_4/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Once upon a time in a realm far, far away, everything was lush and green. The unicorns mingled among the trees and the elves and humans lived peacefully in harmony with their surroundings. Yet somewhere at the edge of a clearing half-hidden among the trees, obscured by a rising veil of fog in the hazy half-darkness of a weather-beaten hut, a shape huddles over a large and ominously glowing crystal ball. A mumbling voice sings ancient formulae, urging the swirling glowing mists inside the crystal to part and give an insight into the future.<br/><br/>“All is in flux, nothing seems certain. Come, oh vagaries of space and time, separate the veil and show us what is yet to come”, the voice grumbles with the hint of an eye faintly reflecting the glow in front of its hood. The shape’s audience, only barely visible in the dim light, leans in closer and listens intently. “Time ebbs and flows, forming pools and wrinkles… but when the mists part only vague images rise from beyond the veil. Shhhh—don’t come too close, you don’t want to disturb my delicate magical weavings do you?” The shape, still bent over the orb, mutters and shoos the other back a bit more into the shadows. “Ah, now it seems to be clearing a little. I can see… something… several somethings, hints of voices echoing in the haze. A baby, something happening on Hill Doom and the coming together of the Council of Snots – what could all this mean?”<br/><br/>In a flash, the light reflected in the eye turns red and a distant evil laughter echoes through the woods. Stay tuned for the return of the Soothsaying Evil!</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/dungeons-4.gif?t=1701355158"><br/><br/>The Absolute Evil and its trusted *cough* servant, the Dark Elf Thalya, return in <strong>Dungeons 4</strong> after the events of its fabulous predecessor to bring about their triumph over the forces of good once more.<br/><br/><strong>Build a cozy and comfortable Dungeon</strong> to suit your creatures’ needs and rule over them, then send them out into the Overworld to kindly remind the good people living there that the Absolute Evil rules over their lands. <strong>Gather your Evilness</strong> in new and dynamic ways <strong>and unleash it upon</strong> the lush green forests and plains of <strong>the Overworld</strong> to turn them over to the dark side. But make sure that <strong>your Dungeon is well-secured</strong> by traps and defended by your creatures, for those pesky Overworlders won’t just twiddle their thumbs while you <strong>turn their land into the Absolute Evil’s most pleasurable holiday paradise</strong>.<br/><br/>But what is that noise? <i>“Gold, gold, gold and gems, gold and gems and gold!”</i> The ancient song echoes throughout the underworld, accompanied by the clanging steel of hammers and axes. <strong>The Dwarves have arrived</strong> to claim their share of the abundant resources and together with the Elves and Humans of the Overworld, they send out their raiding parties to find the Dungeon’s heart.<br/><br/>Dungeons 4 keeps the spirit of its predecessor, but everything is now <strong>bigger, better, and with even more dynamic Evilness™</strong>.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-1_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Everything is better with Dwarves™:</strong> The Dwarves have arrived to build their underground strongholds and the hardy little fellows (although they don’t like being called that) compete with the Ever-Expanding Evil for space and resources.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-2_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>It makes your Dungeon great again:</strong> Dungeons are up to four times larger than before and there are many more creatures who wait for the All-Commanding Evil’s orders to conquer the Overworld. Now the time has come for massive armies and truly sprawling dungeons!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-3_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Ripe for the taking:</strong> The Overworld is bigger than ever before. Gain Evilness by beating Mini Bosses like the obsessively harmonious Unicorn and use it to transform the Overworld into stunning biomes of pure evil.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-4_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>New and shiny:</strong> An ability-based Perk system for Thalya, the Absolute Evil’s trusted *cough* and most loyal subordinate, grants her impressive new powers. The Absolute Evil can now enjoy taking over the world, governing the creatures and slapping subordinates even more with the customizable Evil Hand.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-5_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Minions, everywhere:</strong> The Horde, the Undead and the Demons wait to do the Absolute Evil’s bidding, with more creatures than ever eagerly following the gesturing Evil’s orders, and Snots will play a much more prominent role this time.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-6_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Many ways to tell the story:</strong> A long campaign, narrated by the beloved English Narrator from previous titles, as well as several skirmish maps all to challenge your rule as the Absolute Evil.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-7_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Change the world:</strong> Spread your Evilness across the Overworld to bring lush and green environments over to the dark side, now shining even more vibrantly and beautifully evil as you spread your evilness across many new biomes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-8_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Work together, slay together:</strong> 2-player co-op multiplayer with both players managing one Dungeon together. All maps from the skirmish mode and the campaign are playable in co-op.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little Goody Two Shoes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1812370/Little_Goody_Two_Shoes/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/DIVIDER_grapes_616.png?t=1702566240"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/Dive_into_the_FairytaleEN.png?t=1702566240"><br/>There once was Elise , a vibrant and ambitious young lass with a big dream – becoming filthy rich. In spite of this, the stars didn’t seem to have reserved our protagonist much fortune in life. Elise, who came from humble beginnings, had no choice but to spend her days away assisting her fellow neighbours with menial tasks to make a living.<br/>One day, Elise discovers a pair of beautiful shiny red shoes buried in her backyard – what a surprise! Bewitched, Elise embarks on a fearful journey that pulls her closer and closer into the heart of the mysterious Woods!<br/>Will Elise risk it all for the sake of a dream come true, or settle for her humble day-to-day life? The ending of this tale is yours to write…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/Steam_Page_GIF_02.gif?t=1702566240"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/Venture_into_the_WoodsEN.png?t=1702566240"><br/>Little Goody Two Shoes is a horror narrative adventure game, set in a hand-painted fairy tale environment. There are 10 possible endings to fit your choices and actions in the game.<br/><br/>But there’s more than meets the eye here, as you must also manage multiple aspects of Elise’s life in the village to stay alive. Remember, all decisions matter in this story!<br/><br/>During the day, you will need to strengthen Elise’s bonds with her fellow villagers and work to make a living by playing fun minigames.<br/><br/>But once the moon rises, make sure to keep Elise fed, healthy and sane in the multiple encounters with deadly foes as she makes her way further into the Woods.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/Steam_Page_GIF_01.gif?t=1702566240"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/EN_-_Key_Features.png?t=1702566240"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Kieferberg is a small and devout village, which means Elise will need to carefully navigate her relationships with the villagers to avoid arousing suspicion of witchcraft and be left to die in the Woods as punishment. <br/></li><li>At night, Elise can roam around the Woodlands, a mystical and phantasmagorical  realm where enigmas and deadly enemies await as she tries to uncover its secrets.<br/></li><li>Through a limited day and night cycle Elise will need to carefully manage her needs if she wants to stay alive to finish her tale.<br/></li><li>Get struck by Cupid’s arrow and fall in love with the charming bachelorettes of Kieferberg. In this all-female cast of romanceable characters, unlock dreamy date scenes and storylines for each of them.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/HEADER_SteamDeck_616.png?t=1702566240"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812370/extras/DIVIDER_grapes_616.png?t=1702566240"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good Morning Cruel City</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2709990/Good_Morning_Cruel_City/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The City is a cruel place governed by greedy corporate overlords with money and fear where the wealthy live in upper level utopia while people below is drowned in crime and consumerism.<br>
<br>
You are a Fixer, someone with a role that enables these crime by bringing together shady people to do shady jobs for a bit of cash while avoiding the existential dread of working 9 to 5 daily.<br>
<br>
You woke up this morning thinking it'll be another usual day where you meet Ethel, your client for the day, to snatch a mysterious object from people you normally wouldn't want to mess with.<br>
<br>
But little did you know, this job would brush your elbow with something beyond the stars...<br/>
<br/>
FEATURES:<br/>
- Multiple ways to finish your goal.<br/>
- Unique camera perspective.<br/>
- Many poses and expressions.<br/>
- Explorable city.<br/>
- Endings with variants.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reckless Rally</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2688730/Reckless_Rally/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Race on 2 tracks adapted from the real world, with a selection of Rally Cars bosting Hybrid or ICE Powertrains. Push the maximum out of the cars without going over the threshold and crashing to get the fastest time on the tracks.<br/><br/>Indulge in your pro rally driver fantasies by building your own tracks based off real world roads and finally experience how you really want to drive down some of those roads!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688730/extras/store_route_builder.png?t=1702641041"><br/>Using websites like ‘RideWithGPS’, ‘Garmin Connect’ &amp; ‘Strava’ plot out custom race tracks using roads from the real world. Download the GPX file and import it in-game, pick the road width and barrier type before jumping into the virtual roads to see what you can really do!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688730/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif.gif?t=1702641041"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anemis: Desktop Animator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667350/Anemis_Desktop_Animator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667350/extras/about_image.png?t=1702639792"><h2 class="bb_tag">Current List</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667350/extras/current_list.png?t=1702639792"><h2 class="bb_tag">Animated On Your Desktop</h2>A virtual pet, companion, or other digital friend that lives on your desktop as you work, play or relax at your computer.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>They can be as big or as small as you want them to be</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>You can change how fast they animate</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667350/extras/walk_compressed.gif?t=1702639792"><h2 class="bb_tag">Interact</h2>Want them in a different spot? They can be picked up and moved around your screen.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667350/extras/pick_up.gif?t=1702639792"><h2 class="bb_tag">Name Them</h2>Give each of them a unique name.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667350/extras/names.gif?t=1702639792"><h2 class="bb_tag">Create Anything</h2>Create entirely new virtual pets, companions, or whatever you wish, by using any PNG image. You can add as many animations as you want to your creations.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PNG images can be any size</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each animation can have its own movement speed</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667350/extras/create.png?t=1702639792"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KILLFISH</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551200/KILLFISH/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to <strong>KILLFISH</strong>, an immersive gaming experience that will take you on a journey like no other. In this <strong>Action/FPS</strong> game, you'll dive into a captivating world where robots have taken control on a factory. Embark on an epic adventure filled with a unique hook mechanic that will give you freedom to explore and kill in flashy ways.<br/><br/><strong>Key Features</strong><br/><br/> · Fast-pace movement mechanics: Immerse yourself in a fast-pace world in which you will have to use the hook and move fast in order to kill all enemies.<br/> · Stunning Visuals: Dive into a visually stunning world where every detail is meticulously crafted to bring KILLFISH's universe to life. From breathtaking illumination to intricately designed characters, prepare to be amazed.<br/> · Customization Options: Tailor your gameplay to your liking with an array of customization options. Express your personal gameplay style as you explore KILLFISH's levels.<br/> · Unique Style Meter: Kill in flashy ways to improve your score and buy the upgrades such as the explosive sniper.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magnet Mania 3D</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2298650/Magnet_Mania_3D/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2298650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Magnet Mania 3D is a fun and educational simulation game for small and big engineers to learn about the fascinating world of magnetism and physics. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2298650/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif.gif?t=1702639906"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2298650/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__1_.gif?t=1702639906"><br/><br/>With Unique gameplay minigames <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2298650/extras/ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1702639906"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2298650/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__2_.gif?t=1702639906"><br/><br/>Players will take on the role of a scientist, experimenting with different magnets and objects to explore the properties of magnetic force. They will learn about the north and south poles, magnetic fields, and how magnets interact with different materials. The game features colorful graphics, engaging gameplay, and interactive tutorials that make learning about science fun and easy. With Magnet Physics, children will be able to develop a deeper understanding of the laws of physics and be better prepared for their science classes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2298650/extras/ezgif.com-optimize__1_.gif?t=1702639906"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulator Z</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2267990/Simulator_Z/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2267990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Zombie Simulator Z takes an imagination and some ingenuity to create some of the most intense battles between humans and zombies. Whether it is trying to overrun the prison with a zombie horde or protecting the hospital from a swarm of savage zombie dogs. Simulator Z is your Zombie Simulator playground and over time we will give you all the tools to create unlimited amounts of opportunities to satisfy the Zombie experience. If you are looking to follow the progress of this adventure, Join our development discord:<br>
<br>
https://discord.gg/MDZyjcw64W<br>
<br>
We are excited to begin this journey with you! The citizenz of Simulator Z must survive at all cost because if they cannot, what hope do we have if they come our way?						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trinity Fusion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1911360/Trinity_Fusion/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take control of your parallel selves on a mission to save the dying multiverse. Explore dark, sci-fi worlds and engage in fast-paced, smooth and precise combat.<h2 class="bb_tag">A rogue-lite journey through the multiverse</h2>The various branches of the multiverse are always changing. Fight through a combination of procedurally-generated levels as well as hand-crafted challenges and arenas that will put your skills to the test. Levels with 3D graphics are seamlessly constructed out of hundreds of custom-made rooms.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/extras/Ranger_Factory.gif?t=1702635042"><h2 class="bb_tag">High-intensity combat</h2>With weapons and attack systems that leverage our previous experience working on fighting games. You’ll slide, dash and dodge between enemy attacks and strike back with an arsenal of satisfying special weapons and abilities.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/extras/Ranger_City_Walls_GIF_Cleanup.gif?t=1702635042"><h2 class="bb_tag">Three characters, three universes to explore</h2>Each of your parallel selves has their own world with multiple biomes to explore, as well as their own sets of unique abilities and weapons. Travel through a universe of desolate wastes and caverns roamed by mutant creatures, escape the endless forges and labs of a world ruled by machines, and survive the dangerous sky cities of a post-human society.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1911360/extras/Player_Running_Cleanup.gif?t=1702635042"><h2 class="bb_tag">Constant Progression</h2>Unlock permanent upgrades in the Hub and discover new starting points for your run as you reclaim major locations in each universe. Finding yourself getting stuck in one area? Start your next run in a different one! No matter where you die, or which starting point you pick, you're making progress somewhere.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1911360/Trinity_Fusion/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1911360/Trinity_Fusion/</a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United States of America Jigsaw Puzzles</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2703370/United_States_of_America_Jigsaw_Puzzles/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a mesmerizing journey through the enchanting landscapes of the United States with "United States of America Jigsaw Puzzles." This captivating puzzle adventure invites players to piece together iconic scenes from the nation's diverse regions, from the bustling cityscapes to the serene beauty of natural wonders.<br>
<br>
Choose your difficulty level, starting from a breezy 30-piece puzzle to a challenging 285-piece masterpiece, ensuring a satisfying experience for puzzle enthusiasts of all skill levels. As you solve each puzzle, unlock panoramic views that showcase the unparalleled beauty of the United States, whether it's the vibrant energy of New York City, the tranquility of the Grand Canyon, or the coastal charm of California.<br>
<br>
Delve into the heart of the game with a meticulously crafted map that unveils the geographical wonders of the United States. Your puzzle-solving prowess breathes life into this virtual map, revealing uncharted territories, hidden gems, and triggering dazzling animations that mark your triumphs.<br>
<br>
What sets "United States of America Jigsaw Puzzles" apart is its stunning artwork. Each puzzle is a visual masterpiece, capturing the essence of America's landscapes with vibrant colors and intricate details. Immerse yourself in the artistic spectacle as you piece together scenes that celebrate the nation's natural and architectural wonders.<br/>
<br/>
For those seeking an extra challenge, timed trials add a thrilling dimension to the gameplay, testing your speed and puzzle-solving skills. Your progress also unlocks special rewards, from guardian spirits of nature to magical tools, enhancing your quest to assemble the nation's most stunning landscapes and discover hidden treasures.<br/>
<br/>
More than just a game, "United States of America Jigsaw Puzzles" is a tribute to the nation's beauty, offering compelling storytelling, breathtaking artwork, and hours of immersive gameplay. Soar through this captivating world and experience the magic of the United States from a perspective like never before.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Mambo</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/849280/John_Mambo/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/849280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							John Mambo is a frenetic Retro Arcade Game with an isometric top down view.<br/>A Game with a detailed 2D hand drawn Pixel Art style for Windows.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/849280/extras/14-AnimatedGif_1_-_Copie.jpg?t=1702632709"><br/><br/>Met <strong>John Mambo</strong>, a one man army, crazy enough to embark on a dangerous mission in the heart of a jungle. Explore various landscapes, infiltrate enemy bases, cross cities occupied by the enemy and more! Nobody in the allied army trusts John, but John Mambo doesn’t care. <br/>He knows his mission and he will put all his effort to neutralize the enemy. The Colonel will send him on various missions, both funny and dangerous. The outcome of those missions depends on you – the player!<br/><br/>John Mambo is an action video game based on the era of the arcade machines and 16-bit consoles of the 90's, but taking advantage of modern control mechanics and graphics engines . The game is inspired by retro classics like Ikari Warriors, Commando, Mercs and Cannon Fodder.<br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>6 Levels<br/></li><li>Main Features: Arcade / Strategy / Surreal Humor.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speed Night</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2708500/Speed_Night/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							· This is a racing role-playing game.<br>
· The player assumes the role of a road driver<br>
· Experience the plot and make choices that trigger different stories<br>
The story sometimes triggers car races, which the player needs to win in order to continue the story<br>
· Motor racing includes practice, regular season, pursuit and time trial<br>
· Beautiful 3D character modeling<br>
· Expansive scenes<br/>
· Real car models<br/>
· Authentic or entertaining driving experience<br/>
· Attractive story plot						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>甜蜜狂潮Honey Fury</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2508450/Honey_Fury/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508450/extras/mi.png?t=1702628512"><br/><strong>Base Construction and Strategic Card Management. You will construct and defend your base from enemy invasions. Employ clever layouts to enhance your base's defenses and acquire resources through card management. Get ready to embrace this strategic and thrilling honey-fueled frenzy!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508450/extras/y1.png?t=1702628512"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508450/extras/build.gif?t=1702628512"><br/><strong>The operation of most buildings rely on worker huts.<br/>In addition, various BUFF buildings can provide powerful buffs for defensive towers.<br/>Layout smartly, maximize the utilization of worker huts and BUFF buildings, and create an indestructible base!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508450/extras/y2.png?t=1702628512"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508450/extras/1z.gif?t=1702628512"><br/><strong>Only by holding on to 30 waves of enemy attacks can you win the game.<br/>The number of enemies will be increasing, and the attacks of the 5th, 10th, 15th, 20th, 25th, and 30th waves are even more fierce!<br/>Get ready for this battle!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508450/extras/y4.png?t=1702628512"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508450/extras/2z.gif?t=1702628512"><br/><strong>Character development &amp; building blueprints<br/>Complete the levels and get a lot of honey immediately; light placement gameplay is also available!<br/>Upgrade your character's attributes and enhance your technology with a variety of ways to play!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508450/extras/y5.png?t=1702628512"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508450/extras/fight.gif?t=1702628512"><br/><strong>Only by holding on to the 30 waves of enemy attacks will you be able to achieve the final victory of the game.<br/>The number of enemies will intensify, and the 5th, 10th, 15th, 20th, 25th, and 30th waves will be even more ferocious!<br/>Get ready for the battle!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508450/extras/y6.png?t=1702628512"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508450/extras/3z.gif?t=1702628512"><br/><strong>Different maps have different characteristics and special items<br/>Each map has hidden special items for you to explore</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508450/extras/y3.png?t=1702628512"><br/><strong>Each card gives you corresponding resources of the same texture every ten seconds.<br/>After you successfully resist the enemy's attack, multiple cards will be drawn according to your resource building.<br/>Pay attention to card type management. Three cards in a row will trigger a straight, bringing twice the output;<br/>And Triplet brings three times the output! Play your mahjong talent and win more resources!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508450/extras/y33.png?t=1702628512"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508450/extras/y333.png?t=1702628512"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Master Forge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1784730/Master_Forge/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1784730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Having inherited an old forge, it is now up to you to gather resources and turn them into various products. Display your creations for the locals to buy and fulfill specific requests for those who have them. Gain riches and fame, upgrade your forge and gain access to new resources to expand your product selection. One day, word of your skill may reach the ears of more than just commoners. Will you be able to gain true recognition for your mastery of the forge?<br>
<br>
Master Forge is a first-person singleplayer simulation game with a medieval story. You can cut down trees in the forest to get wood. You can gather iron ore or coal in the dark mines. These collected resources are then stored in certain chests. One chest per resource. Two times a day a trader comes by, who wants to sell resources, with varyien prices. Furthermore you can craft different products on the forge by combining the different resources cleverly. In Addition you want to sell all those products to different customers with varying preferences. By earning new gold, you can unlock upgrades which increase your production.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Way Out</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2717140/No_Way_Out/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world situation is becoming more and more chaotic, wars are happening everywhere. The wars continue, leading to a nuclear war spreading throughout the world. The world has now become a pile of ruins. Radioactive substances and toxic substances from laboratories have leaked into the outside environment, exposing living animals and even humans. The survivors had to struggle every day to fight off the zombies stalking them, and they had to search for food and water to survive. At the same time, they must find a way to contact the United Nations to be able to reach the Green Zone, an area where the air is truly fresh enough to live.<br/><strong>Genre</strong>: <br/>Turn-based card battle game<br/><strong> Developer:</strong><br/>The game was conceptualized and programmed by a person named Nguyen Minh Hung.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yeetus</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2640910/Yeetus/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2640910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2640910/extras/FloorIsAmo.gif?t=1702627270"><br/><br/>You are YEETUS! Your weapon? The very floor beneath your feet! YEET your surrounding terrain into destructive projectiles. Be strategic, though. A hasty shot may mean a long fall down to your doom in YEETUS, a casual time survivor game with roguelite elements.<br/><br/>Balance offense and defense! The action here isn't just about YEETing away, but accurately aiming your shots to make sure you're not destroying too much of your own battleground!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2640910/extras/ForcesOfEvil.gif?t=1702627270"><br/><br/>Square off against alien monstrosities from other dimensions! Each enemy tests your strategy, aim and reaction time, requiring a strong command of your YEET! The biters will get up-close and personal, while tentacle stars like to shoot at you from a distance. Big boomers will sneak up on you and blow up, taking a lot of your precious terrain with them if you’re not careful!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2640910/extras/UpgradeEvolve.gif?t=1702627270"><br/><br/>Enhance your strategy with a wealth of upgrades waiting to be unlocked. Each run will play differently depending on your upgrade choices. Focus on defense and maneuverability or strive for maximum power? The choice is yours! Each game will also give you gold you can use to purchase permanent upgrades so each run will not only help you improve not only your YEETing skills but also your YEETUS’ powers!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2640910/extras/Yeetuses.gif?t=1702627270"><br/><br/>As you play you will unlock new levels and characters. You start playing as the balanced Yeetus Regulus; his special skill gives you guaranteed critical shots and doubles tile regeneration. Later step into the speedy boots of Yeetus Speedus, a swifter but fragile choice with a dash skill. Then lastly you will be able to take on the role of the tanky Yeetus Maximus, a slower brute force with more health, damage, and a damage reflecting berserk buff as his special skill.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2640910/extras/YeetusSteamDescription.png?t=1702627270"><br/><br/>With mechanics that are easy to pick up but hard to master and the power of YEETing on your side, YEETUS is a fresh take on the rogue-lite time-survivor genre, making you focus not only on your aim but also your positioning as you fight to avoid a painful fall to your death.<br/><br/><strong>The ground is your weapon, how will you wield it?</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Card Detective</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2308670/Card_Detective/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2308670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Crime, criminal investigation, interrogation. Can these elements, commonly found in mystery dramas and cop movies, be presented in a game?<br/>Out of a strong interest in the subject matter, the production team studied a large number of books on criminal psychology and consulted with professionals in the field, seeking to understand the discipline as deeply as possible. We have brought our findings to "Card Detective", integrating them deeply with the plot and gameplay.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2308670/extras/英文1g.gif?t=1702627051"><br/>During our research, we also considered which art style would best fit the story atmosphere. Ultimately, we chose a realistic comic style, using rich variations in shadows, lines, and tones to present the overall atmosphere and foreshadow the plot direction. This is a new attempt for us on the artistic level, and we hope everyone will like it!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2308670/extras/英文2g.gif?t=1702627051"><h2 class="bb_tag">story</h2>Players will take on the role of newspaper reporter Hazel Gong, who was originally covering a practice exercise at an abandoned building site, but stumbles upon a mysterious corpse in an accidental collapse!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2308670/extras/英文3g.gif?t=1702627051"><br/>Faced with the subjective statements of the witnesses from different perspectives, to uncover the truth, Hazel Gong turns to a mysterious bar owner to learn criminal investigation and psychology, and questions the witnesses. Confronted with complex relationships and a series of emergencies, will Hazel Gong be able to uncover the truth of the case?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2308670/extras/英文4g.gif?t=1702627051"><h2 class="bb_tag">art</h2>Based on a realistic comic style, the story's atmosphere is depicted through changes in shadows and tones, suggesting the plot's direction.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2308670/extras/英文5g.gif?t=1702627051"><br/>In terms of character animation, we aim to replicate the real reactions of people being interrogated through the nuanced depiction of micro-expressions, linking character movements and expressions with gameplay.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2308670/extras/英文6g.gif?t=1702627051"><h2 class="bb_tag">gameplay</h2>Build your deck flexibly, deliver an OTK, and break through the psychological defenses of the witnesses!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2308670/extras/英文7g.gif?t=1702627051"><br/>Pay close attention to the story, analyze the veracity of the testimonies, and win easily with non-traditional card game strategies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2308670/extras/英文8g.gif?t=1702627051"><br/><br/>Detectives, are you ready to solve the case?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soul Street</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1946610/Soul_Street/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1946610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1946610/extras/11y.png?t=1702624770"><br/>   "Falling Soul Street is an extremely busy commercial district in Putnam City, but in the past two years, there have been frequent cases of disappearances here, with missing persons of all ages, including strong men, young women, children and the elderly. Unfortunately, some of the cases have not been solved and remain unsolved. People don't know when the name of the shopping street was replaced by the name "Soul Street". According to the rumor, "Soul Street" is connected to a different dimension, and the missing people are sucked into this other world.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1946610/extras/1y.png?t=1702624770"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1946610/extras/1z.gif?t=1702624770"><br/><strong>As a detective puzzle game, it uniquely integrates the player's choices into the game's plot, creating a strong narrative drive. Every decision you make, whether it's searching for clues, solving puzzles, or even just tiny decisions, will have a direct impact on the direction of the game's plot and the fate of the characters you come into contact with. This design is unique and innovative, and it is cleverly hidden in all corners of the game, requiring the player to use keen observation and reasoning skills to uncover it.<br/>In the course of the game, you will discover secrets hidden in various seemingly insignificant details. Through these clues, you can gradually piece together the truth of the incident and solve the mystery. In the process, you will experience that thrill of pulling the threads out of the cocoon and gradually approaching the truth. However, it is also important to note that some of your decisions may trigger unexpected consequences or even put yourself in danger.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1946610/extras/2y.png?t=1702624770"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1946610/extras/2z.gif?t=1702624770"><br/><strong>You need to use your intelligence and strategy to solve puzzles and move the game forward by exploring, solving puzzles, reasoning and escaping.<br/>Each puzzle has its own unique difficulty and challenge, requiring you to use various logical thinking skills, spatial imagination, and even strategic planning skills to solve it. Each of your challenges may bring unexpected discoveries and rewards, making your gaming experience full of surprises and satisfaction.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1946610/extras/3y.png?t=1702624770"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1946610/extras/3z.gif?t=1702624770"><br/><strong>Players have the opportunity to experience first-hand the process of a real detective working on a case. In this session, players need to investigate the complex case in depth and gradually reveal the truth of the incident by collecting clues, questioning suspects and organizing evidence.<br/>The design of this session is very real and fascinating, making players feel like they are in the real detective world. The player's decisions and actions will affect the outcome of the investigation and the ending of the game, making the game more attractive and challenging.</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The last world</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2646830/The_last_world/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2646830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							After the world ends, the remaining survivors must defend the last spark of human civilization. Use the camp as a position to repel the waves of monsters in each city! Thay are too powerful? It doesn't matter! Get stronger equipment, learn stronger skills, and finally sweep thousands of armies!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2646830/extras/y1.png?t=1702623697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2646830/extras/r1.gif?t=1702623697"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2646830/extras/y2.png?t=1702623697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2646830/extras/r2.gif?t=1702623697"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2646830/extras/y3.png?t=1702623697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2646830/extras/r3.gif?t=1702623697"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Karos Classic</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2720700/Karos_Classic/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2720700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							​<strong>Karos</strong> is a classic of the MMORPG genre, with an amazing fantasy world in which you will find the most unusual adventures. The variety of locations, a great variety of dungeons and monsters will make you plunge into this world headlong.<br/><br/>The beloved world of Azmara, filled with the confrontation between Light and Darkness, returns in its classic form. This legendary version of the game has absorbed all the best things that Karos heroes have loved over the years. It will bring back your original gaming experience and give you the opportunity to take a personal look at the origins of the famous MMORPG and remember how it was used to be. Choose one of four original races, fight for a better future and write your name in the history of your native lands.<br/><br/><strong>FEATURES</strong><br/><br/>- An ideal opportunity to indulge your nostalgia for your favorite game, untouched by years and updates.<br/>​<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2720700/extras/3.gif?t=1702626922"><br/>- Four unique races and many classes, each of which can be developed by choosing additional specializations.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2720700/extras/1.gif?t=1702626922"><br/>- Intuitive game: no difficulties in mastering.<br/>- PvP at every turn: castle sieges, mine captures, endless battles in the open world.<br/>- Variety of PvE content: raid bosses, many dungeons of varying degrees of difficulty, which can be completed either alone or with a reliable team.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2720700/extras/2.gif?t=1702626922"><br/>- Interesting Flett system: get the energy of fallen monsters to create powerful equipment that will improve along with your character.<br/>- Mounts turn into beautiful accessories when you walk, and your little pet friends are able to grow and develop.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2720700/extras/4.gif?t=1702626922"><br/>- Low system requirements.<br/><br/>Years passed, Karos changed, became better, updated. Today, many things look completely different from those in the distant years when we were just launching this legendary MMORPG. And now we are pleased to present you the classic version of Karos. It will take you back to the very beginnings of the Karos world and show you what the game looked like at the time of its inception.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towers and Powers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2501980/Towers_and_Powers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2501980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							It isn’t easy being a god, even during peacetime. You have to lead and support your people, help them with the harvest, and encourage their growth… all without them noticing you. But what if your lands are on the edge of a cliff? What if your people approach a whirlpool while being attacked by a horrible, mysterious monster? Well, when that happens, it’s time for you to display all your power and intelligence!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2501980/extras/tnp_magic.gif?t=1702635460"><br/><br/>When you play Towers &amp; Powers you’ll find yourself in an ancient land surrounded by the beautiful landscape, elegant buildings, mythical creatures and… chaos! These gorgeous places are under attack! As one of the gods, you’ll have to save your residents and keep their islands from sinking. But the rules forbid you from intervening directly… So what can you do? Only one thing is left: take your powers in your hands!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2501980/extras/tnp_setup.gif?t=1702635460"><br/><br/>In Towers &amp; Powers, you’ll create your own teams of peasants, priests, warriors and magicians, decide which buildings they need, use your powers to defend allies and trap foes. Awaiting you on your island you’ll find economic and military tasks to accomplish, exciting battles and travels to undertake, and loyal worshippers, cruel enemies and monsters to encounter. Are you ready to start your divine journey? Play Towers &amp; Powers right this minute!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2501980/extras/tnp_projectile.gif?t=1702635460"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tower defense in VR! <br/></li><li>Play standing or sitting, alone or with your cat next to you!<br/></li><li>Inspect the battlefield from every perspective!<br/></li><li>Build towers that combine different types of units!<br/></li><li>Use your units not only in towers but also on battlefields!<br/></li><li>Accumulate mana and cast spells with your very own hands!<br/></li><li>Build barricades to hold back enemies!<br/></li><li>Become a real powerful god!</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>幸存者少女/Survivor Girls</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2679200/Survivor_Girls/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2679200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Game introduction	<br>
"Survivor Girls" is a roguelite which is about pretty girls and added a variety of strategic ways based on the traditional roguelike,13 different characters available plus hundreds of weapons and items bring the game more possibilities.<br>
<br>
Game features<br>
-Fast-paced and easy to get started with.<br>
-Interesting gameplay. New elements such as entries, skills etc. were added. <br>
-Varied levels, over 10 kinds of enemies and 4 kinds of bosses, feel new at each time.<br>
-A dozen different characters ,hundreds of weapons and items available,unlimited strategies.<br/>
-Collection mode and Endless mode bring you different levels of difficulty and experience.<br/>
-Exquisite original art setting, extraordinary visual feast.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speak of the Devil I: A Deathly Proposition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2686590/Speak_of_the_Devil_I_A_Deathly_Proposition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Can you imagine staking your very soul just to find love? It's a proposition that most people would find unthinkable. However, our dear friend Michi, driven by sheer desperation, found himself making a fateful decision. In a moment of weakness, he struck a deal with a cunning demon, offering his soul in exchange for the fulfillment of his deepest desires. But as the saying goes, "beware the Devil's bargain." Michi now faces the daunting task of finding a girlfriend within a mere 30 days. Failure to do so will condemn him to an eternity of servitude in the underworld, at the mercy of the demon. Join us in the first chapter of this series as we unravel the events that led Michi down this treacherous path.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Content Warning - This VN Contains the Following:</strong><br/><i>Partial nudity of characters, characters in sexual situations, characters in sexual poses, references to the demonic world, dark humor and/or conversations, moderate swearing, and dad jokes. Viewer discretion is advised when purchasing this visual novel.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tochos vs. Brokens</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2686850/Tochos_vs_Brokens/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Brokens are invading and only you can save the planet, use your Tochos and defeat the evil forces in this strategic tower defense game.<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A singleplayer adventure where you'll travel around the world in an attempt to stop the Broken outbreak.<br/></li><li>Astounding graphics and soundtrack.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summon My Girl</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2715180/Summon_My_Girl/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Game Overview<br>
This is a puzzle-filling game with hexagonal blocks. Players need to collect a heart after successfully completing each level, and can increase favorability and obtain items through the love diary option. After accumulating enough hearts, you can summon your wife in the summon interface. Try your luck now!<br>
<br>
Product Features<br>
Casual puzzle-solving gameplay<br>
Heart fragment collection<br>
Interesting love diary<br/>
Random summoning card draw<br/>
CG album mode						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katana Robo: RTA</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658810/Katana_Robo_RTA/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658810/extras/카타나_로보_로봇타워.png?t=1702612884"><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2>To thwart Samurai Robo's plan to take control of all the robots in the universe by awakening the Dominion Sphere from the highest point on the planet Mechanos, Katana Robo rushes to the Robot Tower, which looks like a platformer game stage made up of buildings, cars, space battleships, and more. Raising his Dominion Sphere as high as he can, Samurai Robo harnesses the power of the Dominion Sphere to bring objects together to create an impromptu robot tower, which is defended by numerous enemy robots that serve Samurai Robo. Katana Robo's journey includes battles with a variety of enemy robots, and it's up to you to destroy the Dominion Sphere before Samurai Robo can fully awaken it and turn the robots of the universe into his minions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658810/extras/카타나_로보02.gif?t=1702612884"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2>Katana Robo: RTA is an 'Mechiro+Only Up Style RTA Action' game, where players utilize their honed action and platformer skills from various games to reach the top floor of the Robot Tower and destroy the Dominion Sphere in the shortest time possible. This game demands quick reflexes and precise controls, while also emphasizing strategic thinking and timing in its unique gameplay.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658810/extras/카타나_로보01.gif?t=1702612884"><h2 class="bb_tag">World Battle Hashtag #KatanaRoboRTA</h2>Compete against gamers from around the world in Katana Robo: RTA using the World Battle hashtag #KatanaRoboRTA This game gives you the opportunity to show off your skills, achieve great records, and rise to the top of the global rankings. Show off your abilities to the world and become the world's strongest Katana Robo!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658810/extras/카타나_로보03.gif?t=1702612884"><h2 class="bb_tag">Convenience</h2>Prioritizing convenience and user experience, Katana Robo: RTA, despite being an Only Up like style game, has implemented a checkpoint system to minimize player frustration. If a player fails a jump action or is destroyed in combat, they can resume the game from the nearest recall point. Additionally, if destroyed in battle, players automatically revive after 10 seconds. These systems maintain the flow of the game and provide a smooth gaming experience for the player.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reef Escape</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2627390/Reef_Escape/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2627390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2627390/extras/ABOUT_THE_GAME.png?t=1702612835"><br/><br/><strong>Being a worm is not easy in this side-scrolling adventure.</strong> <br/>After having escaped from the fisherman’s bait can, you plummet down into the reef. There you must make your way out while traveling in a breathable air bubble. Avoid obstacles and explore each level with care since there are hidden items that are essential to get to freedom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2627390/extras/FEATURES.png?t=1702612835"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Old-school difficulty elements<br/></li><li>Precision in-game movement to avoid hazards<br/></li><li>Race against time<br/></li><li>Follow hints to uncover secrets<br/></li><li>Stunning 2D original illustrations<br/></li><li>Classical animation<br/></li><li>Fun for all ages!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2627390/extras/FISHY_FATE.png?t=1702612835"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keep Up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2686750/Keep_Up/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Keep Up</strong><br/>Embark on a journey through a world of minimalistic beauty that will test the limits of your perseverance. <strong>Keep up</strong> is a low-poly platformer that blends difficulty with serenity where every jump is a step towards mastery. Will you be the first to reach the top of the <strong>Keep </strong>?<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Stunning Low-Poly World: Immerse yourself in a visually enchanting universe, explore vibrant landscapes as you navigate through a world that is as delightful to behold as it is challenging to conquer.<br/><br/></li><li> Challenging Platformer Gameplay: Brace yourself for a truly demanding platformer that will push your skills to the limit. Precision and timing are crucial as you navigate an intricate world filled with obstacles and traps. Can you conquer it and rise to the challenge?<br/><br/></li><li> Unlockable Achievements: Test your mettle and unlock a variety of achievements as you progress through the game. Whether you're a completionist or a casual player, the satisfaction of mastering this world will keep you coming back for more.<br/><br/></li><li> Community Challenge: Strive to get your score at the top of the leaderboard!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>maboroshi caravan</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2159670/maboroshi_caravan/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2159670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>■Overview</strong><br/>maboroshi caravan is an auto-play simulation game about a journey through the desert.<br/>The player becomes an observer of the caravan and sometimes watches over, sometimes advises and sometimes helps them on their journey.<br/><br/><strong>■Recommended for</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Who do not have the time or energy to play games, but want to do something<br/></li><li>Who like abstract games (Who want to enjoy the freedom of imagination)<br/></li><li>Who want to enjoy watching the slightest change in the unchanging everyday life<br/></li><li>Who want to enjoy everyday life in a different world<br/></li><li>Who love deserts</li></ul><br/><strong>■Additional information to avoid becoming "Not for me"</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>In terms of classification, it is just like an auto-play game, but <u>it is not a game that focuses on efficiency and growth.</u><br/></li><li>It's not a glittering desert. It's a world of dust and wilderness and camels and robbers.<br/></li><li>There are no shocking developments or heart pounding elements. It's a calm game.</li></ul><br/><strong>■Story</strong><br/><i>This desert is later given another name<br/>People called it the Chain Desert<br/>The cursed sandy earth that binds the souls of the dead<br/>There are caravans there to release the souls of the dead trapped in the desert<br/>Caravans appeared and disappeared like a mirage<br/>Its name is――<br/>This is the story of a caravan and the observer who watches over it</i><br/><br/><strong>■System</strong><br/>The caravan's journey is automatically progressive. They are the ones who decide the destination of the journey.<br/>The player can help them to properly handle the resources they have gathered, expand the size of their caravan, and add more members.<br/><br/>There are three things players should do in the course of the game. It's "Materialization," "Liberation," and "Caravan Leveling Up."<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Materialization: The Materialization of the Soul Caught in the Chain Desert<br/></li><li>Liberation: Liberation of the materialized soul from the chain curse<br/></li><li>Caravan Leveling Up: Expanding the caravan by consuming resources gained during the journey</li></ul><br/>There are other things you can do to make your journey more varied and efficient, but the basics are to do the above three things.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2159670/extras/desc002.png?t=1702609199"><br/><br/>Once in town, the caravan will conduct transactions and listen to the stories of the townspeople.<br/>The stories that can be heard in town vary from town-related stories, useful stories, and personal stories.<br/>Listen to what they have to say and enjoy the journey the world.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2159670/extras/desc001.png?t=1702609199"><br/><br/>The year in the desert is 354 days. It shows a variety of faces depending on the season, weather, and time.<br/>The events that the caravan encounters along the way will also be affected by the changing environment.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Slow Life with the Princess Knight and Her Devoted Handmaiden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1934900/My_Slow_Life_with_the_Princess_Knight_and_Her_Devoted_Handmaiden/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1934900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A visual novel about learning to trust again.<h2 class="bb_tag">STORY</h2><br/>Garland used to be a formidable adventurer.<br/>However, that was back before he was betrayed by his fellows on a quest that left him seriously wounded. Lucky enough to make it out with his life but unluckily without family or relatives, he is in no shape to look after himself due to his injuries. What he does have left is his adventurer’s spirit, which fuels his hopes to make a full recovery and head out to face the world again.<br/><br/>In the meantime, what he needs is someone to take care of him...<br/>But having been deceived by a band he thought he trusted, and now being grievously wounded, what he’s shortest on is faith in anyone else. Complicating the situation even further, word of the fortune Garland acquired through his personal disaster has spread far enough that everyone he meets seems to be after his money. If he had his health he might have little to fear, but as the situation stands, he needs help that he can rely on. At the moment, Garland needs assistance to survive.<br/><br/>As he mulls over what to do, the news reaches his ears that his homeland has captured a certain smaller nation. He also happens to see in passing some citizens from that fallen nation, perhaps captured during the takeover, being transported to be sold off as indentured servants. As an adventurer who believes in freedom, Garland doesn’t like the idea, but with such unfortunates trust is optional: magic makes them obedient. <br/><br/>After much consideration and lacking other options, he makes the decision to get the help he needs—whatever it costs.<h2 class="bb_tag">CHARACTERS</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1934900/extras/chara01_eng.png?t=1702602021"><br/>Alienor <i>(Voice: Aika Kashiwagi)</i><br/><br/>The eldest princess-in-exile of the fallen kingdom of Pixenzax. Called “Allie” by her family and friends, she is a tomboy with a strong disposition, perhaps because of her natural temperament.<br/><br/>Due to her talent with a blade and her popularity, she served as a Princess Knight before her country was destroyed through the dealings of a traitor and she was taken captive. During a physical examination after her capture, she was found to have a birthmark unique to royalty and was thus treated as a high-status hostage.<br/>When Garland comes to town to hire help, she meets her destiny.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1934900/extras/chara02_eng.png?t=1702602021"><br/>Farna <i>(Voice: Miina Ayukawa)</i><br/><br/>Princess Alienor’s lady-in-waiting.<br/><br/>She loves Alienor as if she were her own sister. As a handmaiden, she is good at all household chores, but not so skilled at rougher work.<br/><br/>She was captured alongside Alienor and sold to a broker, in whose care she was treated reasonably well thanks to her good looks and her former station.<br/><br/>When Garland patronizes the shop, she notices that he seems kind and has tons of money. Convincing the shopkeep that she and Allie could turn him a tidy profit if Garland were to buy the two as a set, she succeeds in pushing them through as a package deal.<br/>She trusts Garland to some extent on account of his personality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1934900/extras/chara03_eng.png?t=1702602021"><br/>Garland <i>(Voice: -)</i><br/><br/>An adventurer who hopes to return to his occupation and the main character of this game.<br/><br/>After the death of his parents, he left his unremarkable hometown for the city to become an adventurer. Perhaps because he had an aptitude for the profession, he steadily gained ability and became a formidable adventurer at a young age.<br/><br/>While participating in a quest he was invited onto by colleagues he trusted, his group fell into a dire situation, and he was severely injured after being abandoned to create a distraction.<br/><br/>Now no longer able to trust others, he returns to his family home in the woods. However, his trust issues are not his only problem, because his injuries leave him unable to live alone. As a compromise, he decides to acquire a caretaker in the form of servants who are magically bound never to betray him.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wanting Wings</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2685610/Wanting_Wings/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">STORY</h2>At Seiyou Girls' academy, there are rumors of an angel.<br/><br/>Our story takes place at the end of their second term, just before Christmas.<br/><br/>Hina, Rin, and Fumi: three girls that became roommates since spring.<br/><br/>The three of them all come from diverse backgrounds and have completely different personalities, but they share one strange similarity:<br/>They all saw an angel when they were younger.<br/><br/>And they all gradually begin to suspect that one of their roommates might be the angel they've heard about...<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>- A cute yet touching visual novel<br/>- Lots of colorful CGs to explore!<br/>- Two games in one package! (<i>Wanting Wings</i> &amp; its sequel <i>Faraway Feathers</i>)<br/>- Multiplatform support for Windows, Mac, and Linux!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPIN UP</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684090/SPIN_UP/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Story</strong><br/>SPIN UP is a climbing action game set on a planet.<br/>After falling to an unknown planet, players aim for the top in order to return to their friends.<br/><br/><strong>Overview</strong><br/>The game is controlled with the left and right keys, and the player climbs by "grabbing" and "spinning".<br/><br/>Pressing the key allows the player to grab onto any object,<br/>While grabbing an object, the player rotates while accelerating.<br/>The moment you release the key, it will fly away by the rotational force.<br/><br/>Where it flies depends on the rotation force and the timing of releasing the key.<br/><br/>Don't give up.<br/>We are waiting for you at the top!<br/><br/><br/><strong>About video distribution</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Both individuals and corporations can distribute their videos.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video sharing site.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racket Club</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2407910/Racket_Club/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2407910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							If you’re a fan of racket sports - from tennis to pickleball or padel to ping-pong - Racket Club is for you! Hit the courts in this all-new sport created for VR that combines the best of these sports and allows players to immerse themselves into a fully-social experience of a real racket club. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>REAL FUN </strong>-  Play in singles or doubles multiplayer, or go for single-player glory in Career Mode. <br/></li><li><strong>REAL MOVEMENT</strong> - A new sport that captures the authentic feel of play with real movement (no virtual locomotion!), Racket Club employs physics and interactions as close to real life racket sports as you can imagine, all within a space that fits in your home.<br/></li><li><strong>REAL(LY) SOCIAL</strong> - Step onto the court in an authentic club experience! Meet new players and reconnect with old friends, on and off the court, as you partner up for doubles, compete in singles,  or spectate courtside together.<br/></li><li><strong>REAL GOOD AI BOTS</strong> - Take on AI bots up through the highest competitive level or just use them to warm up and hone your skills.  </li></ul><br/>Coming December 14, 2023. Wishlist today!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starfend</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2540820/Starfend/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Place defenses strategically, upgrade and combine them. <strong>Starfend</strong> is a 3D tower defense game set in a vast space universe where you will take command of a powerful fleet of advanced spaceships. Your mission is to protect the orbit of inhabited planets against a relentless horde of malevolent meteors that threaten to destroy.<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540820/extras/placeShip.gif?t=1702586543"><br/>Get ready to face an endless succession of challenges, as the game has endless levels, each one more intense and exciting than the last. At each level, you'll be confronted with different models of meteors, each with a different type of protection to try to break through your defenses.<br/><br/>Your arsenal of space defenses includes 10 types of ships with 10 levels, each equipped with futuristic weapons and special abilities. Carefully plan your tactics, place ships in strategic locations around the meteor paths, upgrade your turrets and combine them to get strongger and meet the ever-increasing challenges the hostile universe presents.<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540820/extras/upgradeShip.gif?t=1702586543"><br/>In addition, the 3D gameplay brings an immersive and dynamic experience, allowing you to freely explore, rotate the view and get a complete perspective of space combat.<br/><br/>CameraControls: Hold mouse right click and drag to look around.<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540820/extras/lookAround.gif?t=1702586543"><br/>W - move forward, S - move backward, A - move left, D - move right, Q - move down, E - move up or Hold mouse left click and drag to move the camera. hold shift to increase camera speed.F - Change to free camera. R - reset free camera position. use arrows to switch beteween static cameras, use mouse scroll to zoom in and out.Use mouse left click for interactions.<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540820/extras/cameraMovement.gif?t=1702586543"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ordinary Day</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2240220/Ordinary_Day/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2240220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ordinary Day takes place in a fictional town run by The Church. Founded by the early members and quickly swept in darkness as they uncovered the horror contained nearby, clouded and driven by an external force the church enforced their own rules upon the town, driven to rebirth the darkness. You are bound from birth to fufil a singular purpose, it awaits the day your soul is weakened.<br/><br/>⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2240220/extras/seperator-2.png?t=1702586442"><br/><br/>You return from a party running late in to the night, exhausted with a long drive ahead you set off home. A decision that changed your life and kicked in motion the ever growing darkness lingering in your soul, enter this not so ordinary horror and uncover the shroud of mysteries.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2240220/extras/characters.png?t=1702586442"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBM Studio's Gettysburg</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2492030/RBM_Studios_Gettysburg/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2492030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In RBM Studio's Gettysburg, take command of either the Confederate or Union forces for the Battle of Gettysburg, the single bloodiest battle of the U.S. Civil War.  Each side has an historically accurate order of battle that details when and where reinforcements will arrive, letting the player attempt to outdo the generals of history.  As the Confederate commander Lee, it's your task to either crush the Union forces or secure a safe route for your continued invasion of the North.  As the Union commander Meade, you must at least match the losses inflicted by the Confederates while also securing the roads leaving Gettysburg towards D.C.<br/><br/>RBM Studio's Gettysburg features gameplay based on the historical wargaming boardgames of the 70's and 80's.  Players maneuver markers that represent their units on a hexagonal map that mimics the gameboard and cardboard counters of traditional boardgames.  Turns are completed in an "I go, you go" style, wherein players alternate their turns with their opponent until one player passes.  Once that happens, a random number of unopposed actions are given to their opponent.  Pass too early and you risk giving your opponent the opportunity to maneuver completely around your forces.  Combat is resolved through die rolls modified by terrain, battle line factors, and the use of artillery support.  Attackers benefit from flanking defenders.  Defenders benefit from being in defensible terrain.  <br/><br/>Artillery support is a finite resource, so think carefully about when to use it.  If both players use artillery in an engagement, an artillery duel is conducted in which at most one player will receive the bonus but both players risk losing additional artillery support if their opponent's cannon manage to hit their own.<br/><br/>The Confederates begin the game with less artillery support but ultimately receive more units and benefit from a greater area of influence generated by General Lee.  Only the Union player can deploy a special sharpshooter unit that protects a single hex from the Confederate advance.  Careful placement of this unit can help block a Confederate advance farther into the North.<br/><br/><strong>Key Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Command your units in an historically accurate representation of the real Battle of Gettysburg.<br/></li><li>Maneuver to try and pin your opponent's forces, while keeping your own free to act.<br/></li><li>Manage your artillery usage to avoid being overrun late in the game if your opponent still has resources left.<br/></li><li>Choose your fights carefully - losing artillery and men attempting to capture a well-defended hex without adequate preparation is a sure path to defeat.<br/></li><li>Solo play as both sides to explore the rules and potential strategies.<br/></li><li>Online multiplayer play against a human opponent.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cave Runner</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2616490/Cave_Runner/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2616490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Run at blinding speeds using wire anchors,<br>
and escape from the cave in time.<br>
<br>
The game has no heavy story, no tedious material collection, no complicated synthesis, <br>
and no moving encounters and goodbyes.<br>
<br>
We just keep on running.<br>
Faster, faster, faster, faster<br/>
<br/>
There are two ways to play: escape mode and time attack mode.<br/>
In escape mode, the objective is to escape from the cave within a set time.<br/>
In Time Attack mode, you can choose any course and compete for the time from start to finish.<br/>
Once you have a satisfactory time, upload your score and participate in the ranking.<br/>
Players' replay data can also be saved as ghosts and downloaded from the leaderboard.<br/>
(They can also be exchanged directly between users.)						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Cutter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1924430/Cookie_Cutter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Void. The Matter. The Megastructure. A dystopian world with an egomaniac leader determined to unveil the secrets of the universe. INFONET promised a utopia built on the backs of tireless androids called Denzels. It was a lie. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/Cherry.gif?t=1702589263"><br/><br/>200 years later the planet is decaying and the mysterious Red Seed has been stolen. Raz, a renegade mechanic, searches a hidden lab and discovers the Denzel Cherry, butchered and left for dead, clinging to life by sheer will alone. Her creator—and the love of her life, Doctor Shinji Fallon—has been taken by a demented sicko and Cherry intends to make him—and anybody or anything who gets in her way—pay.<br/><br/>Fueled by love and powered by rage, join Cherry on a blood-soaked quest for revenge as she explores the massive Megastructure and eviscerates the armies of INFONET in an unforgettable over-the-top 2D platformer that breaks tropes and bones.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Subversive_Metroidvania.png?t=1702589263"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Subversive_Metroidvania.gif?t=1702589263"><br/>Cookie Cutter is unabashedly irreverent, violent, and risqué. Become Cherry, a badass android on a rage-filled and love-driven quest. To save her beloved creator she’ll explore and fight her way through a unique illustrated sci-fi dystopian world as she chainsaw-murders anybody who stands in her way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Hand-drawn_Action.png?t=1702589263"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Hand-Drawn_Action.gif?t=1702589263"><br/>Every frame of this immersive experience is drawn by hand with copious amounts of love. That means epic, fall-out-of-your-chair visuals. Grotesque bugs and menacing robots. Gargantuan bosses. Ridiculous weapons, special moves, and brutal gory finishers. All of it brought to life with benchmark 2D animation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Epic_Combat_Abilities.png?t=1702589263"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC__Epic_Combat_Abilities.gif?t=1702589263"><br/>Whether you’re ripping the wings off overgrown mosquitos, impaling mini-bosses, crushing robots on Cherry’s motorcycle, or kick-punch-uppercut-stomping waves of foes with complex combos, you won’t find a better fighting experience with responsiveness and all the flair you could ask for in a Metroidvania.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Rage-Filled_Spectacle.png?t=1702589263"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924430/extras/CC_Rage-Filled_Spectacle.gif?t=1702589263"><br/>Far future dystopia? Check. An android companion turned rage-filled killer? Check. Over-the-top characters and enemies? Check. Buckets of blood? Of course. Experience our bizarre tale, inspired by Japanese manga and Quentin Tarantino films, through 10 huge zones, each weirder than the next.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
