<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Hunt: Showdown - The Shadow Under the Cowl</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2643040/Hunt_Showdown__The_Shadow_Under_the_Cowl/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2643040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							This DLC contains one Legendary Hunter, two Legendary weapons, and one Legendary tool: <br/><br/>- The Cowl (Hunter)<br/>- Rib Burster (Springfield M1892 Krag Bayonet)<br/>- Eye Taker (Hunting Bow)<br/>- Swarm Cutter (Throwing Knives)<br/><br/><strong><u>The Cowl</u></strong><br/><br/>The Cowl made his mark by learning how to thrust his blade in just the right place to create the most chaos. But the Assassin’s swarms showed him a new way with no leaders, only followers. Now he seeks to supplant the Target and become a truer instrument of the Corruption.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2643040/extras/hmus_lgnd_assassin.png?t=1705590655"><br/><br/><strong><u>Rib Burster</u></strong><br/><br/>A lifetime ago, The Cowl was assigned this Springfield M1892 Krag Bayonet rifle during his military service. Though dishonorably discharged, The Cowl kept the reliable weapon—both as a constant reminder of how far he’s come, and how far he has left to go.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2643040/extras/krag_bayonet_legendary_a_transparent_01.png?t=1705590655"><br/><br/><strong><u>Eye Taker</u></strong><br/><br/>The near silent strum of The Cowl’s Hunting Bow precipitates the grunts and gurgles of unceremonious death.  It is the moment where all truths are laid bare, and even those with their third-eye open wide can see their futures rapidly dissipate.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2643040/extras/bow_f_transparent_01.png?t=1705590655"><br/><br/><strong><u>Swarm Cutter</u></strong><br/><br/>For each week The Cowl recovered from his encounter with the Assassin, he channeled his pain into the sharpening of these Throwing Knives, training so his aim was as true as his foe's, ensuring his chance for ascension.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2643040/extras/throwing_knife_f_swarmcutter_transparent_03.png?t=1705590655"><br/><br/>The Cowl is a mantle chosen by a man who knew how quickly order could become chaos with just the thrust of a blade. Once called Horatio, as a child he would confuse the pheromones of an ant colony and watch them march in a spiral until death. Or sit with a hand outstretched and a lamp lit, waiting for bugs to settle on his palm. He bottled them, studied them, and confided in them, for he had no one else.  <br/><br/>Horatio learned his insects were closer to humankind than others liked to think. He noticed that we both arrange ourselves into groups with leaders and common goals, sometimes for betterment, sometimes not. Like his father, Horatio went to an Officer Academy, where, surrounded by hierarchies, his obsession with undoing them only grew. The queen of a hive is worth the lives of a thousand workers. <br/><br/>Horatio’s philosophy did not go unnoticed, and eventually he was dishonorably discharged. Though Horatio had nothing, his only pity was for his bugs—they depended on each other so much that they were vulnerable when alone. So, he developed what he knew, and made his living by thrusting his blade in just the right place to leverage the most destruction. His work brought him to the bayou: another moth, another flame.  <br/><br/>Horatio found others like him, wracked by Corruption. His first Hunt, he came face-to-face—or lack thereof—with the Assassin, who slashed his chest open in a single stroke.  Left for dead with beetles enveloping him, he had a revelation: the swarm of creatures shrouding him may have had no leader, but they were all driven by a base instinct towards their greater purpose. It was from that plight that The Cowl would emerge, swearing to ascend to his highest potential.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turnip Boy Robs a Bank</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2097230/Turnip_Boy_Robs_a_Bank/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2097230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2097230/extras/AboutBanner.png?t=1705590256"><br/><br/>Turnip Boy is ready to commit more felonies in this comedic action-adventure game with roguelite elements. This time the career criminal is teaming up with the fearsome Pickled Gang to plan and execute the weirdest heist of all time! Shake down hostages, steal precious valuables, and explore the deep, dark depths and history of the Botanical Bank.<br/><br/>To pull off the perfect heist, you’ll need to purchase an array of dangerous and wacky tools from the dark web, including a diamond pickaxe, C4, and… a cardboard box? However, bank robbing isn’t easy, so be prepared for intense shootouts with security guards, the fuzz, elite swat teams and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2097230/extras/FeatureBanner.png?t=1705590256"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A thrilling single-player adventure full of bank robbing, dark web browsing, and fuzz fighting.<br/></li><li>Roguelite elements to turnip the action.<br/></li><li>A big ol’ bank to explore and loot.<br/></li><li>An array of wacky weapons.<br/></li><li>Take on whoever the bank throws at you in intense shootouts, from security guards to elite veggie swat teams!<br/></li><li>A large cast of quirky food-based characters, including some familiar faces and new citizens with their own stories and problems.<br/></li><li>Earn collectable hats to wear and new banger tracks to blast.<br/></li><li>Discover a deeper history of Turnip Boy’s world and how it became what it is.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pony Factory</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2536530/The_Pony_Factory/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2536530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2536530/extras/PonyFactoryInline.png?t=1705583919"><br/><br/>Winston arrived at a solution to the moral decay of his town.  <br/><br/>He called out to hell, and hell answered.  The human body could, hell promised, be twisted and stretched into a kinder, more equine shape.  Winston's town, now filled with ignorant hate-mongers, could instead be filled with magical ponies, if he could provide a factory in which to make them.  Winston thought they would be beautiful, gentle, and good.  <br/><br/><i><strong>Hell had other plans...</strong></i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2536530/extras/PonyFactoryInline2.png?t=1705583919"><h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Meaty FPS combat against highly agile foes who will attempt to evade and flank you.<br/></li><li>Darkness is your enemy!  Use muzzle flashes, sparks, sound, and other clues to track foes during combat.<br/></li><li>High contrast black and white aesthetic inspired by early 1950's science fiction films.<br/></li><li>A short minimalist campaign that can be completed in about 30 minutes.<br/></li><li>Numerous improvements from the original release, including many new quality of life features, balance and game feel improvements, new story and gameplay content, full gamepad support, and of course bugfixes!</li></ul><br/>Originally made in 7 days for <u>The Dread X Collection</u> as an exercise in doing a lot with a little, The Pony Factory is a horror FPS inspired by Doom 3, with a striking aesthetic and dark sense of humor.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Kingdoms Zhao Yun</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2201710/Three_Kingdoms_Zhao_Yun/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							- Dive into 12 complete story chapters <br/>- Choose from 3 difficulty levels, with a minimum of 30 hours experience of main storyline.<br/>- Master 4 distinct weapon systems: spears, bows and arrows, swords, and steeds, supplemented by equipment systems like crafting, sets, refinement, and enchantment.<br/>- Explore no fewer than 30 expansive maps.<br/>- Encounter dozens of well-known Chinese historical figures, who will either fight by your side or become your adversaries.<br/>- Enjoy a wide range of visually striking outfits for the protagonist and companions.<br/>- Engage in several large-scale, renowned battles that truly capture the essence of the Three Kingdoms atmosphere.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/战场.gif?t=1705662280"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/连招1.gif?t=1705662280"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/大招.gif?t=1705662280"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/射箭.gif?t=1705662280"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immortal Life</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1201230/Immortal_Life/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Immortal Life is a captivating life simulation game where you strive to restore the Guiyun Sect after its near-total destruction – all while you try to achieve immortality through spiritual cultivation.</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/漫步乡野.gif?t=1705592279"><br/><br/>Decided to help your new brothers and sisters make this settlement grow and flourish into a prosperous village, you will work relentlessly with them to restore the Misty Valley by farming, cooking, and crafting decorations for your new home. As you strengthen your bonds with them, you will learn more about their lives, stories, and motivations. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/师兄弟.gif?t=1705592279"><br/><br/>As you work and improve your skills, you will ascend in your cultivation journey; and your adventures will take you far from your Misty Valley. One day you will rebuild the strength of the Guiyun Sect and restore the glory of the Misty Valley. And maybe even achieve immortal life yourself…<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Farm with Spells</h2>Roam through the countryside, using your magic to cultivate fields, and taking care of crops with enchanted tools. Manage your own farmland amidst changing seasons and weather.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/仙法种田.gif?t=1705592279"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cultivate your way to immortality</h2>Master various skills such as fishing, cooking, crafting elixirs, or making furniture. Remember, every skill is important to help you restore the Misty Valley and cultivate your soul and powers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/生活技艺.gif?t=1705592279"><br/><br/>Train your abilities and attend classes before submitting yourself to the tests that allow you to reach a new step in your cultivation journey. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/修仙生活.gif?t=1705592279"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Mystic Realms</h2>Travel to distant lands, uncover treasures and use your magic to defeat mythical creatures. There are more than 10 different Mystic Realms and you’ll have to master different abilities and strategies to find the crafting items that you need from each territory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/秘境战斗.gif?t=1705592279"><h2 class="bb_tag">Fellowship within the Sect</h2>Get to know your brothers and sisters and help them with their daily struggles to strengthen your bond. Each character has their own personality and interests in cultivation. By helping them, you’ll learn more about their lifes and motivations – and receive new items, missions, and skills. You can also invite them to share your dwellings.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/同门.gif?t=1705592279"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Home</h2>Acquire spirit stones, unlock new territories, and initiate construction projects to establish a tranquil sanctuary in the valley of your homestead. With your crafting skills and the help of your brothers and sisters, you will get new decorations and magic tools for your farm and house.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/仙府建设.gif?t=1705592279"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Cut: Samurai Duel</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2193490/First_Cut_Samurai_Duel/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A high-intensity arcade sword-fighting game where <strong>every strike is lethal</strong>. Slash, clash, parry, dodge and watch limbs fly in the atmosphere of historical feudal Japan. Choose your move carefully - <strong>the first cut is also the last.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/stg1.gif?t=1705515941"><br/><br/><strong>A refined and intuitive fighting system</strong> - Aim your sword to block attacks and strike around your opponent's guard. Parry their attacks with your own, dodge to close the distance, and interrupt them with a well-timed shove. It takes a minute to learn, and a lifetime to master.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/jan7.gif?t=1705515941"><br/><br/><strong>Customize your fighter</strong> - An array of different options to wear. Choose and colour each piece separately to make each character your own.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/stg2.gif?t=1705515941"><br/><br/><strong>Dueling with deadly results</strong> - Send heads and limbs flying as blood rains down and stains the characters and environment. Chop your opponent to pieces, or equip a wooden sword instead for a little mercy and possibly a concussion.<br/><br/>Duel your friends in <strong>local multiplayer</strong>, fight custom <strong>AI opponents</strong>, try to stay alive in <strong>Survival mode</strong>, or hunt down enemies in the <strong>Scenario mode</strong> campaign. <br/>Play with friends remotely using <strong>Steam Remote Play Together.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Bonus modes</strong> - Laser swords, custom blood, floating weapons, zombies, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/jan12.gif?t=1705515941"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warframe: Gauss Prime Access - Weapons Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748310/Warframe_Gauss_Prime_Access__Weapons_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							For more Prime Access Bundle options, click <a href="http://store.steampowered.com/sale/warframeprime/" rel="" target="_blank">here</a>.<br/><div class="bb_code"><strong>WEAPONS PACK</strong><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> 1050 Platinum<br/></li><li> ACCELTRA PRIME: Engage your enemies with deadly speed. This weapon reloads even faster when its wielder sprints, faster still with Gauss.<br/></li><li> AKARIUS PRIME: Wield a golden pair of rocket launchers. Sprint to reload them faster. They reload fastest when wielded by Gauss.</li></ul></div>Prime Warframes and Weapons in Prime Access can also be crafted from parts found in Relics in-game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominions 6 - Rise of the Pantokrator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2511500/Dominions_6__Rise_of_the_Pantokrator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2511500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are a God! You are master and ruler of a loyal nation. You have unimaginable powers at your disposal. You have claimed this world as yours. But there are others who stand in your way. You must defeat and destroy these pretenders. Only then can you ascend to godhood and become the new Pantokrator.<br>
<br>
Dominions 6 is a turn based 4x strategy game suitable for both play vs AI, player vs player.  Team play vs AI or players also works great as everyone can do their turns at once.  The game has a huge variety of units, spells, magic items and different nations to play.<br>
<br>
In Dominions you take control of a powerful being that rules a nation and aspires to godhood. The type of Pretender Gods can vary from magically powerful arch mages to huge titans or large monuments. The pretender gods have different strengths dependent on what kind of god you choose and what nation you play.<br>
<br>
When you start the game you decide what kind of god you are and how your Dominion affects your lands, followers and sacred soldiers. It is an expression of your divine might and the faith of your followers. If your dominion dies, so do you. Your dominion also inspires your sacred warriors and gives them powers derived from your dominion.<br/>
<br/>
In order to win and become the one true god you have to defeat your enemies one of three different ways: conquer their lands, extinguish their dominion or claim the Thrones of Ascension.<br/>
<br/>
Dominions is set in a fantasy world that draws inspiration from historical nations, cultures and myths. You will not encounter the elves of conventional fantasy in this game. Instead you might lead a nation of vanir from old norse myth. Aztecs, romans, israelites, greeks, kievian rus and lovecraftian horrors are just a few of the inspirational sources of the game.<br/>
<br/>
The first Dominions game was released in 2002 and was well received by strategy gamers. Since then Dominions has been much refined and Dominions series is still actively played making it one of the longest running 4x turn based strategy games.<br/>
<br/>
----------<br/>
<br/>
Dominions 6 is scaled up compared to Dominions 5 and armies are larger. We wanted to tweak the balance between conventional armies and magic. To accomplish this a couple of changes are introduced. Incomes and resources are increased, while mages are more expensive. Battlefield-wide spells are more difficult to cast and there are instead more mid-tier spells. There are some other changes with the same aim.<br/>
<br/>
The second and probably most influential change is the addition of a new magic path. No longer are illusions the domain of Air magic. Instead illusions, phantasms, dreams and the stuff of forgotten legends are manipulated with the path of Glamour. This has resulted in many new spells, items and sites being added to the game. <br/>
<br/>
A third massive change is the separation of mounts and riders. Riders and mounts now have separate stats and can be targeted individually. This change probably has less impact on gameplay than the previous one, but will still have an impact on cavalry and nations using mounted units.<br/>
<br/>
Dominions 6 features a number of new nations as well. The addition of the Glamour path has also affected several of the old nations. <br/>
<br/>
There are also a number of changes intended to ease gameplay.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cult of the Lamb: Sinful Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2646130/Cult_of_the_Lamb_Sinful_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2646130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Sin to your heart’s content with Cult of the Lamb: Sinful Pack. This pack is the perfect way to indulge for those who enjoy a gluttonous aesthetic befitting kings and queens. Vanity might be a sin, but there’s nothing wrong with that!<h2 class="bb_tag">5 Brand New Follower Forms</h2>Hammerhead, Sphynx, Ladybug, Tiger, and Llama.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2646130/extras/SinfulFollowers_Banner1.png?t=1705596957"><h2 class="bb_tag">6 New Follower Outfits, and a Sinful New Fleece for the Lamb!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2646130/extras/SinfulClothes_Banner1.png?t=1705596957"><h2 class="bb_tag">6 New Base Decorations </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2646130/extras/SinfulDecor_Banner1.png?t=1705596957"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Safety Hotline</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2357910/Home_Safety_Hotline/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/RuntimeLabel-HSH-Dark.png?t=1705432881"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/ShinyLogoOnlyGIF.gif?t=1705432881"><br/><br/><strong>Hearing noises? Seeing things? Call Home Safety Hotline! Our operators are standing by, waiting to give you the answers you need to protect your home from all manner of pests and household hazards.</strong><br/><br/>Home Safety Hotline is an analog horror inspired telephone operator simulator where you answer incoming callers' questions about what's inside their home. Read through a vast catalog of common pests and household hazards, and do your best to become an expert in home safety. You will be held responsible for what happens.<br/><br/>A new horror experiment from Nick Lives, the creator of <i>NiGHT SIGNAL</i> and <i>A Wonderful Day For Fishing</i>. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Navigate a vast catalog of safety information using the latest in 90's technology.<br/></li><li> Listen to original jazzy lo-fi music by David Johnsen while you place callers on hold.<br/></li><li> Correctly deduce what's in your callers' homes or else leave them to suffer the consequences.<br/></li><li> Learn about the various untold horrors that live inside your home.<br/></li><li> "Phobia Toggles" - An accessibility option that allows you to disable in-game images for common phobia triggers including arachnophobia and more.<br/></li><li> Unlockable Art Book detailing the game's development history.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/NumberOnlyGIF.gif?t=1705432881"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingsvein</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2276830/Kingsvein/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2276830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							All contact with the city of Kingsvein has been lost. As Wisp Slayer, your role is to investigate and exterminate whatever evil lurks there.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2276830/extras/castleBanner_616x152.gif?t=1705404781"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adventure through the castle and its outer reaches as you see fit - secret treasures and skulking beasts hide around every corner! <br/></li><li>Dynamic and deep tactical combat - toss your enemies into spikes then electrify their blood, or cover the battlefield in flames <br/></li><li>Customize your team by mixing and matching 15 different classes, each with upgradeable abilities and equippable passives <br/></li><li>Use your abilities to explore - freeze rivers with your magic, blast through cave walls, and throw chains to topple statues <br/></li><li>Ride your loyal steed in and out of combat, and train it to be as fierce as any Knight <br/></li><li>Set in the realm of Graven, a weird subterranean world of living soil and half-stone Diecast <br/></li><li>From the maker of the highly-rated <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1224290/Horizons_Gate/" rel="" target="_blank">Horizon's Gate</a>, <a href="http://store.steampowered.com/app/415920/Voidspire_Tactics/" rel="" target="_blank">Voidspire Tactics</a> and <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/643900/Alvora_Tactics/" rel="" target="_blank">Alvora Tactics</a></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2276830/extras/voidbeam616x152.gif?t=1705404781"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2744170/Artifact_SeekerPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/DS.png?t=1705638389"/></a><br/>The difference between the prologue version and the official version<br/>There is a special artifact in the prologue<br/>Characters: 2 in the prologue, at least 5 in the official version<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 3 in the final version.<br/>Systems: Tavern, Marketplace, and Endless Mode will be added to the game.<br/>Artifacts: More artifacts will be added to the game.<br/>Skills: More skills will be added in the official version.<br/>Words: More words will be added in the official version.<br/>Encounters: There will be more interesting encounters in the official version.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/11y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1z.gif?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/2y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/gif1.gif?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.gif?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong>[/b]<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.gif?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.gif?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><strong><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.gif?t=1705638389"><br/>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </img></img></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Hoplite: Arachne’s Trial</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2738430/Legendary_Hoplite_Arachnes_Trial/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Try out the free prologue to get a taste of the exciting gameplay and easily transfer your progress to the full game.<br/><br/><strong>Transfer your progress to the main game</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_04.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>The main game offers three acts, 38 areas, mini-games, and a lot of gear options for your hero. Progress seamlessly transfers from the prologue to the main game.<br/><br/><strong>Face 10 Levels and 2 Boss Battles</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_02.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>Face the challenge of 10 distinct levels, each filled with hordes of mythic monsters. Try 6 different armies and test your skills against Arachne at the end of the prologue.<br/><br/><strong>Customize Your Build and Power Up Your Army</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_01.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>Customize your build by trying out various gear combinations you come across. Find the perfect match for your playstyle as you explore. Strengthen your army by upgrading them and merging with the Hero to amplify your power, ready to face and conquer the enemy.<br/><br/><strong>War technique</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_03.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>Elevate your armies with War Technique—a fresh way to upgrade. Experiment with various combos and effortlessly switch up your enhancements for effective improvements.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Momodora: Moonlit Farewell</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1747760/Momodora_Moonlit_Farewell/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1747760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Momodora: Moonlit Farewell" is the latest installment in the Momodora series. Join Momo, High Priestess of the village of Koho, as she embarks on a divine mission to save her people from imminent destruction at the hands of the demon hordes summoned by a malevolent bellringer.<h2 class="bb_tag">Story:</h2>Momodora: Moonlit Farewell presents the account of the greatest calamity to befall the village of Koho, five years after the events of Momodora III.<br/> Once the toll of an ominous bell is heard, the village is soon threatened by a demon invasion.<br/>The village's matriarch sends Momo Reinol, their most capable priestess, to investigate the bell and find the bellringer responsible for summoning demons. It is their hope that by finding the culprit, they will also  be able to secure the village's safety, and most importantly, the sacred Lun Tree's, a source of life and healing for Koho...<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Gorgeous pixel art and animation<br/></li><li> Action-packed gameplay focusing on melee combos, dodging enemy attacks, and firing arrows at enemies<br/></li><li> The "Sigil" system, which allows for greatly customizable play styles<br/></li><li> Intense and core-shaking boss battles<br/></li><li> Deep exploration into a world rich in lore and atmosphere<br/></li><li> Freely adjustable difficulty levels, allowing you to relax and explore the alluring world at your own pace or take on mighty foes for a real challenge</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Developer's Voice:</h2>Hello!<br/><br/>This is rdein, creator of the Momodora series. Recently my team and I have announced the latest installment in the series, “Moonlit Farewell”. This is a concluding story, following through from the events of Momodora 3. With this new tale, I also intend to close the book on many of the past games’ mysteries and questions.<br/><br/>I’m aware that many players are more familiar with the story of Kaho, which is set in a distant past. As such, I’m designing “Moonlit Farewell” to be as enjoyable as possible without prior knowledge of Momodora 1 to 3’s stories. Moreover, the series has always been focused on action and minimal stories. So please, don’t worry too much about “catching up”!<br/>Lastly, we hope to bring you our best game with this new title, using all the knowledge we’ve learned in the past 10 years. Please look forward to it!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frostrain</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735630/Frostrain/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/01_Thumnail.png?t=1705651196"><h2 class="bb_tag">Roam the frozen world</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Roam_the_frozen_world.gif?t=1705651196"><br/>Climate change has turned the world white and frozen, and the only thing moving on the planet is you, your passengers, and your train. It's a dead world, but ironically, it's all the more fascinating for it. A vivid landscape awaits you to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Keep your passengers happy</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Keep_your_passengers_happy.gif?t=1705651196"><br/>The passengers on your train will work diligently at your command, but be careful: if you don't manage their happiness properly, they might throw you off the train.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build your own train with card decks</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Build_your_own_train_with_card_decks.gif?t=1705651196"><br/>Each time you pass through a city, you'll be able to add new train cars by launching a heavy lift drone. Be careful with each choice you make. If you are lucky, you'll be able to build a better, more synergized, happily-ever-after train deck, but it won't always go as you planned.<h2 class="bb_tag">Reach the Promised Land</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Reach_the_Promised_Land.gif?t=1705651196"><br/>Lead your passengers in search of the Promised Land, somewhere on the eastern edge of the world. But the journey to the Promised Land isn't all smooth and pleasant. You'll have to pass through toxic areas, and a severe storm is brewing behind you. Pay attention to your passengers' happiness levels and lead them safely to the Promised Land. The journey is in your hands.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoardLand</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735620/BoardLand/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Create your own strategy with the dice</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/extras/Cardnals_1.gif?t=1705310503"><br/><br/>The dice is rolled!<br/>Are you going to move? Are you going to act?<br/>Different effects are applied to each die, and the numbers determine your behavior.<br/>How do you combine numbers to get the best results?<br/>Every time you pick a number, you'll have to choose carefully.<h2 class="bb_tag">Make a powerful board by strengthening the tiles.</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/extras/Cardinals_2.gif?t=1705310503"><br/><br/>Tiles get more and more powerful!<br/>Every time you act on a tile, the tile gains experience, and the tile with enough experience is upgradeable.<br/>Combine tiles with multiple properties to create the best strategy, your own board<h2 class="bb_tag">Defeat the monsters and bosses</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/extras/Cardinals_3.gif?t=1705310503"><br/><br/>Monsters disturb you!<br/>Monsters can summon Fireballs, or they can curse and cause obstacles to certain tiles.<br/>You have to move and act with the dice, avoiding these patterns every time.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Flame: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517810/The_Last_Flame_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_1.png?t=1705541234"><br/>The Last Flame is a roguelike auto-battler which focuses on build creation, strategy and decision making. Recruit special heroes, fight deadly encounters, loot and craft powerful gear, discover and create unique synergetic builds! Every run, you will need to create powerful builds that will take down your foes!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_A3.gif?t=1705541234"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_2.png?t=1705541234"><br/>The Last Flame offers an incredible amount of build diversity. Combine heroes, items, relics and origins together to create amazing builds! Hero and team building have been designed with flexibility and freedom at their core which allows you to discover and create unique synergetic builds every single run!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Builds.gif?t=1705541234"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_3.png?t=1705541234"><br/>In between the automated combats, you will have to cleverly guide your heroes through the adventure by making the smart decisions! Manage your resources, choose the optimal path in the map, make powerful builds, and strategically position and plan the combat phase!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Tactical.gif?t=1705541234"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/comingToFullVersion.png?t=1705541234"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get access to a lot more stuff! Make amazing builds with 300 items, 58 heroes, 125 relics and 60 origins.<br/></li><li>Continue the adventure in the third act, and meet the final boss in a special act!<br/></li><li>Face 30 challenging enemies and 10 bosses!<br/></li><li>Progress through 5 difficulties which will challenge your knowledge and strategy!<br/></li><li>Push your builds to their limit in the endless mode, a mode where you try to reach the highest floor!<br/></li><li>Experience the game in diverse and fun new ways with the challenge modes!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_ENDLESS.gif?t=1705541234"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summoners War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2426960/Summoners_War/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2426960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>▶Features</strong><br/><strong>[Tactical RPG play]</strong><br/>Witness the dazzling display of each monster 's unique skills.<br/>23 different Rune sets to pick and choose additional abilities for your monsters!<br/>Come up with the best strategy to win battles in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[Endless Fun]</strong><br/>Decorate your Village, battle other summoners , explore dungeons , fight in PvP battles , expand your collection, train monsters , and more.<br/><br/><strong>[The Key of Colletion RPG : Massive Collection]</strong><br/>Fire, Water, Wind, Light and Dark!<br/>5 different attributes, and 1500 different monsters!<br/>Collect as many monsters as you can and win battles with your own decks .<br/><br/><strong>[Real-time Raid]</strong><br/>Battle as a team with your greatest monsters !<br/>A real-time battle with 3 users!<br/>Defeat the boss with your fellow Summoners using various tactics.<br/><br/><strong>[Homunculus]</strong><br/>The Forbidden Summoning Magic has finally been revealed!<br/>You can Evolve the skill of your choice with this special monster.<br/>Summon Homunculus and show off your strategy in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[All about Turn-Based RPG : World Arena]</strong><br/>Enjoy a real-time battle with Summoners worldwide!<br/>Experience a breathtaking battle that starts from Pick &amp; Ban.<br/>Reveal your unique strategy to the world and win battles .<br/><br/><strong>[Guild Content]</strong><br/>A sensational Guild PvP battle in the Isle of Conquest!<br/>Explore the Tartarus' Labyrinth and dungeons with Guild Members.<br/>Make your Guild the greatest of all.<br/><br/><strong>[Dimension Hole]</strong><br/>Fight against the ancient power emerged from a new dimension!<br/>Defeat the Ancient Guardians and meet the powerful monsters with new awakening power.<br/><br/><strong>[Artifact]</strong><br/>Artifacts are now dropped with MAX power-up levels!<br/>Summoners , fight against the powerful bosses and acquire Artifacts!<br/>Enhance your monsters with various sub properties of Artifacts.<br/><br/><strong>[Progression and Farming Structure Revamp]</strong><br/>Summoner progression structure renewed and content reward greatly improved!<br/>Dive into Summoners War and experience the enhanced progression system!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portal: Revolution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/601360/Portal_Revolution/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Portal: Revolution is a fan-made mod for Portal 2 which plays before the events of Portal 2 in the dead and decaying Aperture facility.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/ezgif-7-f507c3c464_1_.gif?t=1705083406"><br/><strong>Over 40 new puzzles</strong><br/>The campaign contains 40 brand new puzzles making use of new test elements and presents existing mechanics in a new way not seen in Portal 2.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resurrected "Pneumatic Diversity Vent" element<br/></li><li> New laser cube variant<br/></li><li> Over 15 puzzles using only the blue Portal-Gun<br/></li><li> Gel Cleansing Field</li></ul><br/><strong>Difficulty</strong><br/>Portal: Revolutions puzzle difficulty starts where Portal 2 stops, but fear not. All new mechanics and advanced portal tricks are taught to you. We have ensured through rigorous playtesting that every player can solve the puzzles. Although very few chambers require portals to be fired mid-air, no puzzles require advanced tricky movement.<br/><br/>Depending on your experience with Portal 2 mechanics, you can expect about 5 to 7 hours of playtime.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/banner_story_2.gif?t=1705083406"><br/>Set inbetween Portal and Portal 2, Portal: Revolution tells a brand new story using new characters. You play as a test subject who is awoken by a personality sphere called Stirling and join his mission to find a powerful device capable of restoring Aperture to its former glory.<h2 class="bb_tag">ENGINE</h2>Portal: Revolution uses a modified version of Portal 2: Community Edition's engine, which is a custom version of the Counter-Strike: Global Offensive Source Engine branch using licensed source code provided by Valve Software.<br/><br/>This allowed us to introduce many mechanics and improvements to the engine to create an experience which would be impossible in Portal 2.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Memories</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2495450/Winter_Memories/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1705531460"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Header_EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter-Memories-Cards_GIF.gif?t=1705531460"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Trading_Others_EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_1-EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/>After the unforgettable summer memories you’ve made half a year ago, Yui, Rio, and Miyuki are back. With the change of seasons and the cold falling snow, a new page to your story is about to begin. <br/><br/>Revisit the peaceful, seaside town, and spend time catching up with your family and friends.<br/><br/>What new memories will you make this winter?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_3-EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Miyuki_EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Rio_EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Yui_EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_4-EN.png?t=1705531460"><br/><strong>A Relaxing, Adventure RPG<strong><br/><br/><strong>Explore the Beautiful, Seaside Town<strong><br/><br/><strong>Manage How You Spend Your TIme<strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pesticide Not Required: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2480450/Pesticide_Not_Required_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The free prologue for Pesticide Not Required, a game that combines auto-attacking bullet heaven roguelites with farming game mechanics to create an expansive set of strategies and build combinations. Destroy huge hordes of evil insects, grow tons of crops, create your own build path, and unlock unique characters to play with!<br/><br/>This prologue version contains similar mechanics to the main game, but has less achievements, progression unlocks, unlockable characters, weapons, maps, and enemy varieties.<h2 class="bb_tag">Create Overpowered Builds</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/extras/CombatChaosFisher.gif?t=1705210453"><br/>You are the bullet hell! Grow an arsenal of ridiculous weapons and craft your own unique build with a combination of 40+ stats. Additionally, each character has their own unique traits that keep runs fresh.<h2 class="bb_tag">Farm, Fish, and Mine</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/extras/FarmFishMineWinterGif.gif?t=1705210453"><br/>Earn vital gold and experience from growing crops, catching fish, and mining. Expand your plot to harvest huge quantities of crops and build carefully to enhance your farming, fishing, and mining capabilities.<h2 class="bb_tag">Automate Your Farm With Pets</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/extras/PetsGifAutumn.gif?t=1705210453"><br/>Recruit friendly pets that will enhance your farm, collect loot, and kill enemies.<br/><br/>Other Features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Season-themed map variations with multiple difficulty levels<br/></li><li>Many unlockable characters with special traits<br/></li><li>Persistent skill tree upgrades<br/></li><li>Quick ~20-minute play sessions<br/></li><li>Tons of achievements to unlock<br/></li><li>Full gamepad and keyboard support<br/></li><li>Go WUMBO!</li></ul><br/>Pesticide Not Required: Prologue is inspired by awesome games like Brotato, Vampire Survivors, and Atomicrops.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Esports Godfather Origin</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2739460/Esports_Godfather_Origin/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/游戏简介英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/>"Esport Godfather" is a management simulation card game that revolves around the theme of MOBA esports. In this game, you will assume the role of a coach in an esports club and personally build your own team! Starting from scratch, what kind of playstyle will you devise for your team? In a constantly evolving meta, can you derive a unique understanding of what it takes to win? How will you unlock the potential of your handpicked athletes and mold them into superstars?<br/><br/>Ultimately, will you be able to become a legendary figure in the esports industry, crafting your own esports story and lifting the championship trophy?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/选手培养英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/>Each athlete is unique! They all have their own strengths and weaknesses.<br/>If an athlete's efficiency in earning money increases over time, they are undoubtedly a skilled late-game specialist.<br/>Successful ambushes can unlock hidden potential, propelling some athletes onto the path of godlike.<br/>As a coach, it's your responsibility to analyze each athlete's characteristics, devise training plans tailored to their needs, and guide them on their journey to becoming superstars!<br/><br/>· Every athlete possesses distinct abilities that will impact their performance on the battlefield!<br/>· An athlete's hero pool is crucial for Ban &amp; Pick strategies!<br/>· The tactic cards utilized by athletes in matches serve as the foundation of all strategies!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/版本变更英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/>The meta environment is ever-changing!<br/>Changes in the equipment pool, the structure of economic income, and the source of decisive advantages, even slight alterations to the rules can drastically shift the priorities of Ban &amp; Pick and alter the strategic approach!<br/><br/>· Equipment will be added or removed as the versions change!<br/>· The timing of crucial team fights will shift with each version update, making team composition crucial!<br/>· Does harassment grant more gold? Do kills damage towers? Each gameplay rule brings a fresh experience!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/指挥战斗英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/>You have the power to command the battlefield, with athletes attentively listening to your orders.<br/>Should you play it safe and focus on farming under the towers, or launch aggressive assaults and initiate attacks?<br/>Perfect team composition requires perfect leadership! The game is ever-changing, and you must face your opponents head-on!<br/><br/>· Each hero and athlete possesses their own tactic cards. It is through creative combinations and strategic application that they become unstoppable!<br/>· Offense or defense? Aggression or caution? The outcome rests in your hands. Formulate strategies and implement tactics!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/其他内容英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/>· Over 50 unique heroes in the starting lineup, each with their own special abilities!<br/>· 200+ tactic cards, granting you control over the battlefield!<br/>· Diverse athlete training options! As a mentor, it's important to tailor your teachings to each individual!<br/>· Unearth young talents and cultivate new forces in the youth training camp!<br/>· Choose sponsors, a top-tier club deserves the support of top-tier sponsors!<br/>· Trash-talking sessions, asserting dominance is a must before crucial matches!<br/>· Abundance of events, includes unexpected occurrences, athlete communication, team pep talks!<br/>· Training match plans, knowing your opponents inside out ensures victory after victory!<br/>· Regular season, playoffs, transfer periods—different decisions await you at different times!<br/>· When athletes reach their limits, you must help them break through and reach new heights!<br/>· Create a custom team logo for your club!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/工作室LOGO英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowbreak: Containment Zone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668080/Snowbreak_Containment_Zone/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Snowbreak: Containment Zone is a 3D sci-fi RPG-shooter powered by the Unreal Engine 4 that offers a next-gen, cross-platform gaming experience, sharing your progress across all of your devices. <br/><br/>The Descent of the Titans turned a once-vibrant city into the devastated wasteland of Containment Zone Aleph. As the Adjutant of Heimdall Force, bravely undertake missions alongside Manifestations with the powers of gods and unique personalities, seeking to bring this bitter winter to an end...<br/><br/>[Enjoy Hybrid Combat]<br/>Snowbreak's weaponry injects realism into a sci-fi setting, with designs closely simulating future firearms technology. This combines with the otherworldly, RPG-like skill mechanic to create a refreshing combat experience.<br/><br/>[Take on Titans]<br/>The Descent of the Titans completely changed the world, and the battlefield. Feel the thrill of battling giants in this dystopian future!<br/><br/>[Befriend Operatives]<br/>Spend time with your Heimdall Force companions in the Base system. Decorate, chat, and give gifts to grow closer!<br/><br/>[Play Co-Op in Gigalink] <br/>Tired of exploring alone? Join up with friends and fight enemies together!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703868247"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1705569806"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1705569806"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1705569806"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1705569806"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1705569806"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1705569806"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1705569806"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1704804364"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1705439381"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1705439381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1705439381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1705439381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1705439381"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Born of Bread</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1555140/Born_of_Bread/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Beings from another age are causing havoc across the land! And with their mischief comes a great threat to everyone. The unlikeliest hero, a golem born of bread, will find himself and his newfound buddies in the middle of a drama that's thousands of years in the making. Together, they will visit incredible locals and meet fascinating characters. Although he may not look like much, Loaf might be the hero this land kneads.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Sentient Bread on a Quest</h2><br/>Play as a flour golem who possesses a never-ending childlike wonder and a set of odd abilities in this 2.5D adventure game!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Cinematic_opti.gif?t=1705570384"><br/><br/>Explore the different regions of a wonderful world ripe with mysteries and team up with a colorful cast of fleshed-out characters. With the help of your buddies, face off against menacing and weird baddies and engage in a fun and quirky turn-based combat system.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Enviro_opti.gif?t=1705570384"><br/><br/><strong>A home-cooked battle system</strong><br/>Born of Bread puts a twist on turn-based combat tropes with a fun interaction system that will test your reflexes.<br/>This interactive system also features a weaknesss and resistance system that makes battles more strategic.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Combat_Opti.gif?t=1705570384"><br/><br/><strong>Team up with your buddies</strong><br/>Loaf can't do it alone. Meet new characters during your adventure, each with their own abilities and personnality. Use their unique skills to overcome threats and obstacles whether in fights or when exploring.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Buddies_opti.gif?t=1705570384"><br/><br/><strong>Stream your fights to a fake audience!</strong><br/>Your dragon buddy Dub will let you save your progression but also stream your fights to a fake audience with his little laptop! Gather more viewers and answer their demand to get rewards!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven Betrayers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2729570/Seven_Betrayers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a pixelated casual action game that tells the story of a sea-rimmed continent. In the story, our protagonist obtains information by defeating monsters and unlocking elite monsters to learn about the history and culture of the continent, and gradually learns the truth about the demonic infection. The story is told from the perspective of the seven betrayers, and the player defeats them through battle and leaves the continent for a new world after learning the truth!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad Santa</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2745250/Bad_Santa/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Collect keys and solve puzzles to collect your christmas gifts. But be careful there is a lurking evil santa that knows your every move, and whatever you do don't go to the basement.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745250/extras/Featuresbanner.png?t=1705666752"><br/> <ul class="bb_ul"> <li>Challenging <br/> </li><li>Jump Scares<br/> </li><li>Problem Solving<br/> </li><li>Milk &amp; Cookies<br/> </li><li>Christmas Spirit</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745250/extras/GAMEPLAY_BANNER.png?t=1705666752"><br/>In Bad Santa use your speed and agility to avoid Santa, he hears and sees everything. Solve puzzles, find clues, and collect keys to help find your well earned christmas gifts and bring the christmas spirit back to your neighborhood.<br/><br/><u><strong>Gather keys to open doors:</strong></u><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745250/extras/Keygifforstorepage.gif?t=1705666752"><br/><br/><u><strong>Complete different types of puzzles:</strong></u><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745250/extras/keypadpuzzle.gif?t=1705666752"><br/><u><strong>Collect all presents to win the game!:</strong></u><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745250/extras/Storepagegiftgif.gif?t=1705666752"><br/><br/><br/>Also check out the guy who made the music: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@Myuu" rel="" target="_blank">https://www.youtube.com/@Myuu</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Petit Game Collection vol.1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2757490/Petit_Game_Collection_vol1/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Petit Game Collection vol.1" is a spin-off minigame collection of "Needy Streamer Overload".<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757490/extras/GameSelect.png?t=1705667849"><br/><br/>In Volume 1,<br/>we are featuring 3 mini-games that receive inspiration<br/>from good old retro bishōjo games!<br/><br/>There's just something about ""retro"" that you can't feel elsewhere...<br/>So go give it a try!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Contents</h2></strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757490/extras/Galgame.jpg?t=1705667849"><br/><strong>■Ame's Happy Happy Dating Game</strong><br/>A retro-style visual novel,<br/>where you get to experience a rare date scene that can't be seen in the main game.<br/>Take Ame to a nice place and give her the time of her life!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757490/extras/ShootingGame.jpg?t=1705667849"><br/><strong>■Don't Die, Kangel!</strong><br/>A rogue-like shooting game.<br/>After ariving at the scene of everyone's favorite anime convention,<br/>what awaited our lovely internet angel were some filthy otakus... ew!<br/>It's an angel's job to keep herself and the convention filth-free, so get shooting with... huh?!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757490/extras/BreakOut.png?t=1705667849"><br/><strong>■Break Out Kangel</strong><br/>A game for the cultured.<br/>Oh no, our internet angel is stuck in some blocks!<br/>Break the blocks to reveal... *cough* ...help her out!<br/>*This mini-game can only be played in Japanese.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757490/extras/Room.jpg?t=1705667849"><br/><strong>■KAngel's Room</strong><br/>Full of staff comments and inside stories. A must read for NSO fans.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Battles: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2746200/Tiny_Battles_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Tiny Battles is a tactical action auto-battler where battles take place automatically in the arena.<br/>Prologue is a demo version of the Tiny Battles game, where 2 of the 5 factions and 3 of the 15 enemy opponents are available to play.<h2 class="bb_tag">BATTLES</h2>Battles happen automatically:<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746200/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converted__1_.gif?t=1705666527"><h2 class="bb_tag">STRATEGY IS THE PATH TO VICTORY</h2>Build the right units for your strategy - early attack, midgame or consistent late game build with ultimate units for victory - the choice is yours.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746200/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converted__2_.gif?t=1705666527"><h2 class="bb_tag">COMBINE TROOPS </h2>Each faction has multiple paths to victory. Brute force, artillery attack or summoning creatures.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746200/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converted.gif?t=1705666527"><h2 class="bb_tag">STUDY YOUR OPPONENT</h2>Each enemy commander and his race have strengths and weaknesses, study them to defeat them!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746200/extras/11111.png?t=1705666527"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viking Heroes 5</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2725020/Viking_Heroes_5/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							HISTORY:<br/><br/>Embark on a festive journey as Everand, Brunnhilde, Helga, and Boromere prepare for Yule! Amidst enchanting festivities, the Viking siblings discover Odin has lost control over his vision of time and the threads of fate, prompting a mysterious journey throughout the famous realms of the nine worlds.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725020/extras/Banner_1.png?t=1705663719"><br/><br/>It is up to you to help the vikings rediscover the lost Rune of Balance to restore order to the nine worlds. The vikings will have to confront mystical challenges and unveil the truth of their surroundings. They will battle powerful adversaries and team with old and new companions alike. Though not all may be as they seem. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725020/extras/Banner_2.png?t=1705663719"><br/><br/>Download now to guide the Viking heroes through illusions, confront powerful adversaries, and claim Odin's extraordinary gifts, shaping their legendary fate!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725020/extras/Banner_3.png?t=1705663719"><br/><br/>GAME FEATURES:<br/><br/>In Viking heroes 5, as in any time manager you have to accurately calculate the time for building, collecting resources and timely use of bonuses. <br/><br/>The game has a large variety of buildings and unique items, collecting them you will perform tasks and participate in unique adventures. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725020/extras/Banner_4.png?t=1705663719"><br/><br/>Viking heroe 5 is a classic time manger with base building and level resource gathering. To perform at your best, you need to time and give strategic orders to your characters. Each level can be completed for 3 stars, for this you need to complete all tasks as quickly as possible in the timer. The game has 60 elaborate levels and 3 difficulties.   <br/><br/>60 exciting levels<br/>5 levels with mini-game<br/>Step-by-step level guide<br/>Catchy downloadable Original Soundtrack<br/>Beautiful desktop wallpapers<br/>A collection of God's gifts<br/>Collectible owls<br/>Achievements						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sentinels</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2399040/Sentinels/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2399040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2399040/extras/타이틀_수정_610.png?t=1705663586"><br/><br/>Sentinels is a free-to-play hero shooter game created by ClearSky Studio. Master the powerful abilities of the various agent characters in the game and experience tactical squad play, fast-paced hero shooting and team deathmatch.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Contract with various agents!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2399040/extras/Steam_Description1.png?t=1705663586"><br/><br/></img></li><li> Develop a strategy with your teammates!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2399040/extras/Steam_Description3.png?t=1705663586"><br/><br/></img></li><li> Organize your squad strategically!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2399040/extras/Steam_Description2.png?t=1705663586"/></li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cub</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1941410/The_Cub/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1941410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1941410/extras/Inspired_by_the_classics.png?t=1705664725"><br/>Challenging platform parkour inspired by classic SEGA games of the 90s - The Jungle Book, Aladdin, Lion King – but with modern twists and ideas. Platform parkour through the remains of humanity. Outwit evolved wildlife and dangerous hybrid flora. Crack environmental puzzles that keep you guessing. And stay one step ahead of the wicked humans who pursuing you in a twisted apocalyptic safari hunt.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1941410/extras/Gif_1.gif?t=1705664725"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1941410/extras/The_story_of_the_hunted_cub.png?t=1705664725"><br/>After the Great Ecological Catastrophe, the ultrarich flee to Mars and leave the rest to perish. But among them a small child who developed immunity to the hostile planet remains. Decades pass and those on Mars venture back to Earth to do recon. When they spot a small human child, The Cub, they immediately try to capture it. This sets off a journey of escape, exploration and discovery through the urban ruins of humanity coupled with frantic cat and mouse chases.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1941410/extras/Gif_2.gif?t=1705664725"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1941410/extras/This_world_tells_tales.png?t=1705664725"><br/>Explore the ruins of humanity after the Great Ecological Catastrophe wipes out most of the civilization and leaves our remains to be reclaimed by an evolved mother nature. The story and clues of how and why humanity fell are strewn throughout the world. Crumbling brutalist tower blocks and abandoned genetics labs. Depleted chemical mines and overgrown battlefields. Each level has a story to tell.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1941410/extras/Gif_3.gif?t=1705664725"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1941410/extras/The_perfect_tunes_to_keep_you.png?t=1705664725"><br/>Accompanying you on the journey is Radio Nostalgia From Mars, a custom soundtrack that’ll crash land into your psyche. Sink into thought-provoking survivor stories from the few ultrarich living on Mars, while a smooth-voiced radio DJ keeps the show moving with a collection of chill apocalypse-wave tunes.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1941410/extras/Gif_4.gif?t=1705664725"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1941410/extras/If_look_could_bring_back_memories.png?t=1705664725"><br/>Meticulously drawn and stylized to look like the classic animated films of the late 90s - Atlantis, Tarzan, Road to El Dorado - while also taking a page from Samurai Jack’s creator Genndy Tartakovsky's critically acclaimed series, Primal.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1941410/extras/GiF_5.gif?t=1705664725"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edward's Journey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1976190/Edwards_Journey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/extras/TheGame_copy.png?t=1705660511"><br/>Edward's Journey is a full 3d top-down action-adventure RPG. It is a single player game with a large world that you can explore. More of the world can be accessed as you gain certain items and/or solve puzzles. Teleports exist throughout certain parts of the world for quicker travel.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/extras/Gif1.gif?t=1705660511"><br/><br/>Your main weapons in the game are sticks. Each stick has one main weapon slot and a possibility of two additional slots for equipping stones. The main weapon slot can be used to equip items that will add additional damage to your weapon, damage over time, or give you the ability to shoot magic from your weapon. If you find nails in the world you can add them for more damage. If you kill a monster with spines, you can add a spine to your weapon for additional damage. If you kill a bee, you can add its abdomen to your weapon to do poison damage over time using its stinger. This can all be done on the fly. Equipment stones can be added to the two additional slots and are used to improve the players stats. Edward can also wear helmets and shields. They can have up to three equipment slots available.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/extras/TheStory_copy.png?t=1705660511"><br/>You are a small boy named Edward.  You live in a small isolated little village with your gram and your little sister.  It comes to your attention that your sister has gone missing.  Your gram sends you out to find her.  You have never left your village before and have no idea the dangers that await you beyond the safety of your home.  You will have to learn to fight and defend yourself along your journey.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/extras/Game.jpg?t=1705660511"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/extras/TheWorld_copy.png?t=1705660511"><br/>The world of Edward’s Journey is a beautifully unique hand-crafted fantasy world filled with many hidden treasures and surprises.  There are several large maps.  Each of these maps has several dungeons, caves, and other areas to explore.  Certain dungeons are randomly generated.  Teleporters can also be unlocked throughout the world for quick travel.  Some areas will have to be visited again later once you have a certain item to allow you to proceed.  You will find many helpful NPCs across the world.  You help them out and they will help you in return.  Merchants can also be found scattered around the world.  Each one will have different stock.  Find one if you are low on crafting items or if you are in need of a specialized item that only they have.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/extras/Crafting_copy.png?t=1705660511"><br/>Edward has the ability to craft many items in the game.  Some items, such as potions and food, require Edward to be near a cauldron to craft.  Many other items can be crafted at any time provided Edward has the necessary items in his inventory.  Most of the helmets and shields will need to be crafted.  Recipes for crafted items can be found throughout the world and are automatically added to Edward’s recipes in the crafting window when they are picked up.  You do not need these recipes in order to craft an item if you figure them out yourself by experimenting.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/extras/Crafting.jpg?t=1705660511"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/extras/Combat_copy.png?t=1705660511"><br/>Edward is a small boy who has no fighting experience.  He learns by necessity as he fights his way to his sister.  His weapons of choice are sticks.  He will have some basic swinging attacks at first but will learn more attacks has he levels up or finds a npc trainer.  Attaching magic runes to Edward’s sticks will allow him to shoot magical bursts from his weapon.  If you attach a fire rune, his weapon will shoot fireballs and do fire damage over time to the enemy.  If he attaches an ice rune, it will freeze an enemy for a short time and do damage over time.  You can also add runes to your action bar instead of your weapon.  When used from your action bar they will do area of effect damage around Edward.  Using magic runes will consume Magic Points (MP).  If a rune is equipped on a weapon and Edward has no MP left it will no longer have a ranged attack.  It will still do damage over time if an enemy is hit in melee range.<br/>When a shield is equipped, Edward will be able to block a certain percentage of incoming damage if he has his shield up.<br/>Edward can also dash to help him dodge out of the way of enemy attacks.  The dash and more powerful attacks will use up Edwards’s stamina bar.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/extras/Gif2.gif?t=1705660511"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/extras/Fishing_copy.png?t=1705660511"><br/>Edward can fish in nearly every body of water in the game.  First, he will need to craft a rod.  Once a rod is crafted, he will need to dig up some worms.  Fishing can help Edward in a few ways.  If he catches a fish, he can take the fish fillets and craft up some fish soup at a cauldron.   The soup will heal Edward’s magic points over time.  He can also fish up other items, like jewels, health hearts, and other crafting items.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/extras/Fishing.jpg?t=1705660511"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/extras/TreasureHunting_copy.png?t=1705660511"><br/>Treasure maps can be found throughout the world.  Each map will have a clue that will point you in the direction of the treasure.  When you find the right location a large ‘X’ will appear on the ground where you need to dig.  You will need to craft a shovel to dig.  You can dig in most places in the world as you wish.  Who knows what you will find?  Mostly worms I suppose.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/extras/Treasure.jpg?t=1705660511"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/extras/Pets_copy.png?t=1705660511"><br/>Edward can find pets throughout the world.  Each pet can help Edward while it is summoned.  Some will randomly pop health hearts, some will find jewels, some will help with replenishing Edward’s magic, and some may even help damage monsters in the area.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1976190/extras/Pets.jpg?t=1705660511"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kona &amp; Snowrabbit</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2726560/Kona__Snowrabbit/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Kona, an ice artist with a reputation for mischief, and Snow Rabbit, a snow-white rabbit.<br/>After hearing rumors of the mermaid god Aquis, the two young artists set out to create the ultimate ice sculpture of the mermaid god and to break into the monastery of the mermaid god, known as the "sea on land".<br/><br/>Quarter-view casual "frozen" shooting action with a twist on the arcade genre.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Cool 'Frozen' action</strong></li></ul>Frozen Action Is A Must to Defeat Enemies!<br/>Your snobbish but reliable partner, Snow Rabbit, has the ability to freeze enemies by firing ice bullets.<br/>Once frozen, you can freeze them a second time to break them, or smash them with your hammer to send them flying!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Nostalgic arcade gameplay</strong></li></ul>We've included all the "yummy" elements of the arcade genre!<br/>Intuitive controls with the attack button to attack and the dash button to dash,<br/>Stage-by-stage progression through rooms filled with menacing enemies,<br/>And an item that gives you access to a powerful attack for a brief moment!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Personalized Comedic Elements</strong></li></ul>Rabbit with ice coming out of its mouth is used as weapon and the rabbit turns into hammer,<br/>Enemies get frozen in the air and sink underwater, the protagonist is a villain who makes his enemies suffer...<br/>Enjoy the humorous atmosphere of this game with its comedic elements!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost Princess: City</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2765350/Lost_Princess_City/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2765350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Story:</h2><br/>Play this FPS walking simulation where mission is to collect hidden items to get achievements. Princess are again lost in big city and player mission is to find princess to finish journey.  Game contains also several other collectable items which gives player steam achievements  So explorer big open city and other areas find all hidden objects<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2>- lot of collectable items which gives steam achievements<br/>- Relax andbig city with lof of different items						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hypnosis Card</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2544990/Hypnosis_Card/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2544990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2544990/extras/Title1.png?t=1705651507"><br/>The protagonist is a poker player who only cares about playing cards, and he has always been single. On his 30th birthday, he received a magical card that could hypnotize other girls. As a card player, what does he want to use this ability for?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2544990/extras/Title4.png?t=1705651507"><br/>"Hypnosis Card" is a card battle game centered around deck building, which introduces a <strong>body part</strong> concept. Players have access to many cards from five major genres. Encounter various events on randomly generated maps, develop the plot, and have exciting battles with cute girls.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2544990/extras/Title2.png?t=1705651507"><br/><strong>Kanome Shinichi</strong><br/>The younger sister brought here by my stepmother. She likes sports and good at both morals and academics. She is friendly to others, and is very popular. But in fact, he hates any boy who comes close to her, and she is especially cold towards me.<br/>Measurements: 82 58 88<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2544990/extras/Girl1.gif?t=1705651507"><br/><br/><strong>Kasuga Nana</strong><br/>The top maid in the maid café. Always dressed as a cat. She is cute and enthusiastic and is the pillar of my soul. She is so popular with guests that sometimes it's difficult to name her for service.<br/>Measurements: 98 62 92<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2544990/extras/Girl2gif.gif?t=1705651507"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2544990/extras/Title3.png?t=1705651507"><br/>❤ 5 beautiful girls<br/>There are 5 different girls to encounter in the game!<br/><br/>❤ Dynamically changing map<br/>Maps are randomly generated, and each experience is completely different.<br/><br/>❤ Random mysterious events<br/>Have many mysterious events, trigger plots or powerful cards? It all depends on your choice.<br/><br/>❤ Rich cards and combinations<br/>Customizable decks to form different strategies!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAKEUMA 2D</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2752760/TAKEUMA_2D/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2752760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Whoever can climb that tower on TAKEUMA without dismounting once will be blessed with eternal happiness.<br>
A boy on TAKEUMA was about to challenge the five towers, where such a rumor was circulating among the public......<br>
<br>
TAKEUMA 2D is a game in which the player moves a boy on TAKEUMA to climb a tower where various gimmicks lie and take the boy to the top.<br>
The controls are very simple, but the boy is on stilts and cannot stop, so climbing the tower may not be easy.<br>
Each of the five odd-looking towers has a different gimmick, and will repeatedly knock you and the boy down as you try to climb to the top.<br>
If you manage to climb all five towers without giving up, what lies ahead?<br/>
You will have to see for yourself how it ends.<br/>
There will be something there that you will not be able to see unless you complete the game yourself.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChildStory</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469260/ChildStory/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Sonya and the Album</strong></h2>Every month, the girl Sonya comes to the polar town of Albom to eat the Moon again and continue the cycle.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469260/extras/cottown2.gif?t=1705651191"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469260/extras/orn.png?t=1705651191"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Compose!</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The main character of the game is a small but resourceful adventurer! Sonya will find a way out of any situation. Using improvised tools and objects, make your way through an unfriendly and cold world.<br/></li><li>Make friends with charming characters in the Album city and taste cotton candy! Who knows, maybe you'll become best friends?<br/></li><li>Sonya, like all people, doubts what she is doing. What will she learn from this special cycle that the PLAYER will help her create?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469260/extras/social.gif?t=1705651191"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight!</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Challenge the ancient spirits and monsters of the Album to test your strength!<br/></li><li>Boss battles are made in the genre of the good old bullet hell! We'll have to destroy the SPACE BAR!<br/></li><li>Keep an eye on your health points, have a snack on time, and remember to be safe when working with resin!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469260/extras/fight1.gif?t=1705651191"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Solve it!</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Solve the riddles of Nora, the grumpy witch who rolls out her moon circle every month.<br/></li><li>Explore a mysterious fantasy world. You can find unique areas and you can meet cute creatures there. Interact with various characters, help them find the meaning of life. Or destroy everything they hold dear.<br/></li><li>The New Star Festival will be held in the city soon. Become a part of it, plunging into an unforgettable winter atmosphere.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469260/extras/puzzles__1_.gif?t=1705651191"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grim's Gambit</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748880/Grims_Gambit/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a captivating journey with "Grim's Gambit," an intricately crafted interactive puzzle visual novel that immerses you in the role of our main character named Nox. A character entangled in the disruption of the natural order, now standing trial for their alleged crimes. The storyline takes a daring turn, offering a unique twist to the traditional trial by sentencing Nox to a fate that is both unexpected and hauntingly bizarre. Nox's punishment unfolds in the haunting ambiance of a peculiar coffee shop, situated amidst the desolate realm of the Stygian Keep. Nox wakes with amnesia, gradually piecing together his forgotten past throughout the game. As players guide him through the puzzle visual novel, uncovering dark secrets in the Stygian Keep, the narrative weaves a compelling tale of self-discovery and mystery.<br>
<br>
Chapter 1 Available Now!<br>
<br>
For development and game updates, follow our official Instagram Page: @grimsgambit						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUNGEON: Cradle of hell</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2619790/DUNGEON_Cradle_of_hell/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Immerse yourself in an exciting turn-based Roguelike adventure with RPG elements. Become a hero! Go through all hell, kill the devils and return home!<br/>Will you be able to go all this way without going crazy?<br/>Who knows?!<br/><br/><br/>THERE ARE SCARY MONSTERS WAITING FOR YOU THE EXISTENCE OF WHICH YOU DID NOT EVEN SUSPECT:<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619790/extras/enemy.gif?t=1705645611"><br/><br/><br/>MAGIC THAT EVEN HARRY POTTER HAS NOT HEARD OF:<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619790/extras/magic.gif?t=1705645611"><br/><br/><br/>AND OF COURSE THE LOOT YOU SIMPLY CAN'T COPY WITHOUT:<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619790/extras/loot.gif?t=1705645611"><br/><br/><br/>...AND DON'T SAY I DIDN'T WARN YOU!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2番線 | Nibansen</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2699510/2__Nibansen/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2699510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							If something unusual happens, return to the opposite passage!<br/>A mysterious respect-based escape game from the subway station to the exit "Line 2 | Nibansen"<br/>・There is a bit of mild horror on this train. Please give up your seat to all passengers, including the elderly, those who are uncomfortable with fear, and those who are pregnant or with infants.<br/>・We will soon be arriving at Line 2. The elements of abnormality, escape, puzzle-solving, and mild horror are here for your transfer. The exit is ahead at C7.<br/>・Please be careful where there is a gap between the world and the platform.<br/>【Game Description】<br/>Escape from the endlessly repeating Line 2 of the subway station!<br/>We've created abnormalities with the unique creativity of students! Enjoy!<br/><br/><strong>Please use it without missing any abnormalities</strong><br/><br/><strong>If you find an abnormality, immediately turn back and head towards the opposite exit</strong><br/><br/><strong>If you don't find any abnormalities, just keep going as you are</strong><br/><br/>Exit outside from Exit C7<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2699510/extras/2bansen_store_kotira.png?t=1705646984"><br/><br/>"Line 2" is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese subway stations and places like Exit 8.<br/>【Playtime】<br/>15 minutes to 60 minutes<br/>【Video Distribution Guidelines】<br/><br/>Distribution is allowed without permission for both individuals and corporations.<br/>Monetization is only possible using the features provided by the video distribution site.<br/>It would be appreciated if you include the game's<br/>name in the title of the video or stream and a link to the Steam page in the description or similar.<br/><br/>Furthermore, we take no responsibility for any damages that may occur as a result of distributing videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<br/>【Settings Screen】<br/>You can restart from the settings screen. Additionally, you can adjust window settings, mouse sensitivity, volume, etc. It is advisable for streamers to restart after launching before starting recording.<br/><br/>【Camera Shake】<br/>To prevent motion sickness, the camera is set not to shake.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2699510/extras/nibansen_herohero.png?t=1705646984"><br/><strong>Vehicle Used</strong><br/>Uses vehicles from the popular "Big Ed Line" subway, which recorded a total of 350,000 views on YouTube<br/><br/>Created with a focus on clarity. Please feel free to provide any feedback.<br/><br/>English Translation: ChatGPT						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruins of Majika</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1902640/Ruins_of_Majika/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1902640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Craft and strategically position defenses to safeguard your home against the perils of a hostile environment.<br/>Prepare for the challenge as the world teems with wild beasts and formidable adversaries that emerge under the cover of night.<br/>Are you ready to fortify your defenses and brave the untamed wilderness?<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>Gather vital resources, food &amp; minerals. Embark on an exploration through diverse and unique biomes, <br/>unraveling their secrets as you navigate each distinct landscape</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1902640/extras/SteamGif_01_Gather_Optimize.gif?t=1705644549"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>Build shelter, and craft items then upgrade your weapons, armor, and <br/>other equipment. </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1902640/extras/SteamGif_02_Build_Optimize.gif?t=1705644549"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>Battle your way through the lands and fight to survive.<br/>Some enemies drop rare resource materials that you will need to <br/>upgrade new towers, weapons, &amp; armor.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1902640/extras/SteamGif_03_Snow_Optimize.gif?t=1705644549"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1902640/extras/SteamGif_04_Desert_Optimize.gif?t=1705644549"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1902640/extras/SteamGif_03_Beach_Optimize.gif?t=1705644549"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>Immerse yourself in the thrilling adventure of survival, honing your skills to protect your haven from relentless threats that lurk in the shadows.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1902640/extras/SteamGif_06_Night01_Optimize.gif?t=1705644549"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1902640/extras/SteamGif_06_Night02_Optimize.gif?t=1705644549"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>Keep your defenses up and protect your territory.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1902640/extras/SteamGif_07_Buildt02_Optimize.gif?t=1705644549"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>If you're not yet strong enough to fight, there is always the option of running,<br/>but keep your stamina in check.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1902640/extras/SteamGif_08_Run_Optimize.gif?t=1705644549"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glory to Ukraine!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2757520/Glory_to_Ukraine/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							On February 24, Russia invaded Ukraine. Your task is kill the invaders. Use any available weapons: knive and axe, machine gun and grenades. Be careful, the enemy is crafty and merciless. The fate of Ukraine depends on you.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Frantic Arcade-Style Action.<br/></li><li>Historical references.<br/></li><li>Autosave on level changing.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher of prophecy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2747620/Teacher_of_prophecy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2747620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a very interesting simulation business game. <br>
How can one transform from a novice chef to a top chef at a Michelin restaurant? <br>
As a store owner, you need to entertain every customer and create delicious dishes for players based on their needs. Different customers have different taboos. Use the freshest game ingredients to ensure quality and safety issues. <br>
Use various props and equipment to create more delicious food and receive gold coins as rewards. Even when running a restaurant alone, it is necessary to prepare ingredients in an orderly manner, receive customers, and provide the best service to entertain customers, creating delicious food full of love. Come and keep learning, grow into a top chef who is crazy about food!						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apex Heroines</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2464800/Apex_Heroines/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2464800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2464800/extras/标题1-英文.png?t=1705629689"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2464800/extras/描述区Gif.gif?t=1705629689"><br/>Enjoy limitless dodging, infinite sprinting, zero cooldowns on abilities, and instant enemy eliminations. Controls are user-friendly, making it easy for beginners. Yet, higher levels demand skilled tactics and strategies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2464800/extras/标题2-英文.png?t=1705629689"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2464800/extras/角色操作2.png?t=1705629689"><br/>Initially, you'll control just one heroine. But as you advance to the game's second phase, you'll gain the freedom to choose from six unique characters at no extra cost. Each character boasts distinctive traits and entirely different combat styles, offering a fresh gameplay experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2464800/extras/标题3-英文.png?t=1705629689"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2464800/extras/武器.png?t=1705629689"><br/>Your main heroine can wield five different types of weapons, each offering a unique combat style and feel. Throughout the game, you'll encounter weapon-switching stations where you can change your weapon for free. If you find yourself struggling, a simple weapon swap could turn the tide of battle.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2464800/extras/标题4-英文.png?t=1705629689"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2464800/extras/关卡.png?t=1705629689"><br/>Face off against dozens of enemies and bosses, each with their own unique combat mechanics, making every level a rich and varied challenge. Some levels demand high levels of skill, while others require strategic thinking. But no matter the challenge, you'll always find a way to triumph—it's all up to you!<br/><br/><strong>In the Ghost Zone Where Humans Dare Not Tread</strong><br/>Signals of metahuman activity have been detected. You'll step into the shoes of a rookie member of the Metahuman Watch, joining forces with five teammates to venture into this enigmatic realm. Your mission? To fight fire with fire and unravel the dark secrets lurking behind the scenes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stay</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2539440/Stay/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2539440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Stay" follows the experience of a motel maid, Cas, as she becomes entangled in a twisted tale of obsession, love, and terror. Unbeknownst to her, a deranged stalker harbors a dangerous infatuation with Cas, leading to a series of threatening letters and a deadly game of survival.<br/><br/>Throughout the game, the player receives letters that reveal her stalker's twisted perception of affection and his increasing desperation to possess Cas.<br/><br/>Letters written to Cas by her stalker include disturbing messages written to real women, collected by the developer through multiple surveys. As such, the content in the game may be disturbing to read and experience. Those who are triggered by mentions of assault should not play.<br/><br/>"Stay" aims to simulate a PSX survival horror game, utilizing stationary 3rd person cameras and tank controls (the way it's meant to be played) and is intended to be played with a controller. The option to play with a dynamic camera exists, but should be a last resort. <br/><br/>You can stealth and hide through it, or collect weapons to fight back, it's up to you. Exploration influences multiple endings.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Clearly outlined objectives<br/></li><li>Low poly PSX stylized graphics<br/></li><li>Third person stationary cameras (optional, but recommended)<br/></li><li>Tank controls (optional, but recommended) <br/></li><li>Gore<br/></li><li>Survival and stealth elements<br/></li><li>4 different ending possibilities, based on how you play</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knights of Grayfang</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2670370/Knights_of_Grayfang/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2670370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The land of Eldraad is in the midst of a war between the humans, born from the Twilight Deity, and the monsters, born from the Nightfall Deity, to control all nine temples. King Edwahl wields twilight's might, turning humans into vampires via a ritual. Yet, a sinister force awakens among monsters. Will nightfall or twilight triumph?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2670370/extras/002.gif?t=1705622820"><br/><br/>One of the main characters, Thoma, wields a unique Blood Gauge, replacing HP and MP. Using this gauge, characters can activate Bloodthirst, granting new skills and appearances. Equip bats found in dungeons for passive effects like protection from ailments and boosted attack power. Seize victory by claiming all nine temples. Unravel the mysteries and battle the monsters within to conquer them!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2670370/extras/003.gif?t=1705622820"><br/><br/>Features<br/>- Unleash Bloodthirst skills in turn-based battles<br/>- Equip mystical bats for tactical advantage<br/>- Shape destiny with unique Blood Gauge<br/>- Conquer Temples for ultimate victory<br/>- Discover power hidden in dungeons<br/>- Master the art of vampire supremacy<br/>- Unravel mysteries, vanquish monsters<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2670370/extras/001.gif?t=1705622820"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle for Desert City</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2752490/Battle_for_Desert_City/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2752490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Pff, I played 100 Turn-Based Tactics, they EASY! Right?</strong>! </h2><br/>    Your City is under siege and your status is:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>4 Soldiers against 2 dozen Tanks<br/></li><li>All units have 5 movement points each turn<br/></li><li>All units have 1 action points in each turn</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>You must destroy all Tanks and save at least 1 Soldier</li></ul><br/>   You can hear enemy Tanks moving, but you can not see them afar due to no electricity, no light, night time, dust storm. It feels like there is no hope. When you finally able to see enemy Tank near you, make both plan A - attack and plan B - back to save zones. You can hide behind buildings, destroyed Tanks, just know that Tank has same line of sight as your Soldiers. Remember, this is your City, you must take last stand, you must save your citizens.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>You sure you can pass level 1 difficulty?</strong></h2><br/>Level 1 Difficulty - IQ 80<br/>Level 1 Difficulty - IQ 100<br/>Level 1 Difficulty  - IQ 120<br/><br/>Game tested by professional Chess player - Failed at level 2, and TBS/TBT player at level 1 when tried for the first time. Challenge begins. No cheating, be honest with yourself.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Technical marvel</strong></h2><br/>    Battle for Desert City supports both latest <u>DLSS 3.5</u> and <u>FSR 3.0</u> with <u>Frame Generation</u>. Game also offers ability to run compact <u>720p</u>, competitive <u>1080p</u>, best cost-value <u>1440p</u> and high-end display setups with <u>4K</u> resolution with 5 scalable visual settings.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2752490/extras/example.gif?t=1705621778"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>P.S.</strong></h2><br/> <i>Game was fully developed and published by single person from Kazakhstan, hopefully together, with your support, suggestions we will make this game even better, we will get further contents such as new game modes, maps, Multiplayer and more coming up features. Thank your for you support!</i> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Thug's Ascension</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391950/A_Thugs_Ascension/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391950/extras/1.jpg?t=1705619608"><br/><br/>Step into the dying metropolis of Maratha as the feared mercenary ‘Chief', and join a gang of outlaws in the war against billionaire industrialist Dr. Sarkar and his violent attempts to rebuild the nation's greatest city in his own image. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391950/extras/2.jpg?t=1705619608"><br/><br/>This is a dark, grounded, character-driven crime drama, exploring the dreams, chaos, and mental turmoil of two broken men with clashing ideologies, brought up on opposite sides of the great bridge. It's the story of what it means for them to find the human inside them once again, and as painful as it may be, rediscover who they once were.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391950/extras/3.jpg?t=1705619608"><br/><br/>In this epic four-hour-long campaign combining intense first-person shooter gameplay with deeply emotional storytelling, you explore, shoot, drive, and wreck your way through the slow-paced, dialogue-driven story delivered through the 47,000-word-long screenplay penned by writer-director Adi Chandra.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haikuna</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2493430/Haikuna/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2493430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Haikuna is a word search game set inside <i>The Wonderful Wizard of Oz</i>, J<i>ourney to the Center of the Earth</i>, and <i>Don Quixote</i>. Players teleport around these stories to find the words to haiku written during the Nanboku-chō, Edo, Genroku, and Meji periods of Japan*.<br/><br/>Click <strong>yōkai</strong> to reveal the words they hide.<br/><br/>Click <strong>words</strong> to either:<br/><br/> <strong>Fly</strong> to that word <strong>OR</strong><br/> <strong>Teleport</strong> through that word (haiku word)<br/><br/>Clicking a word can reveal a <i>hidden</i> yōkai. Hidden yōkai once revealed will create temporal distortions or present other obstacles that inhibit game play. As you complete more levels, they become more likely to show up, but the problems they create can be canceled out or mitigated with the right magic.<br/><br/>Find all the words for all 14 haiku to win the game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escape From Inferno</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2726470/Escape_From_Inferno/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A angel named Lordrid is flying through her cloudy paradise, until she is kidnapped by a bunch of demons and sent to the bottom of Hell. Hoping to fight against the nefarious creatures, she finds a lost bow from the withered corpse of a former soldier. Combined with her ability to spawn arrows of light from thin air, Lordrid slays her fiends through distanced combat, while flying upward towards her home. Lordrid must rely on her impeccable archery skills in an effort to survive the gauntlets of demons awaiting her and escape Inferno.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belonging</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2081580/Belonging/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2081580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Belonging is a first-person adventure game about a cult and its victims. As the hacktivist Jayce, you are scouting the abandoned estate of the Entelechism cult. You are there to find data you can leak to the public and uncover uncomfortable truths about what happened to the people that lived there.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2081580/extras/para_img1.png?t=1705604633"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the remains of a reclusive community</h2>Entelechism is a community devoted to self-optimization. Its members spend their days pursuing perfection in all aspects of life. A cause that seems innocent or even worthwhile on the surface, reveals its dark sides when manipulative actors take control. What other secrets are the Entelechism leaders hiding?<br/><br/>Inspired by real-life cult survivor stories this game makes sure the player understands how human it is to fall for the narrative cults peddle. The story builds empathy for people we might think are lost or worse irredeemable.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2081580/extras/para_img2.png?t=1705604633"><br/><br/>Collect and decide what data should be leaked to the public while unlocking every door inside the cult estate to reveal what suddenly made the cult disappear.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Laid-back story: explore at your own pace<br/></li><li> Find out Jayce's personal connection to Entelechism<br/></li><li> Explore an abandoned estate of the Entelechism cult, a twisted paradise for a reclusive community<br/></li><li> Unlock different areas of the estate to unveil every mystery<br/></li><li> Collect data that reveals secrets about the cult<br/></li><li> Decode and watch video recordings of the final days of the elusive group<br/></li><li> Get to know complex and layered characters and their reasons for joining Entelechism<br/></li><li> Decide whose story matters by choosing which information you reveal to the public</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2081580/extras/para_img3.png?t=1705604633"><h2 class="bb_tag">You decide who matters</h2>Jayce is the first one on the scene after the Entelechists have mysteriously vanished. As you scour the secret island estate for pieces of information, you will uncover more and more about the final days before everyone disappeared. Browse video recordings for evidence and vital details on dramatic incidents. You decide what information will be leaked to the public and who will ultimately be responsible for what has transpired inside Entelechism.<h2 class="bb_tag">Supported by</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Film- und Medienstiftung NRW<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2081580/extras/FS_Logo_2zeilig_rot_360x100.jpg?t=1705604633"><br/></img></li><li> Federal Ministry for Economic Affairs and Climate Action<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2081580/extras/BMWK_Logo_mit_Foerderzusatz_en_146x150.png?t=1705604633"/></li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Forgotten Cabin!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517970/The_Forgotten_Cabin/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							dense forest. The setting is initially calm, but as time progresses, strange and perhaps supernatural events begin to unfold around you. The game is designed to be a brief, yet intense experience, lasting about 10 minutes.<br>
<br>
Your main objective in the game is to witness these mysterious events, which are scripted and occur in real-time as you explore the house. These events are designed to build tension and a sense of unease, immersing you in the game's eerie atmosphere.<br>
<br>
After witnessing these events, your task shifts to finding a key. This key is crucial for your escape from the house and the unsettling occurrences within it. The search for the key involves exploring the house, which, despite its small size, holds many secrets and hiding places.<br>
<br>
The game's short duration ensures a compact and intense experience, with a focus on atmospheric storytelling and suspense. The challenge lies in quickly uncovering the key's location while navigating the increasingly tense environment created by the unfolding events.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, this game offers a unique blend of observational horror and puzzle-solving, all set within a hauntingly isolated forest setting.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Unusual Cadence</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748660/An_Unusual_Cadence/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join Airia, a Bard from a small town, on a huge quest to save the World.<br>
The Legendary Instruments were stolen; Can she get them back? She can...with help. Grab your...Flute and get going! <br>
<br>
The story takes place on the planet of Pangaea where you'll travel from a small bardic farm town to a power plant (filled with robots!), to the lava world called Styx beneath the surface. Travel between 2 world maps using your airship and take down The Opus Quintet before they unlock the secrets of the instruments!<br>
<br>
With a throwback to classic turn-based RPGs, you adventure along picking up allies along the way. Topping out at 16 recruitable characters, you'll have to manage a roster of characters each with unique passive traits and a unique selection of skills. Packed full of gear and skills, this game offers deep customization and a character class system designed to put you in control.						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crumbling</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1701870/Crumbling/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1701870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1701870/extras/TitleBanner_600px.png?t=1705600809"><br/><br/>Crumbling is a VR rogue-like action adventure. Taking control of a Crumbling, a cute little action figure, you fight plastic monsters that are minions of the evil Böse Corp. As you progress from one meticulously crafted diorama to the next your Crumbling grows ever stronger!<br/>Talk to the devs on <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fk3PPEQ54W6" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Discord</a><br/>----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------<h2 class="bb_tag">Action-Figure VR</h2><table><tr><td>In Crumbling, you control your character directly with your motion controller, as if it was an action figure in your hand. Unwrap your hero from its blister pack, wave it around and smash monsters with powerful attacks!<br/><br/>But observe your foes closely! Only if you anticipate their every move can you avoid their assault. Evade and counter at just the right moment to keep the upper hand in action-packed hack'n'slash combat.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1701870/extras/Crumbling_04.gif?t=1705600809"><h2 class="bb_tag">Comics</h2>Discover the story of Crumbling through animated and narrated comic books. Learn how the evil Böse Corp. stole all the magic from Mr. and Mrs Crumble in order to make their horrible monster toys come alive. Can you stop them and reclaim the magic? The fate of the Crumble's famous store is in your hands - quite literally!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1701870/extras/ReadingComic.gif?t=1705600809"><h2 class="bb_tag">Unlock Content</h2>Reclaim the stolen magic and use it to revive all kinds of toys: New Crumblings, more theme worlds, comic pages, and collectible power ups! Discover the lovingly created toy worlds of Mr. and Mrs Crumble and enjoy all the details. Between the glass covers and the cardboard backdrops you set the stage and put the monsters of Böse Corp. in their place!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1701870/extras/Crumbling_03.gif?t=1705600809"/></img></img></td></tr></table> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulletstorm VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2451320/Bulletstorm_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bulletstorm VR is a brutal first-person shooter that puts you in the ass-kicking boots of the hotheaded space mercenary Grayson Hunt. Get the hands-on creative carnage experience with classic, fast-paced gunplay and devastating melee combos powered by fully redesigned controls for Virtual Reality.<br/><br/>As an exiled member of the elite assassin group Dead Echo, blinded by a thirst for vengeance, Grayson gets stranded in the hostile world of Stygia, where he has to confront the ex-commander who betrayed him.<h2 class="bb_tag">EXCLUSIVE TRISHKA CONTENT</h2>For the first time, lace up your badass mercenary babe boots as the legendary Trishka Novak exclusively in Bulletstorm VR. Dual-wield your new Energy Blade weapons to carve your way through mutated hordes in 2 brand-new levels.<h2 class="bb_tag">UNLEASH CREATIVE CARNAGE</h2>Use power kicks, slides, charged shots, explosives, and your environment to execute a symphony of Skillshots. Aim for maximum carnage combos to ramp your rewards and unlock new weapons, charge shots, and ammo capacity.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451320/extras/Thunder_Sept2023_Steam_Firepower.gif?t=1705600648"><h2 class="bb_tag">FIREPOWER AT YOUR FINGERTIPS</h2>Take the iconic Energy Leash and the entire Bulletstorm arsenal of weapons to the next level with exclusive dual-wielding in VR! See an enemy out of reach? Pull them in closer to admire the barrel of your gun or fling them into oncoming bullets for some not-so-friendly fire.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451320/extras/Thunder_Sept2023_Steam_DestroyEverything.gif?t=1705600648"><h2 class="bb_tag">DESTROY ANYTHING AND EVERYTHING</h2>Battle your way through hordes of Stygia's mutated inhabitants! Gun down everything in your path, from crazy raiders to colossal skyscraper-sized beasts, as you cut a swathe of destruction through badlands, urban ruins, and terror domes.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fling to the Finish</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1054430/Fling_to_the_Finish/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/header_alt_assets_8.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/smallMontage.gif?t=1705601037"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_WhatIsIt.png?t=1705601037"><br/>In Fling to the Finish, teams of two players race through colorful, chaotic obstacle courses while tethered by a stretchy elastic rope. <br/><br/>When you and your friends first pick up the game your rope will get tangled in practically everything you pass. But as you quickly improve your communication skills you'll learn that the rope is your biggest asset. <br/><br/>Experienced players can use the rope to swing around perilous obstacles, and fling their partner up ledges before they fall to their doom. When partners master using their rope, they're capable of acrobatic feats unachievable in any other platformer!<br/><br/>Teams can show off their skills by competing in online or local races with a bunch of other players!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_WaysToPlay.png?t=1705601037"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/ways2play.png?t=1705601037"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_Courses.png?t=1705601037"><br/><br/>Every course in Fling to the Finish has a unique theme and style. Race through floating parks, giant casinos, and even worm filled asteroid fields to reach the finish line! We designed every obstacle to force you to use the rope in a new way, so every second is filled with new surprises and memorable moments. The race track even evolves to challenge you as you play, so every race is a nail biter. You'll never know what weird obstacle you'll find next. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Fling_Golf.gif?t=1705601037"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_Attacks.png?t=1705601037"><br/><br/>Opponents battle back with hails of plungers, sinking weights, and evil lasers if they fall behind. Our items keep the races interesting, and help even the score if one player has more experience than another.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/NAdC5A8_-_Imgur.gif?t=1705601037"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_Characters.png?t=1705601037"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/smallerCharRotate.gif?t=1705601037"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_ShareController.png?t=1705601037"><br/>Because you're literally attached to your partner, Fling to the Finish is a truly cooperative experience. If you want, you can even play through Fling to the Finish by sharing a controller with your partner. <br/><br/>This control scheme is great for local co-op, and adds an extra dimension to the game. While you push and pull each other in game, try not to do the same in real life!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/optimizedShareGif.gif?t=1705601037"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fling to the Finish</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1054430/Fling_to_the_Finish/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/header_alt_assets_8.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/smallMontage.gif?t=1705601037"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_WhatIsIt.png?t=1705601037"><br/>In Fling to the Finish, teams of two players race through colorful, chaotic obstacle courses while tethered by a stretchy elastic rope. <br/><br/>When you and your friends first pick up the game your rope will get tangled in practically everything you pass. But as you quickly improve your communication skills you'll learn that the rope is your biggest asset. <br/><br/>Experienced players can use the rope to swing around perilous obstacles, and fling their partner up ledges before they fall to their doom. When partners master using their rope, they're capable of acrobatic feats unachievable in any other platformer!<br/><br/>Teams can show off their skills by competing in online or local races with a bunch of other players!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_WaysToPlay.png?t=1705601037"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/ways2play.png?t=1705601037"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_Courses.png?t=1705601037"><br/><br/>Every course in Fling to the Finish has a unique theme and style. Race through floating parks, giant casinos, and even worm filled asteroid fields to reach the finish line! We designed every obstacle to force you to use the rope in a new way, so every second is filled with new surprises and memorable moments. The race track even evolves to challenge you as you play, so every race is a nail biter. You'll never know what weird obstacle you'll find next. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Fling_Golf.gif?t=1705601037"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_Attacks.png?t=1705601037"><br/><br/>Opponents battle back with hails of plungers, sinking weights, and evil lasers if they fall behind. Our items keep the races interesting, and help even the score if one player has more experience than another.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/NAdC5A8_-_Imgur.gif?t=1705601037"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_Characters.png?t=1705601037"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/smallerCharRotate.gif?t=1705601037"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_ShareController.png?t=1705601037"><br/>Because you're literally attached to your partner, Fling to the Finish is a truly cooperative experience. If you want, you can even play through Fling to the Finish by sharing a controller with your partner. <br/><br/>This control scheme is great for local co-op, and adds an extra dimension to the game. While you push and pull each other in game, try not to do the same in real life!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/optimizedShareGif.gif?t=1705601037"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane Accident: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2104670/Plane_Accident_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2104670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1682340/Plane_Accident/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1682340/Plane_Accident/</a><br/><br/>Wield advanced investigative tools and immerse yourself in the intricacies of aviation disasters in 'Plane Accident: Prologue,' as you decipher the enigma of a plane crash using cutting-edge techniques and expert analysis.<br/><br/>Your task will be <strong>to get to the site of the plane crash</strong>. With the help of <br/>such tools as a <strong>drone</strong> find the likely location of the plane wreckage<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2104670/extras/8v2.gif?t=1705632905"><br/><br/>and <strong>Investigate the crash site</strong>,<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2104670/extras/9v2.gif?t=1705632905"><br/><br/>You will have to mark the area of the accident, <strong>find evidence</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2104670/extras/7v2.gif?t=1705632905"><br/><br/>and take photos so that the entire plane wreckage is finally transported to<br/>the hangar. Transporting the plane wreckage is only the beginning of your<br/>investigation. To get to the causes of the crash you will have to<br/><strong>reconstruct the wreckage of the plane</strong>,<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2104670/extras/2v2.gif?t=1705632905"><br/><br/>send parts for analysis or <strong>examine the black box</strong>.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2104670/extras/1_v2.gif?t=1705632905"><br/><br/>An integral part of any investigation is <strong>questioning witnesses</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2104670/extras/5v2.gif?t=1705632905"><br/><br/>and gathering all the clues to work out <strong>the true scenario</strong>of the cause<br/> of the crash.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2104670/extras/6v2.gif?t=1705632905"><br/><br/>Experience a tantalizing glimpse of the aviation mystery world in Plane Accident: Prologue.<br/>But remember, what you see here is just the tip of the iceberg. Dive deeper into the full game to uncover a universe of secrets waiting to be revealed.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising Lords</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/835650/Rising_Lords/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/835650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/835650/extras/divider.png?t=1705660739"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/835650/extras/wishlist.png?t=1705660739"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/835650/extras/header.jpg?t=1705660739"><br/><strong>Rising Lords</strong> is a <strong>medieval turn-based strategy game</strong> with card and board game elements. Send your serfs to fight and die in your name... or let them prosper, and use them to your advantage!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/835650/extras/_RULE.png?t=1705660739"><br/><strong>Collect taxes and resources.</strong> Dictate rations and field work. Forge weapons, raise armies, and <strong>build mighty fortified cities</strong>. Help your people become knights, or dump them on a battlefield far away, but be careful: even the most humble peasants will revolt eventually and an unlucky event card can change the fate of your realm quickly...<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/835650/extras/_SCHEME.png?t=1705660739"><br/><strong>Be ready to expand your realm or defend your provinces!</strong> Relationships with other Lords are a fickle thing and you will find yourself on the battlefield sooner or later. Raise a well-rounded army, give yourself an edge through a <strong>card-based skill system</strong> and engage your enemies in mortal combat in <strong>highly tactical, grid- and turn-based encounters</strong>!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/835650/extras/_CONQUER.png?t=1705660739"><br/><strong>In addition to its campaign mode, Rising Lords features robust multiplayer functionality.</strong> Play a quick game, or settle in for an evening or more. Play mind games with your friends with <strong>Rising Lords</strong>’ special figures and spread false infos. Let them pay for their insolence in questioning your right to rule!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Expand your realm</strong> - Juggle production, resource gathering, construction, diplomacy and treason, tax and rations - all vital in the success of your provinces<br/></li><li><strong>Deep tactics</strong> - Use counters to troop types, morale, terrain and cards to get the upper hand even against seemingly impossible odds<br/></li><li><strong>Prove yourself</strong> - Make use of a variety of unique figures to gain an advantage, and triumph in special game modes such as Challenge Island and Invasion<br/></li><li><strong>Up to 4-player simultaneous multiplayer</strong> - No need to wait for each individual player to take their turn<br/></li><li><strong>Customisation</strong> - Tailor your leader’s look and skills, and craft your perfect cities and troops<br/></li><li><strong>Modding support</strong> - Create your own maps and story missions for Scenario Mode and share them using <strong>Steam Workshop</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/835650/extras/divider_inverted.png?t=1705660739"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holidays in Khrushchevsk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398630/Holidays_in_Khrushchevsk/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i>Ordinary story<br/>It’s a usual story that takes place in our time in Russia. Sasha came to Khrushchevsk town to visit his granny, whom he had not seen for a long time. He used to spend all his summers in this town when he was a little boy and knew all the children in the play yard and even  neighbours. Sasha’s granny had recently felt worser, so he decided to visit her. He should figure out is it a real disease or something else…</i></strong><br/><br/><strong>Holidays in Khrushchevsk </strong> is a psychological horror game in the genre of "walking simulator"<br/>Average game completion time: 50 minutes<br/><br/><br/><u><strong>Holidays in Khrushchevsk</strong></u> is a game that will be familiar to everyone who grew up in Russia and the CIS. The developer tried to make the atmosphere of the past and to reveal some problems that exist at the moment. The story took place last summer.<br/><br/><br/><strong>IMPORTANT NOTE</strong>: <br/>The main emphasis of the game is on the process of exploration, as the tension slowly builds up, creating an even more complete and vivid effect of presence.<br/><br/><strong>DESCRIPTION OF CONTENT FOR ADULTS</strong><br/>The developer describes the content like this:<br/>The game contains scenes of violence that can cause negative impact on the psyche. The game also contains scenes of alcohol or drugs, as well as elements that may not be suitable for people of a certain age. A reasonable restriction of the audience of the game is recommended.<br/><br/><i><u>Game Features:</u></i><br/>- The main genre of the game is "Walking Simulator";<br/>- The gameplay is close to realism.<br/>- You will need to study carefully the environment to complete the game<br/>- It’s better to read all notes and assignments to understand the plot						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
