<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>FINAL FANTASY VII EVER CRISIS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2484110/FINAL_FANTASY_VII_EVER_CRISIS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484110/extras/Gif_SEJ_Sample_01_-_deliverable.gif?t=1701917926"><br/><br/>Relive the most memorable moments from FFVII and experience the journey of a young hero Sephiroth in FINAL FANTASY VII EVER CRISIS, making its debut on Steam.<br/>Experience both classic and new stories within the FFVII universe presented in a retro-style look combined with modern, beautifully rendered graphics. Team up your favorite characters and customize each one with iconic gear and weapons to defeat powerful opponents in Solo or Co-op battle mode.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484110/extras/Gif_SEJ_Sample_02_-_deliverable.gif?t=1701917926"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">◆ EXPERIENCE NEW AND ORIGINAL STORIES FROM THE FINAL FANTASY VII UNIVERSE</h2></strong><br/>Discover the never-before told story of a young hero, Sephiroth.<br/><br/>Encounter new characters along the way and play as iconic heroes, such as Cloud and Zack, in the epic storylines of the original FINAL FANTASY VII and CRISIS CORE -FINAL FANTASY VII- in episodic installments.<br/><br/>FINAL FANTASY VII: The story of Cloud Strife, an elite SOLDIER operative turned mercenary. Cloud lends his aid to an anti-Shinra organization: Avalanche, unaware of the epic consequences that await him. Once more begins a story that will shape the destiny of the entire world.<br/><br/>CRISIS CORE -FINAL FANTASY VII- : The story of Zack Fair, a promising young operative in the Shinra military’s elite unit, SOLDIER. The story takes place seven years before the events of FFVII. Follow the tale of Zack’s dreams and honor – and the legacy that connects him to Cloud.<br/><br/>The action unfolds through the characters in a modern-stylized polygon look, inspired by the original FFVII. Even those experiencing FFVII for the first time can enjoy this expansive world in this epic saga that defined RPGs for gamers throughout the world!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484110/extras/Gif_SEJ_Sample_03_-_deliverable.gif?t=1701917926"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">◆ EVOLVED GAME SYSTEM AND FAST-PACED COMMAND-BASED BATTLE</h2></strong><br/>Immerse yourself in beautifully rendered, fast-paced command-based battle evolved from FFVII’s Active Time Battle. The battles give spotlight to classic FINAL FANTASY RPG elements such as, Abilities, Materia, Summons, and heart-pumping Limit Breaks, while supporting additional features such as Auto Mode and Battle Speed that make the game even more enjoyable to play.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484110/extras/Gif_SEJ_Sample_04_-_deliverable.gif?t=1701917926"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">◆ BUILD AND CUSTOMIZE THE ULTIMATE PARTY</h2></strong><br/>Form a party of your favorite characters from FFVII series titles, such as Cloud, Tifa, Aerith, Zack and more! Dress them with new gear unique to FINAL FANTASY VII EVER CRISIS.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484110/extras/Gif_SEJ_Sample_05_-_deliverable.gif?t=1701917926"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>◆ WORK TOGETHER WITH FRIENDS in CO-OP BATTLE</strong></h2>Lead your group of friends from around the world with up-to 3 member Co-op battle to defeat powerful bosses together!<br/><br/>Follow the official #FF7EC Pages:<br/>Website: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fen.ffviiec.com%2F" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://en.ffviiec.com/</a><br/>X: <a href="https://twitter.com/FFVII_EC_EN" rel="" target="_blank">https://twitter.com/FFVII_EC_EN</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III - BlackCell (Season 1)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2596440/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III__BlackCell_Season_1/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2596440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Get Call of Duty® Points* and in-game content for Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III and Call of Duty®: Warzone™.<br>
<br>
Offering includes:<br>
<br/>
- Battle Pass for Season 1<br/>
- 20 Battle Token Tier Skips<br/>
<br/>
Exclusive BlackCell Sector on the Battle Map:<br/>
<br/>
- 1100 Call of Duty® Points<br/>
- BlackCell Operator<br/>
- Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Finishing Move<br/>
- BlackCell Vehicle Skin<br/>
<br/>
- BlackCell Bonus Topper with 10 additional Operator skin alternatives and 6 Weapon Blueprints with Tracers.<br/>
<br/>
Activision may update, replace, or remove this in-game content at any time.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Born of Bread</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1555140/Born_of_Bread/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Beings from another age are causing havoc across the land! And with their mischief comes a great threat to everyone. The unlikeliest hero, a golem born of bread, will find himself and his newfound buddies in the middle of a drama that's thousands of years in the making. Together, they will visit incredible locals and meet fascinating characters. Although he may not look like much, Loaf might be the hero this land kneads.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Sentient Bread on a Quest</h2><br/>Play as a flour golem who possesses a never-ending childlike wonder and a set of odd abilities in this 2.5D adventure game!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Cinematic_opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/>Explore the different regions of a wonderful world ripe with mysteries and team up with a colorful cast of fleshed-out characters. With the help of your buddies, face off against menacing and weird baddies and engage in a fun and quirky turn-based combat system.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Enviro_opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/><strong>A home-cooked battle system</strong><br/>Born of Bread puts a twist on turn-based combat tropes with a fun interaction system that will test your reflexes.<br/>This interactive system also features a weaknesss and resistance system that makes battles more strategic.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Combat_Opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/><strong>Team up with your buddies</strong><br/>Loaf can't do it alone. Meet new characters during your adventure, each with their own abilities and personnality. Use their unique skills to overcome threats and obstacles whether in fights or when exploring.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Buddies_opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/><strong>Stream your fights to a fake audience!</strong><br/>Your dragon buddy Dub will let you save your progression but also stream your fights to a fake audience with his little laptop! Gather more viewers and answer their demand to get rewards!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>While the Iron's Hot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1906830/While_the_Irons_Hot/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/WTIH_Steam_Banner_Game_Header__1_.png?t=1701795624"><br/><br/>In the faraway land of Ellian, legendary artisans have gathered for ages to perfect their craft. Now it’s your turn to join them.<br/><br/>Step into the boots of a journeyman blacksmith on a quest to become a master in While the Iron’s Hot, a crafty adventure assembled with mystery, wit, and charm. Forge, smelt, and combine works of metal to grow your smithing skills and discover exquisite new items to create. Explore an island filled with resources, treasures, puzzles, and fellow artisans with their own motives and designs. Rebuild the ruins of Ellian’s long-abandoned blacksmiths’ village to restore its former glory and grow your own crafting capabilities—and ultimately become a true master smith.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/Village_Upgrade_Gif_-_640x360.gif?t=1701795624"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/WTIH_Steam_Banner_Features__1_.png?t=1701795624"><br/><br/><strong>Forge, smelt, assemble</strong><br/>Master every step of the smithing process. Smelt ore and metal into ingots, and shape them into useful parts. Grind each piece to perfection, then use your creativity, knowledge, and finely honed observation skills to assemble alloyed works of art.<br/><br/><strong>Smith a solution</strong><br/>In a land of artisans, you can forge your own key to almost any challenge. Repair machinery to open up pathways. Overcome puzzling environmental conundrums. Win over the isle’s most hardened personalities with your crafty smithing wiles.<br/><br/><strong>Unearth a whimsical adventure</strong><br/>The land of Ellian is a bright, even a little mystical, world populated by charismatic and quirky characters. Explore tunnels with puzzles and resources, and embark on a combat-free journey to reforge the links of a world where crafting connects everything.<br/><br/><strong>Discover the island’s secrets</strong><br/>Ellian is a land of creativity cloaked in mystery. Craft the equipment you need to venture out to new regions. Meet villages full of adept alchemists or skilled shipwrights, but take care—not everyone trusts that you have the best interests of Ellian at heart.<br/><br/><strong>Rebuild a legendary smiths’ village</strong><br/>Forge a new home in Stal, a former haven for blacksmiths, now in ruin following a mysterious disaster. Revitalize the village to upgrade your own capabilities, and prove to the artisans of Ellian you’re worthy of becoming a master blacksmith.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/Environment_Gif_-_634x356.gif?t=1701795624"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Highland Song</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1240060/A_Highland_Song/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Works beautifully on Steam Deck!</h2><i>We're still waiting for Valve to officially verify A Highland Song for Steam Deck, but we've designed it from the ground up to work perfectly there. So if that's your preferred platform, you're in for a treat!</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Moira McKinnon is running away.</h2>To reach the sea, Moira must first cross the Scottish Highlands—a wilderness of paths, peaks, shortcuts, dangers, and song.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/waterfall-jump.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Platforming</h2>Climb peaks to orient yourself and plan your next steps. Spelunk caves, scale cliffs, jump from rock to rock and slide down scree slopes as you make your way forward.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/survival.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survival</h2>Wind, rain and cold are your enemies. Moira is no superhero, and the Highlands are not to be underestimated. Shelter to survive.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/ascend-peak-shorter.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Navigation</h2>Collect and position 100 map fragments to discover faster routes. The hills are crisscrossed with paths: some well-trodden, others hidden away.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/narrative.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Narrative</h2>Learn the stories and the secrets of the hills, which are filled with lost things, echoes, and memories.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/music-run-sunrise.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Rhythm runs</h2>Skip and jump through the valleys to the incredible music of TALISK and Fourth Moon. The landscape itself forms itself around the shape of the music.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/branching-paths.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Replay</h2>Get ready to make the journey more than once, because a single trip isn't nearly enough to discover the Highlands' deepest secrets.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/moira-and-deer.png?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">The Story</h2>Moira McKinnon has never seen the sea. <br/><br/>For fifteen years she’s lived with her mum in a small house on the edge of the Scottish Highlands—then one day she receives a letter from her Uncle Hamish urging her to come to the coast. If she can reach his lighthouse in time, a wonderful surprise will be waiting...<br/> <br/>And so, Moira runs away.<br/><br/>The hills are full of secrets and stories, but what you find will depend on where you go. The narrative is not branching but weaving; a mesh of history, mythology and family secrets. What truths will you discover? <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/zoom-to-lighthouse.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">The World</h2>In the Highlands, every peak has a story to tell and every valley echoes with song. Giants sleep, ghosts sing, crows carry messages, and eagles lift the dead. <br/><br/>But the Highlands’ crags are unforgiving and its summits are cold—Moira’s trek will not be easy. <br/><br/>Can you help her find a way across this winding wilderness in time?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/talisk.jpg?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">The Music of the Highlands</h2>A Highland Song’s soundtrack is composed by Laurence Chapman alongside two multi-award-winning giants of the Scottish folk scene, TALISK and Fourth Moon. Royalty of the festival circuit, these two bands combine virtuosic instrumental playing with fast, inventive rhythms, to produce new tunes in traditional styles played with beauty, energy and swagger.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood West</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_steam_text_header.png?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>Weird West legends meet eldritch horror in <strong>BLOOD WEST</strong>, an immersive stealth FPS. Become the Undead Gunslinger, doomed to roam the barren lands until he finds the means to purge their curse and free his soul. No, this isn’t your typical Wild West desperado redemption arc. This is a damnation arc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_episodes_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The Canyons, the Swamp, and the Mountains. Each swarming with abominable monsters and unholy demons, these are open-ended worlds for you to explore freely at your own pace. It will take the player over 20 hours on average to complete all three scenarios, and over 35 if they want to see everything the barren lands have to offer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_stealth_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/><strong>Blood West</strong> is a stealth FPS inspired by the genre classics such as the Thief series (whose fans will be happy to hear the voice of Stephen Russell, the actor voicing the master-thief Garrett, returning here as the protagonist), S.T.A.L.K.E.R. games, or - from the contemporary catalog - Hunt: Showdown. The gameplay rewards the careful approach: scouting the area, stalking your enemies, and striking from the shadows. Can you figure out a way to clear a fort full of ghouls and monsters without raising an alarm?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_horror_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The Barren Lands present the player with a nightmarish, twisted vision of the Wild West legends. The curse that has befallen the realm has corrupted every living thing, defiled the land itself, while summoning restless spirits and dark entities. In this mixture of gunslinger pulp and Lovecraftian horror, dark occult magick presents just as much of a threat as sudden lead poisoning.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_characters_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>In <strong>Blood West</strong> you will meet many colorful, yet strangely twisted, fully-voiced NPCs. Just as much prisoners of the Barren Lands as you are, they will sometimes share their unusual stories and send you on various missions. Play nice and they might reward you or become your allies. Cross them and risk their wrath.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_secrets_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The game won’t hold your hand. You’ll have to explore the land for yourself (buying a map from a vendor might prove useful!), and figure out your own way to approach quests. As you poke around the three expansive maps, keep an eye out for hidden places and secret stashes. There’s gold in the mountains! Fair warning - it’s probably cursed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_brutal_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>If sneaking around isn’t exactly your thing, or you feel that you have a power advantage over your enemies, you can always take the head-on approach and meet your enemies guns blazing. <strong>Blood West</strong> comes from the creators of the fan-favorite boomer shooter <strong>POSTAL: Brain Damaged</strong>, so much gratuitous fantasy violence and pixelated blood splatter is to be expected!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_inventory_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>One man’s hell might be another hoarder’s paradise! From simple one-use items like bandages, through medical tinctures, explosives and incendiaries, straight to arcane artifacts that - once slotted - can change the way you play the game, the Barren Lands are just filled with STUFF. There are tons of useful items to discover, and there’s a special player’s stash crate for all those super-rare potions that you’ll hoard and never use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_weapons_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>A gunslinger without a gun would be just a regular slinger. Where’s the fun in that? <strong>Blood West</strong> makes sure you’ll have plenty of weapons to choose from. Revolvers, rifles, shotguns, carabines - a great variety of firearms, from standard army-issue to those infused with powerful magic, or straight-up possessed. And if you prefer not to cause a ruckus, there’s a wide selection of hand-to-hand combat weapons and archery weapons to pick your favorites from.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_skills_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The RPG-like perk-based progression system in <strong>Blood West</strong> will allow you to highly customize the gameplay experience to your liking. Become a stealthy hunter, a revolver-fanning gunman or a relentless berserker. You will gain experience and progress through the skill tree, while discovering new artifacts in each of the scenarios that will bestow on you additional abilities. Combining skills and load-out creates more possible playstyles than you’d normally be able to explore in one playthrough.<h2 class="bb_tag">Are you ready to take back the frontier from the dark forces of demonic corruption and earn the right to move on to a better world? The Barren Lands call you, Gunslinger!</h2><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley: A Rift in Time</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2632050/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley_A_Rift_in_Time/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Once an ancient kingdom full of treasures and magical artifacts, Eternity Isle has become lost in time as a result of Jafar’s meddling in magic. Journey to this faraway land and utilize a mysterious new Royal Tool—the Hourglass—as you discover new secrets and uncover lost treasures. Stop Jafar’s scheme to steal the Spark of Imagination, an ancient relic that holds the fabric of Dreamlight Valley together. With the help of the Hourglass, you are the key to fixing rifts in time and putting an end to Jafar’s evil plan!<br/><br/><strong>Unravel a Whole New Story on Eternity Isle</strong><br/>Help foil the plans of the nefarious Jafar as you meet new friends and find treasures lost in time in a new story unfolding in three acts. Secrets from Dreamlight Valley’s past can be uncovered using a new Royal Tool, the Hourglass, as you reveal what happened long before the Forgetting…<br/><br/><strong>Discover a New Island </strong><br/>Delve into three new Biomes, each with new areas to explore and make your own. From Ancient’s Landing to the Glittering Dunes and the Wild Tangle, each has a fully customizable layout to decorate with lost treasures and exclusive Disney- and Pixar-inspired furniture.<br/><br/><strong>Spend Time with Four New Villagers</strong><br/>Reunite EVE with WALL·E, help Rapunzel start an art class, take lessons in heroics from Gaston, and decide if you can really trust Jafar. Explore Eternity Isle with your new friends… or move them back to live in Dreamlight Valley!<br/><br/>Play Scramblecoin, a new board game that your Villagers are waiting to play with you.<br/><br/><strong>Wield the Royal Hourglass</strong><br/>Find a new Royal Tool, the Hourglass, and use its magic to find Relics lost in time. Build Ancient Machines to help automate Activities such as gardening and cooking, which makes it easier than ever to run your island. Take your new Hourglass back to Dreamlight Valley and explore the Realms to see what other treasures you can find!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1701702754"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1701702754"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1701702754"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1701865363"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1701865363"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SteamWorld Build</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2134770/SteamWorld_Build/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-Homestead.png?t=1701599791"><br/>One final landrush! The planet is dyin', Astrid, and it's dig or die trying! <br/><br/>That mine under our town is sitting empty, and wouldn't you know there's rumours of ancient tech down there that might help us out of this predicament. Round up the posse, circle the wagons, and let's get to buildin' a new home! Collect resources above ground and ores down below so we can get those wealthy bots in here to help us build bigger, and we can get the heck out of here!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_1.gif?t=1701599791"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_manage.png?t=1701599791"><br/>As your borders expand, new steamfolk will find their way to you! Every bot is crotchety in their own way, and it's up to you to keep them steaming along. Barter to boost efficiency, keep goods flowing to and from the mines and keep everyone happy to make them work their darndest and hardest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_2.gif?t=1701599791"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-DIG-DEEP.png?t=1701599791"><br/><br/>Stare into the abyss long enough and it might just stare back... we're going looking for riches and something down there doesn't want to share! Have gun, dig gravel, and make sure the mines don't collapse upon you as you defend yourselves from the creepy crawlies that lurk within...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_3.gif?t=1701599791"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_features.png?t=1701599791"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break ground on a bustling SteamWorld town, inspired by the Old West.<br/></li><li>Keep your steambots from getting cranky by ensuring their complex needs get met<br/></li><li>Dig deep and spread wide to produce resources to aid your search for ancient technologies<br/></li><li>Defend your mine from the creepy varmints that lurk deep below your town<br/></li><li>Trade resources at the local train stop and welcome special visitors who'll lend a hand<br/></li><li>Five distinct maps littered with secrets for the discerning SteamWorld explorer to find<br/></li><li>Developed from the ground up for both mouse and controller, whichever takes yer fancy.<br/></li><li>Four difficulty levels, including a sandbox difficulty for when you just want to Build!</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HoloParade</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2647230/HoloParade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">A lively parade with hololive VTubers and mascot characters!</h2><br/>"HoloParade" is a fan game of hololive and the first title to serve as a test case for "holo Indie". Collect, nurture, and enjoy watching your favorite characters! It's a 2D tower defense game that offers depth, strategy, and can also be enjoyed casually.<br/><br/>What is "holo Indie"?:<br/>It is a general term for a game brand for derivative work games, produced using the "game creator support program" with the aim of co-creating with fans and creators of hololive Production around the world.<h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 1: Simple Yet Deep, Lively Battles</h2>The basic system is a classic 2D tower defense game where you summon characters from your base and march them forward to destroy the enemy's base to win. While the controls are simple, the gameplay is profoundly deep. With over 65 characters, each possessing a variety of abilities like ally healing support and self-destruct attacks, skillful combination and flexible formation are key to enjoying the game.<br/><br/>Additionally, there's an element inspired by parades called the 'Symphony Effect,' where various effects are activated based on the musical instruments played by the characters in march. This adds further strategic depth to the formation of your parade squad and the order of their summoning.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Battle.gif?t=1701417555"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 2: Comprehensive Development Elements</h2>In addition to leveling up and limit breaking, there is a 'Skill' system that allows you to add special abilities not available through regular development. Since you can add up to three types of skills to each character and select them carefully, you can enjoy a unique development process! Furthermore, since you can reset levels and get a full refund of the coins spent, it allows for more freedom in restructuring formations and character development.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Skill_ENG.gif?t=1701417555"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 3: No Gacha Purchases, No Stamina System</h2>The scout gacha, which allows you to acquire characters, can be used by consuming tickets obtained within the game, with no additional purchases required. Also, as there is no stamina system, you are not bound by time and can play as much as you like, whenever you like.<br/><br/>Moreover, the scout gacha allows you to choose from two randomly selected character candidates, enabling players to make selections based on their strategy or preference rather than leaving it entirely to chance.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Gacha_ENG.gif?t=1701417555"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 4: Take a Break with Various Talents and Mini-Games in the Office</h2>When you return to the office, the home screen, you'll be greeted by newly recorded voice lines from Harusaki Nodoka, a staff member of hololive. In the office, talents from hololive may also make appearances, and you might witness some unexpected interactions.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Home_ENG.png?t=1701417555"><br/><br/>Additionally, mini-games with entirely different gameplay from the main story are implemented. These games allow you to collect coins necessary for character strengthening. At the initial release, a mini-game titled "Hurry Up! Miko-Chi!" is available, where Sakura Miko (a VTuber affiliated with hololive) who overslept, dashes at full speed towards her destination while avoiding obstacles. More mini-games are planned to be added in future updates.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/RunMikoti.gif?t=1701417555"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalypse Party</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2351560/Apocalypse_Party/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">The moment of "Apocalypse" approaches, this time... ...you fight for yourself!</h2><br/><strong>「Apocalypse Party」</strong> is distinct from the former 「Project Zero」<br/>In this installment, you will delve deeper into this long-standing battle, with the story gradually becoming incredible! Time travel? Apocalypse? Saving the world? You will face many more unknown challenges... ...<br/>But it still retains our beloved RogueLike + mowing-down-enemies combo, and you will face this catastrophe online with your friends (of course, you can also face it alone)!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Engaging and Deep Mechanics ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT01_Skills_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/><strong>Talent pool expanded to 450! And most of them are mechanics that can change the course of battle</strong><br/>Additionally, there are:<br/>- Hundreds of distinct ranged and melee weapons!<br/>- A plethora of divine ultimate skills!<br/>- 35 varied hero characters, hundreds of unique hero skills<br/>The richness has increased by <strong>more than 10 times compared to the former installment</strong>! Can you build the strongest combo?<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Supports Multiplayer, shall we join the hunting party tonight? ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT02_MutiplePlayerMode_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>Support <strong>up to 3</strong> multiplayer online! <br/>Massive hordes of zombies, exhilarating mowing-down action, why enjoy it alone?<br/>Imagine the joy of roaming through a sea of zombies with your friends!<br/>Call them, support each other, move forward or retreat together, survive here!<br/><strong>Of course, we kindly remind you, a "friendship-ends" scenario is not excluded :)</strong><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ You crave some real challenge, don't you? ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT04_Boss_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>In this game, you will face the ultimate challenge.<br/><strong>9 highly challenging Bosses!</strong><br/>Only rapid growth can help you withstand the fierce attacks from the Bosses, accept the challenge, defeat them, and show them who’s boss now!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Perhaps we can do some time traveling! ■</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT05_Medivel_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>A brand new storyline takes you into this familiar yet strange world, continuing a tale of redemption amidst time traveling:<br/>The tragic death of loved ones<br/>The desperate nuclear explosion<br/>The eerie rebirth<br/>The deathly quiet town<br/>The dark dungeons<br/>... ...<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ We are continuously focusing on your gameplay experience! ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT03_Combat_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>We have keenly listened to the feedback from the players of our former installment, reworked the combat system of the game, continuously bringing more fluid gaming experiences to players.<br/>-<i>Mix and use combat methods like melee weapons, firearms, spells, summoning, witchcraft... ...</i>! They will bring you a fun experience.<br/>-<i>Drive vehicles, summon planes, dragon flying, use otherworldly ninjutsu, even use the mysterious Dual-vector Foi</i>, and more easter eggs await your exploration.<br/>-This game encourages an online experience, but undoubtedly, the single-player part can still experience all the systems and joy of this game.<br/><br/>Smooth operation (handling) is also an important part we continuously focus on！<br/>We have made the game’s operation &amp; flow experience more user-friendly.<br/><strong>Easy to get started, yet "easy to learn, hard to master"!</strong><br/><br/><strong>"Since the apocalypse is here, join us for the last revelry."</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/Library_Hero_EN.jpg?t=1701678706"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-4 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">4-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with three other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1701703276"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinball M</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2337640/Pinball_M/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-1.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-2.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free<br/>- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage<br/>- Thrilling competition<br/>- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation<h2 class="bb_tag">Sink your teeth into these tables as purchasable DLC: </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">- Chucky's Killer Pinball:</h2> Step into a twisted realm where the innocent becomes sinister, and the playful turns menacing. Navigate through an eerie playfield where Chucky lurks in the shadows, ready to pounce.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Dead by Daylight™️ Pinball:</h2> Become the hunter or even the hunted in a thrilling fusion of classic pinball and the excitement of one of the most popular horror games ever created.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Duke Nukem's Big Shot Pinball:</h2> Enjoy the biggest, grooviest, most BADASS pinball table ever made packed with guns and babes. Push start and play with balls of steel!<h2 class="bb_tag">- The Thing Pinball: </h2>Use your pinball skills and battle against the shape-shifting alien through the arctic chill of U.S. Outpost #31. Can you trust anyone, even yourself?<br/>- Even more coming...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-4.png?t=1701703297"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEVI</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2230650/TEVI/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FZ9KrdFvNRK" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/JoinUsOnDC.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Action-Packed_Combo_System.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/戰鬥動圖.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>The protagonist Tevi is nimble and agile, wielding both her trusty dagger and an oversized wrench for dishing out melee damage in style. Alongside her, companions Celia and Sable manifest as two floating orbitars, ready to unleash a variety of ranged offensive and supportive magic in battle. Adapt your combat style to suit any situation and bring down foes with flashy, dazzling combos!<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Thrilling_Boss_Battles.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Boss.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Every boss fight is a unique challenge requiring different strategies to tackle, all while you dodge their attacks and look for openings to counter-attack. <br/>As bosses change phases, their attack and bullet patterns become increasingly challenging, and they can even unleash devastating ultimates. Continual offense can submit bosses into a vulnerable BREAK state, during which you can deal massive bursts of damage.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Myriad_Abilities,_Equipment,_and_Exploration.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/badge.jpg?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Scattered across the the expansive world, there are over 300 different items and pieces of equipment waiting to be discovered. These items can enhance your abilities or introduce new ones, allowing you to find more methods of navigating the world and finding secrets. A cornucopia of equippable sigils can be freely configured to create builds tailored to your preferences and playstyle.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/A_Rich,_Expansive_Fantasy_World.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/場景6.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Dive into the vibrant world of Az, in which you will discover various towns, regions, peoples, histories, and civilizations, each with their own tale to tell. Along the way, you'll meet a large cast of strange and colorful characters. As their tales unfold and intertwine, you'll be drawn into a tale full of adventure, friendship, mysteries, and danger... <br/><br/>Get ready to embark on an unforgettable adventure, writing your own epic journey alongside Tevi!<br/><br/><a href="https://youtu.be/psxior_WswQ" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/角色介紹.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tevi（VA: Lynn）<br/></li><li>Celia（VA: Yoko Hikasa）<br/></li><li>Sable（VA: Natsumi Fujiwara）<br/></li><li>Zema（VA: Tomokazu Sugita）<br/></li><li>Vena（VA: Rie Kugimiya）</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn back immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Option</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.<br/>If you are easily intoxicated, changing the following settings may help.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera shake】</strong><br/>The camera shakes when you walk or run, but if you set the value to 0.0, the camera will not shake.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Acceleration】</strong><br/>If you set the maximum value to 30.0, the camera will move without delay.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Sensitivity】</strong><br/>If the sensitivity is high, the camera will move significantly when the mouse is moved. <br/>Adjust the value if you find it difficult to operate the camera with the default value of 1.<br/><br/><strong>【Motion Blur】</strong><br/>Afterimages will appear when the camera is moved. Recommended to disable at 30FPS<br/><br/><strong>【Preset】</strong><br/>Set the overall graphic settings.<br/>If you do not have sufficient specs, it is better to set it to "Low" to avoid sickness.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1701853441"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1701853441"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1701853441"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats and Seek</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2672090/Cats_and_Seek/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							😻 100 Cats!<br/>🔍 Hint system<br/>🎨 Choose your favorite color<br/><br/>Let's play hide and seek with 100 cats!<br/>Can you find them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/extras/game_play.gif?t=1701587609"><br/><br/>And if bored with black and white doddles you can choose <strong>your own favorite color</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/extras/change_color.PNG?t=1701587609"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Stars And Time</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1677310/In_Stars_And_Time/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FZzFSRUBXEC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/discordbanner620.gif?t=1701180941"/></a><br/><br/><strong>What would you do if you were forced to relive your failures over and over again?</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam5_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> tells the story of Siffrin and their adventurer friends—a found family bound together by fate in order to end the tyrannical reign of an evil king. But as victory is just within the party’s grasp, a tragedy occurs, the clock resets, and <strong>they have to do it all again</strong>. <br/><br/>As Siffrin’s the only one who notices this loop, each new start wears away at his cheerful veneer, yet he keeps going in hopes he can end this temporal tragedy once and for all.<br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> is a <strong>time-looping RPG adventure</strong>. With each loop, Siffrin gains a new perspective on the world around them, opening up new solutions to puzzles and allowing them to make better choices in conversation. Equip memories as armor, pray to the Change God to improve your team’s capabilities each loop, and challenge deadly foes to Rock, Paper, Scissors as Siffrin seeks the truth.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam4_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Our Adventurers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Siffrin (he/they):</strong> Stressed, depressed, and under duress. (Don’t worry about it. They’re doing fine.) The punmaster protagonist of our neverending tale.<br/></li><li><strong>Mirabelle (she/her):</strong> A caring and nervous housemaiden mysteriously blessed by the god she so ardently follows.<br/></li><li><strong>Isabeau (he/him):</strong> Defender with a heart of gold. Cares dearly for his people and his friends.<br/></li><li><strong>Odile (she/her):</strong> The mature and nonsensical researcher studying…something. (No, she will not tell you what it is.)<br/></li><li><strong>Bonnie (they/them):</strong> Wait a minute, who brought this kid along???</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Save the world through the power of Rock, Paper, Scissors in <strong>strategic turn-based RPG</strong> combat encounters.<br/></li><li>Ignore the limits of time and space to <strong>fix your past mistakes</strong> by repeating the same two days over and over again.<br/></li><li>Equip the <strong>memories you have of your friends</strong> to make your party stronger in combat. <br/></li><li><strong>Watch the fate of this world unfold</strong> as you escape the twists and turns of this endless(???) loop.<br/></li><li>Eat <strong>samossas</strong> with your friends!<br/></li><li>Get heckled by a <strong>cheeky ethereal being of infinite starlight</strong>.<br/></li><li>Pray to a god for good luck in your travels. <strong>You’re gonna need it.</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam2_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/>If any of this interests you, you might also want to play the game’s initial prototype, <u><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1691420/START_AGAIN_a_prologue/" rel="" target="_blank">START AGAIN START AGAIN START AGAIN: A Prologue</a></u>. While you don’t need to play it to understand In Stars and Time, it’s fun to see the game’s roots.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header_alt_assets_2.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astral Ascent</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1280930/Astral_Ascent/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Astral Ascent is a 2D platformer rogue-lite game set in a modern fantasy world. As one of 4 Heroes with very different personalities, you must escape from <i>the Garden</i>, an astral prison guarded by 12 powerful and vicious bosses, the Zodiacs.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CREATE YOUR OWN PLAYSTYLE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Gif_playstyle.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Unlock dozens of unique spells for your 4 distinct characters. Optimize your own build or try out new ones to take down 12 powerful bosses. Get stronger with time to match up with your foes. Each run will test your skills and your reactivity.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TWELVE ALMIGHTY BOSSES TO FACE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Zodiacs.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The Zodiacs are 12 experienced guardians dispatched over 4 gorgeous worlds. They’ll bring to the battlefield unique attacks, abilities, and patterns, backstories to uncover, and reasons to be fighting you. Get yourself warned!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>4 PLAYABLE CHARACTERS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/4_Character_banniere_steam7.png?t=1700851162"><br/><i>Unique characters. Unique weapons. Unique ways to play.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Ayla:</strong> The sole survivor of her guild of assassins, she uses her twin daggers to eliminate her enemies before they can react. Her speed and proficiency are unmatched.<br/></li><li><strong>Kiran:</strong> This orphan learned life the hard way. He uses his strength to deliver attacks powerful enough to create shockwaves. Brutal.<br/></li><li><strong>Calie:</strong> This talented sculptor wants her freedom back. She will use her magical gemstones to pierce enemy defenses and shred them to bits. She is unforgiving.<br/></li><li><strong>Octave:</strong> Trained by a powerful witch, this young fighter summons ethereal guns to attack his foes. When needed, he can conjure bigger weapons as well. Lethal in all cases.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A STORY THAT OPENS UP, ONE PIECE AT A TIME</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/ZimZim2.png?t=1700851162"><br/>Astral Ascent is a rogue-lite infused with narration. Replayability is part of our story which will be unraveled piece by piece. As you get stronger, you will discover more about the characters, their motivations, and the secrets of the world they’re trapped in.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>LOCAL CO-OP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Coop.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The weight of destiny is too heavy to carry by yourself? Don’t worry and bring a friend to play in our <strong>two-player co-op</strong> mode. Fight and crush your enemies together in local co-op or online using the <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/remoteplay?snr=1_614_615__1601" rel="" target="_blank"><strong>Steam's Remote Play Together</strong></a> feature.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A VAST, COLORFUL FANTASY WORLD WAITING TO BE EXPLORED</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Panning.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Dash across gigantic landscapes. Explore original and hand-crafted areas. Discover the world created by our artists, with a gorgeous art and frame-by-frame animation.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1701808865"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobalt Core</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2179850/Cobalt_Core/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_1.gif?t=1701600866"><br/><br/>Cobalt Core is a sci-fi roguelike deckbuilder with a unique single-axis combat system that will throw you for a loop. Many loops! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_2.gif?t=1701600866"><br/><br/>Give orders to your crew by playing cards: Will you <strong>raise shields</strong> to protect your ship, <strong>dodge</strong> incoming missiles and cannon fire to avoid damage outright, or <strong>strike</strong> preemptively to disable your enemy’s weapons? Outmaneuver your foes to stay just ahead of impending calamity, and reach the Cobalt Core!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/characters.png?t=1701600866"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fresh new spin on tactics –</strong>  dodge attacks and target weak points in this unique single-axis take on tactics combat. Outwit the enemy in a high stakes game of cat and mouse!<br/></li><li><strong>Customize your deck –</strong> hundreds of cards and split upgrade paths means no two runs will be the same. Find that perfect combo that brings your deck from powerful to overpowered.<br/></li><li><strong>Get to know your crew –</strong> each character comes with a completely unique playstyle and their own personal story. Bring 3 along, mix and match their decks, and see how these little goobers get along with each other.<br/></li><li><strong>Tons of replayability –</strong>  hundreds of different character+ship combinations before you even hit “start run”. Crank up the difficulty and really test your skills!<br/></li><li><strong>Forward momentum –</strong> untangle a narrative and unlock more playstyles as you go. Is there any escape from this time loop?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/grandma_cookies.gif?t=1701600866"><br/><br/>By the makers of <i>Sunshine Heavy Industries</i>, recipient of IGF's <strong>Honorable Mention for Excellence in Design 2022</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658820/Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							10 possible fruits and one goal, reach the Watermelon.<br/>Your job is to combine matching fruits to evolve them to the next one and eventually reach the coveted Watermelon.<br/>To help you, you have 3 different abilities at your disposal. But watch out, using these will cost you some of your points. Be smart about when you use them to get the highest score!<h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLAYER</h2>Measure your fruit skills against another player.<h2 class="bb_tag">GET THE WATERMELON</h2>How many Watermelons can you combine before your basket overflows?<h2 class="bb_tag">USE YOUR ABILITIES</h2>Power, level up and destroy — These abilities will help you reach the Watermelon, using any of those will also allow you to angle your aim.<h2 class="bb_tag">GOLDEN FRUIT</h2>If luck is on your side, you might even see the mysterious Golden Fruit. Find it and witness its effect firsthand.<h2 class="bb_tag">STATISTICS</h2>Track your progress with in-depth statistics. Visit the menu to see the number of fruits you've combined, your ability usage, and much more.<h2 class="bb_tag"></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.codecks.io%2Fwatermelon-game" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/extras/Roadmap_Banner.png?t=1701768047"/></a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707420/3D_Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707420/extras/banner.png?t=1701936072"><br/><strong>Have you ever wanted to make a smoothie in your blender at home? </strong><br/><strong>Have you had trouble fitting all the fruit in there?</strong><br/> Look no more with this top-of-the-line blender simulator using our <i>NASA APPROVED*</i> physics simulator. <br/>No more shall you spill the fruit (of labor) as you try and try again.<br/><br/>Simulate your perfect smoothie in one of our three (3) gamemodes:<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707420/extras/classic_mode.png?t=1701936072"><h2 class="bb_tag">Classic Mode</h2>Drop your fruit whenever you want where ever you want, Match fruit of the same type and they'll combine into the next level!<br/>You lose when a fruit escapes the blender.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707420/extras/Time_Attack.png?t=1701936072"><h2 class="bb_tag">Time Attack!</h2>Classic mode just got a little faster.<br/>Race the timer and match fruit to keep yourself from timing out.<br/>Can you handle the pressure of a full blender and 10 seconds on the clock?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707420/extras/Auto_Dorp.png?t=1701936072"><h2 class="bb_tag">Auto Drop</h2>It seems your spacebar got stuck.<br/>Autodrop constantly forces you to drop fruit at constantly increasing rates.<br/>Planning &amp; Structure go out the blender fast when the cherries rain from above.<br/><br/>* nasa did not aprove any of this and for legal reasons it's a joke.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awesome Pea 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2247630/Awesome_Pea_3/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2247630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Awesome Pea 3 - final chapter now in shape of fast precision platformer where you must run&amp;jump through a series of challenging stages.<br/><br/>What you will definitely find in this game (again):<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 69 (^_^) different stages to show your skill<br/></li><li> Stylish pixel graphics<br/></li><li> Chiptune soundtrack<br/></li><li> Steam achievements for everyone who loves achievements</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parcel Mania: Free Multiplayer Madness</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1142020/Parcel_Mania_Free_Multiplayer_Madness/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1142020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FX8bXg2RMQn" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1142020/extras/00_join_discord_english.png?t=1701929713"/></a><br/><br/>Parcel Mania is a frantic online or local splitscreen party game supporting up to 4 players in a match. Your #1 goal? Collect and deliver the most parcels and become the best courier connoisseur of the match! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1142020/extras/parkour.gif?t=1701929713"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1142020/extras/01_parcels_pranks_pandaemonium_english.png?t=1701929713"><br/><br/>Collect parcels from their stations, or smack ‘em out of your friends hands. Whoever delivers them to the customers gets to rank up high in the scoreboard. And if you want to slow your friends down? Slap the customers and watch them weep! It’s all fair in the world of delivery.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1142020/extras/slapping.gif?t=1701929713"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1142020/extras/02_deliver_agains_odds_english.png?t=1701929713"><br/><br/>Leap over walls, flip switches, zip through shortcuts and defy gravity itself to get your parcels to your customers no matter what. Talk about 'air mail'! In Parcel Mania, you're not just a courier – you're a gravity-defying delivery superhero. Just remember, capes are optional when you're leaping over walls and flipping through the air!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1142020/extras/deliver.gif?t=1701929713"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1142020/extras/03_five_characters_english.png?t=1701929713"><br/><br/>Pick from five distinct characters, each with their own quirky personality and style! Each character brings their own unique flair to the frantic parcel delivery action. So, who will you be today? The choice is yours – pick your favorite and deliver those parcels with style!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1142020/extras/characters.gif?t=1701929713"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1142020/extras/04_turn_tables_english.png?t=1701929713"><br/><br/>Setting traps for your friends is like being in a wacky game show – except the only prize is the sweet, sweet victory of watching them jump in surprise. It's not just about speed, it's about how you play the game – and a little bit of 'parcel-tactical' warfare!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1142020/extras/traps.gif?t=1701929713"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1142020/extras/05_local_online_english.png?t=1701929713"><br/><br/>Challenge your friends from across the globe or from across your couch – all for no price. Yep – Parcel Mania in its current or future versions will remain FREE TO PLAY. Now go get those customers their parcels and beat your friends!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1142020/extras/boss.gif?t=1701929713"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seybul Tech</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2565600/Seybul_Tech/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2565600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Seybul Tech lures you into a voyage through a realm in-between, where unsettling artistry, haunting ambiance, and unique melodies meld together. Navigating these unconventional passages, each step further enhances the uncanny atmosphere.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2565600/extras/AboutThisSunRoom.png?t=1701931539"><h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> This game is <i>basically</i> a walking simulator<br/></li><li> Liminal space design of scenes to explore - extremely odd layouts designed to instill familiarity and discomfort<br/></li><li> Every scene hand-crafted with an extreme attention to lighting<br/></li><li> Interact with limited 90s tech such as PCs, TVs, etc.<br/></li><li> Original soundtrack<br/></li><li> This game is meant to be explored, so runtime will depend on just that with a minimum runtime of 1 hour </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2565600/extras/AboutThisOffice.png?t=1701931539"><h2 class="bb_tag">GAMEPLAY</h2>Beginning in a dimly-lit office, you are faced with a strange encounter that leaves you no choice but to delve deeper into this surreal world.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Soldier of the Ming Dynasty</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2494450/The_Last_Soldier_of_the_Ming_Dynasty/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">The Last Soldier of the Ming Dynasty is a 3D action game inspired by traditional Chinese landscape ink paintings.</h2>You take on the role of a Qi army soldier, tasked with fighting back the Japanese pirate raids during the Ming Dynasty. After your unit's boat shipwrecks, you find yourself cast on an island controlled by the Wokou, Japanese pirates that have been terrorizing the Chinese coasts for decades. You are alone with your sword, the last soldier of the Ming Dynasty standing against the pirates – but your duty won't be fulfilled until your people's coasts are safe again. <br/><br/>Explore the beautifully painted landscapes of Fuling Island to defeat the 5 pirate bosses, each with their own unique characteristics, experiencing the most intense traditional melee combat. Embrace the challenge of this hardcore action game, rich in historical charm and martial arts depth!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494450/extras/pkztf2.gif?t=1701920802"><h2 class="bb_tag">Fighting against Japanese pirates</h2>The Last Soldier of the Ming Dynasty is set during the Jiajing period of the Ming Dynasty. At that time, rampant Japanese pirates plagued the southeastern coastal regions. General Qi Jiguang was tasked with combating these pirates; after successfully finishing his campaign, he headed north to Jizhou, pacifying internal rebellions in his path and guarding against external barbarians. But as the Qi's army moved north, the remnants of the defeated Japanese pirates gathered back its forces and conspired with other sea raiders from Fuling Island, readying to make a bloody comeback.<br/><br/>As a member of the Qi's army stationed to guard the coastal regions, specifically tasked with pacifying the seas, you were patrolling the waters when a storm shipwrecked your boat – and you find yourself a castaway on the shores of Ryukyu Island, the only survivor of your unit. With your sword by your side, you walk into the depths of the Island, set on uncovering and dismantling the clandestine plots of the Japanese pirates.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494450/extras/pkzgs.gif?t=1701920802"><h2 class="bb_tag">Ink and wash painting world</h2>The game's art is inspired by traditional Chinese ink and wash paintings. From the humblest blade of grass to the most majestic mountains of Fuling Island, each scene is beautifully painted in ink and wash. Its artistic design also draws inspiration from ancient Chinese paintings' character styles and proportions, providing players with a captivating visual experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494450/extras/动图5.gif?t=1701920802"><h2 class="bb_tag">Tactical melee with cold weapons</h2>The Last Soldier of the Ming Dynasty will put your reflexes and warrior senses to the test. Its combat system is built upon three basic attack actions: stab, cleave, and sweep, which form the basis of both offense and defense. While executing these moves, it is crucial to discern the enemy's attacks simultaneously. You can deflect their attacks by accurately anticipating the enemy's actions. Stay calm in the midst of the storm while you ponder the enemy's every move, and you will remain undefeated in battle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494450/extras/动图2.gif?t=1701920802"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494450/extras/动图3.gif?t=1701920802"><br/><br/>The game offers a variety of combat styles, ranging from close-quarters melee weapons to long-range bows and arrows. You can either block enemy attacks with your weapons or utilize evading maneuvers and counterattacks. The key to overcoming adversaries lies in swiftly switching between offense and defense, adeptly countering their moves. Only by mastering the art of adaptation and switching styles you will ultimately triumph over your foes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494450/extras/动图1.gif?t=1701920802"><h2 class="bb_tag">Historical weaponry and armor</h2>The game offers a variety of weapons and equipment for players to choose from. Each piece of weaponry is meticulously recreated to reflect its origins in real historical contexts.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494450/extras/更换装备.gif?t=1701920802"><br/><br/>You can also disarm enemies and utilize their weapon skills against them. Through diligent practice, mastering the techniques of your adversaries, and then applying them to your own weaponry, you will become even more formidable in combat.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2494450/extras/动图4.gif?t=1701920802"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINAL FANTASY VII EVER CRISIS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2484110/FINAL_FANTASY_VII_EVER_CRISIS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484110/extras/Gif_SEJ_Sample_01_-_deliverable.gif?t=1701917926"><br/><br/>Relive the most memorable moments from FFVII and experience the journey of a young hero Sephiroth in FINAL FANTASY VII EVER CRISIS, making its debut on Steam.<br/>Experience both classic and new stories within the FFVII universe presented in a retro-style look combined with modern, beautifully rendered graphics. Team up your favorite characters and customize each one with iconic gear and weapons to defeat powerful opponents in Solo or Co-op battle mode.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484110/extras/Gif_SEJ_Sample_02_-_deliverable.gif?t=1701917926"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">◆ EXPERIENCE NEW AND ORIGINAL STORIES FROM THE FINAL FANTASY VII UNIVERSE</h2></strong><br/>Discover the never-before told story of a young hero, Sephiroth.<br/><br/>Encounter new characters along the way and play as iconic heroes, such as Cloud and Zack, in the epic storylines of the original FINAL FANTASY VII and CRISIS CORE -FINAL FANTASY VII- in episodic installments.<br/><br/>FINAL FANTASY VII: The story of Cloud Strife, an elite SOLDIER operative turned mercenary. Cloud lends his aid to an anti-Shinra organization: Avalanche, unaware of the epic consequences that await him. Once more begins a story that will shape the destiny of the entire world.<br/><br/>CRISIS CORE -FINAL FANTASY VII- : The story of Zack Fair, a promising young operative in the Shinra military’s elite unit, SOLDIER. The story takes place seven years before the events of FFVII. Follow the tale of Zack’s dreams and honor – and the legacy that connects him to Cloud.<br/><br/>The action unfolds through the characters in a modern-stylized polygon look, inspired by the original FFVII. Even those experiencing FFVII for the first time can enjoy this expansive world in this epic saga that defined RPGs for gamers throughout the world!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484110/extras/Gif_SEJ_Sample_03_-_deliverable.gif?t=1701917926"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">◆ EVOLVED GAME SYSTEM AND FAST-PACED COMMAND-BASED BATTLE</h2></strong><br/>Immerse yourself in beautifully rendered, fast-paced command-based battle evolved from FFVII’s Active Time Battle. The battles give spotlight to classic FINAL FANTASY RPG elements such as, Abilities, Materia, Summons, and heart-pumping Limit Breaks, while supporting additional features such as Auto Mode and Battle Speed that make the game even more enjoyable to play.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484110/extras/Gif_SEJ_Sample_04_-_deliverable.gif?t=1701917926"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">◆ BUILD AND CUSTOMIZE THE ULTIMATE PARTY</h2></strong><br/>Form a party of your favorite characters from FFVII series titles, such as Cloud, Tifa, Aerith, Zack and more! Dress them with new gear unique to FINAL FANTASY VII EVER CRISIS.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484110/extras/Gif_SEJ_Sample_05_-_deliverable.gif?t=1701917926"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>◆ WORK TOGETHER WITH FRIENDS in CO-OP BATTLE</strong></h2>Lead your group of friends from around the world with up-to 3 member Co-op battle to defeat powerful bosses together!<br/><br/>Follow the official #FF7EC Pages:<br/>Website: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fen.ffviiec.com%2F" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://en.ffviiec.com/</a><br/>X: <a href="https://twitter.com/FFVII_EC_EN" rel="" target="_blank">https://twitter.com/FFVII_EC_EN</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollow Cocoon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2414630/Hollow_Cocoon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">■What Kind of Game is Hollow Cocoon?</h2>It is a first-person horror adventure game set in 1980s Japan.<br/><br/>Step into the shoes of Minato Jinba, a college student returning to his mother's hometown after receiving news that his grandmother is in critical condition. Hide yourself from the monster and gather vital evidence to unravel the bone-chilling truth lurking beneath the surface!<h2 class="bb_tag">■The Story</h2>--198X<br/><br/>Minato Jinba, a university student, lives away from his parents in a boarding house in the city.<br/>One night, Minato receives distressing news from his father, Eiji. Minato's maternal grandmother, Kinu Miyama, is in critical condition.<br/>He embarks on a journey to Ichinose, a village deep in the mountains, where his mother was born.<br/><br/>Minato had not seen his grandmother for over a decade and harbors a deep resentment towards her.<br/>She had refused to even attend her own daughter's funeral, further intensifying Minato's disdain.<br/><br/>As the bus rumbles across the country road, Minato recalls his only conversation with his grandmother.<br/><br/>"-- The thing with silkworms, you know; even if they could leave their cocoons, they have no mouths to eat, and their wings do not fly.<br/>They simply lay their eggs and perish."<br/><br/>"People are the reason they suffer this fate."<br/><br/>The sky reddens in the twilight, and the mountains cast an ominous shadow.<br/>Minato finds himself in this house<br/>There, he finds himself in a terrifying situation with a shocking truth.<h2 class="bb_tag">■Features</h2><strong>-Multiple Endings</strong><br/>  Experience a captivating story with four unique endings.<br/>  Your choices will lead the story down different branching paths.<br/><br/><strong>-Difficulty Selection</strong><br/>  Choose from three difficulty options.<br/>  Whether you want to just enjoy the story or seek a challenging experience, the game can accommodate your needs.<br/>  *You can switch to a lower difficulty during gameplay (Note: The difficulty cannot be raised).<br/><br/><strong>-Auto-Saving</strong><br/>  Both auto-save and manual save options are available.<br/>  Even if you get a game over, you can immediately restart from the last checkpoint.<br/><br/><strong>-Motion Sickness Reduction</strong><br/>  To alleviate motion sickness, various features are available, including adjustable viewing angles, a central dot display, and the option to disable camera shaking.<br/>  Multiple functions are provided to minimize motion sickness caused by visuals.<h2 class="bb_tag">■Uploading and livestreaming Guidelines</h2>Please adhere to the following guidelines when posting or livestreaming game footage:<br/><br/>-Do not post or livestream content that is offensive or severely undermines the value of the game or its world.<br/>-Include the game's name in the title of the video or livestream.<br/>-Include the store page URL in the summary or description section of the video or livestream.<br/>-Monetization is only allowed when using the monetization functions (*1) provided by video sharing sites such as YouTube. Posting or streaming the game for commercial purposes that does not fall under the above is prohibited. (*2)<br/>-Posting or livestreaming content limited to paid members, such as YouTube memberships, is not permitted.<br/>-We request you refrain from uploading unedited gameplay footage. Please add or edit the video in some shape or form.<br/>-NAYUTA STUDIO will not be held responsible for any damages incurred by the publisher or any third party resulting from the posting or livestreaming of videos.<br/>-Please note that these guidelines are subject to change without prior notice.<br/><br/>*1: Creator functions on video sharing platforms that allow for revenue.<br/>*2: Examples include screening in stores or using the content in paid events.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scavenger vr</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2688370/Scavenger_vr/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game requires Oculus Quest. If you do not have the device, you cannot use it.<br>
<br>
You become a member of the rift investigation team and explore the unknown rift.<br>
Collect dinosaur eggs while avoiding the dangerous dinosaurs there.<br>
You can hatch dinosaur eggs to create your own dinosaur garden.<br>
<br>
You can explore jungle, desert, and swamp areas.<br/>
<br/>
Use capture bullets to collect resources and dinosaur eggs.<br/>
<br/>
Dinosaurs can't see you, but they react to moving objects or sounds.<br/>
<br/>
You can use lures, flashes, and smoke bombs to escape dangerous situations or make gathering easier.<br/>
<br/>
Collect points to get upgraded and enjoy a great vacation!!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sees Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2673330/Sees_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Play the game... <strong>SEES GAME!!</strong><br/>Play as Sees in a reimagined take of the classic Snake game.<br/>Eat apples and compete with your friends for the hi-score!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673330/extras/Hi-Scdfdore.png?t=1701903618"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 10 diferent mazes.<br/></li><li> 3 game modes, 2 of them unlockable after reaching a certain amount of points:<br/><u>Normal:</u> Make your way through the randomly selected labyrinths.<br/><u>Classic:</u> No walls! One mistake and it's Game Over. <br/><u>Time Trial:</u> Keep eatng apples before the time runs out. Can't pause in this mode.<br/></li><li> Unlockable skins.<br/></li><li> 8-bit style soundtrack arranged by Marcelo Canario.<br/></li><li> Easter eggs!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>How to play:</strong></h2>Use <strong>arrow keys</strong> or <strong>WASD</strong> to move around.<br/><br/>Press <strong>Q</strong> or <strong>P</strong> to pause the game (you have a 3 seconds cooldown to pause again).<br/><br/>Press <strong>C</strong> to switch the camera.<br/><br/>Eating apples makes you faster. Careful though, because you get REALLY fast.<br/><br/><strong>Red Apples</strong> give you 1 point. <strong>Golden Apples</strong> give you 2 points.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673330/extras/UKaFSz.gif?t=1701903618"><br/><br/><br/>Some mazes feature tunnels you can go through. Play <strong>seestrategically!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673330/extras/bBCFYY.gif?t=1701903618"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Credits:</strong></h2><strong>Kovaldevlog:</strong> Basically all the magic.<br/><strong>Rodricoro:</strong> Big loser, no one cares.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chain Reaction</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2542470/Chain_Reaction/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2542470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Chill out and get creative as you experiment with your own Chain Reactions!<br/><br/>Build up sequences of objects and watch the oddly satisfying result.<br/><br/>Then at the press of the button, magically reset all the pieces. There's no need for a steady hand or extreme patience, here!<br/><br/>Explore and solve many set challenges as you discover a wealth of props and set pieces.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Progress through many hours of set challenges to explore and resolve.<br/></li><li>Explore many different playing pieces from dominos and rockets to rails and mallets.<br/></li><li>Earn in-game money and purchase the elements you want for your own creations.<br/></li><li>Customise the aesthetics of your creation's surroundings.<br/></li><li>Save and return to your creations.<br/></li><li>Get awarded via many in-game accomlishments.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little Chefs: CO-OP</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2610050/Little_Chefs_COOP/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>In this game you will have a great time with your friends with co-op mode up to 4 players! You will have to cook different dishes in total chaos, where your team will be required to work together.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610050/extras/buildMode_border.png?t=1701895971"><br/>Build mode competently allows you to improve your kitchen by building new things that will be unlocked as your character levels up. Thus, with each new round the game will only get more interesting!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610050/extras/customize_border.png?t=1701895971"><br/>Do you like to customize? Welcome to our game! Complete daily tasks and get valuable currency, which you can use to customize both your character and your kitchen! Don't worry, if you're not a game host, you can still change the lobby leader's kitchen! It'll be a surprise for him!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610050/extras/randomizeMode_border.gif?t=1701895971"><br/>In addition to the standard progressive mode, you'll be able to play procedural map generation mode. The next round will be completely different from the last. No more routine!<br/><br/>Improve your character by increasing his different characteristics that give bonuses! And also remember: the higher the level of your character - the more recipes for cooking are available to you!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ballapalooza</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2656220/Ballapalooza/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A simple ball game where you must solve puzzles, platform, and dodge obstacles to collect rings and complete levels.<br/><br/>Up to 50 unique levels to play.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656220/extras/Powerups_Simple_GIF-1.gif?t=1701895720"><br/>Use powerups to complete levels by jumping, cloning and spawning boxes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656220/extras/perfect_run.gif?t=1701895720"><br/>A speedrun mode to see how fast you can complete the game! If you are good enough you can beat the game with the game without dying in the speedrun mode and complete the <strong><i>PERFECT RUN!</i></strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656220/extras/Color_Picker.gif?t=1701895720"><br/>Choose what color you want to have your ball be.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden World 10 Top-Down 3D</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2703190/Hidden_World_10_TopDown_3D/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find the objects that are hidden on the map.<br>
<br>
The game is a Hidden Object Game. <br>
In which you need to find objects with a certain design in beautiful locations, and click on them with the mouse.<br>
<br>
<br>
The game is a 3D level game in which objects and characters are frozen in the picture, you have to find 20 different objects. The system automatically determines which object you need to find at the moment, so the game has a high replay value, you will need to search for different objects each time.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Craft</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678760/Natural_Craft/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Control the falling blocks, stack them correctly, and clear lines by filling them.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each type of block has unique feature, using each feature appropriately is the key to success.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678760/extras/Blocks_1.png?t=1701885552"><br/></img></li><li>Burn everything with flames! Always make sure the blocks are placed properly to avoid destroying everything with flames! Or burn them all!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678760/extras/Fire.gif?t=1701885552"><br/></img></li><li>Explosion is an art! Use bombs to save the situation from failure!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678760/extras/Bomb.gif?t=1701885552"><br/></img></li><li>When you level up, more blocks will be unlocked.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678760/extras/Blocks_2.png?t=1701885552"/></li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Place blocks to collect energy. Each time you fill up your energy, you can exchange it for a powerful bomb!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678760/extras/getbomb.gif?t=1701885552"><br/></img></li><li>Clear lines and level up. With each level up, the challenge increases in difficulty!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678760/extras/getline.gif?t=1701885552"/></li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INARI</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674120/INARI/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DIVINE RETRIBUTION! </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674120/extras/bridgesmaller.gif?t=1701905444"><br/><strong>INARI</strong> is a side-scrolling hack-and-slash game where you play as Daisuke, a heavenly kitsune sent down to liberate Japan from the yokai that have overrun its streets. Overcome the hordes of demons plaguing the land and dethrone the ringleader of the chaos in INARI's story mode.<h2 class="bb_tag">SLICE AND DICE! </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674120/extras/catcombosmall.gif?t=1701905444"><br/>Slay enemies in style with an arsenal of different attacks - from quick stabs to hard-hitting heavies and even aerial swipes. By stringing together moves to create combos, you can cut through enemies with ease and rack up divine style points.<h2 class="bb_tag">CONQUER THE DEMON TRAIN! </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674120/extras/trainsmaller2.gif?t=1701905444"><br/>Banish the yokai yakuza in an additional game mode where you can collect items to enhance your combat abilities. Claw your way through every train car and stop the nefarious plans of the yakuza lords who have taken over the train.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Hunters Survivor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2681340/Four_Hunters_Survivor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2681340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of four fearless hunters to survive countless hordes of enemies, you can play with:<br/><br/><strong>Knight:</strong> An excellent melee combatant.<br/><strong>Archer:</strong> Always ready to finish off everyone from a distance.<br/><strong>Mage:</strong> Scholar of powerful magic.<br/><strong>Cleric:</strong> With light and healing spells, prepared for survival.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2681340/extras/descrição_1.gif?t=1701883589"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Get ready to see:</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Four maps, namely the forest, the snow, the desert, and the dungeon.</li></ul> <ul class="bb_ul"><li> 30+ Different enemies for you to fight.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> </li></ul> Exclusive abilities for each hunter.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Mysterious merchant who will sell you improvements.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2681340/extras/descrição2.gif?t=1701883589"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2681340/extras/descrição_3.gif?t=1701883589"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party Animals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1260320/Party_Animals/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1260320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"> Make Painfully Great Memories with Your Friends in Party Animals. </h2><br/><br/><strong> Mess With Your Friend in 100 Different Ways</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1260320/extras/001.gif?t=1701692409"><br/><br/><br/><strong>Or Together You Could Eliminate Others</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1260320/extras/002.gif?t=1701692409"><br/><br/><br/><strong>Teamwork Is Also Highly Appreciated Here</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1260320/extras/003.gif?t=1701692409"><br/><br/><br/><strong>Especially When Fighting For Gummy Bear</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1260320/extras/2222.gif?t=1701692409"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fimbul's Gemboree</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2688440/Fimbuls_Gemboree/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the enchanting world of "Fimbul's Gemboree," a delightful 3D platformer that invites players on an epic adventure with Fimbul, a charming small ice dragon on a quest for the ultimate party experience. In this whimsical journey, players will navigate through diverse landscapes, from sun-kissed beaches to mysterious rocky forests and even a towering mountainous pinball machine.<br>
<br>
<br>
As Fimbul, your mission is to collect sparkling gems and coveted tickets scattered throughout the vibrant environments. The more gems and tickets you gather, the closer you get to unlocking the grand entrance to the legendary Gemboree, the most exclusive and spectacular dragon celebration in the realm.<br>
<br>
<br>
Embark on an exploration-filled escapade, overcoming platforming challenges, solving puzzles, and encountering endearing snowmen, and treacherous tiki totems. Fimbul's cute personality and nimble abilities make every run, jump, and roll a joy to experience, adding a layer of charm to the immersive gameplay.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destroyer: The U-Boat Hunter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1272010/Destroyer_The_UBoat_Hunter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1272010/header_alt_assets_4.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FBRGJdz4Nr8" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1272010/extras/Destroyer_discord_1.png?t=1701882381"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2153660/Destroyer_The_UBoat_Hunter__Supporter_Pack/" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2153660/Destroyer_The_UBoat_Hunter__Supporter_Pack/</a><br/><br/>Destroyer: The U-Boat Hunter is an innovative, cross-genre destroyer simulation which truthfully depicts the struggle of escort groups protecting allied convoys against German U-boats during the Battle of the Atlantic. Take full control of a Fletcher-class destroyer, using authentic instruments and attack procedures to fully experience the full spectrum of anti-submarine warfare.<br/><br/>Destroyer combines the thrill of commanding an anti-submarine warship with the tactical challenge of managing a whole escort group protecting convoys against relentless wolfpacks. The game goes to great lengths to appeal to fans of realism and immersion, at the same time offering a great experience for beginners in the genre as well.<br/><br/>Whether a military sim veteran or a fledgling captain, immerse yourself in a cinematic naval warfare experience and feel the thrill of the hunt!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1272010/extras/destroyer_gif1.gif?t=1701882381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key game features include:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural battle generation with randomized weather, time of day, and enemy attack patterns, allowing for a virtually infinite number of battle scenarios.<br/></li><li>A detailed Fletcher-class destroyer model with 5 locations meticulously recreated in state-of-the art 3D: the bridge, the combat information center, the sonar room, the gun director, and the lookouts’ station.<br/></li><li>Over 300 voice reports recorded by professional voice actors, navy school cadets and US Navy experts for unparalleled immersion and situational awareness.<br/></li><li>A total of 10 different battle stations covering the most essential duties of the anti-submarine attack team, each complete with its key instruments and gear to give you the edge over the enemy.<br/></li><li>4 different convoy battle configurations (small, medium, large, and custom). <br/></li><li>A dark, thematic soundtrack comprising 4 multi-layered pieces that dynamically adjust to the level of tension between you and the enemy.<br/></li><li>Varied U-boat captain profiles: aggressive, sneaky, patient, or cold professional - each of them with an ace up their sleeve.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1272010/extras/destroyer_gif2.gif?t=1701882381"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital Aliens 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653210/Hospital_Aliens_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are placed in a abandon forest filled with beings that were once human and other creatures called aliens. The Alien boss resides in a house you must find in the forest and you must capture what it is guarding. Will you escape and bring humanity closer to ending the epidemic? Use stealth tactics such as crouching, hiding behind walls and trees, and also a weapon to complete your mission. Their is a indicator in the game that lets you know when you've been spotted.<br>
In this First-Person experience you play as Greg who is a retired soldier who was taken away from his farm to combat aliens and zombies. He is angry and determined to defeat the enemies and return to his former life but be careful, every sound and step you make could make the enemies aware of you!<br>
Will you also find the weapon to make stealth less of a risk for zombies and aliens?						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadows of Rogue: The Sorcerer's Curse</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2591840/Shadows_of_Rogue_The_Sorcerers_Curse/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this roguelite game, you'll face increasingly hordes of enemies and formidable bosses, all while discovering an array of valuable items and surprises along the way. Prepare for a casual yet intensely challenging gaming experience, with a wide range of options and battle combinations at your disposal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591840/extras/qqqqqqqqq.png?t=1701879149"><br/><br/>■ Highly inspired by medieval movies and RPGs.<br/>■ Retro graphics and music, the FIRST true nes-inspired roguelite medieval game!<br/>■ Fight against skeletons, zombies, and even a mimic chest, among others!<br/>■ Unique real voices converted to 8 bit sounds for all characters!<br/>■ An interesting and unique medieval story!<br/>■ Incredible replay factor. Each run is different in some aspects!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591840/extras/1111111111.png?t=1701879149"><br/>■ Choose your preferable class to fight. You can play with classes like the warrior, archer, wizard, and even a barbarian dwarf! More classes planned in the future!<br/>■ Each class has an unique passive skill and main weapon, making the gameplay totally unique for each of them!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591840/extras/foto_lojas.png?t=1701879149"><br/>■ Different stores: Buy useful items(upgrades) in the Gryphon's Goods shop, or eat a troll toe tacos in the tavern, or you can go to the Knight's Forge and improve your weapon up to 3 tiers and unlock its true power!<br/>■ Have a funny dialogue with npcs in the stores, which talks differently depending on your chosen class. PS: The dwarf in the tavern doesn't like the archer; it reminds him of the elves!<br/>■ Unlock useful items that will appear in the shop afterwards!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591840/extras/bpss.png?t=1701879149"><br/>■ Fight against hard oldschool bosses! Want to fight a giant floating skull head? A colossal ancient knight? A hill giant? This game has it all!<br/>■ 2 possible ways to beat the game, with 2 different ending screens!<br/>■ Run at 60FPS!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anx Defense</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2500450/Anx_Defense/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2500450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Defend your Nexus by placing various buildings on the path of your projectiles. Deflect, empower, manage and solve each map using your creative and strategic mind.</i><br/><br/><br/>Anx Defense is a mind-bending twist on the Tower Defense genre.<br/>Place various buildings on the path of your projectiles to create your ultimate defense!<br/>Everything comes at a price though and you will need to manage your available gold, space and Mana wisely.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2500450/extras/Header_Deflect.png?t=1701879974"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2500450/extras/Mirrors_2_NN.gif?t=1701879974"><br/><i>Mirrors make the projectiles do a 90° turn and they can be hit from both sides.</i><br/><br/>This unique mechanic offers a lot of creativity when it comes to solving the map's puzzle.<br/>As the game progresses this will become more and more difficult, as you'll have to keep these things in mind:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Avoid obstacles<br/></li><li> Cover every monster path<br/></li><li> Reach each path in time<br/></li><li> Projectile should be strong enough while crossing a path</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2500450/extras/Header_Empower.png?t=1701879974"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2500450/extras/Gates_2.gif?t=1701879974"><br/><i>A projectile passing through 3 Damage Enhancer and then 3 Speed Enhancer.</i><br/><br/>Use various Gates to empower your shots!<br/>Enhance damage, speed, piercing or infuse Mana to your projectiles by placing the corresponding building on their way.<br/>You'll also need to build some farm to boost your economy, otherwise you won't be able to make it until the end.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2500450/extras/Header_InfuseMana.png?t=1701879974"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2500450/extras/Mana_1.gif?t=1701879974"><br/><i>Projectile passing through a Blue Mana Infuser, a Yellow Mana Infuser and a Damage Enhancer. (with Mana Overlay activated)</i><br/><br/>Gates will need Mana to activate. Manas are infused to projectiles by passing through Mana Infusers (special buildings).<br/>There are two types of Mana -- Blue and Yellow -- and later on in the game, some Gates will have Mana Conditions. This means that in order to activate, the Mana Levels will need to satisfy some special conditions (for instance, holding more Blue Mana than Yellow Mana).<br/><br/>This mechanic leads to an intricate puzzle of Mana management.<br/>Mana Conditions also change with each level, meaning the Mana management puzzle needs to be re-solved by the player each time.<h2 class="bb_tag">Campaign &amp; High Scores</h2>The campaign features a list of levels, each with its own map, building restrictions and Mana Conditions. <br/>Each level also comes with up to 3 challenging High Score goals to reach!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bug &amp; Seek</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2265310/Bug__Seek/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2265310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2265310/extras/175RealBugs_Light.png?t=1701875583"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2265310/extras/BugScroll.gif?t=1701875583"><br/><br/>Being developed by a tiny, two-person dev team, Bug &amp; Seek is a relaxing, open-ended, bug catching sim/creature collector with a mystery twist. In Bug &amp; Seek, you've just sunk your life savings into buying an abandoned Insectarium (bug museum)! Once the lifeblood of the town and its economy, someone stole all the bugs in the dead of night. Now it's up to you to catch and sell bugs, fulfill requests from the local shops, and re-establish the Insectarium as a town icon. <strong>Become a master bug hunter</strong> as you level up your bug-catching skills, upgrade your equipment, and expand your Insectarium. Meet the locals and complete quests to earn special items and discover what really happened during The Great Bug Heist. And relax! There are no wrong choices, no energy levels to worry about, and plenty of time to complete quests and jobs.<br/><br/><strong>*Works great on Steam Deck!*</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2265310/extras/HeadingFeatures.png?t=1701875583"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Catch Bugs</strong> -- With over 175 different real-life bugs, ranging from common insects to some of the most rare and valuable insects in the world, the possibilities are endless. And every bug comes with a humorous tagline and true, informative short description. You'll never look at real insects the same way again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2265310/extras/CatchBugGIF.gif?t=1701875583"><br/><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Customize and Expand Your Insectarium</strong> -- Customize everything, from what tanks you use to what flooring, decorations, and wallpaper you have in your Insectarium. Upgrade your bug-catching equipment and your wardrobe. Build new wings to the Insectarium and create the best Insectarium the town has ever known. And of course, fill it with bugs!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2265310/extras/ExpansionGIF.gif?t=1701875583"><br/><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Explore The World</strong> -- Bugs live in every kind of habitat: from meadows, deserts, and forests to wetlands, beaches, and urban environments. And wouldn't you know it? Buggburg has all of these! Explore the variety of biomes in every season, with Buggburg's booming Town Square in the heart of it all.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2265310/extras/Wetlands.gif?t=1701875583"><br/><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Talk with the Locals</strong> -- From the mayor to the herb farmer, meet the 19+ locals of the town and perform missions for them to earn special gear and items, secrets and gossip, and maybe even haikus.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2265310/extras/ZaraDialogue.gif?t=1701875583"><br/><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Solve the Mystery</strong> -- One year ago someone broke into the Insectarium in the middle of the night and stole all of the bugs in an incident known as The Great Bug Heist. The Insectarium was shut down, and a vital piece of the Buggburg economy ground to a halt. As the new owner of the Insectarium, see if you can piece together what really happened as you solve the mystery and unmask the guilty party!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2265310/extras/BugHeist_wTag.png?t=1701875583"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2265310/extras/RowOfBugs.png?t=1701875583"><br/><br/><strong>Our studio is just the two of us!</strong> <br/><br/>Don't forget to wishlist and follow the game and to and join the <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fu8kAmxpPkj" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> Bug &amp; Seek Discord</a> to stay up to date!</img></img></li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Petit Petit Petit</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2145720/Petit_Petit_Petit/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2145720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Get ready for an exciting and refreshing adventure!<br/>In this thrilling game, you will be in charge of manipulating immune cells and medical nanomachines to fight off invading pathogens and save unknown creatures from deadly diseases.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2145720/extras/ppp_image01.png?t=1701874964"><br/><br/>Prepare for epic battles against hordes of enemies and wipe them out using various attack skills accompanied by fun cartoon-like onomatopoeic words.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2145720/extras/ppp_image02.png?t=1701874964"><br/><br/>Choose from a variety of immune cells and nanomachines, each with unique equipment and abilities that allow for an infinite number of play styles.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2145720/extras/ppp_image03.png?t=1701874964"><br/><br/>As you take control of the body's systems, beware of enemy attacks on weak points. Your character will be weakened and vital signs will drop if attacked, so be sure to respond to any SOS signals immediately.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2145720/extras/ppp_image04.png?t=1701874964"><br/><br/>Experience the thrill of skill inflation and power-up production as you evolve your skills with power-up kits. You never know when the "slot game" will activate, increasing the level of your skills or exploding the number of skills you possess. Collect more power-up kits to take on powerful bosses!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2145720/extras/ppp_image05.png?t=1701874964"><br/><br/>Your success in defeating the enemy and saving the unknown creatures depends on your strategy and luck. So, which combination of characters and skills will you choose to kick the enemy's ass? Get ready to find out!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idle Plant Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2701250/Idle_Plant_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Idle Plant Game</strong><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in the serene world of "Idle Plant Game," where you don't just grow plants — you are the plant. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Succulent<br/></li><li>Fern<br/></li><li>Moss<br/></li><li>Berry Bush<br/></li><li>Colony of Grass<br/></li><li>The Time Vine</li></ul><br/>Each with their own unique path to photosynthetic mastery.<br/><br/>This is an idle game, with the right strategy. <br/><br/>It is also a very active clicker if you want faster progression.<br/><br/>It is also a labor of love that is offered free for the world.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Fireplace</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678480/Pixel_Fireplace/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678480/extras/fire_marshmallow.gif?t=1701916911"><br/><br/>Pixel Fireplace is a cozy, type-controlled simulation. Type commands to strike a match, throw logs onto the crackling fire and watch them burn down to hot coals in real-time (about 20 min per log). Discover commands with the hint system, or just sit back, turn the lights down and enjoy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678480/extras/PF_StickMatches_Banner_alpha.png?t=1701916911"><h2 class="bb_tag">Hint System</h2>Letters you type will appear gold if they're part of a word that's one of the command words.<h2 class="bb_tag">Second Monitor Support</h2>Run Pixel Fireplace on a second monitor while you work. Double-click to switch to windowed mode, then drag the window to another screen and double-click again for fullscreen.<br/><br/>Enjoy a cozy work atmosphere :)<h2 class="bb_tag">How to Quit</h2>1) Press the Esc key or type WATER to exit from the fireplace screen to the title screen.<br/><br/>2) Press the Esc key at the title screen to quit.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polyturbo Drift Racing Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2677290/Polyturbo_Drift_Racing_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Get ready for the ultimate 3D car racing experience! "Polyturbo Drift Racing Simulator" combines the thrill of high-speed racing with the precision of simulation gameplay. Compete against other players in heart-pounding races and prove that you have what it takes to reach the finish line first.<br>
Key Features:<br>
<br>
-Intense Racing Action: Race against skilled opponents in a variety of exhilarating tracks. Show off your driving skills as you drift through sharp turns, dodge obstacles, and blaze towards victory.<br>
<br>
-Car Collection: As you win races, earn money to expand your car collection. Purchase faster and more powerful cars to gain an edge over your rivals.<br>
<br/>
-Earn Rewards: Winning races not only earns you bragging rights but also money. The more races you win, the more cash you'll have to spend on upgrading your car fleet.<br/>
<br/>
-Stunning 3D Graphics: Immerse yourself in the game's detailed 3D environments and beautifully designed cars. The realistic graphics enhance the overall racing experience.<br/>
<br/>
"Polyturbo Drift Racing Simulator" offers a heart-racing blend of simulation and racing, providing hours of excitement for players of all skill levels. Whether you're a seasoned racer or just getting started, this game promises thrilling competition and intense action. Take the wheel and prove you're the ultimate racing champion!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle Stations Blockade</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2581310/Battle_Stations_Blockade/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2581310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Arm the turrets and take aim as you take command of a gunboat in dangerous waters!</h2><br/><br/>Take command of a gunboat on an urgent mission to intercept stolen military intelligence and destroy the enemy’s advanced weapon systems! Battle Stations Blockade is an intense 3D rail shooter presented in voxel style. Receive orders and then set out on treacherous waters as you control a pair of gun turrets, shooting down aircraft, destroying boats and battleships, clearing mines, taking out paratroopers and more.<br/><br/>But watch your health! Each turret has a damage meter that will need to be replenished by eliminating targets, or you’ll fail the mission. Complete your assignments to climb in rank and unlock better weapons for your gunboat turrets, enabling you to shoot for even higher scores. Man both turrets in solo play or team up with a friend in local co-op!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2581310/extras/BattleStationsBlockade_gif_05.gif?t=1701866690"><br/><br/>Features:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Control the dual turrets of a gunboat as you navigate dangerous waters!<br/></li><li>Intercept a wide variety of enemy types and advanced weapon systems.<br/></li><li>Shoot down aircraft, sink boats and battleships, take out troops, clear mines and more!<br/></li><li>Enjoy arcade rail shooter gameplay in a unique chunky pixel style.<br/></li><li>Play solo or team up with a friend in local co-op.<br/></li><li>Climb rank based on performance and unlock more powerful upgrades!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2581310/extras/BattleStationsBlockade_gif_02.gif?t=1701866690"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freestyle Ice Skater</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2596630/Freestyle_Ice_Skater/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2596630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Freestyle Ice Skater is a casual action/sports game that takes place in real and fictional locations. Your goal is to join the local freestyle ice skaters - Nagyerdei Korisok - master your tricks and beat the rival team in an epic freestyle battle.<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br>
-Single player story mode where you progress by learning new tricks (mapped to keypress combos) / or solving puzzles.<br>
-Free skate mode on the maps with a couple of extra elements.<br>
-Fish game mode (a kind of a tag game, optionally with powerups)<br>
-Achievements						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Spellswapper</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682910/The_Spellswapper/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2682910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The Spellswapper</strong> is an arcade roguelite where you use spells to defeat waves of enemies. Command an ever-moving arsenal of spells. Swap out old spells for new ones after each wave, crafting a unique magical repertoire in every run.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2><br/><strong>Battle enemies</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2682910/extras/storeGif1.gif?t=1701861811"><br/><br/>Use your spells to defeat your enemies. Be wary of the various unique enemies you might encounter.<br/><br/><strong>Choose your spells</strong><br/><br/>After each wave, choose a new spell, swapping it out for one of your old spells. Gather three spells of the same element to activate potent synergy effects. Over the course of a run, you will eventually find more powerful spells in the form of rare spells and variant spells. If you are fortunate enough, you might even obtain one of the powerful legendary spells.<br/><br/><strong>Obtain items</strong><br/><br/>After every 5 waves you can select a powerful item. Choose wisely, the items will shape the identity of your run.<br/><br/><strong>Survive</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2682910/extras/storeGif2borders.gif?t=1701861811"><br/><br/>Survive 20 increasingly difficult waves and defeat the final boss to win. In true roguelite fashion, if you die, you will have to start over from the beginning. But, if you do succeed, you get to unlock new characters and items as rewards for winning.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 5+ characters, each one using different elements and having effects that modify your run right from the start<br/></li><li> 15+ base spells, each one available in 10+ different elements and modifiable by multiple different variants  <br/></li><li> 90+ items, which can improve your run in various ways<br/></li><li> 15+ Steam achievements<br/></li><li> 10 challenging "ascension" difficulty levels<br/></li><li> Seeded "daily runs" which are the same for all players on a given day<br/></li><li> Endless mode, allowing you to try survive as long as possible against the strengthening hordes</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Square Word: Hello Winter!❄️</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2615510/Square_Word_Hello_Winter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/description_steam_picture00.png?t=1701857718"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Winter is here!!! Let's play!!!</strong></h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Grab your winter gear and a blanket to enjoy a new SQUARE WORD episode!</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/separator.png?t=1701857718"><br/><br/><strong>ALEX, the little penguin,</strong> is very happy to start a new adventure with you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/puce.png?t=1701857718"> <strong>Four very cool themes: Christmas - Cold - Toyz - Cozy House</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/puce.png?t=1701857718"> 140+ words to find.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/puce.png?t=1701857718"> Handcrafted grids.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/puce.png?t=1701857718"> Daily challenge.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/puce.png?t=1701857718"> 4 difficulties (easy to very hard).<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/puce.png?t=1701857718"> Difficulty increasing gradually.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/puce.png?t=1701857718"> Letter &amp; word hints.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/puce.png?t=1701857718"> Collect Stamps with extra objectives and receive rewards!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/puce.png?t=1701857718"> Additional songs.<br/><br/><br/><strong>Are you ready?</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/description_steam_picture01.png?t=1701857718"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/separator.png?t=1701857718"><h2 class="bb_tag">All Square Word games:</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/34938/Square_Word_Bundle/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/poster_bundle.png?t=1701857718"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1707670/Square_Word_Summer_Edition/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/poster_1.png?t=1701857718"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2521940/Square_Word_Back_to_Work/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/poster_2.png?t=1701857718"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2615510/Square_Word_Hello_Winter/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615510/extras/poster_3.png?t=1701857718"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CheckMaze</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2348970/CheckMaze/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2348970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2348970/extras/wishlist.gif?t=1701855108"><br/><br/>Checkmaze is a simple game that's based on actual chess scenarios and uses original chess pieces. With more than 50 levels of puzzles that rely exclusively on classical chess pieces, there's plenty to keep you challenged, especially if you're a fan of classic old chess.<br/><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2348970/extras/cannon-600x338.gif?t=1701855108"><br/><br/>But that's not all Checkmaze has to offer. Checkmaze  becomes even more complex, surprising, and enjoyable as new pieces are added.  We have new pieces like traps, portals, and wizards with different abilities and behaviors that add an exciting twist to the game.<br/><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2348970/extras/spear-600x338.gif?t=1701855108"><br/><br/>New pieces  and mechanics are being added. <br/>3 new chess pieces and minimum 18 level for each of them.<br/>4 great levels.<br/>Moving pieces were added. Now mazes are changing as you play.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2348970/extras/ConditionalMove3-cut-600x338.gif?t=1701855108"><br/><br/>#### How to Play #### <br/>- you control the white pieces in CheckMaze.<br/>- your only purpose is to reach to the king and check it.<br/><br/>check the puzzle below and see how many moves it takes to reach checking position<br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2348970/extras/top_view.png?t=1701855108"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twizzle Puzzle: Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2704230/Twizzle_Puzzle_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Twizzle Puzzle: Cats - is the perfect puzzle game for a fun and rewarding pastime.<br/>Your goal is to assemble a picture of cute cats that has been cut into an equal number of pieces.<br/>Rotate the pieces to create the full picture, but think logically about the connections and solve the puzzle. <br/>There are 50 levels to complete, and the challenge becomes increasingly difficult as you progress.<br/>Enjoy a relaxing time connecting the pieces to create a beautiful picture of cats<br/><br/>In Twizzle Puzzle: Cats:<br/><br/>•50 levels<br/>•Beautiful art<br/>•Simple controls (mouse)<br/>•Achievements<br/>•Relaxing music<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704230/extras/3.png?t=1701851045"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704230/extras/1.png?t=1701851045"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704230/extras/2.png?t=1701851045"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704230/extras/4.png?t=1701851045"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nafanya the Poltergeist</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2704370/Nafanya_the_Poltergeist/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A game about a house spirit - Houseboy. With the name Nafanya. The player will have to get out of a multi-unit Soviet house, which is run by the Domovoi. To find the way out, you will have to solve riddles from the spirit, and maybe even make friends with him. Soviet atmosphere and immersion in the world of Domovy - their habits and whims.<br>
As you progress, you will need to find keys and open locked rooms. Perform various tasks and solve puzzles. A first-person game with elements of horror. Explore the house, apartments and mysteries. Find clues and assemble the whole story into a single picture. The darkness can conceal various mysteries.<br>
<br>
F - flashlight, Tab - inventory<br>
In-game controls WASD - move, left mouse button - pick up an item. Right mouse button - inspect the item.<br>
<br>
Features:<br/>
- pleasant graphics;<br/>
- simple control;<br/>
- interesting gameplay						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angrbotha Mountains</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2318670/Angrbotha_Mountains/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318670/extras/symbol_logo.png?t=1701845559"><br/><br/>"Demons and undeads roam the land they say..." <br/>Imagine yourself being unwillingly caught in the fight between your world and the evil god Nemurtviya. The evil god has been trying to enter the world once more, and this time, he intends to stay and rule a desolate world forever. Forces of good have spent a long time keeping him away but have forgotten the weapons and alliances that stopped him hundreds of years ago. In this situation, you hear rumors in the inns that demons and undeads roam the land. Evil cults are popping up everywhere. And you need to take your blacksmithing supplies to Fallegthorp as usual. To get there you cross the Angrbotha mountains as usual. This is where the adventure begins.<br/><br/><strong>Angrbotha Mountains</strong>, an adventure RPG game that immerses you in a dark story and cinematic experience. It is a short cinematic, story-driven adventure RPG game. <strong>Regard it as a short solo RPG session with a game master</strong>. Levelling up, meet wandering creatures, putting the story together, making choices, exploring and finding items are important parts to put the events to rest. Sneak up on enemies and make kills in one hit if successful, so called Assasination mode.<br/><br/>In Angrbotha Mountains you will take on the role of a hero on a quest to uncover the truth about the past and stop the terrifying from happening. The game is short but packs an intense punch with its storyline and cinematic elements.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318670/extras/banner2.png?t=1701845559"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepped - Tower Defense</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684720/Prepped__Tower_Defense/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<u><strong>ONLY THE PARANOID SURVIVE</strong></u> , as a Prepper you have been stock piling &amp; tinkering with some new machinery. <br/><br/>It was only after coming out of the bunker you <strong>knew </strong> you'd make use of it.<br/><br/>Make use of your hordes of helpers, actually.. Use as many as you'd like!<br/><br/>One last thing... Don't forget about what locals call Big Mama. Rumored to be the height of a two story building, she is a lot to put down!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684720/extras/backgrounder__2_.jpg?t=1701841328"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong><u>NO LIMIT UNITS</u></strong> - build to your hearts content.<br/></li><li> Maybe you'd like to make use of the firearms you've been stock piling. <br/></li><li> OR maybe you can make use the New York man you let live with you when the bombs dropped. <br/></li><li> OR maybe you could put Mr. New York on a turret.<br/></li><li> ALSO don't forget about Big Mama.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
