<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_TITLE_FULLSCREEN.gif?t=1707759948"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_1.png?t=1707759948"><br/> <br/>In New Eden, 1695, communities of settlers are plagued by a dreadful curse. As Banishers, step into their lives, investigate the source of evil, unravel chilling mysteries, explore diverse landscapes, and interact with unforgettable characters whose fate lies in your hands.<br/><br/>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden is an all-new title crafted by renowned studio DON'T NOD, known for their acclaimed titles such as Life is Strange and Vampyr. Immerse yourself in an intimate narrative Action-RPG, taking you on an exhilarating journey between life, death, love and sacrifices.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_2.png?t=1707759948"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_FANTASY.gif?t=1707759948"><br/>Play as a couple of Banishers, Red and Antea, experienced spirit hunters entrusted with the daunting task of dispelling a malevolent curse through powerful rituals. Protect the living from the threat of lingering ghosts and specters, and become a beacon of hope in a world consumed by darkness.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_3.png?t=1707759948"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_NARATION_LOVE.gif?t=1707759948"><br/>Experience a heart-wrenching love story between Antea Duarte and Red mac Raith. When Antea is killed and turned into a spirit, you find yourself facing a choice. Will you uphold your oath and ascend her soul, or will you sacrifice the living in the hope of bringing her back? Your decisions will shape the fate of New Eden’s inhabitants - may they be living or dead, and determine the end of your journey.<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>BLAME</strong> the living and sacrifice their lives, holding them responsible for their actions<br/></li><li><strong>BANISH</strong> souls of the departed, condemning them to eternal suffering<br/></li><li><strong>ASCEND</strong> souls, liberating them from eternal sorrow and granting them serenity</li></ul><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_4.png?t=1707759948"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_COMBAT.gif?t=1707759948"><br/>Banishers are specialized in combat against undead creatures, such as specters or ghosts. Combine Red's physical arsenal with Antea's supernatural powers in a dynamic combat system. Find your own style by mixing weapon attacks and spiritual abilities. Powerful synergies will lead you to defeat New Eden’s most dangerous enemies and bosses.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_6.png?t=1707759948"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_SKILL.gif?t=1707759948"><br/>Unleash the full power of the Banishers by unlocking new gear and supernatural abilities. By exploring New Eden, you will find ancient artifacts, trinkets and valuable resources to enhance your equipment in preparation of future fights. In addition to your arsenal, progress in Antea’s skill trees to upgrade her devastating spectral powers and unseal new combos.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_5.png?t=1707759948"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_EXPLORATION.gif?t=1707759948"><br/>Investigate haunting cases in a mystical world full of dark secrets. Discover New Eden, a North America settlement marked by terrible stories and secrets of its tormented inhabitants. Understanding each resident’s motivations will be essential to guide your decisions throughout the game.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_7.png?t=1707759948"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Ninja Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_9" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🥋🐾 WELCOME TO 100 NINJA CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🗡️</h2>🗡️Join the cutest adventure in the Ninja world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of ninja themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game.<br/>😊Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x200.png?t=1707750752"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Ninja Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Extra.png?t=1707750752"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816000/100_Ninja_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1707750752"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815980/100_Ninja_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Artbook.png?t=1707750752"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x1.png?t=1707750752"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1707750752"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_10" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_11" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Tiles TD: Tower Wars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2447060/Monster_Tiles_TD_Tower_Wars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447060/extras/build.png?t=1707638414"><h2 class="bb_tag">Join millions of others - Play <u>Monster Tiles TD: Tower Wars</u> for free today!</h2><br/><br/>Forget the boring old days of defending a fixed path that the developers created for you 👎. <strong>Monster Tiles TD offers a breath of fresh air in the tower defense genre, allowing you to build your own path to defend 💪!</strong><br/><br/>After completing each wave, you gain a new randomly generated tile to place wherever you want (try to be smart and strategic about it, though 😛). Building your own custom tower defense allows you to <u>play how YOU want</u>, with the <u>characters and strategies that YOU enjoy</u> the most, and <u>on a map that YOU created</u>. This dynamic base-building mechanic creates endless replayability with every single game being different than the last! ✨✨✨<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447060/extras/evolve.png?t=1707638414"><br/><br/>🔥 <strong><u>FEATURES</u></strong> 🔥<br/><br/>A fleet of medieval space pirates are invading the monsters' base, and it is up to you to stop them! Unlock, upgrade, and evolve your monsters to defend the base from spacefaring knights, mages, pirates, and countless other unique enemies.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Build and defend a custom tower defense maze.<br/></li><li>Roguelike progression and upgrades.<br/></li><li>Over 35 monster tower types to build, each with unique skills and synergies.<br/></li><li>Evolve monsters to greater forms for powerful stat and skill bonuses.<br/></li><li>Multiple RPG and TD classes and specialties.<br/></li><li>Optimize tower placements to activate powerful synergy effects.<br/></li><li>Equip monsters with epic gear dropped from bosses.<br/></li><li>Conquer different maps, difficulties, and game modes.<br/></li><li>Unlock, upgrade, and evolve your monsters to defend against spacefaring knights, mages, pirates, and more!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447060/extras/conquer.png?t=1707638414"><br/><br/>🛠️ <strong><u>BUILD YOUR BASE</u></strong> 🛠️<br/><br/>Monster Tiles TD features a unique tower defense mechanic where you manually rotate and place a randomly generated tile after each wave to control the enemy path. Each game starts off easy, with only one enemy spawn location and a simple straightforward path. However, as you reach higher waves, the path will branch off into dozens of spawn points, increasing the difficulty and number of locations to defend.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Strategically placing tiles to optimize tower placements and enemy spawn locations is key to a successful defense.<br/></li><li>Influence your defensive positions and enemy pathing by choosing where to place the next tile and expand your base after each wave.<br/></li><li>Branch out to loot Treasure Islands for huge rewards, while still maintaining a strong, consolidated defense.<br/></li><li>Each new tile is randomly generated, meaning every single game you play is different!<br/></li><li>Roguelike and RPG base defender mechanics.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447060/extras/roguelike.png?t=1707638414"><br/><br/>💪 <strong><u>EVOLVE &amp; UPGRADE</u></strong> 💪<br/><br/>Improve your defense and speed up your gameplay by researching countless upgrades that affect nearly every aspect of the game. Strengthen your monsters, bolster your tower defenses, debuff your enemies, and influence the tiles on the map with <i>several hundred</i> upgrade combinations. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Unlock and upgrade countless artifacts, spells, specialties, and technologies.<br/></li><li>Collect and upgrade dozens of powerful equipment, ranging from common to divine.<br/></li><li>Upgrade your player level and collect rewards by completing games.<br/></li><li>Upgrade monsters by collecting gold, energy, credits and PvP Tournament points.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447060/extras/defend.png?t=1707638414"><br/><br/>🚀 <strong><u>ENDLESS PROGRESSION</u></strong> 🚀<br/><br/>Progress through multiple difficulty modes ranging from easy to impossible. Then, spice the end-game up with the unique endless and score attack modes. Each game mode adds new powerful enemy types and additional challenges. Reach higher waves on each difficulty to unlock new monster towers and upgrades, and compete against others on the leaderboards! The fun never ends in Monster Tiles TD!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Reach higher waves and difficulties to unlock new monsters, upgrades, and rewards.<br/></li><li>Each game mode adds new enemy types and challenges.<br/></li><li>Unique Endless, Sudden Death, Score Attack, and Swarm game modes.<br/></li><li>Competitive PvP game modes.<br/></li><li>Compete against other players for the highest rank on the leaderboards.<br/></li><li>Customize your personal leaderboards look by completing challenges to unlock custom leaderboard icons, titles, and backgrounds.<br/></li><li>Complete daily tasks and achievements to bolster your towers.<br/></li><li>Enjoy free rewards from regular in-game events and gifts.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447060/extras/actionPacked.png?t=1707638414"><br/><br/>In Monster Tiles TD: Tower Wars, you're not only defending, but also building a custom maze, evolving monsters, and strategizing for the next level. The dynamic roguelike base-building system makes each wave unique and unpredictable, requiring you to adapt your tactics on the go. Unleash a variety of monsters, each with its own evolution path and unique skills, and evolve them into legendary creatures. Synergize your towers to defeat even the toughest foes.<br/><br/>Build and guard your base, evolve your monster towers, defend against the attacking space pirates, and compete in PvP Tournaments. The fun never ends in Monster Tiles TD!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FgYfZXyVD2W" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447060/extras/discord_logo.png?t=1707638414"/></a><br/>Chat with the developer and other players, and get more information on our Discord!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2 - Upgrade to Super Citizen Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2514130/HELLDIVERS_2__Upgrade_to_Super_Citizen_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Edition includes:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>‘DP-53 Savior of the Free’ Armor Set.<br/></li><li>‘Will of the People’ Cape.<br/></li><li>‘MP-98 Knight’ Weapon.<br/></li><li>Super Citizen Status.<br/></li><li>Stratagem Hero Ship Game.<br/></li><li>‘Steeled Veterans’ Premium Warbond.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1707382807"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1707382807"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1707382807"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1707382807"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1707382807"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION </h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1707382807"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1707382807"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort.<br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KONOSUBA - God's Blessing on this Wonderful World! Love For These Clothes Of Desire!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2349140/KONOSUBA__Gods_Blessing_on_this_Wonderful_World_Love_For_These_Clothes_Of_Desire/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/KonoSuba_KeyArt_Landscape_WithLogo.png?t=1707479148"><br/>Follow Kazuma and company, as they discover a mysterious "Black Slab" which curses them with desires contrary to their personality. The gang must now find and feed ingredients to the slab to create outfits which match and fulfil their new desires, and thus break their curse. Are you ready to meet Darkness as a ruthless dominatrix? How about Aqua as a prim and proper goddess? Or Megumin as the proud leader of the Lolita League?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/new-narrative-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/01._Black_slab!_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Witness a new story in visual novel form! Featuring a full cast of fan-favourite characters from the series, this wild adventure gives you the chance to build up affection with up to seven heroines!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/get-to-work-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/02._Schedule_overview!_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Fill out a weekly planner for each character based on their strengths to earn funds and resources which can be used for making outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/make-decisions-orange-1.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/decision_making_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Each of them has her own story endings and special dress-up CGs, so pick your words wisely and avoid invoking their wrath! Your choices matter! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/Manage-resources-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/04._Resources_schedule_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Collect resources to create outfits by completing tasks and quests. Manage your finances carefully to afford the materials you are missing, and prioritise gathering the outfit-specific ingredients you will need.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/play-dress-up-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/05._Make_more_clothes!_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Once the mystical outfits have been made it’s time to play dress-up! Be ready for twists and turns as your favourite characters’ personalities change with each curse and desire-fulfilling piece of clothing.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/DANCE-smaller-no-boaarder.gif?t=1707479148"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III - BlackCell (Season 2)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731840/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III__BlackCell_Season_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Get Call of Duty® Points* and in-game content for Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III and Call of Duty®: Warzone™.<br>
<br>
Offering includes:<br>
<br/>
- Battle Pass for Season 2<br/>
- 20 Battle Token Tier Skips<br/>
<br/>
Exclusive BlackCell Sector on the Battle Map:<br/>
<br/>
- 1100 Call of Duty® Points<br/>
- BlackCell Operator<br/>
- Assault Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Battle Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Finishing Move<br/>
<br/>
- BlackCell Bonus Topper with 11 additional reactive Operator skin alternatives and 6 Weapon Blueprints with Tracers.<br/>
<br/>
Activision may update, replace, or remove this in-game content at any time.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jigsaw Puzzles Infinite</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1946140/Jigsaw_Puzzles_Infinite/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1946140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							If you like jigsaw puzzles - this is your game.<br/>Sit back, relax and build puzzles to your heart's content.<h2 class="bb_tag">What you get with Jigsaw Puzzle Infinite:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Infinite possibilities</strong>- Choose from one of the dozens of included puzzles or add your own images without any limits<br/></li><li><strong>Classic mode</strong> - Jigsaw puzzles you know and love. Take your time and build the puzzle with the help of useful sorting features<br/></li><li><strong>Sorting</strong> - Sort pieces by section, sort out edges, or just spread them out neatly <br/></li><li><strong>Zen Mode</strong> - Enter the flow and assemble the puzzle piece by piece<br/></li><li><strong>Pieces snap to each other </strong>and are not placed on a preset grid - just like real puzzles<br/></li><li><strong>Adjust difficulty </strong>- Freely choose number of pieces and snapping distance<br/></li><li><strong>Different piece shapes </strong>- Choose from multiple possible shapes of the pieces<br/></li><li><strong>Free camera movement </strong>- Zoom in and out, and move around the board freely <br/></li><li><strong>Every puzzle unique </strong>- Pieces are randomized each time new puzzle is generated<br/></li><li><strong>Never lose any progress </strong>- Don't worry about losing data, autosaving will keep it safe<br/></li><li><strong>No microtransactions </strong>- Enjoy the puzzles up to 200 pieces or unlock all current and future content with a single purchase</li></ul><br/><i><strong>Disclaimer</strong>: The base game puzzle images (base game + Full Unlock DLC) use AI generated art. All additional free puzzle packs do NOT use AI art.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jigsaw Puzzles Infinite</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1946140/Jigsaw_Puzzles_Infinite/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1946140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							If you like jigsaw puzzles - this is your game.<br/>Sit back, relax and build puzzles to your heart's content.<h2 class="bb_tag">What you get with Jigsaw Puzzle Infinite:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Infinite possibilities</strong>- Choose from one of the dozens of included puzzles or add your own images without any limits<br/></li><li><strong>Classic mode</strong> - Jigsaw puzzles you know and love. Take your time and build the puzzle with the help of useful sorting features<br/></li><li><strong>Sorting</strong> - Sort pieces by section, sort out edges, or just spread them out neatly <br/></li><li><strong>Zen Mode</strong> - Enter the flow and assemble the puzzle piece by piece<br/></li><li><strong>Pieces snap to each other </strong>and are not placed on a preset grid - just like real puzzles<br/></li><li><strong>Adjust difficulty </strong>- Freely choose number of pieces and snapping distance<br/></li><li><strong>Different piece shapes </strong>- Choose from multiple possible shapes of the pieces<br/></li><li><strong>Free camera movement </strong>- Zoom in and out, and move around the board freely <br/></li><li><strong>Every puzzle unique </strong>- Pieces are randomized each time new puzzle is generated<br/></li><li><strong>Never lose any progress </strong>- Don't worry about losing data, autosaving will keep it safe<br/></li><li><strong>No microtransactions </strong>- Enjoy the puzzles up to 200 pieces or unlock all current and future content with a single purchase</li></ul><br/><i><strong>Disclaimer</strong>: The base game puzzle images (base game + Full Unlock DLC) use AI generated art. All additional free puzzle packs do NOT use AI art.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WitchHand</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420880/WitchHand/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/store-gif-01.gif?t=1707460594"><br/><br/>In <strong>WitchHand</strong>, you use cards to build your empire of witches. Maximize the production of your villages and use your resources strategically to upgrade and expand. Focus on trade, alchemy research, or war in order to secure your coven's place amongst the Council of Fates, influencing the destiny of all. Work with your neighbors to secure a better future or crush them and use their bones to fuel your spells. When the witching hour comes each night, your witch's powers are at their strongest, while unseen forces work against you. You must expand and manage your coven to new heights if you are to withstand the coming darkness. No rest for the wicked.<h2 class="bb_tag">A CIVILIZATION OF WITCHES</h2>WitchHand folds the 4X strategy formula into card-based gameplay. You'll perform strategic actions like exploring, expanding, and exterminating through real-time card placement. Manage worker placement, village production, and research in order to advance the strength and reach of your coven.<h2 class="bb_tag">WIELD THE POWERS OF THE WITCHES OF THE REALMS</h2>Each witch has a unique selection of spells, buildings, and units that defines them. Empower your villages and production with the Celestial Witch. Overpower your enemies with the might of the Chaos Witch. Cook delicious, stat-boosting meals with the Chef Witch. Choose the witch that best suits your playstyle and have full control over your research paths to further personalize your playthrough.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/spellbook_and_wonder_crop.gif?t=1707460594"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXPLORE THE MYSTERIES OF THE NINTH</h2>The Council of Fates does not have faith in your expedition to the Ninth. Make alliances with rival factions or declare war and take their resources for your own. Manage your relationships through trade and gifts or with a well-placed fireball spell. Grow your coven to new heights and prove the Council wrong.<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES:</h2>🧭 <strong>Explore</strong> the Ninth Realm to discover new sites for your villages, necessary reagents to fuel your spells, and clues to the mystery of the Ninth's sudden appearance.<br/><br/>🏘️ <strong>Expand</strong> your coven by building new villages, perfecting production, and trading with the local factions.<br/><br/>🔥 <strong>Exterminate</strong> the beasts of the void, whose relentless assaults on your coven jeopardize your mission.<br/><br/>🧙‍♀️ <strong>Choose</strong> the witch to lead your coven, each with unique spells and playstyles.<br/><br/>⌛ <strong>Impress</strong> the Council of Fates and benefit from their powerful boons.<br/><br/>🕊️ <strong>Peaceful Mode</strong> - The option to play without the constant threat of extinction.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/combat-crop.gif?t=1707460594"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/store-gif-04.gif?t=1707460594"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1707785084"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal from ECHOS</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1707785084"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about the future of Sheepy, limited edition merch and more.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXIT KUN</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781370/EXIT_KUN/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a game of finding differences and observing. Our game challenges players to carefully observe and spot the distinctions that lead them to the elusive "Exit KUN."<br>
<br>
Game Overview:<br>
<br>
You find yourself trapped in an enigmatic underground labyrinth, and your only goal is to reach "Exit KUN." The journey demands keen observation of your surroundings. Every detail matters, and anomalies could be your key to progress.<br>
<br>
How to Play:<br>
<br/>
Observe Carefully: Scrutinize your surroundings to uncover anomalies that may guide your way or pose a threat.<br/>
Turn Back if Needed: If anomalies are detected, swift decision-making is crucial. Turn back immediately to avoid unforeseen consequences.<br/>
Forward Momentum: Should your observation reveal no anomalies, press forward. <br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Developer Notes:<br/>
This game is inspired by Exit 8. You are free to create, upload, and monetize videos and any other content featuring Game on platforms such as YouTube, Twitch, and other video-sharing websites. The characters, places, and elements involved in the game are fictitious. Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, or events is purely coincidental.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soak &amp; Splash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2051500/Soak__Splash/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2051500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the Soak &amp; Splash! Get ready to sweat, socialize, and have a blast with your friends in this unique game that combines the best of traditional sauna culture with modern party fun.<br>
<br>
First, step into the steamy sauna and feel the heat and humidity envelop your body.<br>
<br>
Once everyone is inside, it's time to start the fun. You can start by whisking each other with broom.<br>
<br>
Feeling competitive? You can also fight with other players with sauna equipment. Or you can simply relax and enjoy the company of your friends, chatting, singing, or telling jokes.<br>
<br/>
Finally, when you've had enough of the sauna, you can cool off in the nearby pool or shower.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, this game is all about having fun, bonding with your friends, and experiencing the unique benefits of sauna culture. So why wait? Download game and get ready to sweat, laugh, and enjoy life to the fullest!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/315210/Suicide_Squad_Kill_the_Justice_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Rocksteady Studios, the creators of the Batman: Arkham series, Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is a genre-defying third-person action shooter where the ultimate band of misfits must do the impossible to save the world: Kill the Justice League.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/SSKTJL_Intro.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Join the newly “recruited” members of Amanda Waller’s infamous Task Force X (aka the Suicide Squad), Harley Quinn, Deadshot, Captain Boomerang and King Shark, as they set out on an impossible mission to Kill the Justice League. Drop into an expansive and dynamic open-world Metropolis ravaged by Brainiac’s invasion and terrorized by the heroes who once protected it. <br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/Traversal_2.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Each Squad member brings their own traversal mechanics to help them navigate a sprawling and battle-torn Metropolis, combining free-roaming exploration and combat verticality for an unforgettable experience. Players are free to experiment with a variety of different play styles to unleash maximum damage on their enemies. Whether in single player or online with up to three of your friends, players can take on this suicide mission their own way.<br/><br/>Post-launch, players can expect a continuously evolving Metropolis with free new playable villains, environments, weapons, in-game events, and more, all included with purchase of the base game.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788630/Nothing_Together/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play together. Maybe.<br/><br/>Just do Nothing as the timer goes up and climb the leaderboards. If you do Something, you lose.<br/><br/>Play in <strong>Together </strong>mode, where up to 20 players unite to do Nothing, or compete with other players in <strong>Battle Royale</strong> to find out who's the best at doing Nothing!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161700/Persona_3_Reload/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a transfer student thrust into an unexpected fate when entering the hour "hidden" between one day and the next. Awaken an incredible power and chase the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fight for your friends, and leave a mark on their memories forever. <br/><br/>Persona 3 Reload is a captivating reimagining of the genre-defining RPG, reborn for the modern era.<br/><br/>Key Features: <br/>- Experience the pivotal game of the Persona series faithfully remade with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, and signature stylish UI. <br/><br/>-Fully immerse yourself in an emotional, gripping journey with new scenes, character interactions, and additional voiceover.<br/><br/>- Choose how to meaningfully spend each day through various activities, from exploring the Port Island to forging genuine bonds with beloved characters.<br/><br/>- Build and command your optimal team to take down otherworldly Shadows and climb closer to the truth.<br/><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Deluxe Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook: Filled with 64 pages of character art, concept art, backgrounds and other illustrations from the game!<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack: Listen to newly arranged tracks from the original Persona 3 plus all-new tracks from Persona 3 Reload, presented by the Atlus sound team for a total of 60 new songs.</li></ul><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Premium Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack<br/></li><li>Persona 3 Reload DLC Pack:  P5R Phantom Thieves Costume Set, P5R Shujin Academy Costume Set, P5R Persona Set 1, P5R Persona Set 2 , P5R BGM Set, P4G Yasogami High Costume Set, P4G Persona Set</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLCARD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1201540/HELLCARD/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Hellcard</strong> is a <strong>cooperative roguelike deckbuilder</strong> that can be played in both <strong>Singleplayer </strong>and <strong>Multiplayer </strong>modes. The game takes place in the paper dungeons known from Book of Demons, and its main mechanics revolve around deckbuilding and fast-paced tactical card battles. <br/><br/>If you are excited about <strong>HELLCARD</strong>, be sure to <strong>wishlist </strong>the game on Steam. Otherwise, consider wishlisting anyway - who knows, we might surprise you yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif5_600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/>What makes <strong>HELLCARD</strong> unique and different from other deck-building games is that <strong>monster placement actually matters</strong> and can be used to your advantage.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif4_600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>HELLCARD</strong> supports <strong>co-op battles</strong> with up to three heroes facing the Archdemon's hordes. In <strong>singleplayer mode</strong>, you can descend into the dungeons solo or recruit computer-controlled companions. In <strong>multiplayer mode</strong>, your friends or strangers can help you battle the hordes of hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif1-2-3-600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/r2g_logo_fixed.png?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>Return 2 Games</strong> is a series of unique mid-core games inspired by the golden days of PC gaming. Each R2G title is a tribute to a single hit game from the '90s: a reimagining of a single universal story for a brand-new audience, using modern means and innovative, often vastly simplified gameplay mechanics.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/pillars.png?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>HELLCARD</strong> was first envisioned as a new game mode inside the Book of Demons universe, but we soon realized that its design is huge and that it should be executed as a stand-alone spin-off game. If you want to learn more about Return 2 Games or support us in the development of the series, visit the <strong>Supporter Pack</strong> store page. On release, <strong>HELLCARD </strong>will be a part of it.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/706770/Return_2_Games_Supporters_Pack/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/706770/Return_2_Games_Supporters_Pack/</a><br/><strong>Book of Demons</strong>, the first part in the series is already here, be sure to check it out as it includes a free demo. <br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/449960/Book_of_Demons/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/449960/Book_of_Demons/</a><br/>Also, be sure to check out <strong>Book of Aliens</strong>, the second book in the series and a tribute to MicroProse’ UFO: Enemy Unknown that’s also in the works:<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1196230/Book_of_Aliens/" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1196230/Book_of_Aliens/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1131620/Dominion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Expand a small kingdom to a mighty Dominion!  <br/><br/>Play the Spiel des Jahres winning boardgame beloved by millions around the world. This is the officially licensed implementation.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Reigning.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Discover the game that defined a genre, Dominion was first to popularize deck-building and remains a staple of tabletop. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/GrowYourKingdom.png?t=1707010484">Collect as many Victory Points as you can by building a powerful deck. Your deck starts out a small sad set of Estates and Coppers, but you hope that by the end of the game it will be brimming with Gold, Provinces, and the inhabitants and structures of your kingdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/BuildEngine.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Choose wisely among the 10 cards available in the tableau to create the strongest combos to dominate your opponent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CollectAllExpansions.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Make your games more exciting with additional cards and rules from up to 15 expansions including the recent Plunder expansion! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/NearInfiniteVariety.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Over one hundred thirty-two septillion possible Kingdom combinations, 500+ cards, 15 and counting expansions, and ongoing promo packs make Dominion one of the most extensive and replayable boardgames in the hobby. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CompeteComputer.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Sharpen your skills with solitaire style solo play against a robust AI, with four levels of difficulty. Our innovative AI learns through self-play. Earn Achievements and win in Recommended Sets against each AI level. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/PlayWithFriends.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Join up to 6 players online through your device or pass and play among your friends. Play ranked or unranked matchmaking, with realtime and asynchronous modes. Set up a private table for a family game, challenge a stranger in the lobby, or invite a friend!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Daily.png?t=1707010484"><br/>A daily ritual to relax with over a cup of coffee. Try the Daily Dominion, a free puzzle level available to players around the world. Practice your strategy to keep up a winning streak and climb the leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CrossPlatform.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Play from any supported device, whenever you want, after verifying your email in-game. Join games with opponents on platforms other than your own to enjoy the largest possible multiplayer pool and speedy matchmaking. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/JoinCommunity.png?t=1707010484"><br/>With an active Discord and online community, make new friends or challenge new people to a game. Export and share kingdoms and game summaries to compare strategies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/FreeToPlay.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Download the game that started it all for free! The base set of Dominion is available at no charge. Try the rotation of expansion cards in the Daily at no cost once per day. Jump into a lobby game with expansions enabled to try before you buy. Only the host needs to own the expansions.    <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Intro.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Learn the ropes in this easy to pick-up, hard to master title. Play one of the most highly regarded strategy tabletop games of all time through our simple tutorial.  The core loop is easy to follow, but offers a wealth of strategy to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>1-6 player</strong> support<br/></li><li><strong>500 </strong> plus <strong>cards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Solo play</strong> against four AI difficulties<br/></li><li><strong>Async </strong>&amp; <strong>real-time</strong> multiplayer<br/></li><li><strong>Ranked</strong> &amp; <strong>unranked</strong> matchmaking<br/></li><li><strong>Lobby</strong> &amp; <strong>Private game</strong> tables<br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform multiplayer</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform purchases</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Daily challenge</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Challenging AI</strong> that learns through self-play<br/></li><li><strong>Recommended Sets</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Customize</strong>, save &amp; share <strong>Kingdoms</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Achievements</strong>, <strong>Stats </strong>&amp; <strong>Leaderboards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Pass &amp; Play</strong> mode<br/></li><li>Automated <strong>score-keeping</strong> &amp; hints<br/></li><li><strong>Smart-play</strong> options to streamline gameplay<br/></li><li><strong>Jumbo mode</strong> for readability on phones<br/></li><li><strong>Turbo mode</strong> to zoom through games quickly<br/></li><li><strong>Tutorial</strong> &amp; <strong>Rules</strong><br/></li><li><strong>4 languages</strong>: English, Japanese, German, French<br/></li><li><strong>15 expansions</strong> plus three promo packs </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Awards for the Boardgame</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Awards.png?t=1707010484"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/881020/Granblue_Fantasy_Relink/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/881020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Story<br/>
Granblue Fantasy takes place in the Sky Realm, a world where myriad islands float in a great blue expanse. Take your role as captain of a skyfaring crew, joined by a scrappy little dragon named Vyrn and a young girl with mysterious powers named Lyria. Together you sail with a colorful cast of crewmates, including kings and misfits alike, for Estalucia, a fabled island beyond the end of the skies.<br/>
<br/>
In the Zegagrande Skydom, islands are guarded by powerful creatures known as primal beasts and winds carry tales of a secretive organization known as the Church of Avia. Unveil a web of intrigue reaching far beyond the borders of Zegagrande and engage in a battle for the fate of the Sky Realm itself.<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay<br/>
Engage in real-time combat with a party of four in this character action RPG—choose from a diverse roster of skyfarers, each with their own unique weapons, skills, and combat styles. Teamwork makes the dream work with party-based mechanics such as Link Attacks and Chain Bursts to help you crush foes in spectacular fashion. Tackle quests solo or with the help of others for up to 4-player co-op and take down treacherous foes to score rare loot to further enhance your gear. Every enemy and party formation has its own strengths and weaknesses—the key to victory lies in working out how these pieces fit together.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced combat not your thing? Assist modes can provide accessibility for gamers of all skill levels. Toggle on Full Assist to have all actions performed automatically during battle!<br/>
<br/>
The Sky Realm is rich in lore and history. Browse Lyria's journal at any point during the game to access a trove of writings on the world's peoples, places, and more. In addition to the wealth of side quests available, Fate Episodes allow you to delve into the backstories of each member of your crew!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlazBlue Entropy Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2273430/BlazBlue_Entropy_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/原创声明-英语.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗EN_.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>Charismatic character designs with unique aesthetic styles and dramatic animations create a flamboyant, awesome combat experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快的动作连招EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快动作连招.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>Smooth controls, infinite possibilities of combos, and realistic combat feedback. This is the roguelite game with the best action experience yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超多角色豪华制作EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/全员图618x346.jpg?t=1706765621"><br/>Ten playable characters with vibrant personalities, unique combat styles, and immersive voice-acting.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式自由定制EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式，自由定制en.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>There are hundreds of moves for you to build around, plus countless elemental effects and legacy skills passed between characters. The possibilities are infinite. Time to make the best fighter of your own!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/抉择拯救世界EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/GIF-抉择拯救世界EN.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>In the future where the world has been plunged into chaos, people enter a cyberspace called ACE, seeking their last chance to resolve the crisis.<br/>If you are the only person in this world who knows the truth, how will you react?<br/>The ending is also the beginning. Your decision will decide humanity's future.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BioGun: Clinical Trial</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2778550/BioGun_Clinical_Trial/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778550/extras/BGN_Prologue_GIF_1.gif?t=1707142146"><br/><br/><strong>Transfer your progress from this prologue to the main game</strong><br/><br/>Join Bek on his journey to save the entire canine species from an extinction caused by the sinister Dooper Virus. Inject yourself into a zany hand-drawn world of germs, cells, and winding passages full of vibrant characters and ferocious bosses with a story that takes place inside our beloved pets.<br/><br/>Give your dog a fighting chance by aiding its immune system to fight off the Dooper Virus. Befriend cells on your journey, absorb new powers from vanquished foes and explore vital organs to prevent them from failing! Will you be the vaccine to save dog-kind from extinction or will DocX have to return to the drawing board?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778550/extras/BGN_Prologue_GIF_2.gif?t=1707142146"><br/><strong>Game Features</strong><br/><br/>Prologue version of the game BioGun. The story begins with clinical trial.<br/><br/>Fast paced side-scrolling 360 shooter action with all the modern gameplay mechanics you’ve come to expect and more.<br/><br/>Blast your enemies with an impressive array of weapons. Augment your DNA and modify your playstyle using Nano-Chips. <br/><br/>Take on bosses inspired by real diseases in uniquely designed encounters.<br/><br/>Complete side missions to aid Cells in need. Explore each organ to earn rewards and learn about the life forms that live there.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778550/extras/BGN_Prologue_GIF_3.gif?t=1707142146"><br/>Traverse a hand-drawn microscopic world full of traditionally animated cells, germs, viruses and bacteria. Meet the wondrous creatures, both friendly and hostile, that inhabit it. Discover the many secrets cleverly hidden in your dog's body.<br/><br/>You will be accompanied on your mission by a blood-pumping score by Juhani Junkala<br/><br/>Save humanity's best friend. Prove that you’re the vaccine that can put an end to the pet-demic. What are you waiting for? Put on your hazard suit and blast some viral scum! The fate of dog-kind is in your hands!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2772560/Supermarket_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This Prologue is a limited version of the full game to stop waiting and jump into running your supermarket already. Don't forget to wishlist the full game to continue your most fun supermarket experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Design your store, optimizing for efficiency and aesthetics. Determine where products are displayed, manage your aisles, and ensure a smooth shopping experience for your customers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Order stock using an in-game computer and anticipate the arrival of your next delivery. Unpack goods, organize them in your storage room and display them on shelves, fridges, and freezers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Read product barcodes, handle cash and credit card transactions, and ensure customers leave satisfied with their shopping and checkout experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier_Raw.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Navigate the complexities of a real-time market. Buy products when prices dip and determine the best-selling prices to balance customer satisfaction with profit margins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><br/>Wishlist the full game "Supermarket Simulator" where every decision matters. Will you rise to the occasion, transforming a modest establishment into a retail powerhouse, all while balancing customer satisfaction, finances, and mafia expectations?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Lily - Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2220360/Paper_Lily__Chapter_1/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Something terrible has happened. You can’t bear to think about it - but you can’t live like this anymore. You stopped attending school, you haven’t left your house in months, you have no reason to get out of bed anymore. There are no choices left.<br/><br/>No choice except... that strange golden letter.<br/><br/>It’s time to get your life back together. <br/><br/>One last try.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/divider.png?t=1706724298"><br/><br/>Paper Lily is a story-driven, psychological horror RPG where each puzzle has multiple solutions and outcomes. <strong>There is always another way.</strong><br/>Follow Lacie's story as you explore a dangerous hidden world, solve puzzles in multiple different ways, and face strange enemies. The game is playable in about 4 hours and contains multiple endings depending on your actions.<br/><br/>Paper Lily - Chapter 1 is the continuation to the prologue, <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1698960" rel="" target="_blank">Project Kat</a>, but it can also  be enjoyed without having played it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/lacie_sai_walk.gif?t=1706724298"><h2 class="bb_tag">Out of Context Features</h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple ways of solving puzzles!<br/></li><li>Touch grass, and trees<br/></li><li>Minigames where you press buttons and push boxes around<br/></li><li>Call your mother<br/></li><li>Harmless Snack™<br/></li><li>Various things made of paper<br/></li><li>Bunnies (or whatever those things are)<br/></li><li>Demons<br/></li><li>Fast demons<br/></li><li>Social anxiety simulation<br/></li><li>Table salt<br/></li><li>...Is that Kat? Nah, probably not<br/></li><li>Bathroom etiquette<br/></li><li>Death</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2072450/Like_a_Dragon_Infinite_Wealth/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/Accolades_616.png?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>EPIC EMOTIONAL DRAMA</strong><br/>Two larger-than-life heroes brought together by the hand of fate, or perhaps something more sinister…<br/><br/>Ichiban Kasuga, an unstoppable underdog who’s no stranger to crawling up from rock bottom, and Kazuma Kiryu, a broken man facing down his last days.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/2_Epic_Emotional_Drama.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>BEST-IN-CLASS RPG ACTION</strong><br/>Experience one-of-a-kind combat with dynamic, fast-paced RPG battles where the battlefield becomes your weapon, and anything goes. Adapt your party’s skills to the situation with outlandish jobs and customizations to strategically subdue enemies with over-the-top moves. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/3_Best_In_Class_RPG_Action.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>INFINITE ADVENTURE</strong><br/>Live it up in Japan and explore all that Hawaii has to offer in an adventure so big it spans the Pacific. Unforgettable moments await at every step of the journey with a unique mix of quests and activities to enjoy at your leisure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/4_Infinite_Adventure.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Deluxe Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Ultimate Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/>- Assorted Outfit Bundle: Customize your party's look with outfits &amp; swimwear<br/>- Sujimon &amp; Resort Bundle: Get legendary Sujimon, resort guests and special boosters<br/>- Yakuza CD Collection Set: Increase your in-game playlist with classic karaoke tracks						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apollo Justice: Ace Attorney Trilogy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2187220/Apollo_Justice_Ace_Attorney_Trilogy/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2187220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2187220/extras/13_Apollo_CustomImages_600x338.png?t=1706177279"><br/><br/>Apollo Justice's Legal Journey Begins Anew!<br/><br/>Join rookie attorney Apollo Justice and his mentor, the legendary Phoenix Wright, in this collection of 3 games! This title features the 14 episodes of "Apollo Justice: Ace Attorney", "Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney - Dual Destinies", and "Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney - Spirit of Justice", and the 2 previously DLC-only Special Episodes for a total of 16 episodes!<br/><br/>Also included is a mountain of extra goodies that's sure to satisfy any Ace Attorney fan!<br/><br/>Orchestra Hall - Listen to the in-game background music and select orchestral arrangements!<br/><br/>Art Library - View illustrations, design specs, commissioned pieces, and even the special Spirit of Justice Prologue anime!<br/><br/>Animation Studio - Play around with character animations and recreate your favorite scenes!<br/><br/>This collection supports Japanese, English, French, German, Korean, and Traditional and Simplified Chinese. Mix and match to play in whichever languages you'd like!<br/><br/>Immerse yourself in this beautiful collection as you shout "Objection!" in these newly renovated halls of justice!<br/><br/>Some of the contents of the games in this collection are presented as initially released to preserve the games as originally created.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summon Masters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2100140/Summon_Masters/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2100140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a card and board game with the following features:<br>
<br>
Deck Building: Players can build their own decks to battle with. Depending on different strategies and opponents, players can choose different cards to counter.<br>
<br>
Tactical Gameplay: The game uses a 3x10 chessboard, and players can freely place cards to fight. Players need to develop tactics and arrange card positions and usage order within limited space.<br>
<br>
Different Professions: Players can choose freely from four professions - swordsman, mage, monk, and archer. Each profession has different characteristics and skills, and players can choose according to their preferences and tactical needs.<br/>
<br/>
Competitive Battles: Players can battle with other players after building their decks, and it is fun to fight with other people. Through battles with other players, players can improve their strength and tactical skills.<br/>
<br/>
Team Dungeons: In addition to fighting against other players, players can also team up with others to challenge high-difficulty dungeons. Players need to defeat powerful bosses through cooperation and strategy to get more rewards and cards.<br/>
<br/>
Special Challenges: Players can participate in special rules challenges and use their intelligence to defeat other players. These special rules make the game more interesting and challenging, and players need to constantly think and try new strategies.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced: Each game is fast-paced (within 5 minutes), and can be played in short fragments of time. The fast pace of the game allows players to enjoy the game in a short time, while also being able to play at any time and anywhere.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2248950/TransSiberian_Railway_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take the helm of a classic Russian locomotive, discover the raw beauty and wildness of Siberia and try to survive on the longest railway line in the world. This is the Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator. A game for real adventurers!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/drinking1.gif?t=1707121961"><br/><br/>Complete the tutorial and the first kilometers of the route for free.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/explosion_gif.gif?t=1707121961"><br/><br/>The Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator offers amazing rail and survival challenges on real Russian dangerous routes. Feel what it is like to put your hands at the helm of a powerful freight locomotive and explore the untouched natural landscape that is sure to delight you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/shooting_gif.gif?t=1707121961"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Prologue features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Detailed simulation of driving a VL10 locomotive - the locomotive control is slightly simplified.<br/></li><li> Locomotive repair system - Manage and replace locomotive parts that are constantly wearing out.<br/></li><li> Train traffic simulation - Follow rail signs and signals to avoid derailment or damage to a part of the locomotive.<br/></li><li> Work system - Earn by completing transport orders. <br/></li><li> Game modes (Survival) and (Simulator). It is recommended to play in the (Survival) mode. This is the leading game mode that is constantly being developed. <br/>For players who are not interested in survival mechanics, a simple Simulator mode is available. <br/></li><li> Mafia system - Complete missions for the mafia to earn extra money.<br/></li><li> Survival system with statistics of hunger, thirst, alcohol, hangover, disease and hypothermia - Eat and drink to avoid death. <br/>Keep the right temperature so you don't freeze.<br/></li><li> Shooting system - Use your weapons for hunting and self-defense.<br/></li><li> Purchase and sales system - Buy various items, food, tools, weapons and ammunition.<br/></li><li> Locomotive inspection mode - Inspect the condition of locomotive parts and replace them in time to avoid damage.<br/></li><li> Dynamic weather system with day and night cycle - Survive extreme weather conditions.<br/></li><li> Route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Novosibirsk-Main) - scale 1:1. Buy the full version with the route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Krasnoyarsk).<br/></li><li> Police system - A corrupt militia watches over your movements.<br/></li><li> Much more to discover.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intravenous 2: Mercenarism</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2651330/Intravenous_2_Mercenarism/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Wishlist_Game.png?t=1705699394"><br/><br/>Step into the shoes of Gideon, a ruthless mercenary who cares about nothing but his wealth. Set two months before the events of Intravenous 2, you will take on seemingly simple jobs, the effects of which will ripple out and affect the main game's protagonist. But why should Gideon care? He's just in it for the money.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Stealth_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Stealth or Firepower:</strong> the choice is yours. Sneak through shadows, turn off the lights, pick doors, or unleash a hail of bullets. The game will adapt to your play style.<br/></li><li> <strong>Customize Your Skills:</strong> develop your skills the way you want to, whether it's mastering the art of stealth or becoming a gunslinging virtuoso.<br/></li><li> <strong>Bullet Time:</strong> Gideon is no stranger to stimulants that enhance his cognitive abilities - bending time to give him the edge in tense situations.<br/></li><li> <strong>Vast Arsenal:</strong> choose from firearms, gadgets, and a variety of ammo types to creatively tackle the challenge<br/></li><li> <strong>Weapon Modification:</strong> personalize each firearm with suppressors, laser sights, and more, tailoring your arsenal to the task at hand.<br/></li><li> <strong>Responsive AI:</strong> engage in intense combat with enemies that react to your actions, take cover, use tactics and call for backup.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Action_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2744170/Artifact_SeekerPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/DS.png?t=1706492908"/></a><br/>The difference between the prologue version and the official version<br/>There is a special artifact in the prologue<br/>Characters: 2 in the prologue, at least 5 in the official version<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 3 in the final version.<br/>Systems: Tavern, Marketplace, and Endless Mode will be added to the game.<br/>Artifacts: More artifacts will be added to the game.<br/>Skills: More skills will be added in the official version.<br/>Affixes: More Affixes will be added in the official version.<br/>Events: There will be more interesting Events in the official version.<br/>Progress: No need to worry, all progress will be carry into the official version.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/11y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1z.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/2y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/gif1.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong>[/b]<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><strong><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </img></img></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frostrain</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735630/Frostrain/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/01_Thumnail.png?t=1706325941"><h2 class="bb_tag">Roam the frozen world</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Roam_the_frozen_world.gif?t=1706325941"><br/>Climate change has turned the world white and frozen, and the only thing moving on the planet is you, your passengers, and your train. It's a dead world, but ironically, it's all the more fascinating for it. A vivid landscape awaits you to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Keep your passengers happy</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Keep_your_passengers_happy.gif?t=1706325941"><br/>The passengers on your train will work diligently at your command, but be careful: if you don't manage their happiness properly, they might throw you off the train.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build your own train with card decks</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Build_your_own_train_with_card_decks.gif?t=1706325941"><br/>Each time you pass through a city, you'll be able to add new train cars by launching a heavy lift drone. Be careful with each choice you make. If you are lucky, you'll be able to build a better, more synergized, happily-ever-after train deck, but it won't always go as you planned.<h2 class="bb_tag">Reach the Promised Land</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Reach_the_Promised_Land.gif?t=1706325941"><br/>Lead your passengers in search of the Promised Land, somewhere on the eastern edge of the world. But the journey to the Promised Land isn't all smooth and pleasant. You'll have to pass through toxic areas, and a severe storm is brewing behind you. Pay attention to your passengers' happiness levels and lead them safely to the Promised Land. The journey is in your hands.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696480/Nothing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2696480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play. Or is it?<br>
<br>
Just do Nothing as the timer goes up. If you do Something, you lose.<br>
<br>
If you don't like doing Nothing, go play Something instead.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KinitoPET</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2075070/KinitoPET/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>*note: This game is designed and tested for Windows 10 - Due to the nature of this game you may experience some issues with using older or newer windows versions.</i><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Join the Discord!</strong></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FKinitoPET" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/KinitoPET</a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enter the Everlasting Fun!</strong></h2>Would you like a friend? Yes? Well, I have something special for you.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075070/extras/BoxSpin.gif?t=1707340597"><br/>KinitoPET invites you to their wonderfull world of fun and excitement!<br/>Where he will be your very own virtual friend and personal helper! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075070/extras/KinitoWelcome.png?t=1707340597"><br/>Kinito is able to walk, talk, browse, adapt, and play games as Kinito is like no other with its adaptive technology! Kinito is h̶i̶d̶i̶n̶g̶ ̶a̶ ̶d̶a̶r̶k̶ ̶s̶e̶c̶r̶e̶t a friend you'll never forget with its critically acclaimed react respond algorithm to make your experience in̶d̶e̶f̶i̶n̶i̶t̶e truly unique. Where d̶i̶d̶ he ̶g̶o else can you find a friend like Kinito with its multitude of great features and friendly love! <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075070/extras/SteamImageLowerRes.png?t=1707340597"><br/>Kinito will be your friend and you can s̶t̶o̶p̶ ̶i̶t be there's! <br/>So why wait as with your new virtual assistant and friend you can have f̶o̶r̶e̶v̶e̶r everlasting fun!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summoners War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2426960/Summoners_War/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2426960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>▶Features</strong><br/><strong>[Tactical RPG play]</strong><br/>Witness the dazzling display of each monster 's unique skills.<br/>23 different Rune sets to pick and choose additional abilities for your monsters!<br/>Come up with the best strategy to win battles in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[Endless Fun]</strong><br/>Decorate your Village, battle other summoners , explore dungeons , fight in PvP battles , expand your collection, train monsters , and more.<br/><br/><strong>[The Key of Colletion RPG : Massive Collection]</strong><br/>Fire, Water, Wind, Light and Dark!<br/>5 different attributes, and 1500 different monsters!<br/>Collect as many monsters as you can and win battles with your own decks .<br/><br/><strong>[Real-time Raid]</strong><br/>Battle as a team with your greatest monsters !<br/>A real-time battle with 3 users!<br/>Defeat the boss with your fellow Summoners using various tactics.<br/><br/><strong>[Homunculus]</strong><br/>The Forbidden Summoning Magic has finally been revealed!<br/>You can Evolve the skill of your choice with this special monster.<br/>Summon Homunculus and show off your strategy in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[All about Turn-Based RPG : World Arena]</strong><br/>Enjoy a real-time battle with Summoners worldwide!<br/>Experience a breathtaking battle that starts from Pick &amp; Ban.<br/>Reveal your unique strategy to the world and win battles .<br/><br/><strong>[Guild Content]</strong><br/>A sensational Guild PvP battle in the Isle of Conquest!<br/>Explore the Tartarus' Labyrinth and dungeons with Guild Members.<br/>Make your Guild the greatest of all.<br/><br/><strong>[Dimension Hole]</strong><br/>Fight against the ancient power emerged from a new dimension!<br/>Defeat the Ancient Guardians and meet the powerful monsters with new awakening power.<br/><br/><strong>[Artifact]</strong><br/>Artifacts are now dropped with MAX power-up levels!<br/>Summoners , fight against the powerful bosses and acquire Artifacts!<br/>Enhance your monsters with various sub properties of Artifacts.<br/><br/><strong>[Progression and Farming Structure Revamp]</strong><br/>Summoner progression structure renewed and content reward greatly improved!<br/>Dive into Summoners War and experience the enhanced progression system!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JongRo 3_Street</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2752770/JongRo_3_Street/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2752770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">About This Game</h2><br/><strong>"In the year 2024, South Korea has become a wasteland due to the Epsilon virus. South Korea is full of infected people. In this desolate landscape, a man hears a rumor about a path to salvation at Jongno 3-ga Station and decides to head there."</strong><br/><br/>You, intrigued by the rumor, make your way to Jongno 3-ga Station. There, you find traces left behind by those who have already ventured to this place. Reading their notes, you follow clues to unravel the mysteries and solve problems along the way. Through their traces, you gradually uncover the hidden secrets of this place.<br/><br/>It's based on the real Jongno 3-ga station. <br/>the game strives to authentically capture the atmosphere unique to this location.<br/><br/>The play time for all section is 4 hours to 5 hours<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2752770/extras/forStore.png?t=1707797300"><h2 class="bb_tag">Developer</h2><br/>This game is made by indie developer who is a university student majoring in design, using the Unreal Engine. Attention has been given to intricate details such as the map and UI, resulting in a polished game. Feel free to expect and enjoy!<h2 class="bb_tag">Control</h2><br/>WASD/ Mouse Click<br/>During play, pay close attention to notes and manuals. manuals can be revisited in the settings.<h2 class="bb_tag">Notify</h2>If there are any omissions in copyright attribution, please contact me via email, and I will address the issue by providing the necessary copyright.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dangerous adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2789450/Dangerous_adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2789450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dangerous adventure is an adventure game with role-playing game (RPG) elements. You have to take on the role of a traveler who was shipwrecked and ended up on an unnamed island. Arm yourself with a magical staff and hit the road in search of adventure! Explore mysterious locations, get out of the maze, fight monsters in a dark dungeon! Whether you can walk this path is up to you to decide!<br>
<br>
Peculiarities:<br>
- Beautiful graphics<br>
- Interesting levels<br>
- Nice soundtrack						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cursed sarcophagus</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2789440/Cursed_sarcophagus/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2789440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cursed sarcophagus is an addictive 3D puzzle game where you have to lower sarcophagi on or off the island!<br>
<br>
Magic enveloped the kingdom and cursed sarcophagi appeared on the islands. No one knows where they came from or what harm they can cause. Take control of the situation and do whatever is necessary to secure the kingdom!<br>
<br>
In the game you will find many different levels and blocks that you have to destroy! Complete the game from start to finish, solving interesting puzzles! Whether you can walk this path depends only on you!<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br/>
- Many levels<br/>
- Convenient controls<br/>
- Physics<br/>
- Colorful graphics						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explorer of the deep</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2789470/Explorer_of_the_deep/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2789470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Explorer of the deep is a dynamic 3D game in which you have to fly a futuristic space transport through an endless tunnel and avoid dangerous obstacles! Earn points and unlock new vehicles that suit your taste! Avoid various traps and score as many points as possible and set a new record!<br>
<br>
Peculiarities:<br>
- Beautiful graphics<br>
- Various obstacles<br>
- Multiple modes of transport						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutants Invasion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2789480/Mutants_Invasion/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2789480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Mutants Invasion is a 3D adventure FPS game in which you have to break through hordes of mutants and find a nuclear bomb before the mutants destroy the entire world. You are one of a squad of fighters who decided to go to a city overrun by zombies. Explore various locations, including an abandoned city, and do everything to avoid being eaten by mutants!<br>
<br>
Peculiarities:<br>
- Play a short campaign in single player mode.<br>
- Explore a new world.<br>
- Embark on an exciting journey!						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steal Quietly!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2789490/Steal_Quietly/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2789490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Steal Quietly! - You are an ordinary person who owes a huge amount to the most dangerous people in your city. The only option to repay the debt is to provide them with the service they ask for.<br>
<br>
Team up with your partner and start your journey! You have to rob people and steal everything that has any value. Look for important documents that will help you pay off your debts! But be careful not to get noticed, otherwise you may attract the attention of the police. The game will definitely appeal to fans of heist films!<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
- Different difficulty levels<br>
- Beautiful graphics<br/>
- Pleasant music						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Story of Dreams</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2789500/Story_of_Dreams/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2789500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Story of Dreams is a 3D meditative walking game that opens up the world of dreams, where you have to travel through various dream worlds. Solve exciting puzzles! Go through interesting locations where various challenges await you! Uncover the secrets of your subconscious and enjoy a magical journey in the world of dreams!<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
- Interesting puzzles<br>
- Beautiful graphics<br>
- Pleasant music						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slide Magic</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2758800/Slide_Magic/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You play as a witch who controls a flask with a magical decoction. He is able to move on his own wherever you want! Set the desired direction for the flask to fly and color everything around! You need to cover the entire floor with magic paint to pass the level!<br>
<br>
Slide Magic - A game in the Top Down genre where the player controls a flask that flies in one chosen direction, coloring the floor behind it, all you need to do is paint the floor in the correct sequence, otherwise you risk getting stuck in the level, deprived of the opportunity to win .<br>
<br>
Control:<br>
WASD - walking<br>
<br/>
Game Features:<br/>
- Visual style<br/>
- Logic game<br/>
- Difficulty						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rune Gate: Retribution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731350/Rune_Gate_Retribution/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FmeSfrrUQ2x" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731350/extras/StoneFront_Top_New.jpg?t=1707792718"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731350/extras/Battle.gif?t=1707792718"><br/><br/>Rune Gate: Retribution unveils a sneak peek of the 'Retribution' game mode, soon to premiere in Rune Gate. This mode delivers a condensed but intensively challenging experience, inviting players to overcome increasingly difficult trials and ascend the leaderboard. Fundamentally, the game is a deck-building roguelite that allows for deep customization of cards through the integration of various elemental runes, offering a unique blend of strategy and personalization.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731350/extras/StoreTitles_CustomizeCards.jpg?t=1707792718"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731350/extras/Customization.gif?t=1707792718"><br/><br/>The Rune system makes card customization swift and effortless. You have the freedom to forge synergies between cards, determining their power and utility. Insert attack runes for high-damage cards; use draw or energy runes for utility cards; and debuff runes transform your cards into potent curses. Want more versatility? Simply upgrade your card to add a new rune slot!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731350/extras/StoreTitles_ElementalRunes.jpg?t=1707792718"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731350/extras/RuneTypes.gif?t=1707792718"><br/><br/>Currently, the game features nearly 200 unique runes, each with its own signature abilities and constraints. Players can acquire runes by winning combats, crafting them from lower-tier runes, or obtaining them through encounters and merchant inventory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731350/extras/StoreTitles_FormSquad.jpg?t=1707792718"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731350/extras/StoneTitles_SquadImage.jpg?t=1707792718"><br/><br/>In the game, you lead a party of champions against adversaries. Each champion wields a specific type of weapon and utilizes unique runes. Every weapon type corresponds to a distinct deck, offering a unique set of cards for strategic deck-building. With 18 champions available, featuring three from each elemental type, a rich variety of team compositions and strategies awaits your command.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gears and Augments</h2><br/>Not only do you acquire runes following combat, but you can also obtain gear and augments. Gear enhances your champions' offensive and defensive capabilities and includes runes for further customization. Augments provide unique buffs to your champions during combat, offering additional strategic depth.<h2 class="bb_tag">Units to Summon</h2><br/>Followers represent another form of 'Gear' available in the game, capable of being summoned as allies during battles. They each possess a distinct set of cards that can be customized with runes, and can be a great help to your mid to late game strategy.<h2 class="bb_tag">Meta Progression</h2><br/>Fame is earned through combat across different realms, and it serves as a key resource. You can utilize this fame to permanently unlock specific runes, granting yourself a range of advantages that significantly aid in progressing through future runs.<br/><br/>-Discord: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FmeSfrrUQ2x" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/meSfrrUQ2x</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>River Tails: Stronger Together - Original Soundtrack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2717430/River_Tails_Stronger_Together__Original_Soundtrack/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							The original soundtrack for River Tails: Stronger Together is out now!<br>
Listen to the relaxing and cartoony melodies of River Tails and remember all the adventures Finn and Furple had together!!<br>
<br>
A must listen soundtrack for all River Tails fans!						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shrimp.io</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2782530/Shrimpio/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A simple survivor-like where you play as a shrimp, you must kill fishies &amp; other creatures, gather microplastics, and purchase meta upgrades.<br/><br/><strong>Current Meta Upgrades:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> +5% Move Speed - 4 Levels<br/></li><li> +10% Max Health - 5 Levels<br/></li><li> +5% Outgoing Damage - 5 Levels<br/></li><li> -1 Incoming Damage - 3 Levels</li></ul><br/>The gameplay is simple, just move, and use the patterns of the auto-firing weapons you have to murder the oncoming swarms of fishies &amp; creatures. <br/><br/>if you have issues with the game or suggestions, make sure to let me know. <br/><br/>have a good day! :D						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ling Hun</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653910/Ling_Hun/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653910/extras/Cenefa_STEAM_MEJORADO_Blanco.png?t=1707775195"><br/><br/>An imp fox stole Yun's soul just to have some fun. Because of that, Yun now is incomplete, therefor jumping is not attached to gravity rules anymore. Jumping becomes the first of new abilities that has to be mastered in order to follow and catch the imp fox and recover Yun's soul. <br/>Yun has to face some challenges and learn new ways to succeed and get the soul back to be complete again.<br/>Will you be able to help Yun?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653910/extras/SEPARADOR_SCREENSHOT_1.png?t=1707775195"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653910/extras/Cenefa_STEAM_MEJORADO_Blanco.png?t=1707775195"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Feature:</strong></h2>Yun's ability to jump is quite different than in any other Platformer game out there. Due to the lack of soul, Yun's jump keeps momentum and direction untill hit against a ceiling or a wall or else press jump again.<h2 class="bb_tag">Against the ceiling or a wall:</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653910/extras/YUN_BUMP_JUMP.gif?t=1707775195"><h2 class="bb_tag">Jumping again:</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653910/extras/YUN_NORMAL_JUMP.gif?t=1707775195"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653910/extras/Cenefa_STEAM_MEJORADO_Blanco.png?t=1707775195"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Game Features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Classic 2D pixel art mixed with handmade Asian ink style art.<br/></li><li>Puzzle Platformer with a twist on the core mechanics.<br/></li><li>Collectibles to enhance the experience of the Gameplay.<br/></li><li>Relaxed gameplay and options to increase the game speed.<br/></li><li>No hard punishments, no "Game Over". Just try as much as you want or need.<br/></li><li>Fun and engaging mechanics to learn and have a great experiencie.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653910/extras/SEPARADOR_SCREENSHOT_3.png?t=1707775195"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653910/extras/SEPARADOR_SCREENSHOT_4.png?t=1707775195"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653910/extras/SEPARADOR_SCREENSHOT_2.png?t=1707775195"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653910/extras/Cenefa_STEAM_MEJORADO_Blanco.png?t=1707775195"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slipstream: Rogue Space</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2765860/Slipstream_Rogue_Space/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2765860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2765860/extras/TitlesRun.gif?t=1707774292"><br/>In Slipstream: Rogue Space, Streamers captain a massive starship and viewers are the crew. Together they explore the galaxy, fight aliens, and operate the ship in real-time. Battle through challenging rogue-like maps as a team and work together to see how long you can survive.<h2 class="bb_tag">Captains and Crew</h2>Play as two unique roles:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The <strong>captain</strong>, who makes key decisions, gives orders, and leads the ship. This is usually a live streamer leading their community.<br/></li><li> The <strong>crew</strong>, who work together to operate the ship: shoot, repair, hack, and more.</li></ul>Captains can play LIVE on stream, with their audience, in real time. Dozens of players can join across desktop or mobile platforms to form an elite crew. Deep gameplay, persistent progress, and tons of interaction help build strong ties for your community.<h2 class="bb_tag">Crew Classes</h2>Choose from a variety of specialized crew classes, including:<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2765860/extras/LineupWide620.gif?t=1707774292"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2765860/extras/Lineup2_620.gif?t=1707774292"><br/>As you play, earn permanent XP to level-up your skill tree and customize your character builds.<h2 class="bb_tag">Many Ways to Play</h2>Launch a small ship with some friends, join a streamer of a few dozen crew, or take on major challenges with a streamer piloting 100+ players towards victory.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Dangers Of Rogue Space</h2>Aliens invaded and conquered our solar system. Those few earthlings that escaped have banded together on the cold edges of space, seeking to survive and exact revenge. There will be no quick victory, but day by day, zapped slug by zapped slug, hope survives.<br/><br/>Explore a variety of regions to battle through randomly generated maps. Each run is a unique experience with dangers and rewards constantly evolving. Whether you're piloting a scout with a few friends or a massive cruiser with dozens of players, the game will adapt to provide a fair but challenging experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">Just the Beginning...</h2>Slipstream is just getting started; keep an eye out for regular updates to gameplay, locations, crew classes, character customization, and more. We are committed to helping build strong communities through collaborative gameplay, and we hope to see you aboard!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Successful business</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2807360/Successful_business/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2807360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Successful business - A meditative game that will help you relax. You just started a new job and received your first order! Your task is to clean up the building and remove all unnecessary cargo. Use all the tools at hand that will help you with your work and finish it!<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
- Different difficulty levels<br>
- Lots of exciting levels<br>
- Beautiful graphics<br>
- Pleasant music						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrong Landing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2527050/Wrong_Landing/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2527050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">in General :</h2>You're ex-military, you and your team were sent on a secret mission after 10 years of non-service, to check out an island where nuclear weapons and radiation were allegedly being tested, after you land badly on the island you have to face hunger, thirst, cold, but most of all fear, you have to make tools, build shelters and try to SURVIVE. You are the only survivor in the whole team and you try to understand the island.<h2 class="bb_tag">Procedural vital system :</h2><br/>- For example to keep from getting cold, just start running to keep warm or you need to find a heat source like fire or armor or your health will decrease<br/>- when you are in a scary situation, your fear rises and hunger is decreasing faster<br/>- each level procedurally increases the maximum level of hunger and thirst<br/>- etc...<h2 class="bb_tag">Interesting inventory and crafting :</h2><br/>Each item has specific place, like in game the forest...<h2 class="bb_tag">About me and team:</h2><br/>Hi, i am Honza Záruba, i am 16 years old and I've been interested in games since I was little, but I didn't always want to just play games but also create them... since 2018 I've been interested in game development in unity engine so at the end of 2022 I decided to do this... it's not as I expected but it's enjoyble and that's the main thing, I want to share it with you and collect feedbacks for future updates :) Thanks for all!<br/><br/>We also have a lot of testers, art designers and story creators (Daniela Drábková, Miroul, Jamal, Filip, etc...)						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Recurrence</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2790180/The_Recurrence/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2790180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Help <strong><i>Nia Summers</i></strong> end this <i>hellish nightmare</i> and find her daughter, <strong><i>Blaire</i></strong>.</h2><br/><strong>THE NIGHTMARE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2790180/extras/Nightmare.gif?t=1707761714"><br/>A place filled of evil. With anatomic entities coursing through every vein of this unsettling town; don't let the darkness find you.<br/><br/><strong>GAME MODES</strong><br/><u><i>Divination</i></u><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2790180/extras/Divination.gif?t=1707761714"><br/>The Divination Nightmare is the main game mode in—<i>The Recurrence</i>—where you must use your EMF Reader to find spiritual crosses to perform alter rituals to escape the nightmare.<br/><br/><u><i>Vindication</i></u><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2790180/extras/Vindication.gif?t=1707761714"><br/>Slay the <i>Evil Spirits</i> until the Blood River is content with sacrifices. The Vindication Nightmare is a horde / wave-based game mode that introduces a heavy action element to <i>The Recurrence</i>.<br/><br/><u><i>Restoration</i></u><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2790180/extras/Restoration.gif?t=1707761714"><br/>Restore your holy rosary to find peace in this demonic world. The Restoration Nightmare is a collect-a-thon game mode, where Nia must find and collect all 59 beads to restore her rosary before escaping the nightmare.<br/><br/><strong>THE ENTITIES</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2790180/extras/Entities.gif?t=1707761714"><br/>The evil spirits of this world are quite malicious. Use your flashlight to burn the entities that lurk in the darkness. Be careful of the <i><strong>Bloodfall</strong></i>; where enemies become enraged and grow more powerful throughout the night.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic Party Quest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2024810/Epic_Party_Quest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2024810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Assemble the team of heroes and recreate the epic quest line by taking on your friends in a series of fast-paced mini-games in this brand-new local multiplayer party game!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2024810/extras/EpicPartyQuest_Tavern.gif?t=1707760944"><br/><br/>After completing their many adventures, the team of heroes meets at the tavern to brag about their great deeds in a relaxed atmosphere. It turns out that everyone remembers their role in saving the world in a slightly different way! It’s time to play a series of retrospective mini-games and show your friends who was (and still is) the best!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>4-players local multiplayer!</strong></h2>Up to four players can enjoy the game through local multiplayer! Gather your friends, get some snacks and let’s party!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2024810/extras/EpicPartyQuest_HotPotions.gif?t=1707760944"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Mobile phones as controllers!</strong></h2>You can play the game using keyboard and gamepads, but if you don’t have as many – just grab your phone, download an app and use your mobile phone as controller!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Create your hero!</strong></h2>Choose from four heroes, various outfits and colourful skins to create your own character! Show other players who’s the best – with style!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2024810/extras/EpicPartyQuest_GUI.gif?t=1707760944"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Choose your own adventure!</strong></h2>Every round vote for one of many different mini-games and re-live past adventures of your party! Fight the monsters, race for treasures, try to be the last-man-standing or bash your friends, every mini-game is a different experience! Also, every mini-game comes in two distinct versions!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Easy-to-learn action RPG gameplay!</strong></h2>Every mini-game is fast-paced and easy-to-learn, so everybody can get the controller and play! Challenge other players and get the highest score to win!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Tested on friends and families!</strong></h2>We tested the game with variety of players to ensure everyone can find something for them and can play together to have fun!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2024810/extras/EpicPartyQuest_Looters.gif?t=1707760944"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Classic fantasy retro style!</strong></h2>Every mini-game is set in one of the unique realms, and each is a tribute to games from golden era of pixel art!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Reaction system!</strong></h2>After each mini-game raise the stakes using reaction system and enjoy humorous visual novel-style narration, when characters thrash-talk each other!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Unlockables!</strong></h2>Earn points with each played session and unlock crazy mini-game variations, new skins and outfits, new reactions and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2024810/extras/EpicPartyQuest_Survival.gif?t=1707760944"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kumi-Daiko Beatoff</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2669560/KumiDaiko_Beatoff/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the ultimate showdown of thumb dexterity, whippiness and cunning! In Kumi-Daiko Beatoff, you control a mask who is forever tied to a drum with a string. This drum is not only an instrument that makes a fun sound, but a formidable weapon when coming into contact with other masks at high speeds! Up to four players can join in on the drum-spinning fun, clearing the playing field of angry red masks together or seeing who’s who in last-mask-standing Battles. Avoid getting hit by other masks &amp; have fun whackin’ it out with everyone you love!<br/><br/><strong>Survival Mode (1-4 players):</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Destroy as many Tengu masks as you can, alone or cooperatively with friends!</li></ul><br/><strong>Battle Mode (2-4 players):</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight against other players, evading their drums and trying to hit them with yours!</li></ul><br/>To play Kumi-Daiko Beatoff, each players should have a controller with an analog stick and at least one finger they can use to twirl it.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_TITLE_FULLSCREEN.gif?t=1707759948"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_1.png?t=1707759948"><br/> <br/>In New Eden, 1695, communities of settlers are plagued by a dreadful curse. As Banishers, step into their lives, investigate the source of evil, unravel chilling mysteries, explore diverse landscapes, and interact with unforgettable characters whose fate lies in your hands.<br/><br/>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden is an all-new title crafted by renowned studio DON'T NOD, known for their acclaimed titles such as Life is Strange and Vampyr. Immerse yourself in an intimate narrative Action-RPG, taking you on an exhilarating journey between life, death, love and sacrifices.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_2.png?t=1707759948"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_FANTASY.gif?t=1707759948"><br/>Play as a couple of Banishers, Red and Antea, experienced spirit hunters entrusted with the daunting task of dispelling a malevolent curse through powerful rituals. Protect the living from the threat of lingering ghosts and specters, and become a beacon of hope in a world consumed by darkness.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_3.png?t=1707759948"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_NARATION_LOVE.gif?t=1707759948"><br/>Experience a heart-wrenching love story between Antea Duarte and Red mac Raith. When Antea is killed and turned into a spirit, you find yourself facing a choice. Will you uphold your oath and ascend her soul, or will you sacrifice the living in the hope of bringing her back? Your decisions will shape the fate of New Eden’s inhabitants - may they be living or dead, and determine the end of your journey.<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>BLAME</strong> the living and sacrifice their lives, holding them responsible for their actions<br/></li><li><strong>BANISH</strong> souls of the departed, condemning them to eternal suffering<br/></li><li><strong>ASCEND</strong> souls, liberating them from eternal sorrow and granting them serenity</li></ul><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_4.png?t=1707759948"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_COMBAT.gif?t=1707759948"><br/>Banishers are specialized in combat against undead creatures, such as specters or ghosts. Combine Red's physical arsenal with Antea's supernatural powers in a dynamic combat system. Find your own style by mixing weapon attacks and spiritual abilities. Powerful synergies will lead you to defeat New Eden’s most dangerous enemies and bosses.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_6.png?t=1707759948"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_SKILL.gif?t=1707759948"><br/>Unleash the full power of the Banishers by unlocking new gear and supernatural abilities. By exploring New Eden, you will find ancient artifacts, trinkets and valuable resources to enhance your equipment in preparation of future fights. In addition to your arsenal, progress in Antea’s skill trees to upgrade her devastating spectral powers and unseal new combos.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_5.png?t=1707759948"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_EXPLORATION.gif?t=1707759948"><br/>Investigate haunting cases in a mystical world full of dark secrets. Discover New Eden, a North America settlement marked by terrible stories and secrets of its tormented inhabitants. Understanding each resident’s motivations will be essential to guide your decisions throughout the game.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_7.png?t=1707759948"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off-Road: Redneck Racing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2742010/OffRoad_Redneck_Racing/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2742010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Yeehah! Stop yer grinnin' and drop yer linen, cause the slam bangin'est, mud-flappin'est off-road driving game ever created is comin' to Steam! Motor trucks 'n Buggies over the most brutal Southland terrain ever seen in a racing game.<br/><br/>Whether you're just a good ol'boy out for a Sunday drive or want to compete head-to-head against those other Rednecks in Championship mode, you've never seen anything that compares to Off-Road Redneck Racing!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Rip it up on six different terrains from the Everlastin' Everglades the Crushin' Colorado Highlands.<br/></li><li>16 different vehicle types including jeeps, pick-up trucks, Off-road-beetles and Dune Buggies.<br/></li><li>Amazin' Appalachee soundtrack!<br/></li><li>Upgrade your vehicles for better acceleration &amp; handling.<br/></li><li>Neither rain nor snow nor the Sheriff himself can stop these mud-machines!<br/>Drive through dozens of different weather and day and night environments!<br/></li><li>LAN Network play allows you to race against 4-6 other players in frantic multi-player action!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Stand at Camp Zombie</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428780/The_Last_Stand_at_Camp_Zombie/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428780/extras/02_1.gif?t=1707761053"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Pan Pan Boom Boom!</strong></h2>Face hordes of zombie in this black and white, top down shooter! Alone or in local coop, annihilate everything -and everyone- that stands in your way in order to make a safe exit from Zombie Camp!<br/>Camp Zombie is a cooperative arcade game with a fun and immediate concept, incorporating some mechanics from a zombie mode with the easy handling of a top-down shooter, all with a unique graphical style!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428780/extras/07_1.gif?t=1707761053"><br/><br/>Explore the multiple rooms to increase your firepower and purchase every single boost to match the ever increasing waves of zombies! Beware, however, as darkness might become an even bigger problem that those putrid foes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428780/extras/06_1.gif?t=1707761053"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A word from the manager!</strong></h2>In our post-apocalyptic zombie world, will you be able to survive my life-threatening, hyper-modern escape game? Try your best not to die, or be prepared to become zombies for the next challengers!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428780/extras/03_1.gif?t=1707761053"><br/><br/>Please note, you must connect at least one controller to play local multiplayer.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alvo VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2000590/Alvo_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2000590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2000590/extras/logo.png?t=1707756715"><br/><br/>Alvo is a unique competitive FPS designed from the ground up for VR to provide some of the most thrilling and intense combat seen in the VR FPS genre. Trading ultra-realism for faster-paced gameplay, Alvo is a finely-tuned cocktail of mechanics that will keep you addicted and coming back round after round.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Free for all<br/></li><li> Team Deathmatch<br/></li><li> Hardpoint<br/></li><li> Search and Destroy<br/></li><li> Zombies</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2000590/extras/Steam_Store.png?t=1707756715"><h2 class="bb_tag">Accessibility:</h2><br/>Not all gamers want or have the same play-style, we understand this and try to accommodate for everyone. You can play Alvo sitting or standing, using manual reload or button reload, and choose the amount of in-game UI you want to see.<h2 class="bb_tag">Customization:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> In-game UI color theme<br/></li><li> Weapon attachments<br/></li><li> Weapon skins<br/></li><li> Characters<br/></li><li> Perks<br/></li><li> Killstreaks </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2000590/extras/Steam_Store2.png?t=1707756715"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bioguard</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2669910/Bioguard/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dive into the microscopic world inside the human body with Bioguard, an amusing and infectious tower defense game with roguelite elements!<br/><br/>Use three special resources and upgrades to develop unique strategies for each stage of this biological combat, handling different enemy combinations and level design.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669910/extras/Towers.png?t=1707750171"><br/><br/>Tower are your base defense, use each one of the four towers and its upgrades wisely to take advantage of its specific qualities. Use the ATP gathered by defeating enemies to build these immune defence structures.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669910/extras/Card_En.png?t=1707750171"><br/><br/>Put together a deck of cards of diverse effects and buy a card each and every wave. Keep up to three cards in hand and use them to influence game a tower mechanics.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669910/extras/Skills_En.png?t=1707750171"><br/><br/>Unlock unique skills with tower thematics. Use them in key moments during combat to aid your towers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669910/extras/Upgrade_Panel_En.png?t=1707750171"><br/><br/>Spend the DNA attained by completing levels on new towers, cards, skills and all of its upgrades. Discover the ideal build to beat every new challenge!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Ninja Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_9" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🥋🐾 WELCOME TO 100 NINJA CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🗡️</h2>🗡️Join the cutest adventure in the Ninja world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of ninja themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game.<br/>😊Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x200.png?t=1707750752"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Ninja Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Extra.png?t=1707750752"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816000/100_Ninja_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1707750752"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815980/100_Ninja_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Artbook.png?t=1707750752"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x1.png?t=1707750752"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1707750752"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_10" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_11" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airhead</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/771700/Airhead/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/771700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/771700/extras/MeetAirhead_Arihead_SteamPage.gif?t=1707752264"/></h2>Airhead is an adventure through a sprawling interconnected world, where you must explore, evolve and overcome intricate puzzles to succeed.<br/><br/>You play as Body, a small creature who meets a round, inflated organism and uses it as a head. And while Head is slowly but surely deflating, you have a chance to save its life.<br/><br/>To do so, you need to use air cylinders to keep Head inflated while you explore Airhead’s interconnected world and learn about its secrets.<br/><br/>On your adventure, it will be up to you to uncover the true connection between Head, the air cylinders, and the technology that litters the world so that you can save Head no matter the cost.<h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/771700/extras/Gameplay_Airhead_SteamPage.gif?t=1707752264"/></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/771700/extras/exploration.png?t=1707752264"><br/>Finding your way through Airhead's world is not always easy. You must brave dark caverns, ancient structures, and other mysterious locations in order to save Head.<br/><br/>Along the way, you will find new abilities, and uncover new areas and puzzles, and if you go even farther afield, who knows what hidden truths you may stumble upon?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/771700/extras/puzzles.png?t=1707752264"><br/>As you explore, you will encounter numerous puzzles involving the environment, strange creatures, and old technology to challenge your logic and creativity.<br/><br/>Everything is there for a reason and can be overcome by piecing together the puzzle and understanding the rules of Airhead's strange world. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/771700/extras/companionship.png?t=1707752264"><br/>Body and Head must work together to accomplish their goal, and as time passes, their bond and abilities will grow. What will you do to preserve their companionship?<br/><br/>And when the impact of your choices becomes clear, are you willing to shoulder the consequences of saving a friend?<h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/771700/extras/Features_Arihead_SteamPage.gif?t=1707752264"/></h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>A beautiful art style, embracing bold colors and bleak shadows.<br/> </li><li>An immersive 2.5D platformer experience. <br/> </li><li>Exploration in a mysterious world, filled with secrets and hidden paths.<br/> </li><li>Challenging puzzles, exploring the unique mechanics of a detachable head full of air.<br/> </li><li>Many powerful abilities to discover, each giving access to new areas and puzzles. <br/> </li><li>A personal story of companionship, discovery, and responsibility. <br/> </li><li>A myriad of creatures and machines to hinder and help you on your adventure.<br/> </li><li>A library filled with background information about Airhead's world and its inhabitants.<br/> </li><li>A ton of collectibles and even very hidden secret endings to uncover.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/771700/extras/Wishlist.gif?t=1707752264"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/771700/extras/Airhead_Logo_600_shadow.png?t=1707752264"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autobus Park Sim</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2715640/Autobus_Park_Sim/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Autobus Park Sim is an exciting game that will put your parking skills to the test as you learn to park a passenger bus correctly. <br>
<br>
Your mission is to find the necessary parking space within a limited time and perform a correct parking maneuver, whether it's a lateral or perpendicular park. You'll need to use the correct camera angle to help you park with precision.<br>
<br>
To succeed in Autobus Park Sim, you'll need to be patient and precise, taking your time to carefully maneuver the bus into position. You'll also need to use the correct camera angle to get a clear view of your surroundings and ensure that you don't hit any obstacles or other vehicles.<br>
<br>
Autobus Park Sim is a game that requires precision, patience, and a steady hand. Can you park the passenger bus correctly and beat the clock? Download the game now and find out!<br/>
<br/>
Game features :<br/>
- More than 100 levels<br/>
- Different camera angles<br/>
- Limited time for parking						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majyo Crush</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779070/Majyo_Crush/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2779070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Game Overview<br>
One night, when you find yourself in a dream with a group of people who don't belong there, these girls all have their own troubles. As a caring gentleman, are you eager to try and can you conquer them all before dawn?<br>
<br>
Features<br>
This is an elimination game that combines gravity system and connecting lines. By collecting color balls with different effects, attacking opponent characters, and keeping your own blood volume from being depleted, you can successfully awaken the girls and defeat their inner demons. Multiple fairies with different attributes are waiting for you to meet!<br>
<br>
Many exciting Live2D girls ♥<br/>
Different girls with unique encounters and storylines<br/>
Rich storyline options<br/>
Gravity elimination gameplay<br/>
♥CG viewing mode♥<br/>
<br/>
◆ Upcoming Updates ◆<br/>
New characters and storylines<br/>
New action poses<br/>
Challenge levels and pigeon gameplay						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daedalus</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2364790/Daedalus/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2364790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>DEMO AVAILABLE NOW!</strong> --------------&gt;<br/><i>Please be sure to check the demo out so you know that this is the game for you! The journey into labyrinth is unforgiving but has many lessons to teach those who are willing to learn. You will die, you will start again, but this is no Sisyphean task. The afterlife awaits you, go earn your place.</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Overview</h2>You are a poor recently lost soul. Expecting Charon and the River Styx, you instead awaken in a cold dark dungeon greeted by Daedalus himself. What cruel fate is this? Before you lay three ornate weapons, a shortbow, a labrys, and a staff. Dormant elemental runes scatter the surface of each weapon, what hidden powers do they hold?<br/><br/>Hades, driven mad by the endless horde of the dead whom he must steward, has devised a new trial in order to allow only the greatest of souls into the afterlife. One must demonstrate mastery with all four elements to unlock the inner chambers, and only within will they be truly tested. Will you emerge victorious, or will you spend eternity wandering the winding halls.<h2 class="bb_tag">Class Driven Combat</h2>By choosing a weapon, you take on the abilities of the Archer, the Guardian, or the Oracle. Each has a unique set of elemental powers, unlocked through imbuing the weapon along the journey into the Labyrinth.<h2 class="bb_tag">Challenging Boss Fights</h2>Defeat the elemental Titans to imbue your weapon. Demonstrate your skill on challenge bosses to upgrade your abilities. With your build set, take on the inner chamber final bosses and earn your rightful place in the afterlife.<h2 class="bb_tag">Stats &amp; Speedrunning Tools</h2>Built in speedrunning timers and splits.<br/>Detailed individual and aggregate stats with embedded comparisons to watch your skill grow.<h2 class="bb_tag">About Daedalus</h2>Daedalus is the culmination of a 6-month challenge that I set out for myself. It was an incredible learning experience and I feel extremely grateful that I have something to present at the end! I really hope you find it fun, and that it brings you some joy! ♥						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spark &amp; Kling</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2712910/Spark__Kling/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Spark &amp; Kling is a stylized couch co-op puzzle platformer for all ages, you and your friend play as:<br>
<br>
- Spark, the electric bug, who can possess different electronics, she also carries baby sparklings to shoot at generators and magnets!<br>
- Kling, the metal gel blob, who shoots the metal gel to put weight on objects in order to make them heavy! <br>
<br>
Cooperation is key, you will need to work together and use their abilities to progress through the level:<br>
<br>
Kling can shoot metal gels in a line which Spark can jump into and travel through the level!<br/>
Spark can shoot sparklings at Kling for him to do his double jump!<br/>
Overcome obstacles and puzzles by working together to gain your freedom!<br/>
<br/>
Spark &amp; Kling is a multiplayer game and needs two players to beat it. It is recommended to play with 2 gamepads (Preferably Xbox) for the best experience and the controllers must be connected before starting the game.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complex Tragedy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2767400/The_Complex_Tragedy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767400/extras/TragedyGif.gif?t=1707736684"><br/><br/><strong>Background</strong><br/>Explore the enigmatic world of Complex, a one building city abandoned by the government, leaving behind a haunting mystery. Home to 40,000 souls, Complex was abruptly evacuated without explanation, and its borders sealed off from the outside world. Those who left Complex were relocated to a distant island, their communication with the outside world severed by the government.<br/><br/>Our protagonist, having infiltrated Complex through its sewage system, now faces a point of no return. As the secrets of Complex unfold, embark on a journey to unravel its mysteries within the confines of this desolate place.<br/><br/>Venture into the unknown corners of Complex, where thousands once thrived. Roam through the spaces where a happy dream turned into a haunting nightmare. Join us as we delve into the heart of Complex, where the answers lie shrouded in secrecy.<br/><br/><br/><strong>User Experience</strong><br/>Homes, communal areas, schools, facilities, stores... – these are the visible facets of Complex. Yet, as you delve into the unseen layers, you'll witness an extraordinary and unsettling experience. Explore the hidden faces of Complex, where the familiar transforms into the extraordinary, and where every revelation takes you deeper into the heart of an unparalleled nightmare.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wizened Dream</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2640600/Wizened_Dream/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2640600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Withered Dream is a 2D story exploration game based on card stacking and limited-time operation.<br>
By modifying the stacking relationship between the cards, new cards can be generated and the story can be advanced.<br>
The game contains three stories: going to school, going to work, and being unemployed.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soulshard</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2617190/Soulshard/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617190/extras/logo.png?t=1707735372"><br/><strong>In a realm between life and death, a confused soul, haunted by a life filled with misguided choices, seeks redemption and freedom.<br/>In Soulshard, you command a soul in search of an exit from a dark and desolate realm, using the environment to your advantage and avoiding treacherous traps alone or in cooperative mode!</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Single-Player!</strong></li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617190/extras/1.gif?t=1707735372"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Local CO-OP! (Offline)</strong></li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617190/extras/2.gif?t=1707735372"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>30 levels with more than 6 mechanics!</strong></li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617190/extras/3.gif?t=1707735372"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Minimalistic visual in pixel art.</strong></li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617190/extras/4.gif?t=1707735372"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nerd Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2648990/Nerd_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2648990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The ordinary gaming night among four friends takes a chaotic turn when they find themselves transported to a preposterous fantasy realm teeming with thousands of wacky monsters!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2648990/extras/NS_Friendship.gif?t=1707781632"><br/><br/>Equip yourself with pizza frag-grenades, enchanted fidget spinners, unleash preposterous magic spells, or even fling your very own friends into the fray to repel the relentless hordes of monsters determined to obliterate you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2648990/extras/NS_Fart_2023-10-13.gif?t=1707781632"><br/><br/>And if that's still not enough, scavenge resources and blueprints, then harness the 'Forge of Destiny' to customize your weapons or craft the ultimate armaments of your nerdy wet dreams! Can you endure for 20 minutes of non-stop madness and make your way back to your gaming night?<br/><br/>Nerd Survivors is a bullet-heaven action rogue-lite survivor adventure, set in the Doom &amp; Destiny Worlds universe.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Path to Magehood</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2798950/Path_to_Magehood/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2798950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag">path to Magehood</h2></h2>This is a passion project made just on my own. It is a bullet heaven that starts of slow, gaining traction quickly through upgrades and rogue-lite elements.<br/>In this game, you play as an apprentice mage determined to develope their prowess by summoning and overcoming an ancient monster. All of this, as hordes of smaller enemies relentlessly spawn, attempting to thwart your progress and prevent the accomplishment of your magical feat.<br/>On your journey, you'll have access to <strong>over 40 in-game upgrades</strong> along with <strong>additional base-stat upgrades</strong> in the main menu. By strategically combining these upgrades, you'll uncover either <i>formidable synergies or occasionally underwhelming</i> combinations. Your selection of in-game upgrades will <i>influence the probability</i> of encountering powerful subsequent upgrades.<br/><br/>As a skilled wizard, you must demonstrate not only your magical prowess but also your wisdom and endurance in navigating the challenges that await you in my game!<br/><strong>Good luck Mages!</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drop Doll</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2459870/Drop_Doll/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Game Introduction:<br>
"Drop Doll" is a casual puzzle game.<br>
In this game, players earn points by combining balls of the same type. The goal is to continuously merge larger balls to earn more points. It is important to carefully choose the placement of the balls and anticipate the next type of ball that will appear. Be cautious not to place them carelessly, as it may result in game failure. Come and challenge yourself!<br>
<br>
How to Play:<br>
Use the mouse to click and place the balls for merging.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
The game difficulty is at a casual level, making it suitable for players who prefer a game that doesn't require too much effort. We hope everyone will enjoy this game.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Georgia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2485180/Cats_Hidden_in_Georgia/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Georgia is a <strong>very difficult</strong> but cute hidden object game set in the highly underrated country of Georgia.<br/><br/>100 cats are waiting for you to be discovered within a hand-drawn background.<br/>Relax, thanks to the chill soundtrack<br/><br/>Found a cat? Click on it!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485180/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1707717391"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485180/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1707717391"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
