<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Between Horizons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1921980/Between_Horizons/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1921980/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fassemble-entertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1921980/extras/SteamPageLink_Discord.png?t=1711386337"/></a><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmailchi.mp%2Fassembleteam%2Fassemble-newsletter" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1921980/extras/SteamPageLink_Newsletter.png?t=1711386337"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/AssembleEntertainment" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1921980/extras/SteamPageLink_Steam.png?t=1711386337"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1921980/extras/between-horizons-gif-investigate-new.gif?t=1711386337"><h2 class="bb_tag">ABOUT THE GAME</h2><br/>Between Horizons is set aboard the Zephyr, humanity's first generation ship en route to another star. You assume the role of Stella, who was born on the ship 24 years ago and recently inherited her father's post as Chief of Security. Dive into the conspiracy behind the incident that threatens to disrupt the Zephyr's social order and foil its mission.<br/><br/>Between Horizons is a modern 2.5D pixel art adventure that brings a branching narrative into a semi-open world. The team at DigiTales has applied numerous lessons from their first game Lacuna and proven solutions to detective game design problems to maximize player agency in the investigation process – all the while maintaining the tight pacing of a meaningful story that will ask you to reevaluate your moral compass and make increasingly tough decisions as the situation aboard the ship spirals out of control.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1921980/extras/between-horizons-gif-show-evidence-new.gif?t=1711386337"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>A New Kind of Experience:</strong> Between Horizons merges investigative-style gameplay with a branching sci-fi story in an ever-expanding Metroidvania-style environment.<br/></li><li><strong>Solving Cases for Yourself:</strong> The flexible evidence system lets players assign clues to cases, confront ship denizens about them, and submit any case with evidence players have connected to it. Everything found on the ship is connected, but figuring out how — that’s the challenge.<br/></li><li><strong>At What Cost?:</strong> Underneath the game's exciting and plausible sci-fi plot lies a number of thought-provoking problems inviting players to weigh intergenerational responsibility against personal freedom.<br/></li><li><strong>Getting New Perspective:</strong> Timeless pixel art mixed with 3D environments and compelling visual effects come together in Between Horizons, creating a unique, beautiful art style.<br/></li><li><strong>Failure is Very Much an Option:</strong> There are no second chances — submitting wrong solutions means the story will go on and players live with the consequences. A new and improved auto-save system will make sure there is no going back, as the story branches and endings are based on player decisions, none of which can be taken back.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1921980/extras/between-horizons-gif-walk.gif?t=1711386337"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1921980/Between_Horizons/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1921980/Between_Horizons/</a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2510720/Artifact_Seeker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/DS.png?t=1711367082"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/11y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>The unique “Artifacts sharing code function” allows you to share the Artifacts you collect with your friends! !<br/>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/1y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/1z.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/2y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/gif1.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/3y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/3y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/4y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/4y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/5y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/5y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/6y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/6y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living With Sister: Monochrome Fantasy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2429860/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1711168850"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_1__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/>Living in a fantasy world, it's always been your dream to grow up to be a famous adventurer just like your father. Reality proves to be more boring than fiction, however, as your days are mostly spent doing odd jobs for the villagers. With your friends by your side, you enter the Tournament of the Eights and strive for something greater: the chance to become the top guild in the country. Will you realize your ambitions, or will your hopes slip through your fingers and doom you to a life of monochrome monotony?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_2__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/>As a member of your town's Adventurers' Guild, it's your job to protect the townsfolk. Go on hunts, kill dangerous beasts, and hone your abilities to better tackle whatever challenges tomorrow brings.<br/><br/>Once you get home from work, you'll have your sister to attend to. She's a very sickly girl who needs a lot of help. Manage your household finances well, build up your relationship with your sister, and who knows, perhaps you might even be able to solve the mystery behind her illness.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_3__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Big_Brother_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Little_Sister_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Kana_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Yui_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Kasumi_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Yukari_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Akatsuki_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_4__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><strong>Hand-Drawn Monochrome Art</strong><br/>Though it may lack color, this game's world is anything but colorless! The stunning black-and-white art is chock-full of personality and is sure to leave you with plenty of marvelous monochrome memories!<br/><br/><strong>Unique Combat System</strong><br/>With tons of bizarre and ferocious monsters to fight and dozens of unique skills to unlock, your adventures are sure to be full of challenge and excitement!<br/><br/><strong>Charming Characters</strong><br/>Build up your relationships with your guildmates and your sister to learn about what makes them tick and unlock character-specific abilities to further assist you in your quest to become the top guild in the country!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Chilla's Art] Shinkansen 0 | 新幹線 0号</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2793370/Chillas_Art_Shinkansen_0___0/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2793370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Shinkansen 0 | 新幹線 0号 is a game set in Japan where players are tasked with finding anomalies in the Shinkansen. (Japanese bullet train)<br/><br/><i><strong>Supporter content can be turned on and off at the title screen. (It is on by default) </strong></i><br/><br/><i><strong>Motion Blur and Headbob is turned off by default.</strong></i><br/><br/><strong>Controls:<br/><br/>WASD - Move<br/>Left Click - Interact　<br/>Right Click - Zoom<br/>Shift - Run<br/>ESC - Options</strong><br/><br/>Easy mode - There is an easy mode in the mainmenu available for everyone to enjoy<br/><br/>Auto-save: auto-save for each chapter<br/><br/>Endings: There are two endings<br/><br/><strong><i>If you encounter any technical issues, do the following:<br/><br/>-Update GPU driver<br/>-Lower the Graphics settings/Screen resolution<br/>-Update Windows OS<br/>-Check if your anti-virus software is blocking the game or its save data. (Save Data location: C:\Users\[YOURUSERNAME]\AppData\LocalLow\Chilla's Art, LLC\Shinkansen0)<br/>-Delete save, then try again (Save Data location: C:\Users\[YOURUSERNAME]\AppData\LocalLow\Chilla's Art, LLC\Shinkansen0)<br/>-Check if your PC meets the system requirements</i></strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears In Space</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1309620/Bears_In_Space/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FG6w3Zxbp8W" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/Steam_CTAbutton_Discord.png?t=1711123009"/></a><br/>Get ready to unleash your inner bear in Bears in Space, the over-the-top<br/>bullet-hell FPS that's bound to have you ROARING with excitement! Dive headfirst into hordes of oil-thirsty robots as you embody Maxwell Atoms, a Spacetronaut turned extraterrestrial castaway, whose DNA has been merged with Beartana, the She-Bear. <br/>Embark on a zany and humorous out-of-this-world adventure that'll have you blasting your way across exciting and varied locations, from wastelands to space carnivals to ancient hidden temples and more as you quest to find your way back to earth and if there’s time, save your crew.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fast-paced Mayhem</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/BulletHell_acid2.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Bears In Space offers non-stop, high-energy gameplay. Fight your way through waves of fiendish robots using an arsenal of outrageous weaponry and gadgets. Double jump, dash, and dodge enemy attacks in the tradition of the best old-school shooters.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Mighty As A Bear</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/BearMode.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Consume elusive honey pots and unleash your Ursine rage, transforming into a bear!  <br/>Use your unique DNA fusion to your advantage, carving up robot enemies with your mighty bear powers and masterful knowledge of the ancient art of Bear Fu and the fabled Kuma No Ken.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Upgrade Your Arsenal</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/UpgradeRadial.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Complete challenges and break open loot crates to purchase guns, choosing from a diverse range of over 25 weapons!<br/>Most weapons upgrade, with each kill gaining your equipped weapon XP until it evolves into its next evolution tier! So, get out there and let the lasers fly!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Varied Gameplay</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/Varied_Gameplay_BasketCube.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Venture beyond the ordinary FPS experience and discover Substories, secrets and collectibles across every level!<br/>Learn how to bake a cake, investigate a crime scene, battle a Rock God, play a round of Basketcube and even bust some ghosts! All while meeting a colourful cast of characters with their own quirks and stories to tell.<br/>Completing these exciting optional encounters brings with it a hefty loot pay off, making these encounters even more rewarding to search out as you save up for your next weapon!<br/><br/>Choose your difficulty and play the game your way!<br/>Modify your difficulty with independent sliders for incoming and outgoing damage. You can also engage our Platform Helper mode, making all platforming segments of our game significantly easier to conquer! Perfect for kids or gamers new to the FPS genre!<br/><br/><br/>Whether you're a seasoned gamer looking for a blast from the past or a casual player seeking a fun-filled adventure, Bears in Space promises a fun and absurd, action packed time. Get ready to shoot, chuckle, and unleash your inner bear in this one-of-a-kind bullet-hell FPS adventure that’s truly out of this world!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Forgotten World:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827510/The_Forgotten_WorldPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FVuKggh6WYN" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/dss.png?t=1711106032"/></a><br/><br/><strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 8 in the official version.<br/>Chapters: 2 prologues, 6 official versions</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/111.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>This is about Alice after Wonderland.<br/>Oblivion is the vilest of spells. As an adult, Alice also experiences a less fairytale-like life and stops dreaming, which also means that everything about Wonderland is slowly disappearing. The people of Wonderland have even forgotten why they exist, and before everything dissipates, the Cheshire Cat casts a phantom spell to try to find Alice in the hope that she can save Wonderland once more.<br/>But the Cheshire Cat can't remember the spell either, and the wrong spell sends it traveling to a parallel world, a world where Alice has no idea that Wonderland even exists.<br/>In order to keep Wonderland from being forgotten, the Cheshire Cat brings Alice from each parallel world back to Wonderland, trying to awaken people's memories, and despite failures after failures, the Cheshire Cat still believes that he will find the right Alice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/1y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/1.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Play as different Alice and utilize different abilities and decks to defeat your enemies, each Alice has her own story! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/2y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/2.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Spellbound "monsters" are not real monsters, so defeat them to break the spell and discover their true nature! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/3y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/3.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Playing cards, which seem to be everywhere, will become your biggest fighting force at this moment! Poker soldiers can get different runes to increase combat power! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/4y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/4.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Arrange Poker Pawns of the same number of points or color to get a reinforcement effect, they don't have emotions but are very good at fighting! </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2054970/Dragons_Dogma_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Note: There are other sets that include this item.<br/><br/>Set forth on your grand adventure, Arisen!<br/><br/>Dragon’s Dogma is a single player, narrative driven action-RPG series that challenges the players to choose their own experience – from the appearance of their Arisen, their vocation, their party, how to approach different situations and more. Now, in this long-awaited sequel, the deep, explorable fantasy world of Dragon’s Dogma 2 awaits.<br/><br/>On your journey, you’ll be joined by Pawns, mysterious otherworldly beings, in an adventure so unique you will feel as if accompanied by other players while on your own adventure.<br/><br/>All of these elements are elevated further through physics technology, artificial intelligence (AI) and the latest in graphics, to create a truly immersive fantasy world in Dragon’s Dogma 2.<br/><br/><br/><strong><u>Action that challenges your creativity </u></strong> <br/><br/>Wield swords, bows, and chant magick.<br/>The vocations in Dragon's Dogma 2 give you the ability to approach combat the way you want.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_01.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Company in your single-player experience </u></strong> <br/><br/>Players can customize their own main Pawn, who will always accompany your Arisen, <br/>and enter a covenant with up to 2 additional Pawns from other players through the network. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_02.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Facing the monsters in this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Beyond the town borders, you will encounter diverse monsters that inhabit the lands. <br/>You will need to decide between engaging in battles or finding alternatives; <br/>so be aware of your party’s setup, the terrain around you, and the monsters you face.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_03.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Inhabitants of this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Travelers, merchants, soldiers and other folk go about their daily lives. <br/>Preoccupied by their own objectives and motives, they all exhibit different emotions.<br/>At times, they may lead you to a quest by approaching you and asking for a favor. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_04.gif?t=1711067553"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cureocity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2612680/Cureocity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							We are "Bread On Board," a collective of independent game developers spread across four countries, united by our passion and meeting during a GameJam. <br/>Our game demo was born in the "BOOOM CHALLENGE", a GameJam by GCORES. With only 21 days, we created a game based on a given theme. After the competition, we even won the "Most Popular Game" award at an Online Game Trial Event.<br/>The full playthrough of our game will take about an hour. We hope to give you a short, but super heartwarming and loving adventure❤️.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/1.奇幻而治愈（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>A rookie adventurer fresh on the scene and a former mercenary who was transferred into an adventurer due to injury. Two protagonists with contrasting personalities will embark on an adventure of fantasy and healing together. In the mysterious ruins of an underground dungeon that lies in the depth of a jungle, what awaits them will be...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/2.两位冒险者（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>According to the tavern's adventurer logs, the team heading into the dungeon features a rookie adventurer and an ex-mercenary who is now working as a healer. The adventurer looks as charming as a doll, and the enthusiasm never disappears; the healer is cool and a bit traditional, acting as a guiding figure for their adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/>What stories have unfolded between these two contrasting characters, and what challenges will they face together in this adventure? The continuation of this adventurous story is yours to discover.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/3.注重手法的回合制解谜（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>"People think battles need powerful weapons, but strategy at hand is key." <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_3_en.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/>In "Cureocity," the power of your strategy is materialized as the numerical values of your hands in combat. You can swap different weapons or items held in your left and right hands to alter your character's attack and defense stats. You may also change "gestures" to focus attacks or land heavy blows on specific enemies.As you delve deeper into the dungeon, you will take the unique traits of monsters into consideration and discuss strategies with your allies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/4.你的选择决定冒险归途（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>In this adventure, you'll discover not only the secrets hidden within the dungeon, but also the truths about the world and the  characters themselves. When faced with contaminated monsters, you can choose to either fight them or attempt to purify them. Of course, you also have the option to let things take their own course.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_4_en.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/>With each decision,the fate of the protagonists may change. The end of this adventure... is yours to decide.<h2 class="bb_tag">About the Publisher</h2>GCORES PUBLISHING is an independent game publishing venture formed by GCORES, committed to bringing you more outstanding indie games from the BOOOM CHALLENGE.<br/>Feel free to follow our <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/44750639" rel="" target="_blank">publisher webpage</a> for future updates.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midnight Ghost Hunt</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/915810/Midnight_Ghost_Hunt/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/915810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>MIDNIGHT GHOST HUNT IS A <i>PETRIFYING</i> PROP HAUNT GAME TO PLAY WITH PALS! </strong><br/><br/>Lying in wait across a series of cursed locations, relentless spirits stalk the halls. Assigned to eliminate them are the Ghost Hunters, armed to the teeth with the ghoul-busting tech to banish them to another realm! Play both Ghost and Hunter in a chaotic 4v4 struggle between the living and the dead.<br/><br/><strong>TONGUE-IN-CHEEK HIDE-AND-SEEK</strong><br/>As a Ghost, conceal yourself inside seemingly harmless pieces of furniture to evade preying Hunters… but when their backs are turned, turn the environment against them with telekinetic bombardment. No chair, lamp, or grandfather clock is innocent in this hijinks-heavy frenzy.<br/><br/><strong>MIDNIGHT MAYHEM</strong><br/>The fun isn’t over yet...when the clock strikes twelve, the witching hour begins, and the Hunters become the Hunted. The tables turn and Ghosts become supercharged, giving Hunters a limited amount of time to survive their vengeful wrath.<br/><br/><strong>MURDEROUS 4v4 MULTIPLAYER</strong><br/>Play together and communicate with your team and ensure a triumphant victory, giving each other pointers on the paths enemies tend to tread. Create synergies with your team's abilities to outthink and outwit your opponents.<br/><br/><strong>HARNESS SUPERNATURAL ABILITIES</strong><br/>The restrictions of reality don’t apply to Ghosts, of course. Claim your supernatural powers, which include turning invisible, causing furniture to float, and conjuring a dangerous Ghostly miasma. Ghosts can even hide in plain sight by masquerading as a Hunter’s doppelgänger!<br/><br/>Ghostly Perks include dramatically increasing your weight, extending your possessing range, the ability to see nearby Hunters through walls, and much more. <br/><br/><strong>ARMED AND READY</strong><br/>Hunters must choose their weapons from a full range of hi-tech gadgets designed to cast out Ghosts from our plane of existence. Detect ghostly presences with the Spectrophone, Radar and Pathfinder, capture them with a Trap, and suck up their spectral remains with the Vacuum – or just blast them to smithereens with the Spectral Cannon, sledgehammers, harpoons, salt-spewing shotguns, and more.<br/><br/>Hunters can also select Perks to give them a special boost. Choose from an extra burst of speed, health-replenishing capabilities and a host of other powers to get ahead of the game.<br/><br/><strong>A BEVY OF BLOOD-CURDLING MAPS </strong><br/>Explore ten unsettling locations, including an abandoned theatre, eerie mansion and cursed carnival. Each map brings with it different tactical considerations and items to throw about… as well as plenty of opportunities to play tricks on the enemy.<br/><br/><strong>FRIGHTENING NEW FEATURES</strong> <br/>As it crept through Steam Early Access, Midnight Ghost Hunt picked up a gaggle of game-changing features, built on the feedback of its community of Ghosts and Hunters.<br/><br/>Dedicated servers and host migration support make setting up matches a breeze, while the Progression Tier and Challenge systems bring added competition to the hunt. Looking for less of the silly and more of the scary? The Experimental Darkness game mode lends a chill to the chaos. Not to mention crossplay, full controller support, and even the GhostMaster minigame to pass the time during the van ride to your next match!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horizon Forbidden West™ Complete Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420110/Horizon_Forbidden_West_Complete_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/extras/horizon_forbidden_west_cinemagraph_610x610.gif?t=1711032993"><br/><br/>Join Aloy as she braves a majestic but dangerous new frontier that holds mysterious new threats. This Complete Edition allows you to enjoy the critically acclaimed Horizon Forbidden West on PC in its entirety with bonus content, including the Burning Shores story expansion that picks up after the main game.<br/><br/>Explore distant lands, fight bigger and more awe-inspiring machines, and encounter astonishing new tribes as you return to the far-future, post-apocalyptic world of Horizon.<br/><br/>The land is dying. Vicious storms and an unstoppable blight ravage the scattered remnants of humanity while fearsome new machines prowl their borders, and life on Earth is hurtling toward another extinction.<br/><br/>It's up to Aloy to uncover the secrets behind these threats and restore order and balance to the world. Along the way, she must reunite with old friends, forge alliances with warring new factions and unravel the legacy of the ancient past.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>See every gameplay detail with Ultrawide 21:9 and Super Ultrawide 32:9 resolutions, as well as 48:9 triple monitor support.*<br/></li><li>Witness the Forbidden West coming to life, with NVIDIA DLSS 3 upscaling and frame generation, image enhancing NVIDIA DLAA and latency reducing NVIDIA Reflex. AMD FSR and Intel XeSS are also supported.**<br/></li><li>Customize graphic settings to your preference, with the potential for unlocked frame rates.**<br/></li><li>Take control with full support for the DualSense™ controller, including haptic feedback and adaptive trigger functionality.*** </li></ul><br/>* Compatible PC and 4K display device required. <br/>** Compatible PC required. <br/>*** Wired connection required to experience the full range of in-game controller features.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age of Water: The First Voyage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2841350/Age_of_Water_The_First_Voyage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The First Voyage is the very beginning of your Age of Water experience. Jump right into the intense naval combat, craft your first boats, explore the waterworld and get a good idea of what Age of Water is about. Don’t forget to wishlist the full game now!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_ship_anim.gif?t=1711025025"><br/><br/>Become a sea captain on a post-apocalyptic Earth completely covered in water and go on an adventure in a huge open world. Sail through storms, fight and trade, capture other people's boats or build your own, extract resources from the bottom of the ocean, reveal the secrets of the Age of Water world.<br/><br/><strong>Water post-apocalypse</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_1.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>The ocean destroyed a once great civilization, but people survived and adapted. They built settlements on the roofs of tall buildings and the tops of other man-made structures. People travel across the ocean in tiny boats and huge combat vessels. The ocean provides everything they need, including extractable resources on the seabed. And yet, the dream of real land is still alive.<br/><br/><strong>True open world</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_2.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Explore the world at your own pace, discover new settlements and meet their inhabitants. Complete tasks, search for and extract valuable resources from the bottom of the ocean, earn money on trade or simply sell the artifacts you have obtained, and when you get the idea of how this world works, build your own base.<br/><br/><strong>Hundreds of unique ships</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_3.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Build boats from scratch or modify existing ones. Players have access to dozens of hulls and hundreds of parts, from which they can assemble anything ranging from a small boat to a hefty vessel 30 meters long, and then install equipment, armor and weapons. It’s important not to forget to gather a team of good crewmembers so that there is someone to stand behind machine guns and cannons or do other work on board.<br/><br/><strong>Fierce naval battles</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_4.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Pirates are always waiting for you at sea, and in some cases more aggressive players even start to chase you, so do not forget to install enough guns on your deck.  You can destroy an enemy vessel, or you can capture it in battle and take it for yourself forever. Adventures might also get you into storming enemy fortresses and defending allied settlements!<br/><br/><strong>Personal naval base</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_5.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>This shelter is reliably protected from enemies, and it allows a player to organize the production of everything that the captain may need on it. Build factories for the production of equipment, weapons, hulls for boats of all sizes, as well as the necessary resources.<br/><br/><strong>Flexible balance between PvE and PvP</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_6.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>At first, you will only meet computer opponents, but later you can challenge other players if you are confident enough in your skills and gear. Always be on the lookout: if your task is to transport illegal goods, then other players may well take the quest to hunt smugglers. In Age of Water, everyone decides for themself who they are today - a peaceful traveler or a bloodthirsty pirate.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slice &amp; Dice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1775490/Slice__Dice/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1775490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Slice &amp; Dice is a tactical dice battle roguelike.<br/><br/>Take control of 5 heroes, each with their own unique dice. Fight your way through 20 levels of monsters and try to take on the final boss. If you lose a single fight you have to start over so be careful/lucky!<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/>- 3D dice physics, choose which dice to reroll<br/>- Simple turn-based combat<br/>- Level up a hero or gain an item after each fight<br/>- Randomly-generated encounters<br/>- Ridiculous combos<br/>- Undo actions as much as you like<br/>- Each turn is like a mini-puzzle<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/>- 128 hero classes (+99999?)<br/>- 73 monsters<br/>- 473 items<br/>- Too many modes<br/>- ∞ curses<br/>- Weird modding<br/>- Online leaderboards<br/><br/><strong>Credits</strong><br/>- Created by tann (it took ~7 years)<br/>- Pixel art by a3um<br/>- Music by Ziggurath, Aleksander Zabłocki, Louigi Verona, Cold Sanctum, Ro'sø, Andrew Goodwin<br/>- Trailer by Everdraed<br/><br/>I plan to not participate in any sales/deals/bundles. No AI was used to make this game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone in the Dark</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1310410/Alone_in_the_Dark/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Alone in the Dark weaves a chilling tapestry of psychological horror and Southern Gothic charm, reimagining the iconic game that set the benchmark for the genre. We invite you to join us on a journey into madness, where each encounter could be your last. With each step you take closer to unravelling Derceto's mystery, the eyes that watch from the darkness grow hungrier. Every bullet means the difference between survival and an unthinkable end. The next door you unlock could lead to a nightmarish realm offering nothing but slashing claws, grasping tentacles, and frayed sanity.  Journey to interbellum Louisiana, where an era of decadence hides a darker tale - of escape from past traumas and an intolerant society, into the waiting grasp of something darker, something that has patiently lurked for impossible eons. This is Alone in the Dark as you've never seen it - a skillfully-woven narrative of Southern Gothic elegance and eldritch madness that pays homage to its legendary origins while taking the next step forward in survival horror storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_VIPIntro_2.gif?t=1711356992"><h2 class="bb_tag">A Haunting Tale of Mystery and Madness</h2>Step inside Derceto Manor, an asylum shrouded in intrigue, guarding a terrible secret. Client Emily Hartwood and private investigator Edward Carnby embark on a harrowing quest for answers; Emily to the mystery of her missing uncle, Edward to the toughest case he will ever face, and both to questions they dare not ask themselves. This re-envisioned classic invites you to explore an unforgettable single player adventure rich with suspense, frights, and revelations that will test the limits of your imagination.<h2 class="bb_tag">Featuring Hollywood Talent</h2>Experience some of the greatest acting survival horror has ever seen through the performances of award-winning actors Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow) in their first videogame roles. Jodie and David’s immaculately captured likenesses breathe life into Emily Hartwood and Edward Carnby, lending a deeply personal aspect to Alone in the Dark’s story that demands it be played twice to get the full experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Tribute to Horror Pioneers</h2>Rediscover the essence of psychological horror in a game that respectfully nods to its 1992 origin, the game that established the survival horror genre. Alone in the Dark is your gateway to an experience steeped in the atmospheric dread of classic horror, with next-generation storytelling and gameplay. A must-play for fans of twisted tales, nerve-wracking exploration, and desperate combat.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Story That Challenges Reality</h2>Envisioned by Mikael Hedberg, acclaimed writer behind modern horror classics “SOMA” and “Amnesia”, Alone in the Dark’s intricate web of mystery delves into themes of trauma, faith, evil, and abandonment. Whether you choose to brave the nightmare as Emily or Edward, you will uncover secrets that defy everything you thought about videogame storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Atrmo_2.gif?t=1711356992"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore Derceto Manor in this reimagination of Alone in the Dark, a love letter to the 90’s cult classic horror game.<br/></li><li>Return to the roots of psychological horror and experience an atmospheric journey worthy of the game that started the genre.<br/></li><li>Dive into a world full of sounds that make your skin crawl with a haunting, yet mesmerizing doom jazz soundtrack.<br/></li><li>Enjoy the thrill of desperate survival in a world where reality starts to crumble, evil lurks in every shadow and ammunition is scarce.<br/></li><li>Experience this nightmare from either Emily Hartwood’s or Edward Carnby’s perspective and unearth the dark secrets of a gothic mansion.<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in a deep psychological story that goes beyond the realms of the imaginable, by Mikael Hedberg, cult horror writer of SOMA and Amnesia.<br/></li><li>See Emily and Edward brought to live by the Hollywood talent of Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow), who lend their voices, their appearance, and their formidable acting skills to the protagonists.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Riddles_2.gif?t=1711356992"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raw Metal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2279600/Raw_Metal/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2279600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Raw Metal is a sci-fi stealth-action dungeon crawler with a focus on smooth, stylish gameplay.<br/><br/>You are a lone scavenger on the distant, barren exoplanet Charybdis. In search of gear and supplies, you infiltrate the depths of Katabase 6, a massive mining facility run by a corrupt megacorporation known as Orpheus Tech. Sneak through the mines undetected, cleverly utilizing various gadgets and equipment to your advantage, but beware; if you're caught, you'll need to rely on your combat skills for a fighting chance to escape.<h2 class="bb_tag">High-Stakes Stealth</h2><br/>Use taser darts, noisemakers, improvised concussion grenades, and more to slip past and isolate guards. The shadows are your domain; manipulate your environment and your enemies well enough and they'll never see you coming.<h2 class="bb_tag">Breakneck Combat</h2><br/>Combat in Raw Metal is fast and punishing. The guards stationed at Katabase 6 are stronger and more heavily armored than you, so fighting them head on will take skill, cunning, and a great degree of risk. However, mastering combos and using your environment will allow you to come out on top, and yield far greater rewards. Depending on whether it is initiated through a clever ambush or a stealth slip-up, combat can range from a calculated risk to a desperate fight for survival.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Blend of top-down stealth and third-person beat 'em up combat<br/></li><li>Freeform combo system that rewards aggression, improvisation, and precise timing and positioning<br/></li><li>50+ unique gear pieces to find and upgrade<br/></li><li>Distinct visuals for each gear piece to customize the look of your character<br/></li><li>Risk vs. reward extraction system that grants you the choice of cashing out your loot, or pushing deeper into the facility<br/></li><li>3 memorable and challenging boss fights, each with their own fighting styles, twists, and story development<br/></li><li>9 hand-crafted levels to infiltrate, with a few variants each to mix up your approach each time<br/></li><li>Environmental hazards and enemy variants to keep you on your toes as the game progresses<br/></li><li>5 deployable gadgets to utilize to your advantage in stealth and combat alike</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Park Baseball 25</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384620/Out_of_the_Park_Baseball_25/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_banner_1.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/>We are incredibly excited to announce <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong> - the special 25th Anniversary edition of our award-winning baseball strategy series. Can you believe it's been a quarter of a century? Out of the Park Baseball is not just a game - it's a legacy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_henry.png?t=1710574531"><br/><br/>If it happens in real baseball, it happens in Out of the Park Baseball! Discover new talent, draft the next superstar, negotiate with free agents, enter trade talks with other teams, build your dynasty and guide a franchise into an infinite future! As a manager, dive into the more hands-on management and set your team's lineups, pitching staffs, in-game strategy and call the shots from the dugout. You can oversee your league at a high level, or play out each game in the gorgeous 3D game mode, managing play by play or even pitch by pitch. OOTP has it all covered!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_badge.png?t=1710574531"><br/>Here are just a few of the new features coming to <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong>:<br/><br/><strong>A game-changing new Player Development Lab!</strong><br/><br/>Shape the future of your upcoming stars! You can channel your inner Player Development Director like never before. A modern new Player Development Lab is here for every team that allows you to give players individual programs to work on, developing them how you like. Do you want your hitter to work on improving their baserunning? Bunting? Contact? Would you prefer your pitcher to work on building up their stamina? Developing a new pitch? Velocity? It's all up to you - for each of your upcoming future stars!<br/><br/><strong>Massive Player Ratings and AI Upgrade!</strong><br/><br/>It’s the most comprehensive player ratings upgrade in the 25 year history of Out of the Park Baseball! Batting, Pitching, and Fielding ratings have been painstakingly modified to capture the essence of baseball, with modifications to Contact and Power for hitters, Movement and Stuff for pitchers, the addition of Catcher Framing and Stealing Aggressiveness, and much more. BABIP is now front and center for hitters and hurlers, while new internal ratings updates allow for even more flexibility for Commissioners around the world to adjust the game to their detailed delight. Plus, the AI throughout the game has been improved dramatically to deliver the most challenging OOTP experience ever! <br/><br/><strong>Even More Detailed Player Development Control!</strong><br/><br/>Delegate how each and every player on your team will spend their time day in, day out with coaches at practice. Want your power hitter to worry less about avoiding strikeouts and put that time and effort into working on his home run swing instead? Want your aging starter to spend more time practicing his control instead of spending that time worrying about his stuff? By allocating their time and focus to the areas you want, over time you can influence how players develop, maintain their skillset, and fight the aging curve.<br/><br/><strong>2024 Rosters and Rules!</strong><br/><br/>As always, Out of the Park Baseball features up-to-the-minute 2024 MLB rosters that get updated all season long, with every franchise represented from its big league club all the way down to the low minors, and everywhere in between! Plus, OOTP 25 features officially licensed leagues from South Korea (KBO) and Europe.<br/><br/><strong>Improved Historical MLB Modes!</strong><br/><br/>Set up historical MLB games in an all new streamlined way - and benefit from vastly improved historical player ratings! It’s never been faster or easier to experience the entire history of Major League Baseball, now producing even more realistic outcomes thanks to those comprehensive ratings and simulation engine upgrades.<br/><br/><strong>New Retro Visual Immersion!</strong><br/><br/>Watch games with a variety of experiences, including retro-style black and white, ‘50s-era, and ‘70s-era television presentations. Choose from all of these to play games, watch highlights, or just catch a ballgame from a bygone era!<br/><br/><strong>New Licensed Leagues!</strong><br/><br/>For the first time ever, Out of the Park Baseball features an officially licensed Honkbal Hoofdklasse league from The Netherlands and the British Baseball Federation from the United Kingdom! Look for their official clubs, players, competitions, and more!<br/><br/><strong>For the first time ever - an official partnership with the Baseball Hall of Fame!</strong><br/><br/>What happens when you combine the only game that has the entire history of baseball and the the greatest Hall of Fame in sports? An incredible, year-long journey! Join us as we partner with the Baseball Hall of Fame all season - and beyond. Explore Hall of Fame Plaques, with the official, accurate text for each Hall of Famer. Discover incredible Hall of Fame artifacts, curated and released in fun "exhibits" over the course of the season in concert with the Hall - and more surprises too. It's going to be amazing! <br/><br/><strong>Dozens of upgrades big and small!</strong><br/><br/>--&gt; Updated in-game engine base advancement and camera movements<br/>--&gt; A new manager decision history screen gives you a look back on your best and worst trades and transactions<br/>--&gt; Improved trade packages for prospect packages <br/>--&gt; Updated two-way functionality with injured players<br/>And much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/pt_store_text_banner2.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/><br/><strong>Perfect Team is back - bigger than ever!</strong><br/><br/>It’s an all-new Perfect Team! There’s nothing in the world like the incredible online competitions of Perfect Team. Featuring by far the largest player pool ever, and taking advantage of all the player rating and balance upgrades, this year’s Perfect Team is a whole new ballgame.<br/><br/><strong>Brand New Perfect Team Combinator Series Cards!</strong><br/><br/>Pulled non-live cards have a chance to be a special Combinator Series version of the card! Use other cards that share a link (for example being teammates) with the player to get a chance to boost the raw ratings of the Combinator Series card.<br/><br/><strong>A Perfect Team Tournament Roster Builder!</strong><br/><br/>Want to design rosters for the incredible array of Perfect Team Tournaments - all on your own? For the first time ever, Perfect Team will feature a Tournament Sandbox! You can tinker to your heart's content with varying rosters for every type of tournament, with no pressure. This long-requested feature makes its debut in Out of the Park Baseball 25!<br/><br/>In addition to the brand-new Tournament Roster Builder and Combinator Series, Perfect Team 25 also features:<br/><br/><strong>Team Chemistry</strong> - Players who played together in real life will get extra bonuses when on your roster together. Players gain bonuses for seasons they played together, as well as simply being part of the same team or from the same decades<br/><strong>Perfect Team competitions starting on the first day</strong>, including a huge Opening Weekend of Tournaments with big prizes and Perfect Team Championship Series qualifying from Day One! <br/><strong>New content all season long - and beyond!</strong> All new programs, missions, competitions, and excitement await you every day.<br/><br/>Out of the Park Baseball 25 runs on PC/Mac and features the American League and National League logos, the World Series trophy, official logos and jerseys for all 30 MLB teams and 15 KBO teams, over 150 Minor League Baseball league and team logos, and historical MLB logos.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Shire: Room One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517850/Toy_Shire_Room_One/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FkhSxB2MSgD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/Toy_Shire_-_Discord_Banner.png?t=1710352808"/></a><br/><br/><br/>Play through the <strong>three levels in Kevin's Room</strong> and defend your room against your old toys. Face Memphis-X in the final level and put a stop to his assault as he crushes your soldiers in an attempt to get to your base.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyVengeance.png?t=1710352808"><br/>You received new toys from your family. Isn't that lovely? Oh, it's for sure... <br/>Your old toys, though, aren't getting along as well. They are no longer cared for and have been forgotten. So what follows next? They're going to join together against you and assault your brand-new toys, so be prepared. But never worry! You're in luck since your brand-new toys are troops of green soldiers. They still require your aid though! Control, strengthen, and defeat the opposing forces! However, focus with care, the enemies you encounter might not be your old playthings!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/InteractiveTowerDefense.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Tower building alone won't be sufficient to repel incoming attackers. Build up your own troops in the best feasible positions, then unleash attacks into enemy territory. Never abandon your towers, and deploy your troops in accordance with the traits of the enemy. First, the attacking forces will attempt to get past your defenses. Build and improve towers to aid your army. By using unique abilities, you can support your troops and towers as well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/EpicBattles.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Safeguard your base against waves of attackers. You need to pick the right troops if you would like to prevail. Clean the paths and guard any open routes. Upgrade your troops and unlock new ones to take down the waves and claim victory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyRealm.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Enter a world and a narrative built around the toys that enriched your youth, including toy soldiers, dinosaur sets, robots, building blocks, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_3.gif?t=1710352808"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dune: Imperium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1689500/Dune_Imperium/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Header.png?t=1710955211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body0_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Experience the ultimate blend of strategy and intrigue as you navigate the treacherous landscapes of Arrakis in the award-winning board game <i>Dune: Imperium</i>!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle online, locally with AI, or against the formidable House Hagal.<br/></li><li>Earn Achievements that showcase your prowess as a leader.<br/></li><li>Embark on more than a dozen Challenges that will test your wit and cunning.<br/></li><li>Compete for badges in the rotating Skirmish Mode where no two games are the same!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body1_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Arrakis. Dune. Desert Planet. Raise your banner above the vast wasteland before you. As the Great Houses of the Landsraad marshal their forces and their spies, whom will you influence, and whom will you betray? A tyrannical Emperor. The secretive Bene Gesserit. The shrewd Spacing Guild. The ferocious Fremen of the Deep Desert. The power of the Imperium can be yours, but war is not the only way to claim it.<br/><br/><i>Dune: Imperium</i> blends deck-building and worker placement in a deeply thematic new strategy game where the fate of the Empire hangs on your decisions. Will you seek political allies or rely upon military might? Economic strength or subtle intrigues? A council seat… or a sharpened blade? The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body2_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>In <i>Dune: Imperium</i>, you'll step into the role of one of the leaders of the Great Houses of the Imperium in a struggle to control the planet Arrakis and the invaluable Spice it provides.<br/><br/>The game plays out in a series of ten rounds, each of which is defined by a new Conflict on the surface of the planet; some award critical resources, and some provide Victory Points that will propel you to dominance. But choose your battles wisely: spread your forces too thin, and you'll find your enemies growing too strong to oppose.<br/><br/>Each round, you'll draw a hand of five cards from your deck, which will get stronger over the course of the game as you acquire new cards. Each card can be played in one of two ways: To send an Agent out into the Imperium to gather resources, or to Reveal at the end of the round to purchase new powerful cards. You must maintain a careful balance to get the most of the resources available to you. How will you find your path?<br/><br/>As your game progresses, you'll vie for Influence with four factions of the Imperium: The Emperor, the economically powerful Spacing Guild, the mysterious Bene Gesserit, and the ferocious Fremen of the deep deserts. Earning Influence among the various groups helps you to earn the Victory Points you need...but will you compete with your rivals for their favor, or abandon alliances to pursue other opportunities?<br/><br/>Many strategies are at your disposal, and many paths to victory. The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Footer.png?t=1710955211"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals Zero Hour</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732960/Command__Conquer_Generals_Zero_Hour/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals Zero Hour brings you closer to the enemy than ever before. Engage opposing forces at hot spots around the globe as you match strategies and arsenals against the new masterminds of modern war.<br/><br/><strong>Arsenal.</strong> Unleash the next generation of 3D new units and 20 new upgrades including China's ECM Tank, GLA's BattleBus and the USA's Spectre Gunship.<br/><br/><strong>Missions.</strong> Take on 15 new missions and make tomorrow's headlines. Root out a splinter cell in Cairo, steal deadly toxins from a U.S. lab and more.<br/><br/><strong>Generals.</strong> Match strategies and arsenals against 9 enemy commanders with unpredictable personalities and tactics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Tiberian Sun™ and Firestorm™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229880/Command__Conquer_Tiberian_Sun_and_Firestorm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Second Tiberium War begins in this legendary sequel to the original Command &amp; Conquer. <br/><br/>With his forces stronger than ever, arch villain and leader of The Brotherhood of Nod - Kane - is pitched in an epic battle against the world's war machine - the Global Defense Initiative. Now you must orchestrate the fate of mankind.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on Dynamic Battlefields. Nature itself provides tactical opportunities - destroyable and deformable terrain, forest fires, treacherous ice fields and many more surprises that help or hinder your strategies.<br/></li><li>Exciting New Strategies and Units. Jump Jet Infantry, Hover Tanks, Tunneling APCs, Hunter Seekers, Laser Fences, Mechanized Battle Units and many more.<br/></li><li>The "Veterancy" Factor. Units can become faster and stronger as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>New Kinetic Battlefields. Flying shrapnel, shock waves and crashing debris are just a few of the exciting new technologies developed to enhance the in-game experience.<br/></li><li>The mood and attitude of the battlefield comes alive like never before - covert night missions, searchlights and new defenses intensify the thrill and excitement.</li></ul><br/>Then take the battle further in <strong>Firestorm, the official expansion pack for the game</strong>. Includes all-new campaign missions, cinematics, and units to decide the future of mankind.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Renegade™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229890/Command__Conquer_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer gets up close and personal in this classic First Person Shooter for one of the most iconic franchises.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wreak Havoc</strong> - Experience the Command &amp; Conquer universe on foot as Havoc, wise-cracking GDI Commando.<br/></li><li><strong>Make Your Own Rules</strong>  - Take on the evil Brotherhood of Nod using your own mix of brute force, stealth, and strategy.<br/></li><li><strong>Assault at Ground Level</strong>  - Dish out the damage in either first or third person.<br/></li><li><strong>Total Access</strong>  - Sneak inside and explore full-scale structures, like immense Tiberium Refineries and the ominous Hand of Nod.<br/></li><li><strong>Grind the Gears</strong>  - Beef up your arsenal by commandeering lethal vehicles, such as Nod Buggies, Flame Tanks, and Mammoth Tanks.<br/></li><li><strong>Weapons of Mass Destruction</strong>  - Choose from a multitude of weapons, including the Tiberium Auto Rifle, Chemical Sprayer, and the devasting Personal Ion Cannon.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™, Counterstrike™ and The Aftermath™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229840/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_Counterstrike_and_The_Aftermath/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert</strong> pushed the envelope for the RTS genre in the mid-1990s and became one of the most iconic strategy games of all time. <br/><br/><strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert</strong>  gives you the opportunity to be more devious, cunning, and ruthless than ever before. Red Alert puts the fate of the world in your hands!<br/><br/><strong>Counterstrike</strong>, the exciting expansion pack to Red Alert, is full of clandestine activity, experimental technologies, and disavowed tactics. Includes 16 all-new missions, where you decide the ultimate fate of the struggle between the Allies and Soviets.<br/><br/><strong>In The Aftermath expansion pack</strong>, prepare for guerilla tactics, insidious strategies, and forbidden weapons. Includes 18 all-new missions and multiple units in a showdown that will test your mettle.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ and The Covert Operations™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229830/Command__Conquer_and_The_Covert_Operations/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The legendary RTS game which started it all. Will you side with the humanistic GDI or bring the world to its knees with Kane and the Brotherhood of Nod. Your adversaries are without mercy. And so are you.  <br/><br/>Includes the <strong>The Covert Operations</strong> expansion pack with a range of challenging new missions.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit Hole</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2831340/Rabbit_Hole/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/smaller.png?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Remember you will live.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Rabbit Hole is a fast paced, tough-as-nails 2D Platformer-RogueLike-Shooter inspired by popular roguelikes, made with a love for the genre. <br/>You are Disc, someone who was suddenly brought to the Rabbit Hole. <br/>Collect guns, fight foes and meet strange new characters on your descent to the bottom, all in an attempt to find your heart again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/1.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“This place is like its own ecosystem. A big living breathing mess.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Every run is different. Enjoy hours of replayable content through randomly generated floor layouts and 50+ weapons to collect and use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/2.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Hey, hey, hey! How's my favorite anxiety-fueled nutjob!”</i></strong><br/><br/>Unlock new characters with diverse playstyles. Each of the 6 unlockable characters keep gameplay fresh and give a unique perspective on the gameplay loop.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/3.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“There was a blank line, almost as if I had erased it”</i></strong><br/><br/>Discover the truth that lies beneath the surface. Collect books and fill out your library to understand its unseen history. In the end, you may even come to understand yourself?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Grindea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/269770/Secrets_of_Grindea/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/269770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Secrets of Grindea</i> is an old-school Action RPG with co-op support for up to 4 players. It is a tribute to and sometimes a parody of the old SNES games so many of us grew up with and loved! Journey through fantastical lands, and battle tons of different enemies and bosses in your quest for truth, friendship and, above all, finding the world's rarest treasures!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A rich world filled with 300+ unique, colorful characters and an engaging story to drive your journey forward.<br/></li><li>Co-op support for up to four players! Enjoy the entire storyline with your friends or call someone in to help with the more difficult challenges.<br/></li><li>Customization, customization, customization - design a character that represents you, then mix and match any of the 31 spells and skills across 9 different categories.<br/></li><li>30+ epic boss fights! Overgrown slimes, giant robots, mimics - we have it all!<br/></li><li>Side content - design your own home, fish, craft items, tame pets, partake in mini-games, grow plants - there’s plenty to keep you entertained when you want a break from the main story.</li></ul><br/>And last but not least:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Arcade Mode - Separate from Story Mode, the game includes a <strong>full roguelite</strong> version where you need to battle your way to the top on a single life, building a town of your own as you progress.  How far can you get?</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<br/><br/>※ <i>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</i> is the free-to-play version of <i>Meta-Ghost: The breaking show</i>, to showcase some of the gameplay content.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709870080"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Epoch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/899770/Last_Epoch/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Epoch combines time travel, exciting dungeon crawling, engrossing character customization and endless replayability to create an Action RPG for veterans and newcomers alike. Travel through the world of Eterra’s past and face dark empires, wrathful gods and untouched wilds – to find a way to save time itself from The Void.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Gameplay.gif?t=1709060046"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>15 Mastery Classes</strong><br/>Embark on your adventure as one of five powerful classes and, through your journey, ascend into a unique Mastery Class that unlocks more specialized abilities and build-options. <br/></li><li><strong>120+ Skill Trees</strong><br/>Every skill has its own augment tree that will allow you to control, alter, and empower your playstyle. Transform your skeletons into archers, your lightning blast into chain lightning, or make your serpent strike summon snakes to fight alongside you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Nodes.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Hunt Rare &amp; Powerful Loot</strong><br/>Fill your arsenal with magic items that you may craft to perfection, change the rules of your build with powerful unique and set items, and always have that next upgrade just on the horizon with Last Epoch's deep and randomized loot system.<br/></li><li><strong>Rewarding Crafting System</strong><br/>The items you wield are yours to forge! Last Epoch’s community-revered crafting system allows you to control your character's power progression, featuring robust and deterministic upgrade mechanics.<br/></li><li><strong>Uncover the Past, Reforge the Future</strong><br/>Travel to different moments of time where you will discover the many factions and secrets that exist within the world of Eterra and fight to set the timeline onto a new path.<br/></li><li><strong>Endless replayability</strong><br/>With a wealth of classes and skills to customize, deep game systems, randomized loot, and continuing development, Last Epoch is a game that will keep you coming back for years to come.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Monolith.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Easy to Learn, Hard to Master</strong><br/>We’re committed to making gameplay approachable for new and veteran players alike by allowing you to jump into the fray quickly and providing many in-game resources. Though don’t be fooled, Eterra has many dangers waiting for you that require a mastery of combat and build-crafting.<br/></li><li><strong>Zero Pay-To-Win</strong><br/>Last Epoch will never offer gameplay advantages by being able to spend real money. We believe in creating a fair environment for all players. </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2379780/Balatro/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Balatro is a poker-inspired roguelike deck builder all about creating powerful synergies and winning big.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Endless_Possibility.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Combine valid poker hands with unique Joker cards in order to create varied synergies and builds. Earn enough chips to beat devious blinds, all while uncovering hidden bonus hands and decks as you progress. You’re going to need every edge you can get in order to reach the boss blind, beat the final ante and secure victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Jokers_Clean_Thin.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The definitive poker roguelike experience.<br/></li><li>Endless possibilities - every pick-up, discard and joker can dramatically alter the course of your run.<br/></li><li>In-depth campaign mode complete with 8 difficulties, as well as challenge, daily and seeded runs. </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Break_The_Game.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Deftly deploy an array of potent tools: different Decks, Jokers, Tarot cards, Planet cards, Spectral cards, and Vouchers. Use these versatile instruments to ignite a combo frenzy and turbocharge your poker hands, crafting electrifying, adrenaline-fueled synergies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro_5_Aces_GIF__HQ_.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 Jokers, each with their own unique abilities<br/></li><li>15 Decks with distinct modifiers to choose from for each run<br/></li><li>5 potential variants of each Joker which add further abilities<br/></li><li>22 Tarot cards variants that can enhance your regular playing cards<br/></li><li>11 Planet cards that help level up your possible poker hands<br/></li><li>32 Voucher cards to help provide permanent buffs for your current run</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Find_Your_Flow.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in Balatro’s distinctive psychedelic world. Let the synthwave soundtrack wash over you -  wind down, escape the daily grind and prepare to enter the ultimate roguelike flow state.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improve your collection and discover new cards and secrets with every single run.<br/></li><li>Make use of the in-depth stats screen to study your best hands, most used Jokers, and more!<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the CRT fuzz and enjoy detailed, hand-crafted pixel art.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Spectral_Pack.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F5mH3dNhjx2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro-join_the_discord.png?t=1710160593"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOTTOLOT</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2512830/NOTTOLOT/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							NOTTOLOT is a robot hacking action game.<br/>Use the main character's ability to hack enemy robots to escape from the factory!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512830/extras/ene.png?t=1711439918">　<br/><br/><strong>■Exhilarating hacking action</strong><br/>Control enemy robots with the main character's ability to hack them.<br/>Sneak up from behind...tackle and hack!<br/><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512830/extras/nottori2_jp.gif?t=1711439918"><br/><br/><strong>■Enemy robots with various functions</strong><br/>Fly in the sky, climb walls, and more,<br/>Manipulate enemies to break through gimmicks and clear all three stages!<br/><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512830/extras/gif2_jp.gif?t=1711439918"><br/><br/><strong>■Tense factory escape</strong><br/>The main character "Rolly" longs for the outside world.<br/>Can he escape from the robot production factory guarded by enemy robots?<br/><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512830/extras/open_jp.gif?t=1711439918"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DORONKO WANKO</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2512840/DORONKO_WANKO/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							『DORONKO WANKO』 is a <strong>DORONKO Action</strong> Game.<br/>In this game, you can become a cute, innocent pomeranian.<br/>And you can make your master's home messy and dirty.<br/>Let's explore this beautiful house and make it dirty and muddy at will!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Action_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Action.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>Pomeranian can get muddy by "rubbing"  against the "mud" spread on the floor.<br/>Spread out the mud with "splash"!<br/>Let's make the whole area muddy and messy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Goal_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Goal.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>Sometimes you can find "hidden pome" when you are spreading mud all over the house.<br/>When you find all the "hidden pome", the "Good Smell Room" 's door will open.<br/>(Let's go inside quietly before others notice!)<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Damage_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Damage.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>More mud, more damage!<br/>You can check the total amount of damage you have caused from the ending “Receipt”.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Present_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Present.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>When you cause enough damage, you will receive a “gift”?!<br/>They will help Pome’s exploration by making it easier to splash mud and obtain key items.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Gimmick_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Gimmick.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>A little action can cause a huge damage?<br/>Use personal appliances and toys to get even muddier.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Badge_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Badge_EN.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>The Pomeranian's adventures will remain as a "badge of memory".<br/>A random move may get an unexpected badge.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Customize_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Customize.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>"Put on" the "Goods" and make your Pomeranian more pretty.<br/>Don't forget the special goods that can release mud!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOMEROAD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2512820/BOOMEROAD/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">■『BOOMEROAD』</h2><strong>BOOMEROAD is an exhilarating action-adventure game in which players slide along boomerang rails you will create.<br/>You will be playing as the main character, Boomy. Boomy has to reach a tower with a mysterious boomerang while overcoming the obstacles and aims for the Ancient Tower.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">▼A new experience in the vast sky</h2><strong>The game is set in an ancient ruin floating in the sky, and the player slides through the vast skies at their own will while searching for the Artifacts.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512820/extras/gif1_1_1_1.gif?t=1711439593"><h2 class="bb_tag">▼Aiming, throwing, and sliding. Easy operation and exhilarating action</h2><strong>The exhilarating action with the "rail-drawing boomerang" is the charm of this game.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512820/extras/gif1_2.gif?t=1711439593"><h2 class="bb_tag">▼Numerous gimmicks to make the action more fun</h2><strong>You will aim for the Ancient Tower with the boomerang while dodging lasers and using a blower to generate wind on several occasions.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512820/extras/gif1_2_1.gif?t=1711439593"><h2 class="bb_tag">■"TimeAttackMode" to test your skills</h2><strong>Choose efficient routes and skillfully handle boomerangs to reach the goal quickly.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512820/extras/シーケンス_タイムアタック.gif?t=1711439593"><br/><br/><br/><strong></strong><h2 class="bb_tag">■The setting is an ancient ruin floating in the sky</h2><strong>The game is set in an ancient ruin floating in the sky.<br/>Boomy, a young archaeologist boy, visits the ruins as he believes in the legend that there are hidden treasures of an ancient civilization in the towers of the ruins.<br/>Using one of the ruin's artifacts,  a boomerang that can draw rails, he adventures through the ruins, which are shrouded in the veil of secrecy.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">▼The Ancient City area is where you can enjoy the clear sky</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512820/extras/シーケンス_エリア1.gif?t=1711439593"><h2 class="bb_tag">▼The Ancient Fortress City area is where you can immerse yourself in the shining moonlit night view</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512820/extras/シーケンス_エリア2.gif?t=1711439593"><h2 class="bb_tag">▼Collect the "Oparts" hidden in the ancient ruins</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512820/extras/画像のサイズを変更_プロジェクト.png?t=1711439593"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512820/extras/画像のサイズを変更_プロジェクト__1_.png?t=1711439593"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512820/extras/画像のサイズを変更_プロジェクト__2_.png?t=1711439593"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contraptions Collection</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827950/Contraptions_Collection/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>On every level there are several objects and monsters...The goal is to rid the level of the monsters. This can be achieved in different ways...The objects are affected by the laws of physics and play a key part in solving the puzzle. The objects form a “contraption” which are placed in such a way, which creates a chain reaction that will wipe out all monsters. The catch is that the contraption is broken - some objects are not in the right place. Your goal is to fix the contraption. You do this, by repositioning, flipping, or connecting the different objects.<br/><br/>When the level starts “time is frozen”, gravity doesn’t affect the objects and all machines or gadgets are not running. During this time, you can move things around, connect things, flip things, to make the chain reaction work. Once you are done, you set things in motion (unfreeze time) by pressing the Play button and watch things play out.<br/><br/>If you did everything correctly the chain reaction will wipe out all monsters and you will progress to the next level. If your solution is not correct, you can pause the contraption and fiddle with the objects again.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gadgets</h2>Some of the gadgets are activated by igniting them, other by touching, pushing, or pulling them. Some gadgets work on their own, while other gadgets must be connected to function. For example, for the conveyor belt to turn, it must be connected to an active engine, using a belt. Likewise for the laser gun to fire a laser, the trigger must relate to a rope, to a moving object, like a car.<h2 class="bb_tag">Objectives</h2>To rid the levels of the monsters! The simplest way is to push the monster off the edge of a platform and make it fall off the screen. You could cut the rope holding a heavy object, which will smash the monster; pull a rope, connected to a laser gun; igniting the engine of a rocket with a lighter in which the monster is in, etc.<br/><br/>The solution is achieved through chain reactions, Rube Goldberg style. The more you progress through the game, the more complex the new puzzles become.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>• Solve over 500 wacky puzzles form each game across 5 different worlds.<br/>• Create an unlimited number of your own levels and challenge a friend to try to beat it.<br/>• Use a plethora of goofy gadgets from scissors to washing line pegs.<br/>• Complete the levels in multiple ways...get as bonkers and creative as you like.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sultan Jumps</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2875940/Sultan_Jumps/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2875940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2875940/extras/SultanOG.jpg?t=1711437958"><br/><br/><strong>Sultan Jumps</strong> is a platformer game with difficult challenges. You play a grandmother who goes looking for her grandson who got lost while chasing his balloon. It has challenging platforming levels and mastering jumping is very important. One mistake can cause a long fall.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay:</h2><strong>-You must master jumping!</strong><br/>There are many difficult sections throughout the game. You won't be able to pass all the platforms in one go. You have to try again and figure out where you should jump. Even if you pass a platform, you may fall much lower than that platform and have to cross the same platform again. <br/><br/><strong>-Use your double jump ability!</strong><br/>Sultan is a character who can double jump. But when you make the second jump is very important. If you make the second jump too early or too late, you may miss the platforms or hit your head on a wall. <br/><br/><strong>-Sultan has some things to tell you!</strong><br/>Sultan is a character who talks a lot. If you hit the ground with a certain speed, Sultan will say something to you afterwards and they won't be nice words. Sultan has dozens of unique things to say to you. Be patient and don't make her angrier.<h2 class="bb_tag">Content:</h2>Sultan Jumps is a game developed by one person. All graphics, sounds, levels, music and story were created entirely by one person. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fully hand-drawn pixel graphics<br/></li><li>Quality sound effects, all organically recorded<br/></li><li>High resolution pixel landscapes<br/></li><li>Levels prepared by a developer who is passionate about platformer games<br/></li><li>Full controller support</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parking Driver</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2861270/Parking_Driver/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2861270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a simulation parking game with a total of 28 levels, roughly ranging from easy to difficult.<br>
<br>
If you have rich driving experience in reality, then you must also be at ease in the game.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weed Harvest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2865830/Weed_Harvest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2865830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Game story:</h2>Drive harvester machine in this open world driving simulation game. Cut weed areas in big open world and enjoy cool enviroment. Earn steam achievements by driving enough and collecting different items. Be a best weed cutter in world and cut all areas in this immersive open world driving simulation game<h2 class="bb_tag">Features::</h2>- Open world<br/>- Lot of achievements<br/>- weed to cut<br/>- different camera angles						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wage Slave TD: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2871760/Wage_Slave_TD_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2871760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The difference between the prologue and the official version:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Wage slaves: 10 in the prologue, 15 in the official version<br/></li><li>Boss: 10 in the prologue, 14 in the official version<br/></li><li>Maps: 18 in the prologue, 45 in the official version<br/></li><li>System: The official version adds challenge mode, endless mode, and random mode<br/></li><li>Archive: Don’t worry, the official version will inherit the archive progress of the prologue</li></ul><br/>Arrange your wage slaves, pass wave after wave of boss reviews, win, and unlock more project maps!<h2 class="bb_tag">Wage slaves showing their special abilities</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2871760/extras/units.png?t=1711436536"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 15 kinds of wage slaves, including hardworking pig, licking dog, old white rabbit, egg hen, pan sheep, mud horse, bloody rooster, and proud cow.<br/></li><li>Rich movements, sounds, and Emoji<br/></li><li>There is also an elephant</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"> Endless changes and events</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2871760/extras/rogue.gif?t=1711436536"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Various events<br/></li><li>Workplace memes<br/></li><li>Wage slaves can learn from others, and the combinations are endless</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">A boss group full of wisdom</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2871760/extras/boss.png?t=1711436536"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 14 types of bosses including Bird Director, Wolf Director, Crocodile Manager, Lucky Horse, Airborne Bat, etc.<br/></li><li>Pickup aritist, sexual harassment, crocodile tears, boss features are all there</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Additional game mode</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2871760/extras/challenge.gif?t=1711436536"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Private work from lonely boss<br/></li><li>Challenge the best wage slave configuration and refresh personal best results</li></ul><br/>The game is developed by an individual and mainly draws inspiration from: Carrot Fantasy, Bloons, and Plants vs. Zombies.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hydroplane: Riptide Racers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2706460/Hydroplane_Riptide_Racers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Hydroplane: Riptide Racers is a fast paced arcade racer. Race through the canal streets of Nautica to earn parts and piece together your ideal speed boat. Blast, jet, float, navigate, and dominate your way to first place to unlock equipment to play how you want.<h2 class="bb_tag">Race Through The City</h2>Rev your engines and dominate the waterways in an adrenaline-fueled arcade boat racing experience unlike any other! In Hydroplane: Riptide Racers, you'll immerse yourself in a high-speed thrill ride through the diverse districts of Nautica city. Feel the rush as you race across the unique urban landscape!<br/>From the untamed Nomad's Oasis in Nautica's outskirts to the bustling streets of the Sandstone Enclave, and the neon-lit grunge of the Noble Nexus, each district offers a distinctive backdrop for pulse-pounding competition.<br/>Engage in epic races against your rivals through the districts, unique races featuring dynamic obstacle, hairpin turns, and strategic power-ups to outmaneuver the competition. Break the waves! Chase the glory!<h2 class="bb_tag">Unlock New Parts and Equipment</h2>Conquer every twist, turn, and wave as you dominate each district to unlock a treasure trove of ship parts and cutting-edge equipment. Tailor your vessel to perfection, fine-tuning every aspect to suit your racing style for each heart-pounding rally. Seeking sharper turns? Explosive acceleration? Mind-bending speed? Craft your ultimate speedboat with an arsenal of customizable ship parts!<br/>Take your pick from a range of top-of-the-line gear, including the jet boost for blistering speed bursts, the rocket for devastating power, the magnet harpoon for tactical maneuvers, mines to delay and disrupt racers, and the encompassing arc blast! Unleash creativity to give you the critical edge on the waterways!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KERIBATO!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2463000/KERIBATO/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2463000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A simple and exhilarating RPG puzzle game. In a dungeon packed with monsters, the goddess Nike fights while kicking enemies to regain her wings!<br>
<br>
■Story<br>
Long ago, the gods of Olympus, led by Zeus, and the Titans, led by Zeus' father Kronos, fought for control of the universe. This battle of the gods was known as the Titanomachia, and it was so large in scale that it nearly destroyed the world.<br>
However, the battle between the immortal gods was inconclusive, and neither side was able to win. Zeus tried to win Nike, the goddess of victory who had the blood of the Titans, to his side, but Cronus, learning of this, tricked Nike into taking away her wings and plunged her into the abyss of Tartarus, the cave of the abyss.<br>
In the cave, crammed with demons, the only person she could rely on was Pupo, an owl.<br>
Will Nike be able to recover her wings from the giants and return to the earth?<br/>
<br/>
■How to play<br/>
This is a puzzle RPG with simple rules.<br/>
Nike will take damage when fighting enemies with a higher level than her, but can defeat enemies with a lower level by kicking them from behind.<br/>
Kicking an enemy will deal damage to the enemy ahead.<br/>
Treasure chests appear from time to time, some of which contain useful items and some of which are traps.<br/>
There are also powerful enemies that chase Nike. Level up while running away from them and aim to escape from the dungeon.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPIDARY: Jewel Craft Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2539820/LAPIDARY_Jewel_Craft_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2539820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Non-verbal Experience</h2>"LAPIDARY: Jewel Craft Simulator" is developed with non-verbal expressions, making it universally enjoyable regardless of language barriers!<h2 class="bb_tag">Overview</h2>LAPIDARY: Jewel Craft Simulator is a simple gem crafting simulator. Follow the provided recipes to cut raw stones and produce dazzlingly sparkling gems.<br/><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2539820/extras/summary01.gif?t=1711414559"><h2 class="bb_tag">Selecting Raw Stones</h2>When you start the game, you will be presented with the color and shape of the gemstone you should create. Select an appropriate raw stone from the list provided and begin processing.<br/><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2539820/extras/summary02.gif?t=1711414559"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gemstone Processing</h2>Rotate the 3D model of the raw stone and carefully lower it onto the lathe. By repeating this process, you will carve the raw stone and shape the gemstone. Once it matches the shape of the gemstone you are supposed to make, press the finish button and check the results of your work!<br/><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2539820/extras/summary03.gif?t=1711414559"><h2 class="bb_tag">Confirming the Results</h2>Your gem crafting results will be evaluated! The more accurately you work, the better the rewards you will receive. The gems you create can be named and added to your collection!<br/><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2539820/extras/summary04.gif?t=1711414559"><h2 class="bb_tag">Video Streaming Guidelines</h2>We at THINK &amp; FEEL welcome the posting and streaming of LAPIDARY: Jewel Craft Simulator videos and hereby establish the following guidelines for video posting and streaming of the game.<br/> <br/><strong>Permission for Posting and Streaming</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>For posting and live streaming of gameplay, commentary, and review videos of LAPIDARY: Jewel Craft Simulator, no special permission is needed, regardless of whether you are an individual or a corporation. You are free to post and stream.</li></ul><strong> Content Requirements</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>When posting or streaming, please include LAPIDARY: Jewel Craft Simulator in the title of the video or stream.<br/></li><li>In the description, include a link to the Steam store page.<br/></li><li>Use of the game's visuals and music is limited to within the video itself. Separate distribution of music or sale of images is prohibited.</li></ul><br/><strong>About Monetization</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Monetization of videos through the monetization features provided by video streaming sites is permitted.</li></ul><br/><strong>Prohibited Actions</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Posting or streaming content that violates laws, or content that is offensive to others is prohibited.</li></ul><strong>Disclaimer</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>THINK &amp; FEEL is not responsible for the content of posted videos.<br/></li><li>The guidelines are subject to change without notice. Please check the store page for the latest information.</li></ul><br/>We sincerely hope that you enjoy LAPIDARY: Jewel Craft Simulator and share its charm with people around the world. We fully support your creative content creation.<br/><br/><strong>THINK &amp; FEEL</strong> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of Gun</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2319640/Rise_of_Gun/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2319640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2319640/extras/Steam_wishlist_us.gif?t=1711406599"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Rise of Gun</strong></h2>  A simulator of a weapons store in a world overrun by zombies after a global epidemic. The entire world is enveloped in darkness, but humans have not given up and are fighting to the end. After losing his family, the main character sets out in search of survivors in despair. The journey was difficult, but he was able to find a wonderful settlement with few people but all of them determined to rebuild the world. As the only master who can create weapons, the main character is very valuable in this town. The mayor of the town has allocated a shop with a workshop so that we can create and sell the weapons that we make.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Features</strong></h2><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Weapon Crafting</strong></h2>You will be able to create weapons without any restrictions, even from incompatible parts. Unleash your imagination and create the most creative weapons.<br/>The weapon crafting system is as convenient and enjoyable as possible, so you can enjoy the result rather than get tired of the countless actions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2319640/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__1_.gif?t=1711406599"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Many components</strong></h2>There are over 200 different weapon parts that allow players to create over a million different weapon combinations. The parts are divided into several types and differ in rarity. The main part to which all subsequent parts are attached includes the barrel, scope, stock, grip, magazine, silencer, and bayonet. With these parts, players can create an incredibly unique weapon.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2319640/extras/ezgif-5-daa0c9184f.gif?t=1711406599"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Weapon Sales</strong></h2>In the store, players can display and sell their weapons. There are many different shelves for displaying weapons. Once a resident of the town finds a suitable weapon, they will buy it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2319640/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__2_.gif?t=1711406599"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Shop Upgrades</strong></h2>Players can upgrade their shop with various buildings, from decorative elements to workbenches and generators. Each building adds something new to the gameplay, such as attracting more customers, making the store more cozy, opening up more space for selling weapons, speeding up the creation of weapons, adding new functions, such as disassembling parts for materials, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2319640/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__4_.gif?t=1711406599"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Atmosphere</strong></h2>This small town is very cozy. The mayor of the town makes an effort to ensure the safety of all residents and create a pleasant atmosphere. You will also experience day and night cycles, weather changes, and cheerful residents.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy Dungeon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684390/Fantasy_Dungeon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Crawl your way through 20 different dungeons as you fight over 50 enemies on your way to glory. Dungeons are procedurally generated in 12 different themes  and can be replayed as often as wanted. Don't like a dungeon, redo it and give it another shot.<br/><br/>Each dungeon takes about 1 hour to get through. 20 levels means 20 hours of gameplay per character. With 3 distinct character classes, that comes to about 60 hours of total gameplay.<br/><br/>Choose from 3 classes ( fighter, mage or archer ) and fully customize your hero:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Customize armor, weapons, accessories, hair, beards and even skin color<br/></li><li> Over 60 different weapons and shields based on character and level<br/></li><li> Accessorize your hero with bling, head gear, sun glasses and more<br/></li><li> Different styles of game play based on character</li></ul><br/>Your character progress is saved at every level. Make changes to your character at anytime and replay the levels as often as you like. Leave the dungeon at anytime, make changes and get back in.<br/><br/>Unlock over 120 different skills based on character and level. Each class with its own unique skills to learn and master.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fireball / Fire Bolt / Fire Comet<br/></li><li> Lightning Shot / Lightning Strike / Lightning Chain<br/></li><li> Power Shot / Bleeding / Vine Spikes / Poison Shot<br/></li><li> Ice Bolt / Ice Shot / Ice Spikes<br/></li><li> Critical Hit / Ruinous Slash<br/></li><li> Rage / Berserk<br/></li><li> Melee attacks<br/></li><li> and more</li></ul><br/>Over 50 different enemies to slay:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Goblins<br/></li><li> Ghouls<br/></li><li> Trolls<br/></li><li> Skeletons<br/></li><li> Rogue Knights<br/></li><li> Golems<br/></li><li> Mechanoids<br/></li><li> and more</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fragmented Memories: Escape Room</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2784510/Fragmented_Memories_Escape_Room/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2784510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Immerse yourself in an intriguing world of mystery and darkness with "Fragmented Momories: Escape Room." You take the role of Robert Williams, a retired former police officer, whose life is shrouded in shadows after a fatal car accident that haunts his nightmares.<br>
<br>
In a desperate attempt to find answers and relief, Robert seeks the help of Dr. Emily Harris, a trusted therapist. However, the therapy takes an unexpected turn when Dr. Harris begins prescribing mysterious pills, designed to block and erase traumatic memories of the fateful day.<br>
<br>
Enter a captivating escape room that will unravel the darkest secrets of Robert's mind. You must decipher intriguing clues, solve puzzles and discover the truth behind the conspiracy that threatens to consume Robert. Each step will take you closer to the truth, but can you trust your own memories?<br>
<br>
Get ready for a unique experience, where every clue is crucial and every decision counts. "Fragmented Memories: Escape Room" will immerse you in a journey full of mystery and suspense. Can you escape the shadows of the past and discover the hidden truth? Robert's fate is in your hands.<br/>
<br/>
- In this game you can find many rooms with different puzzles ranging from easy to more advanced.<br/>
- The theme of the game is to solve the puzzles in each room in order to discover the character's history.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>METAL BEANS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2792960/METAL_BEANS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2792960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2792960/extras/steam_header_V2.png?t=1711393222"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>METAL BEANS </strong></h2>METAL BEANS is a 3D Action-Arcade game where you control two desktop buddies in a computer space. Protect the PC from digital threats by charging up your way through virus creatures and upgrading Catbot and Robitz in the system!<br/><br/>CATBOT and ROBITZ are your desktop robot buddies that will help you defend the computer! Swap between the two characters as you combine their attack styles and discover their combined battery combo patterns. Upgrade your characters with disks to customize their skills and stats. <br/><br/>--<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2792960/extras/mb_gif_shops.gif?t=1711393222"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>DESKTOP ARENA</strong></h2>The DESKTOP ARENA is your hub to access different stores to upgrade your characters, and replenish their systems back to 100%! <br/>Starting off, Blippy will help you recycle your Bad Bits from viruses into player upgrades. <br/><br/>--<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2792960/extras/mb_gif_modes.gif?t=1711393222"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>WINDOW EVENTS</strong></h2>Enter different windows to face internal computing issues head on in various arcade-action game modes!<br/>How will you upgrade your desktop buddies to prepare them for the ongoing hordes?<br/><br/>--<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2792960/extras/meta_shop_2.png?t=1711393222"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>THE CYCLE REBOOTS...</strong></h2>As the viruses get tougher to delete, so can you! <br/>Use your Databucks earned by your session's scores to unlock more features and upgrades! <br/><br/>--<br/><br/>See you inside the PC! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2792960/extras/blippyTalker.gif?t=1711393222"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707930/Palia/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i>Now available on Steam!</i></strong><br/><br/>Palia is a vibrant new world made just for you. Craft, cook, fish, and farm with friends as you live the life of your dreams and discover an enchanting adventure filled with colorful characters and a mystery to unravel.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Welcome Home</strong></h2>Welcome to Palia, a cozy community sim MMO made for you and your friends! Explore a vibrant new world and craft the life of your dreams and befriend the colorful characters around you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707930/extras/BannerGif_Crafting__1_.gif?t=1711395103"><h2 class="bb_tag">Do What You Love</h2>Fish and farm or cook and catch insects - you can live off the land any way you like! Tend to your home plot and nurture your garden or explore Kilima Valley and Bahari Bay to forage for items, ingredients, and rare critters.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707930/extras/BannerGif_BadruFarm__1_.gif?t=1711395103"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Always-Evolving Adventure</h2>Unravel a deep mystery about what happened to ancient humans as you reappear in a world alongside other players. Befriend the local Majiri, learn their backstories, foster relationships, and maybe even romance! Be sure to give back to the community by providing gifts and honing your skills in fishing, hunting, crafting, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707930/extras/BannerGif_Housing01__1_.gif?t=1711395103"><h2 class="bb_tag">Make Your House a Home</h2>Customize your character and build the home of your dreams! With hundreds of craftable items and customizable options, you can decorate your plot to make your home uniquely yours.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707930/extras/BannerGif_Muujin01__1_.gif?t=1711395103"><h2 class="bb_tag">Better Together</h2>Play solo or jump in with friends at any time! Palia is a friendly, cozy community that's always here to welcome you home. Discover a shared world full of players and new friends and enjoy your adventure together.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rival Books of Aster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/639230/Rival_Books_of_Aster/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/639230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>PROLOGUE TUTORIAL IS TEMPORARILY OFFLINE BUT THE GAME SERVERS ARE WORKING WELL - IF YOU'RE WILLING TO LEARN ON THE FLY YOU'LL BE FINE</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/639230/extras/RBA_atg.jpg?t=1711393891"><br/><i>Four rival books, each a separate translation of a single source that is long since lost to time. All begin with the same phrase: "Take me and hide me, for I am the one true light". Every journey begins with a choice and the time has come for you to make yours.</i><br/><br/>Rival Books of Aster is a strategy card game that features over 140 hand illustrated spells that you can use to build custom decks and go head to head against other players. Each spell is also a page in a living story book that translates itself and reveals its secrets as you play the game.<br/><br/>Rival Books of Aster does NOT contain randomized booster packs. Play for free with a starter deck of your choice, and expand your collection with DLC packs containing known-quantities of cards.<br/><br/>Can you decipher the Rival Books to save your household and rule the plane of Aster?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/639230/extras/RBA_feat.jpg?t=1711393891"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> An easy to use deck-builder<br/></li><li> Training Levels for Practice<br/></li><li> AI Battle Mode<br/></li><li> PvP matchmaking &amp; ranking system<br/></li><li> A unique take on familiar game mechanics<br/></li><li> 4 distinct art styles by award-winning artists<br/></li><li> Over 140 different spells &amp; characters<br/></li><li> Endless gameplay possibilities</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/639230/extras/RBA_exp.jpg?t=1711393891"><br/>Expand your deckbuilding possibilities with new spells and characters from DLC expansion packs. What new strategies and synergies will you uncover? There are 4 Starter Decks and 4 Expansion Packs (will require that house’s Starter Deck) available:<br/><br/><strong>Starter Decks</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Heptameron<br/></li><li>Theurgia Goetia<br/></li><li>Grimoirum Velum<br/></li><li>Pauline Art</li></ul><br/><strong>Expansion Pack (Requires Corresponding House’s Starter Deck)</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Heptameron Expansion Pack<br/></li><li>Theurgia Goetia Expansion Pack<br/></li><li>Grimoirum Velum Expansion Pack<br/></li><li>Pauline Art Expansion Pack</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acolyte of the Altar</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2288880/Acolyte_of_the_Altar/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2288880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2288880/extras/Steam_Header_iteration_1.gif?t=1711391901"><br/>Hunt through the wastelands for colossal Beasts in this roguelike deckbuilder. Beware! Beasts grow stronger during battle, allowing them to consume your creatures or counter your spells. Carve profane Gifts from these behemoths and grow stronger to serve your Patron! But serve them to what end?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2288880/extras/Gif6_iteration_1.gif?t=1711391901"><h2 class="bb_tag"> Hunt the Beasts </h2>Test your wits and your deck against titanic creatures called Beasts, who evolve as you fight them! Rush them down before they reach their potential, or bring large threats of your own to match their strength. Feel the tension of fighting a giant and the excitement of triumphing against the odds with each encounter!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2288880/extras/Gif2_iteration_1.gif?t=1711391901"><h2 class="bb_tag"> Their Rage Builds </h2>As you fight a Beast, their rage will grow and they will unlock new abilities! Beat the whimsical Gilded Grifter at his cup game to gain an advantage. Or, feed The Yearning Woods' Consume ability, which fills its health bar and its stomach... until eventually it bursts!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2288880/extras/Knucklebreak_iteration_1.gif?t=1711391901"><h2 class="bb_tag"> Cut Off their Limbs! </h2>Fight back against the Beasts by infesting them with various swarms of insects, setting parts of them on fire, even cutting off limbs and depriving them of their abilities. Interaction with the Beasts lies at the heart of Acolyte of the Altar.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2288880/extras/Eye_Gouge_iteration_1.gif?t=1711391901"><h2 class="bb_tag"> Gifts From Above... Or Below? </h2>After slaying a Beast for the first time, you can offer their body to your Patron, who will carve a new Gift.  At the start of a new area, your Patron will bless you with a choice of these gifts that can dramatically alter how you hunt. Take the Crumbling Monument's Skyscraper Sword and make your tallest creatures even bigger. Or capture the elusive Mini Jelly who will zap enemies when you cast spells! However, these profane gifts weigh down your spirit by varying amounts, so be careful with your choices!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2288880/extras/Gif5_iteration_1.gif?t=1711391901"><br/><br/><br/>Best of luck, Acolyte, and may your Patron bless you!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.tiktok.com%2F%40blackkitegames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2288880/extras/7.png?t=1711391901"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/blackkitegames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2288880/extras/6.png?t=1711391901"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle Pong</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2736700/Circle_Pong/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Circle Pong: The Circular Twist on Classic Arcade</strong><br/><br/>Circle Pong is a game. A top down 2D arcade game that adds a unique circular twist to a classic, multiple game modes, and fast paced game play with a high skill ceiling.<br/>It's like pong but in a <i>circle</i>. <br/><br/><strong>Visuals and sounds</strong><br/><br/>Circle Pong combines bright vibrant colors, abstract designs, and synthwave music to create a fun geometric/synth feel. <br/><br/><strong>Gameplay Overview</strong><br/><br/>Circle Pong is for the hardcore and casual gamer, whether you are looking for a challenge with an impossible skill celling or just a quick arcade fix. The gameplay is intuitive yet challenging, with a few different game modes that everyone can play but not all can beat:  <br/><br/><strong>Infinite:</strong> The essence of Circle Pong, where the player must keep the ball with in the area for as long as possible. The balls speed increases with each point gained, demanding quicker reflexes. This game mode contains a shield power-up that acts as a onetime safety net until its recharged. <br/><strong>Finite:</strong> Unlike Infinite, Finite has a defined beginning and end, this mode tasks players to decrease a score from 100 to 0 points. But other than that, it is very similar. <br/><strong>Block Bust: </strong>Bust all blocks in each stage to win by aiming the ball to collide with the blocks. There are four unique stages each with a different set of blocks where each stage has different block behaviors. <br/><strong>Double:</strong> Double the balls, double the challenge, and double the points. This mode requires players to manage two balls simultaneously, increasing both the difficulty and the rewards.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Château</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2365980/Le_Chteau/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2365980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2365980/extras/lechateau.png?t=1711389634"><br/><strong>Le Château</strong> (French for "<i>the castle</i>") is a tiny city builder, mostly about showing creativity with limited resources and limited space.<br/>Great for when you've got little to no time, but you have this itch to play a game.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2365980/extras/transition-ezgif.com-crop.gif?t=1711389634"><br/><br/>Make your kingdom as small as 1 tile, or as big as 11x11 tiles, and enjoy the aesthetics of several different color palettes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2365980/extras/cool_popup1-ezgif.com-resize.gif?t=1711389634"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2365980/extras/features.png?t=1711389634"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> ⬜Multiple world shapes<br/></li><li> 🏰Dozens of different types of objects to choose from<br/></li><li> 🎨6 different color palettes<br/></li><li> 👑Complete control over the size of your kingdom<br/></li><li> 🤼A world that slowly comes alive as more tiles are filled<br/></li><li> 🐸Frogs</li></ul><br/>Le Château has no real goal. Just lots of freedom in building the kingdom of your dreams!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2365980/extras/inspiredby.png?t=1711389634"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1995590/The_Block/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1995590/The_Block/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarlet Tower</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2181720/Scarlet_Tower/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2181720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2181720/extras/HEROES.gif?t=1711389768"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Heroes with unique weapons, abilities, and talents<br/></li><li>Over 70 weapons<br/></li><li>Weapon fusion system<br/></li><li>Over 200 passive abilities for building your build<br/></li><li>Racial Abilities<br/></li><li>Pets<br/></li><li>Runes<br/></li><li>Bestiary<br/></li><li>Over 20 hours of content<br/></li><li>Bosses with unique abilities<br/></li><li>Thousands of unlockables<br/></li><li>Long character progression<br/></li><li>Runs perfectly on Steam Deck<br/></li><li>Supports Ultrawide<br/></li><li>Day and Night Cycle<br/></li><li>Endless Mode</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Starting</strong></h2>Hunt during the day, be hunted during the NIGHT! Fight bizarre monsters that will terrify you at night! Strengthen your hero by collecting relics, familiars from around the world.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Day &amp; Night Cycle</strong></h2>Look for relics and vendors that only spawn at night.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2181720/extras/DayNight.gif?t=1711389768"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Weather Events</strong></h2>Be prepared!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2181720/extras/rainT.gif?t=1711389768"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2181720/extras/snow.gif?t=1711389768"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Unique Characters</strong></h2>Characters with unique customizable passives.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2181720/extras/batform.gif?t=1711389768"><br/><br/><strong>Enjoy it!</strong><br/>🧛‍♂️						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neoproxima</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2778760/Neoproxima/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778760/extras/Space.png?t=1711387740"><br/>The year is 1975, humanity can travel to the stars thanks to a mysterious civilization, and the Cold War is getting hotter by the minute. The new and old powers alike are expanding on Neoproxima, the new frontier, looking for what's left of the alien technology.<br/><br/>You are Farah, the leader of a team of treasure hunters who got a bit too bold and pressed the wrong button. Trapped in a time loop, you need to make the most of each passing loop, explore Kairos' Colony surroundings, and meet its inhabitants to find a way out.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778760/extras/StuckTime.png?t=1711387740"><br/>You wake up every day with a limited amount of willpower and time to look for clues. Decide your objective for each loop, explore the world, encounter new colorful characters, and explore intriguing ruins. But remember that while your time is limited, death is not absolute. Be bold, take risks, die, and try again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778760/extras/Steam_SC.gif?t=1711387740"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778760/extras/ExploringTime.png?t=1711387740"><br/>Explore an alternate history in which the Cold War expanded to space and scientists analyze alien artifacts with 70s-era computers. Face the trauma of being imprisoned by time itself, and reflect on the value of memories while your closest friends slowly lose theirs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778760/extras/Steam_Explore.gif?t=1711387740"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778760/extras/StoryTime.png?t=1711387740"><br/>Who were those aliens, and why did they give humanity the power to travel the stars? Is the time-loop an epic industrial accident, or the symptom of something darker? Work your way to the truth in this sci-fi adventure which explores topics like entropy and the finiteness of the universe.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778760/extras/Steam_Chenda.gif?t=1711387740"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778760/extras/FeaturesTime.png?t=1711387740"><br/>Neoproxima is a <strong>text-based adventure</strong> that uses a 3D isometric map and combines exploration and RPG mechanics like inventory management, text adventures, dice rolls, hit points, simple survival mechanics, and time-based puzzles.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Drive your small truck around and explore a gorgeous isometric map<br/></li><li>Master time-loop and unlock perks to make your task easier<br/></li><li>Learn the loop and solve simple time-based puzzles<br/></li><li>Roll the dice using your character stats and increase your odds using items<br/></li><li>Meet other colonists and use them to succeed<br/></li><li>Learn the true nature of the time-loop</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mori Carta</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1570830/Mori_Carta/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1570830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1570830/extras/test_for_steam_store_3.gif?t=1711386897"><br/>Features<br/>Deceptively simple controls:  Almost every interaction in the game is handled with a simple swipe left or right.<br/><br/>Engaging story:  Adventure with a colorful cast of characters that accompany you on your adventures.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1570830/extras/yet_another_store_gif_test.gif?t=1711386897"><br/>Rich depth of builds and combos:  Choosing cards to add to your deck will be critical in surviving your adventures.  With over 1000 cards, the combinations are endless.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1570830/extras/tasty_store_gif.gif?t=1711386897"><br/>4 dramatically different characters with their own unique card sets.<br/>1000+ playable cards.<br/>185 unique enemies.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven Skies to Paradise</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2149490/Seven_Skies_to_Paradise/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2149490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">-Sail with the wind:</h2>The <strong>direction of the wind</strong> dictates the speed of your airship. If u try to go against the wind the ship will slow down.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2149490/extras/giphy__1_.gif?t=1711386696"><h2 class="bb_tag">-Sharpen your skills:</h2>Use the <strong>recoil</strong> of your shots and the speed of the wind to evade enemy bullets. Along the way you will find plenty of different threats to challenge your piloting abilities.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2149490/extras/giphy__3___1_.gif?t=1711386696"><h2 class="bb_tag">-Explore the seven skies:</h2>With each sky comes a new challenge to solve and a new world to explore. Will you be able to survive the journey and reach the Seventh Sky?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2149490/extras/giphy__2___1_.gif?t=1711386696"><h2 class="bb_tag">-Story</h2>Legends say that there are seven skies above the human world. Six of them are worlds of pure madness, each more dangerous than the previous one. But beyond them, at the end of the Journey there is the Seventh Sky, Paradise, a place containing everything men ever wanted. <br/>And every year humans send two sailors on a journey in hopes of reaching it. So far out of countless expeditions none has returned. <br/><br/>You play as Hawk, a young pilot who embarks on the Journey with her trusted companion, a robot parrot. She aims to find her father, who left in search of Paradise many years prior. To reach her destination Hawk will have to question her beliefs and leave everything from her past behind. But will what awaits in the Seventh Sky justify her sacrifice?						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Abyss Within</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428020/The_Abyss_Within/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Deckbuild into the Abyss, more than 200 Cards to play with! </li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428020/extras/GIF_DeckManager_.gif?t=1711386660"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Intricate battle system with a great variety of builds! </li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428020/extras/GIF_Combat.gif?t=1711386660"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Random generated maps with nodes to traverse! </li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428020/extras/GIF_Maps.gif?t=1711386660"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Equipment &amp; Stat System! </li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428020/extras/GIF_EquipmentSkills.gif?t=1711386660"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Classes &amp; Perk System! </li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428020/extras/GIF_ClassesPerks.gif?t=1711386660"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's Missing?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2009500/Whats_Missing/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2009500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2009500/extras/gif1.gif?t=1711386058"><br/><strong>What's Missing?</strong> Is a first-person surreal puzzle game where you'll explore the never-ending loop of <i>(almost)</i> identical rooms. Spot the differences in order to escape this infinite magical loop of rooms.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2009500/extras/gif2.gif?t=1711386058"><h2 class="bb_tag">SPOT THE DIFFERENCES ON A NEXT LEVEL </h2>Challenge yourself with a fast ray of unique levels that makes you to think <i>"outside the box"</i>, as besides physical objects, other abstract aspects might change as well like gravity, color, time etc. Explore these levels in different area's from a magical panetarium to the floating garden.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2009500/extras/gif3.gif?t=1711386058"><h2 class="bb_tag">UNCOVER A DARK PAST</h2>Follow Gregory's journey to escape this magical loop. But in order to escape, he must confront his dark past.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F3kXFzr2UMC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2009500/extras/1xTWeo.png?t=1711386058"> </img></a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's Something In The Ice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2810580/Theres_Something_In_The_Ice/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810580/extras/123123123123123123.png?t=1711386976"><br/><br/><strong><u>There's Something In The Ice</u></strong> is a first-person horror game.<br/><br/><strong>Plot:</strong><br/>In 2015, three scientists at the Antarctic research station Zarya drilled into the ice to a depth of 2 kilometers and took samples to study...<br/>As they were returning to base, a severe snowstorm began.<br/>Arriving at the base, the scientists went down to the old bunker, as the security protocol told them, to wait it out...<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>There is not a single note in the game. The plot is presented through dialogues with characters.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Realistic graphics.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Advanced lighting system LUMEN (Unreal Engine 5).</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Atmosphere inspired by the movie "The Thing" and other sci-fi films and games.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LakeSide</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1552220/LakeSide/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1552220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1552220/extras/ls_3.gif?t=1711383079"><br/><br/>LakeSide is a cozy city builder where you can build the perfect calm town by the lake side or a sprawling city state with wonders that the world has never seen.<br/><br/>With 2d side-scrolling pixel vistas, each game run offers a different set of building combinations, unlocking unique buildings or epic world wonders that offer sprawling growth to your city state<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1552220/extras/ls_img_desc_1.png?t=1711383079"><br/><br/>Build your own city with your own custom architectural and cultural changes. <br/>Unlocking more buildings and expanding your palace gives you with powerful rewards to keep growing your city.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1552220/extras/ls_img_desc_2.gif?t=1711383079"><br/><br/>Feature List<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> More than 60 building variations<br/></li><li> 5 different wonders and counting!<br/></li><li> 3 different background scenarios to start from<br/></li><li> Each game run offers a different set of available buildings<br/></li><li> Manage your resources carefully and keep your citizens alive</li></ul><br/>Development is still in alpha so expect new things to come!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bounties of Babylon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2712650/Bounties_of_Babylon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/lineBreak.png?t=1711407129"><br/><br/><i>Conquer Babylon by progressing through rounds with your ships to complete a run.<br/>Not enough victory points or too much damage taken, means your reign as Admiral will come to an end.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/tiles.png?t=1711407129"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/tiles_2.gif?t=1711407129"><br/>The tile stack procedurally pairs rivers with bounties to create a tile. Pick two from a choice of three to place in the level. Decide based on the physical connection for where you want to go, and what bounty type has for bounty harvesting. You can also discard tiles.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/travel.png?t=1711407129"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/rollAndMove_2.gif?t=1711407129"><br/>Each turn, roll one die per ship. The result is how many connected tiles the ship can travel.<br/>A six allows for teleportation to a settlement. Consider dividing ship responsibilities between harvesting, attacking, and trading.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/tradeTreasure.png?t=1711407129"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/tradeTreasure_2.gif?t=1711407129"><br/>Settlements house merchants to trade with. They rotate in and out with various trade requirements during play, so don't dawdle! Landing on treasure chests will often reward you with an artifact. These are high-value items that can be traded. Can you discover all of them in the game?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/quests.png?t=1711407129"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/quests_2.gif?t=1711407129"><br/>Every round you are given two quests you can complete for victory points. They vary in their nature bringing a new sense of mission to your rounds. For example, <i>Harvest Season</i> requires the player to have a yield of a certain size, whilst <i>Treasure Hunter</i> wants the player to collect treasures.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/combat.png?t=1711407129"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/combat_2.gif?t=1711407129"><br/>The opponent can block your path, so land on them to take them out. Receive one victory point and a proportion of their bounties for combat. If they attack you, you lose some bounties and a life. Acquire more lives throughout play.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FZwxwmvZebs" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/discord.png?t=1711407129"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/lineBreak.png?t=1711407129"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bass Invaders</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2738680/Bass_Invaders/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/bi_logo_text_horizontal_616x49.png?t=1711382140"><br/>Bass Invaders is a rhythmic fusion of classic shoot 'em up and live audio analysis.<br/><br/>Battle to the other side of the galaxy on a mission to save the Earth in a campaign mode with a genre-spanning soundtrack, or load <i>literally any song</i> and experience your favourite music in a new way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/shoot_hold_rotate_L06.gif?t=1711382140"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/UNLIMITED_MUSIC_LIBRARY.png?t=1711382140"><br/>Play using any song you like, loading from your own files or using online video. Any track, any time. No limits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/BEAT_THE_BEST.png?t=1711382140"><br/>High scores and ranked leaderboards for every song. Fill your ship energy levels to unleash power mode. Nail that perfect run and show your skill.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/FIND_YOUR_FLOW.png?t=1711382140"><br/>Five difficulty levels so you can just enjoy the music or really challenge your skills.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/SAVE_THE_WORLD.png?t=1711382140"><br/>Launch into a galaxy spanning campaign mode as Ace and PZO-116 battle to save the world from alien invaders. Enjoy every level with its own custom song from a genre-spanning soundtrack.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/FUN_WITH_FRIENDS.png?t=1711382140"><br/>Two-player local co-op in every game mode (requires at least one controller). Battle through the campaign with your best friend. Play winner-stays-on with your mates and your favourite music. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/2P_powermode_L06_video.gif?t=1711382140"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/ACCESSIBILITY.png?t=1711382140"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Custom colours<br/></li><li>Colourblind modes<br/></li><li>Simplified backgrounds<br/></li><li>Enemy outlines<br/></li><li>Gameplay assists<br/></li><li>Button hints<br/></li><li>Key rebinding</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmer's Father: Save the Innocence</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1905980/Farmers_Father_Save_the_Innocence/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1905980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>"The first casualty of war is innocence"</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1905980/extras/Gif0.gif?t=1711382049"><br/><br/>War breeds heroes you've never heard of. You are the ordinary person holding a huge burden of protecting what's most precious and innocent. Fight with hunger, wounds, cold, disease, and enemy cruelty. Defend your family and survive the war!<br/><br/>Imagine waking up in the middle of the snowy night to the sounds of a falling sky. Explosions, fire, chaos, the frightened whimper of your child. It’s your turn: now or never, slip away from your enemies before it's too late…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1905980/extras/Gif1.gif?t=1711382049"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>FEW OF MAIN FEATURES IN THE GAME</strong></h2><br/>🕊️ Building - animal homestead, baby cradle, trough, and more<br/>🕊️ Crafting - create something useful out of junk<br/>🕊️ Cooking - prepare all kinds of food out of what you can find<br/>🕊️ Sneaking - move quietly then you'll survive<br/>🕊️ Hunting - use guns and provide needed food<br/>🕊️ Exploring - strange sounds, enemies, unknown territories<br/>🕊️ Taking care of family - making family safe, fed, and warm<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>PROTECT YOUR FAMILY</strong></h2>As a father, since the first breath of your child, you’ve always known the responsibility relies on your shoulders… but the stakes were never that high. Do what you must to keep your wife and son alive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1905980/extras/Gif2.gif?t=1711382049"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>FARM, HUNT, IMPROVISE</strong></h2>Nothing can be taken for granted now. You will have to earn every meal and bargain for each piece of comfort for you and your family using extreme measures. Hunt for wild animals, make forest recipes, and, as a farmer, use your skills to create a new home during the occupation…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1905980/extras/Gif3.gif?t=1711382049"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE</strong></h2>Sneak, wait for your moment, and ATTACK! Every. Second. Counts. Your enemies are cunning and trained. Can you handle that while being "just" a farmer? Your everyday abilities may come in handy so don’t underestimate yourself and keep trying!<br/><br/><strong>After all, you’ve got nothing to lose and everything to gain.</strong> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beach Club Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2335810/Beach_Club_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2335810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Beach Club Simulator" is an exciting open-world simulation game where players manage a beach club. In the game, you construct, operate, and develop a beach club located next to a beautiful beach. However, the game is not limited to just the beach club; it also offers the opportunity to explore and complete missions in other areas of the island.<br>
<br>
The game begins with a character named Kevin Mathews coming to Nevermind Island to find a job. Kevin initially settles in a campsite and seeks solutions to meet his basic needs.<br>
<br>
In addition to building your beach club, you can interact with other important buildings on the island. You'll encounter different tasks such as driver training at the driving school and assisting with municipal services at the town hall. There are also a hotel, hospital, and other commercial establishments on the island.<br>
<br>
Completing missions adds richness and diversity to the game. By interacting with people, you can elevate your career, and career points can later be used for improvements. You can also hire staff for your beach club. Efforts are made to meet guests' needs, organize the beach area, and host fun events.<br/>
<br/>
Beach Club is also a life simulation game. Among your goals is to buy better homes and vehicles. If you're not using your old car, you can even rent it as a taxi, and similarly, you can rent out your homes.<br/>
<br/>
One notable detail in Beach Club Simulator is the emotions the game evokes. We worked hard to create a refreshing, relaxing, and enjoyable gaming experience. For example, you'll see people dancing wildly as the sun sets; sometimes, you might forget you're playing a game and just enjoy the atmosphere.<br/>
<br/>
"Toilet Management Simulator" is our previous game, and Beach Club is, in fact, a sequel to it. All the characters you encounter at the camp are reimagined versions of characters who went on vacation at the end of Toilet Management Simulator.<br/>
<br/>
The goal of the game is to expand and improve your beach club, turning it into a profitable business. Beach Club Simulator offers an enjoyable experience with impressive graphics, detailed management options, and a rich game content. Exploring the broader world of the game, including other buildings and missions on the island, allows you to enjoy unforgettable experiences in your adventure with Kevin on the island.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstract Code</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732630/Abstract_Code/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a unique gaming experience that delves into thought-provoking themes... this SHMUP/Visual Novel hybrid offers a compelling narrative interspersed with addictive arcade gameplay.<br/><br/>Play through the captivating <strong>Story Mode</strong>, immersing yourself in a journey that combines engaging storytelling with arcade excitement. <br/><br/>Alternatively, challenge your skills in the pure <strong>Arcade Mode</strong>, a score attack mode featuring 6 levels of intense action.<br/><br/>Explore CODE KNIGHT's personal space within the game, an<strong> Apartment</strong> where you can enjoy a Juke Box, Gallery, and more additional <strong>FREE CONTENT</strong><br/><br/><br/>In the digital world of Abstract Code, assume the role of CODE KNIGHT and embark on a mission to rectify the errors made by those less accountable than yourself. Engage in thrilling battles against the FINK incursion into humanities' knowledge center, CODENAME D1, and uncover the truth behind the enigmatic character known as Katie.<br/><br/>Please note that the game contains content that may be triggering, as it explores various sensitive topics such as social masking, and transhuman identity.<br/><br/>Stay connected with us on our Insta page @_ruok2000_						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridge Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2879260/Bridge_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2879260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In "Bridge Maker," step into the shoes of an ingenious engineer entrusted with a crucial mission: guiding a car across treacherous chasms. The twist? The car is in constant motion, adding a thrilling element of urgency to your task. Armed with a limited arsenal of materials, your challenge is to construct a sturdy bridge capable of withstanding the vehicle's weight. <br>
<br>
Flex your problem-solving prowess as you strategically arrange bridge components to ensure stability and safety. Each level presents a fresh puzzle, testing your creativity and engineering acumen. Can you craft a bridge robust enough to carry the car to its destination without faltering?<br>
<br>
Key features of "Bridge Maker" include:<br>
<br>
1. **Dynamic Bridge Building**: Exercise your architectural ingenuity by constructing bridges on-the-fly to accommodate a moving car.<br/>
<br/>
2. **Infinite Levels**: Embark on an endless journey of bridge-building challenges, with each level offering a unique configuration to conquer.<br/>
<br/>
3. **Personal Records**: Set your own benchmarks as you strive for perfection, aiming to surpass previous feats and establish new records for bridge strength and efficiency.<br/>
<br/>
Whether you're a seasoned problem-solver or a newcomer to engineering, "Bridge Maker" promises an exhilarating experience that will put your skills to the ultimate test. Can you engineer your way to victory and lead the car safely across every daunting gap?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King Kong City Destroyer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2879250/King_Kong_City_Destroyer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2879250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In the thrilling world of King Kong City Destroyer, players are thrust into a heart-pounding simulator where the forces of nature clash with humanity's hubris. Take on the role of an enormous and enraged primate, King Kong himself, as you embark on a rampage of destruction through urban landscapes. <br>
<br>
Your mission is clear: fulfill King Kong's relentless desires as he wreaks havoc upon everything in his path. With no one able to stand against his might, it's up to you to carry out his will. But amidst the chaos, a question lingers: will nature ultimately reclaim its dominion over the concrete jungle, or is King Kong's reign merely a fleeting whim?<br>
<br>
Featuring 10 adrenaline-fueled levels, players will experience the visceral thrill of demolishing buildings, crushing cars, and even confronting civilians in their quest for dominance. With each mission lasting a tense 3 minutes, every second counts as you unleash destruction upon the cityscape.<br>
<br>
King Kong City Destroyer isn't just a game—it's an electrifying journey into the primal power of nature unleashed. Are you ready to answer the call of the wild and leave a trail of destruction in your wake?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only Golf</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2872150/Only_Golf/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2872150/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Only Golf is a challenging golf game that puts players' skills to the test. <br>
<br>
The game features a series of increasingly difficult levels, each with its own unique set of challenges and obstacles. In Only Golf, the objective is simple: hit the ball into the hole. However, the game is not that simple, as player must take into account the direction of the wind and adjust their shot accordingly. If the wind is blowing in the wrong direction, the ball may go too far or too slowly, making it difficult to hit the hole. <br>
<br>
Only Golf is the perfect game for anyone who loves golf or enjoys a good challenge. With its intuitive gameplay, challenging levels, and stunning visuals, this game is sure to provide hours of entertainment for players of all ages. So, grab your clubs, adjust for the wind, and get ready to become a golfing master in Only Golf!<br>
<br>
Game Features :<br/>
- Golf rules<br/>
- Showed wind direction<br/>
- 5 strokes per attempt<br/>
- Multiple levels						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
