<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Park Baseball 25</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384620/Out_of_the_Park_Baseball_25/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_banner_1.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/>We are incredibly excited to announce <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong> - the special 25th Anniversary edition of our award-winning baseball strategy series. Can you believe it's been a quarter of a century? Out of the Park Baseball is not just a game - it's a legacy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_henry.png?t=1710574531"><br/><br/>If it happens in real baseball, it happens in Out of the Park Baseball! Discover new talent, draft the next superstar, negotiate with free agents, enter trade talks with other teams, build your dynasty and guide a franchise into an infinite future! As a manager, dive into the more hands-on management and set your team's lineups, pitching staffs, in-game strategy and call the shots from the dugout. You can oversee your league at a high level, or play out each game in the gorgeous 3D game mode, managing play by play or even pitch by pitch. OOTP has it all covered!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_badge.png?t=1710574531"><br/>Here are just a few of the new features coming to <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong>:<br/><br/><strong>A game-changing new Player Development Lab!</strong><br/><br/>Shape the future of your upcoming stars! You can channel your inner Player Development Director like never before. A modern new Player Development Lab is here for every team that allows you to give players individual programs to work on, developing them how you like. Do you want your hitter to work on improving their baserunning? Bunting? Contact? Would you prefer your pitcher to work on building up their stamina? Developing a new pitch? Velocity? It's all up to you - for each of your upcoming future stars!<br/><br/><strong>Massive Player Ratings and AI Upgrade!</strong><br/><br/>It’s the most comprehensive player ratings upgrade in the 25 year history of Out of the Park Baseball! Batting, Pitching, and Fielding ratings have been painstakingly modified to capture the essence of baseball, with modifications to Contact and Power for hitters, Movement and Stuff for pitchers, the addition of Catcher Framing and Stealing Aggressiveness, and much more. BABIP is now front and center for hitters and hurlers, while new internal ratings updates allow for even more flexibility for Commissioners around the world to adjust the game to their detailed delight. Plus, the AI throughout the game has been improved dramatically to deliver the most challenging OOTP experience ever! <br/><br/><strong>Even More Detailed Player Development Control!</strong><br/><br/>Delegate how each and every player on your team will spend their time day in, day out with coaches at practice. Want your power hitter to worry less about avoiding strikeouts and put that time and effort into working on his home run swing instead? Want your aging starter to spend more time practicing his control instead of spending that time worrying about his stuff? By allocating their time and focus to the areas you want, over time you can influence how players develop, maintain their skillset, and fight the aging curve.<br/><br/><strong>2024 Rosters and Rules!</strong><br/><br/>As always, Out of the Park Baseball features up-to-the-minute 2024 MLB rosters that get updated all season long, with every franchise represented from its big league club all the way down to the low minors, and everywhere in between! Plus, OOTP 25 features officially licensed leagues from South Korea (KBO) and Europe.<br/><br/><strong>Improved Historical MLB Modes!</strong><br/><br/>Set up historical MLB games in an all new streamlined way - and benefit from vastly improved historical player ratings! It’s never been faster or easier to experience the entire history of Major League Baseball, now producing even more realistic outcomes thanks to those comprehensive ratings and simulation engine upgrades.<br/><br/><strong>New Retro Visual Immersion!</strong><br/><br/>Watch games with a variety of experiences, including retro-style black and white, ‘50s-era, and ‘70s-era television presentations. Choose from all of these to play games, watch highlights, or just catch a ballgame from a bygone era!<br/><br/><strong>New Licensed Leagues!</strong><br/><br/>For the first time ever, Out of the Park Baseball features an officially licensed Honkbal Hoofdklasse league from The Netherlands and the British Baseball Federation from the United Kingdom! Look for their official clubs, players, competitions, and more!<br/><br/><strong>For the first time ever - an official partnership with the Baseball Hall of Fame!</strong><br/><br/>What happens when you combine the only game that has the entire history of baseball and the the greatest Hall of Fame in sports? An incredible, year-long journey! Join us as we partner with the Baseball Hall of Fame all season - and beyond. Explore Hall of Fame Plaques, with the official, accurate text for each Hall of Famer. Discover incredible Hall of Fame artifacts, curated and released in fun "exhibits" over the course of the season in concert with the Hall - and more surprises too. It's going to be amazing! <br/><br/><strong>Dozens of upgrades big and small!</strong><br/><br/>--&gt; Updated in-game engine base advancement and camera movements<br/>--&gt; A new manager decision history screen gives you a look back on your best and worst trades and transactions<br/>--&gt; Improved trade packages for prospect packages <br/>--&gt; Updated two-way functionality with injured players<br/>And much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/pt_store_text_banner2.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/><br/><strong>Perfect Team is back - bigger than ever!</strong><br/><br/>It’s an all-new Perfect Team! There’s nothing in the world like the incredible online competitions of Perfect Team. Featuring by far the largest player pool ever, and taking advantage of all the player rating and balance upgrades, this year’s Perfect Team is a whole new ballgame.<br/><br/><strong>Brand New Perfect Team Combinator Series Cards!</strong><br/><br/>Pulled non-live cards have a chance to be a special Combinator Series version of the card! Use other cards that share a link (for example being teammates) with the player to get a chance to boost the raw ratings of the Combinator Series card.<br/><br/><strong>A Perfect Team Tournament Roster Builder!</strong><br/><br/>Want to design rosters for the incredible array of Perfect Team Tournaments - all on your own? For the first time ever, Perfect Team will feature a Tournament Sandbox! You can tinker to your heart's content with varying rosters for every type of tournament, with no pressure. This long-requested feature makes its debut in Out of the Park Baseball 25!<br/><br/>In addition to the brand-new Tournament Roster Builder and Combinator Series, Perfect Team 25 also features:<br/><br/><strong>Team Chemistry</strong> - Players who played together in real life will get extra bonuses when on your roster together. Players gain bonuses for seasons they played together, as well as simply being part of the same team or from the same decades<br/><strong>Perfect Team competitions starting on the first day</strong>, including a huge Opening Weekend of Tournaments with big prizes and Perfect Team Championship Series qualifying from Day One! <br/><strong>New content all season long - and beyond!</strong> All new programs, missions, competitions, and excitement await you every day.<br/><br/>Out of the Park Baseball 25 runs on PC/Mac and features the American League and National League logos, the World Series trophy, official logos and jerseys for all 30 MLB teams and 15 KBO teams, over 150 Minor League Baseball league and team logos, and historical MLB logos.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcast - A New Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1013140/Outcast__A_New_Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							20 years after the award-winning action adventure hit, Outcast, pioneered the genre of non-linear open-world games, the long-awaited sequel sees Cutter Slade return to the spectacular alien world of Adelpha. Resurrected by the almighty Yods, he has returned to find the Talans enslaved, the world stripped of its natural resources, and his own past intertwining with the invading robot forces. It's up to him to go on a mission and save the planet again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/flight_8mb.gif?t=1710511218"><br/><br/>The original team behind Outcast 1 has reunited to create this fascinating world, full of dangerous creatures and home to the Talan people – an ancient culture whose fate has become inextricably linked with earth since the events of the first game. You play as Cutter Slade, ex-Navy SEAL, sporting the same dry wit he had back in the 90s – however, the world around him has changed and eventually, so will he.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/combat01_6mb.gif?t=1710511218"><br/> <br/>To save Adelpha, you will … <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>use your jetpack to jump, air-dash, glide, and quickly traverse the fantastic in-game open world <br/></li><li>combine dozens of different modules to create your own personal weapon for taking down the robot invaders <br/></li><li>have total control to approach the story at your own pace in this non-linear world <br/></li><li>explore the world without boundaries, discover hidden temples and dangerous wildlife <br/></li><li>get familiar with the Talan culture while helping them free their villages and gain access to ancient Talan powers that use forces of nature to destroy your enemies <br/></li><li>experience a beautiful, hand-crafted world accompanied by an epic soundtrack by Outcast's original composer, Lennie Moore </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/combat02.gif?t=1710511218"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skelethrone: The Prey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2139870/Skelethrone_The_Prey/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/Wishlist_Follow_ENG.gif?t=1710431377"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/About_the_Game_628_x_182_bright.gif?t=1710431377"><br/>You're in for a great adventure inspired by games like Castlevania and Dark Souls.  Bloodthirsty monsters, divine creatures and epic boss battles. The game’s story is shaped by  choices that will define your journey.<br/><br/><strong>PROLOGUE KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Metroidvania</strong> - Unlock unique upgrades for movement and combat to expand the world. Maintaining the game's progression requires you to use different relics, items and abilities.<br/></li><li><strong>Challenging bosses</strong> - Test your skills against multiple bosses and other creatures from the Dark Ages. The game will constantly test your patience as you face challenging battles that require their own unique approach..<br/></li><li><strong>Exploration</strong> - The game features a huge world represented by a variety of hand-crafted levels. From fog-shrouded ruins, where undead corpses cling to any living being passing by, and shambling figures emerge. To the Sun-city that hides in the labyrinthine of an ancient tomb where an unspeakable evil lingers, long forgotten by mankind.</li></ul><br/><strong>AVAILABLE IN FULL GAME:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Weapons and Equipment</strong> – Your character can be armed with bows, scythes, longswords, whips, pistols, rifles, and many more traditional weapons. More exotic weapons will also be available to you, so use any means to achieve success.<br/></li><li><strong>Multiple Endings</strong> – Make key decisions along the way to determine Ericona's fate as you progress through the story.<br/></li><li><strong>Non-linear exploration</strong> – Play through levels and bosses, discover side areas with more secrets and enemies to defeat.<br/></li><li><strong>Combat galore</strong> - You must use an ever-expanding arsenal of weapons and equipment to repel  a wide variety of enemies. Put your courage, skills, and resolve on display for them.</li></ul><br/>"Skelethrone: The Prey" is a free prequel to the main game, setting the stage for the events that will unfold throughout Skelethrone's main campaign.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/Story_628_x_182_bright.gif?t=1710431377"><br/>The story takes place a few decades before the events of the game's main campaign. Assume the role of Derek Ericona, a lord who escaped the persecution is now trying to get to the borders of the neighboring kingdom to resist the tyranny of Queen Aurora, but he is being chased and faces an uphill battle. Prepare all your skills to overcome all the obstacles and difficulties prepared for our hero. And now the hunt is on!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F89UKE37PuC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/join_the_comunity_628_x_182_bright.gif?t=1710431377"/></a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Shire: Room One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517850/Toy_Shire_Room_One/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FkhSxB2MSgD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/Toy_Shire_-_Discord_Banner.png?t=1710352808"/></a><br/><br/><br/>Play through the <strong>three levels in Kevin's Room</strong> and defend your room against your old toys. Face Memphis-X in the final level and put a stop to his assault as he crushes your soldiers in an attempt to get to your base.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyVengeance.png?t=1710352808"><br/>You received new toys from your family. Isn't that lovely? Oh, it's for sure... <br/>Your old toys, though, aren't getting along as well. They are no longer cared for and have been forgotten. So what follows next? They're going to join together against you and assault your brand-new toys, so be prepared. But never worry! You're in luck since your brand-new toys are troops of green soldiers. They still require your aid though! Control, strengthen, and defeat the opposing forces! However, focus with care, the enemies you encounter might not be your old playthings!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/InteractiveTowerDefense.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Tower building alone won't be sufficient to repel incoming attackers. Build up your own troops in the best feasible positions, then unleash attacks into enemy territory. Never abandon your towers, and deploy your troops in accordance with the traits of the enemy. First, the attacking forces will attempt to get past your defenses. Build and improve towers to aid your army. By using unique abilities, you can support your troops and towers as well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/EpicBattles.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Safeguard your base against waves of attackers. You need to pick the right troops if you would like to prevail. Clean the paths and guard any open routes. Upgrade your troops and unlock new ones to take down the waves and claim victory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyRealm.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Enter a world and a narrative built around the toys that enriched your youth, including toy soldiers, dinosaur sets, robots, building blocks, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_3.gif?t=1710352808"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dune: Imperium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1689500/Dune_Imperium/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Header.png?t=1710364055"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body0_2.png?t=1710364055"><br/>Experience the ultimate blend of strategy and intrigue as you navigate the treacherous landscapes of Arrakis in the award-winning board game <i>Dune: Imperium</i>!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle online, locally with AI, or against the formidable House Hagal.<br/></li><li>Earn Achievements that showcase your prowess as a leader.<br/></li><li>Embark on more than a dozen Challenges that will test your wit and cunning.<br/></li><li>Compete for badges in the rotating Skirmish Mode where no two games are the same!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body1_2.png?t=1710364055"><br/>Arrakis. Dune. Desert Planet. Raise your banner above the vast wasteland before you. As the Great Houses of the Landsraad marshal their forces and their spies, whom will you influence, and whom will you betray? A tyrannical Emperor. The secretive Bene Gesserit. The shrewd Spacing Guild. The ferocious Fremen of the Deep Desert. The power of the Imperium can be yours, but war is not the only way to claim it.<br/><br/><i>Dune: Imperium</i> blends deck-building and worker placement in a deeply thematic new strategy game where the fate of the Empire hangs on your decisions. Will you seek political allies or rely upon military might? Economic strength or subtle intrigues? A council seat… or a sharpened blade? The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body2_2.png?t=1710364055"><br/>In <i>Dune: Imperium</i>, you'll step into the role of one of the leaders of the Great Houses of the Imperium in a struggle to control the planet Arrakis and the invaluable Spice it provides.<br/><br/>The game plays out in a series of ten rounds, each of which is defined by a new Conflict on the surface of the planet; some award critical resources, and some provide Victory Points that will propel you to dominance. But choose your battles wisely: spread your forces too thin, and you'll find your enemies growing too strong to oppose.<br/><br/>Each round, you'll draw a hand of five cards from your deck, which will get stronger over the course of the game as you acquire new cards. Each card can be played in one of two ways: To send an Agent out into the Imperium to gather resources, or to Reveal at the end of the round to purchase new powerful cards. You must maintain a careful balance to get the most of the resources available to you. How will you find your path?<br/><br/>As your game progresses, you'll vie for Influence with four factions of the Imperium: The Emperor, the economically powerful Spacing Guild, the mysterious Bene Gesserit, and the ferocious Fremen of the deep deserts. Earning Influence among the various groups helps you to earn the Victory Points you need...but will you compete with your rivals for their favor, or abandon alliances to pursue other opportunities?<br/><br/>Many strategies are at your disposal, and many paths to victory. The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Footer.png?t=1710364055"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contra: Operation Galuga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2235020/Contra_Operation_Galuga/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2235020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A new entry in the legendary Contra series is here! Contra: Operation Galuga is a thorough reimagining of the classic run-'n'-gun action game from the '80s, featuring modern graphics and sound, new stages, new enemies and bosses, new play mechanics, an updated weapons system, and explosive co-op combat for up to two players in Story Mode or four players in Arcade Mode!<br>
<br>
When the Red Falcon terrorist group takes over the Galuga Islands off the coast of New Zealand, elite Contra commandos Bill Rizer and Lance Bean springs into action, initiating an all-out war in which the fate of mankind hangs in the balance!<br>
<br>
Run, jump, and shoot your way through eight levels using a devastating arsenal - including the spread shot, laser, and homing missiles - now with stackable upgrades and awesome Overload abilities! The intense action is customizable with three difficulty settings plus a variety of additional challenge options. The true Contra legacy begins now!<br>
<br/>
Key Features:<br/>
•The original run-'n'-gun game is back, reimagined and more action-packed than ever!<br/>
•Attack aggressively across eight explosive stages! Infiltrate the jungle, ascend the waterfall, speed through an enemy base on a hovercycle, and more!<br/>
•Multiple playable characters with distinct abilities!<br/>
•Epic, screen-filling boss battles!<br/>
•New and fan-favorite weapons, now with stackable upgrades and incredible Overload abilities!<br/>
•Multiple difficulty options and a wealth of extra content						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals Zero Hour</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732960/Command__Conquer_Generals_Zero_Hour/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals Zero Hour brings you closer to the enemy than ever before. Engage opposing forces at hot spots around the globe as you match strategies and arsenals against the new masterminds of modern war.<br/><br/><strong>Arsenal.</strong> Unleash the next generation of 3D new units and 20 new upgrades including China's ECM Tank, GLA's BattleBus and the USA's Spectre Gunship.<br/><br/><strong>Missions.</strong> Take on 15 new missions and make tomorrow's headlines. Root out a splinter cell in Cairo, steal deadly toxins from a U.S. lab and more.<br/><br/><strong>Generals.</strong> Match strategies and arsenals against 9 enemy commanders with unpredictable personalities and tactics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Tiberian Sun™ and Firestorm™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229880/Command__Conquer_Tiberian_Sun_and_Firestorm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Second Tiberium War begins in this legendary sequel to the original Command &amp; Conquer. <br/><br/>With his forces stronger than ever, arch villain and leader of The Brotherhood of Nod - Kane - is pitched in an epic battle against the world's war machine - the Global Defense Initiative. Now you must orchestrate the fate of mankind.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on Dynamic Battlefields. Nature itself provides tactical opportunities - destroyable and deformable terrain, forest fires, treacherous ice fields and many more surprises that help or hinder your strategies.<br/></li><li>Exciting New Strategies and Units. Jump Jet Infantry, Hover Tanks, Tunneling APCs, Hunter Seekers, Laser Fences, Mechanized Battle Units and many more.<br/></li><li>The "Veterancy" Factor. Units can become faster and stronger as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>New Kinetic Battlefields. Flying shrapnel, shock waves and crashing debris are just a few of the exciting new technologies developed to enhance the in-game experience.<br/></li><li>The mood and attitude of the battlefield comes alive like never before - covert night missions, searchlights and new defenses intensify the thrill and excitement.</li></ul><br/>Then take the battle further in <strong>Firestorm, the official expansion pack for the game</strong>. Includes all-new campaign missions, cinematics, and units to decide the future of mankind.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Renegade™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229890/Command__Conquer_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer gets up close and personal in this classic First Person Shooter for one of the most iconic franchises.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wreak Havoc</strong> - Experience the Command &amp; Conquer universe on foot as Havoc, wise-cracking GDI Commando.<br/></li><li><strong>Make Your Own Rules</strong>  - Take on the evil Brotherhood of Nod using your own mix of brute force, stealth, and strategy.<br/></li><li><strong>Assault at Ground Level</strong>  - Dish out the damage in either first or third person.<br/></li><li><strong>Total Access</strong>  - Sneak inside and explore full-scale structures, like immense Tiberium Refineries and the ominous Hand of Nod.<br/></li><li><strong>Grind the Gears</strong>  - Beef up your arsenal by commandeering lethal vehicles, such as Nod Buggies, Flame Tanks, and Mammoth Tanks.<br/></li><li><strong>Weapons of Mass Destruction</strong>  - Choose from a multitude of weapons, including the Tiberium Auto Rifle, Chemical Sprayer, and the devasting Personal Ion Cannon.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ and The Covert Operations™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229830/Command__Conquer_and_The_Covert_Operations/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The legendary RTS game which started it all. Will you side with the humanistic GDI or bring the world to its knees with Kane and the Brotherhood of Nod. Your adversaries are without mercy. And so are you.  <br/><br/>Includes the <strong>The Covert Operations</strong> expansion pack with a range of challenging new missions.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 March Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2845260/100_March_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🌸🌹 WELCOME TO 100 MARCH CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌷🐈</h2><br/>Join the cutest adventure in the Lovely world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of romantic 8 march themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x200.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 March Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁 DLC List for this game 🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Extra.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867620/100_March_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867640/100_March_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x1.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_15" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<br/><br/>※ <i>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</i> is the free-to-play version of <i>Meta-Ghost: The breaking show</i>, to showcase some of the gameplay content.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709870080"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruindog:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802430/RuindogPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 4 are available in the official version.<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 4 in the official version<br/>Weapons: 3 in the prologue, 26 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/11z.jpg?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>A long, long time ago, in a solar system not so far away, alien bugs invaded Earth, but they were soon beaten back home, and by the way, their home planet was blown up. After centuries of being invincible, it became popular for humans to watch live alien hunting shows, participate in alien hunts, save up money, equipment, and use the various loot they found to keep going to new maps and defeating more powerful enemies. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1y.png?t=1710487519"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1z.gif?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>Enemies will come at you from all sides on every level, proceed with caution or you'll be torn to pieces in an instant</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3y.png?t=1710487519"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3z.gif?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>Each character has a different growth path and active skills, utilize these skills and choose the most appropriate item for the current hero to achieve the mission objective</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5y.png?t=1710487519"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5z.gif?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>Earn more resources and achieve various mission objectives to unlock different maps/difficulties and even new map mechanics!<br/>Each map has very different mission objectives and combat mechanics, so choose the one that better suits the current mechanic to win the game</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Epoch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/899770/Last_Epoch/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Epoch combines time travel, exciting dungeon crawling, engrossing character customization and endless replayability to create an Action RPG for veterans and newcomers alike. Travel through the world of Eterra’s past and face dark empires, wrathful gods and untouched wilds – to find a way to save time itself from The Void.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Gameplay.gif?t=1709060046"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>15 Mastery Classes</strong><br/>Embark on your adventure as one of five powerful classes and, through your journey, ascend into a unique Mastery Class that unlocks more specialized abilities and build-options. <br/></li><li><strong>120+ Skill Trees</strong><br/>Every skill has its own augment tree that will allow you to control, alter, and empower your playstyle. Transform your skeletons into archers, your lightning blast into chain lightning, or make your serpent strike summon snakes to fight alongside you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Nodes.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Hunt Rare &amp; Powerful Loot</strong><br/>Fill your arsenal with magic items that you may craft to perfection, change the rules of your build with powerful unique and set items, and always have that next upgrade just on the horizon with Last Epoch's deep and randomized loot system.<br/></li><li><strong>Rewarding Crafting System</strong><br/>The items you wield are yours to forge! Last Epoch’s community-revered crafting system allows you to control your character's power progression, featuring robust and deterministic upgrade mechanics.<br/></li><li><strong>Uncover the Past, Reforge the Future</strong><br/>Travel to different moments of time where you will discover the many factions and secrets that exist within the world of Eterra and fight to set the timeline onto a new path.<br/></li><li><strong>Endless replayability</strong><br/>With a wealth of classes and skills to customize, deep game systems, randomized loot, and continuing development, Last Epoch is a game that will keep you coming back for years to come.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Monolith.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Easy to Learn, Hard to Master</strong><br/>We’re committed to making gameplay approachable for new and veteran players alike by allowing you to jump into the fray quickly and providing many in-game resources. Though don’t be fooled, Eterra has many dangers waiting for you that require a mastery of combat and build-crafting.<br/></li><li><strong>Zero Pay-To-Win</strong><br/>Last Epoch will never offer gameplay advantages by being able to spend real money. We believe in creating a fair environment for all players. </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2379780/Balatro/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Balatro is a poker-inspired roguelike deck builder all about creating powerful synergies and winning big.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Endless_Possibility.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Combine valid poker hands with unique Joker cards in order to create varied synergies and builds. Earn enough chips to beat devious blinds, all while uncovering hidden bonus hands and decks as you progress. You’re going to need every edge you can get in order to reach the boss blind, beat the final ante and secure victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Jokers_Clean_Thin.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The definitive poker roguelike experience.<br/></li><li>Endless possibilities - every pick-up, discard and joker can dramatically alter the course of your run.<br/></li><li>In-depth campaign mode complete with 8 difficulties, as well as challenge, daily and seeded runs. </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Break_The_Game.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Deftly deploy an array of potent tools: different Decks, Jokers, Tarot cards, Planet cards, Spectral cards, and Vouchers. Use these versatile instruments to ignite a combo frenzy and turbocharge your poker hands, crafting electrifying, adrenaline-fueled synergies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro_5_Aces_GIF__HQ_.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 Jokers, each with their own unique abilities<br/></li><li>15 Decks with distinct modifiers to choose from for each run<br/></li><li>5 potential variants of each Joker which add further abilities<br/></li><li>22 Tarot cards variants that can enhance your regular playing cards<br/></li><li>11 Planet cards that help level up your possible poker hands<br/></li><li>32 Voucher cards to help provide permanent buffs for your current run</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Find_Your_Flow.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in Balatro’s distinctive psychedelic world. Let the synthwave soundtrack wash over you -  wind down, escape the daily grind and prepare to enter the ultimate roguelike flow state.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improve your collection and discover new cards and secrets with every single run.<br/></li><li>Make use of the in-depth stats screen to study your best hands, most used Jokers, and more!<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the CRT fuzz and enjoy detailed, hand-crafted pixel art.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Spectral_Pack.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F5mH3dNhjx2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro-join_the_discord.png?t=1710160593"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Small Mazes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2570630/20_Small_Mazes/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2570630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a puzzle game with twenty small mazes. If you solve the mazes, you beat the game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>It's about 1-2 hours long, maybe.<br/></li><li>You need a keyboard and mouse to play it. One person played through the whole game on the Steam Deck, but I tried it and think it's better on PC.<br/></li><li> A few puzzles require knowledge of English. No puzzle requires sound or audio to solve it. No puzzle requires being able to recognize different colors.</li></ul> <br/>I hope you enjoy it. <br/> 						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonder</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692570/Sonder/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Local Co-op requires a gamepad controller for both players. Online Co-op supports mouse and keyboard. </i><h2 class="bb_tag">Psychological narrative </h2>- After a mass-scale destruction of all artificial intelligence, a scrapped robot and soul form an unexpected friendship. After a mysterious train knocks them out, they wake up in a world shaped by their own thoughts. Will they be able to cooperate and escape this dark reality?<h2 class="bb_tag">Immersive atmosphere </h2>- Immerse yourself in an atmospheric world crafted with a stylish, minimalistic approach that captivates your attention and enhances the shared adventure. Unleash the power of collaboration, confront existential mysteries, and embark on a gaming journey like no other.<h2 class="bb_tag">Collaboration </h2>- Work together - succeed together. Each character has unique abilities that allow them to manipulate the world in their own way, meaning they can only proceed if they cooperate. In combat, maximum efficiency can be achieved by combining the player’s powers, allowing them to neutralize the most dangerous of foes.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlazBlue Entropy Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2273430/BlazBlue_Entropy_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/原创声明-英语.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗EN_.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗.gif?t=1710258282"><br/>Charismatic character designs with unique aesthetic styles and dramatic animations create a flamboyant, awesome combat experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快的动作连招EN.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快动作连招.gif?t=1710258282"><br/>Smooth controls, infinite possibilities of combos, and realistic combat feedback. This is the roguelite game with the best action experience yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超多角色豪华制作EN.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/全员图618x346.jpg?t=1710258282"><br/>Ten playable characters with vibrant personalities, unique combat styles, and immersive voice-acting.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式自由定制EN.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式，自由定制en.gif?t=1710258282"><br/>There are hundreds of moves for you to build around, plus countless elemental effects and legacy skills passed between characters. The possibilities are infinite. Time to make the best fighter of your own!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/抉择拯救世界EN.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/GIF-抉择拯救世界EN.gif?t=1710258282"><br/>In the future where the world has been plunged into chaos, people enter a cyberspace called ACE, seeking their last chance to resolve the crisis.<br/>If you are the only person in this world who knows the truth, how will you react?<br/>The ending is also the beginning. Your decision will decide humanity's future.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sputnika Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2730270/Sputnika_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Meet our little friend Sputnik. Help its journey to become the greatest star in the solar system - the Sun!<h2 class="bb_tag">Unique Gameplay With Cosmic Gravity</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730270/extras/MainMech.gif?t=1710427471"><br/>Cosmic gravity is applied to the planet, which makes it different from the classic Suika-style game.<br/>The ability to target the other side of the planets adds much more strategy and depth to the game!<h2 class="bb_tag">Merge Planets</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730270/extras/EvoRing2.png?t=1710427471"><br/>Match two identical planets to create bigger celestial bodies.<br/>Discover 10 dazzling planets, each with its own place in the solar system!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730270/extras/GameOver2.png?t=1710427471"><br/>Watch out for the bubble! If the planet pops out of the bubble, it's game over.<h2 class="bb_tag">Meet the Adorable Planets</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730270/extras/Adorable2.png?t=1710427471"><br/>Our planets aren't just celestial bodies – they're full of life! <br/>Watch them interact – they might greet each other with a smile or gaze curiously at one another. <br/>Get ready for a whole lot of cuteness as you merge your way through the solar system.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1708019001"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal Richards (formerly of Echos)</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1708019001"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about the future of Sheepy, limited edition merch and more.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egg</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2784840/Egg/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2784840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><h2 class="bb_tag">About this game!</h2></strong><br/><br/>&gt; <strong>Egg</strong> is an interactive clicker game where you need to click egg to earn more eggs.<br/><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Features!</h2></strong><br/><br/>&gt; This game supports mouse and keyboard.<br/>&gt; This game supports gamepad (use <strong>A</strong> button on joystick to click).<br/>&gt; This game uses best HD quality textures that is possible to create.<br/>&gt; Runs on every hardware. Even on BESM.<br/>&gt; Supports all screen resolutions.<br/>&gt; Supports Windows 10/11 and so on.<br/>&gt; If you don't like the game you can always easily refund it.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/315210/Suicide_Squad_Kill_the_Justice_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Rocksteady Studios, the creators of the Batman: Arkham series, Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is a genre-defying third-person action shooter where the ultimate band of misfits must do the impossible to save the world: Kill the Justice League.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/SSKTJL_Intro.gif?t=1709934841"><br/>Join the newly “recruited” members of Amanda Waller’s infamous Task Force X (aka the Suicide Squad), Harley Quinn, Deadshot, Captain Boomerang and King Shark, as they set out on an impossible mission to Kill the Justice League. Drop into an expansive and dynamic open-world Metropolis ravaged by Brainiac’s invasion and terrorized by the heroes who once protected it. <br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/Traversal_2.gif?t=1709934841"><br/>Each Squad member brings their own traversal mechanics to help them navigate a sprawling and battle-torn Metropolis, combining free-roaming exploration and combat verticality for an unforgettable experience. Players are free to experiment with a variety of different play styles to unleash maximum damage on their enemies. Whether in single player or online with up to three of your friends, players can take on this suicide mission their own way.<br/><br/>Post-launch, players can expect a continuously evolving Metropolis with free new playable villains, environments, weapons, in-game events, and more, all included with purchase of the base game.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788630/Nothing_Together/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play together. Maybe.<br/><br/>Just do Nothing as the timer goes up and climb the leaderboards. If you do Something, you lose.<br/><br/>Play in <strong>Together </strong>mode, where up to 20 players unite to do Nothing, or compete with other players in <strong>Battle Royale</strong> to find out who's the best at doing Nothing!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161700/Persona_3_Reload/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a transfer student thrust into an unexpected fate when entering the hour "hidden" between one day and the next. Awaken an incredible power and chase the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fight for your friends, and leave a mark on their memories forever. <br/><br/>Persona 3 Reload is a captivating reimagining of the genre-defining RPG, reborn for the modern era.<br/><br/>Key Features: <br/>- Experience the pivotal game of the Persona series faithfully remade with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, and signature stylish UI. <br/><br/>-Fully immerse yourself in an emotional, gripping journey with new scenes, character interactions, and additional voiceover.<br/><br/>- Choose how to meaningfully spend each day through various activities, from exploring the Port Island to forging genuine bonds with beloved characters.<br/><br/>- Build and command your optimal team to take down otherworldly Shadows and climb closer to the truth.<br/><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Deluxe Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook: Filled with 64 pages of character art, concept art, backgrounds and other illustrations from the game!<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack: Listen to newly arranged tracks from the original Persona 3 plus all-new tracks from Persona 3 Reload, presented by the Atlus sound team for a total of 60 new songs.</li></ul><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Premium Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack<br/></li><li>Persona 3 Reload DLC Pack:  P5R Phantom Thieves Costume Set, P5R Shujin Academy Costume Set, P5R Persona Set 1, P5R Persona Set 2 , P5R BGM Set, P4G Yasogami High Costume Set, P4G Persona Set</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1131620/Dominion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Expand a small kingdom to a mighty Dominion!  <br/><br/>Play the Spiel des Jahres winning boardgame beloved by millions around the world. This is the officially licensed implementation.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Reigning.png?t=1709070029"><br/>Discover the game that defined a genre, Dominion was first to popularize deck-building and remains a staple of tabletop. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/GrowYourKingdom.png?t=1709070029">Collect as many Victory Points as you can by building a powerful deck. Your deck starts out a small sad set of Estates and Coppers, but you hope that by the end of the game it will be brimming with Gold, Provinces, and the inhabitants and structures of your kingdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/BuildEngine.png?t=1709070029"><br/>Choose wisely among the 10 cards available in the tableau to create the strongest combos to dominate your opponent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CollectAllExpansions.png?t=1709070029"><br/>Make your games more exciting with additional cards and rules from up to 15 expansions including the recent Plunder expansion! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/NearInfiniteVariety.png?t=1709070029"><br/>Over one hundred thirty-two septillion possible Kingdom combinations, 500+ cards, 15 and counting expansions, and ongoing promo packs make Dominion one of the most extensive and replayable boardgames in the hobby. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CompeteComputer.png?t=1709070029"><br/>Sharpen your skills with solitaire style solo play against a robust AI, with four levels of difficulty. Our innovative AI learns through self-play. Earn Achievements and win in Recommended Sets against each AI level. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/PlayWithFriends.png?t=1709070029"><br/>Join up to 6 players online through your device or pass and play among your friends. Play ranked or unranked matchmaking, with realtime and asynchronous modes. Set up a private table for a family game, challenge a stranger in the lobby, or invite a friend!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Daily.png?t=1709070029"><br/>A daily ritual to relax with over a cup of coffee. Try the Daily Dominion, a free puzzle level available to players around the world. Practice your strategy to keep up a winning streak and climb the leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CrossPlatform.png?t=1709070029"><br/>Play from any supported device, whenever you want, after verifying your email in-game. Join games with opponents on platforms other than your own to enjoy the largest possible multiplayer pool and speedy matchmaking. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/JoinCommunity.png?t=1709070029"><br/>With an active Discord and online community, make new friends or challenge new people to a game. Export and share kingdoms and game summaries to compare strategies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/FreeToPlay.png?t=1709070029"><br/>Download the game that started it all for free! The base set of Dominion is available at no charge. Try the rotation of expansion cards in the Daily at no cost once per day. Jump into a lobby game with expansions enabled to try before you buy. Only the host needs to own the expansions.    <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Intro.png?t=1709070029"><br/>Learn the ropes in this easy to pick-up, hard to master title. Play one of the most highly regarded strategy tabletop games of all time through our simple tutorial.  The core loop is easy to follow, but offers a wealth of strategy to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>1-6 player</strong> support<br/></li><li><strong>500 </strong> plus <strong>cards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Solo play</strong> against four AI difficulties<br/></li><li><strong>Async </strong>&amp; <strong>real-time</strong> multiplayer<br/></li><li><strong>Ranked</strong> &amp; <strong>unranked</strong> matchmaking<br/></li><li><strong>Lobby</strong> &amp; <strong>Private game</strong> tables<br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform multiplayer</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform purchases</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Daily challenge</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Challenging AI</strong> that learns through self-play<br/></li><li><strong>Recommended Sets</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Customize</strong>, save &amp; share <strong>Kingdoms</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Achievements</strong>, <strong>Stats </strong>&amp; <strong>Leaderboards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Pass &amp; Play</strong> mode<br/></li><li>Automated <strong>score-keeping</strong> &amp; hints<br/></li><li><strong>Smart-play</strong> options to streamline gameplay<br/></li><li><strong>Jumbo mode</strong> for readability on phones<br/></li><li><strong>Turbo mode</strong> to zoom through games quickly<br/></li><li><strong>Tutorial</strong> &amp; <strong>Rules</strong><br/></li><li><strong>4 languages</strong>: English, Japanese, German, French<br/></li><li><strong>15 expansions</strong> plus three promo packs </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Awards for the Boardgame</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Awards.png?t=1709070029"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OG Puzzlers: Synthwave Boats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2673380/OG_Puzzlers_Synthwave_Boats/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>OG Puzzlers: Synthwave Boats</strong> is an casual puzzel game with stunning images in the synthwave style. You have to assemble a single image from random generated indivdual pieces. <br/>Combine all of the smart singel frames into one big image and unlock the next level.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 12 Levels<br/></li><li> casual puzzle adventure<br/></li><li> auto saving<br/></li><li> simple mouse control<br/></li><li> 100 steam awards</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete Heart - 离散之心</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2617300/Discrete_Heart/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Discrete Heart is an emotion-building game in a 2D pixel style from a top-down perspective. Joy, trust, fear... Each initial emotion corresponds to different initial attributes and props. "Inject" and control the characters to build 8 basic emotions, looking for the answer named "Unintentionaler".<h2 class="bb_tag">Background settings:</h2>In the past, carriages and horses were very slow, and letters were far away. Doves connected the two ends of longing, symbolizing "love and peace";<br/>Nowadays, machines are noisy, people are crowded, and information is expanding. Flying doves symbolizes "betrayal and disputes."<br/>In a certain cyberpunk future world timeline, more and more people in a society where order has collapsed must correctly understand and process the emotions encountered at a faster speed:<br/>The waiter in the restaurant mistakenly captured the mood of the guest, and the office staff failed to understand the leader's thoughts in time, and they lost their jobs...<br/>Those who were greedy for pleasure before their lives were settled, got pregnant before marriage, had no one to take care of their offspring, those affected by the war, their emotions, and where should their future go?<br/>With great anticipation, AlphaMood has developed the first-generation discrete heart emotion module. One of the important functions of this module is to train participants' adaptability to the module through simulated consciousness. This test activity is now recruiting volunteers.<br/>"Everything is becoming faster, and so are emotions," an anonymous person commented. "It is imperative to implant electronic emotional chips."<br/>As a result, one after another emotionally numb characters, who have been beaten to death by life, are planning to participate in emotional module training and become the "Unintentionaler" who knows better about "relaxation", and all their worries will disappear.<br/>We are one step closer to becoming the best tool person who knows how to work without eating or drinking. "This is just a small step for AlphaMood, but it is a giant step for all part-time workers," AlphaMood's CEO said at the press conference.<h2 class="bb_tag">Main target:</h2>None of the above is what the player should care about, the player only needs to complete the game.<br/>The main goal of each game is to find the empathy recipe for empathy within a limited time index(a value used to simulate real time) and become an "Unintentionaler", And you can complete a game by talking to the "Guider".<h2 class="bb_tag">Main features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Emotion-building is the core gameplay, which is inspired by the Plutchik-wheel<br/>    1. Restores the main content of the emotion wheel theory, including basic emotions, combined emotions, etc.<br/>    2. Emotions are set to increase or decrease various abilities. After obtaining the empathy recipe, you can adjust this combination through empathy.<br/>    3. You need to decide for yourself which emotions you should obtain or retain based on the situation you encounter, and...occasionally you may encounter a little accident that breaks your plan.<br/>    4. The guider will only allow complete the game people who is "Unintentionaler".<br/></li><li> There are not many system-level restrictions. Players do not have to play a certain protagonist to save the world in some way. You can deliberately play a certain role, it is up to you.<br/></li><li> Interact with NPCs. The plot includes puzzle elements. There may be connections between various plots, but they do not necessarily have to be connected.<br/></li><li> Simplified ARPG combat system: There are no fancy skills and magic systems, and there are several cold weapons that can be used as combat weapons.<br/></li><li> Mild ROGUE: Tailored RogueLike mechanism.<br/>    1. Players will start activities in a map with limited vision.<br/>    2. Randomly generated sub-maps (generated once per game, different sub-maps will have different terrain and a greater possibility of encountering specific types of units).<br/>    3. Random attribute point rewards.<br/>    4. Encounter randomly generated units in the sub-map and choose possible plots.<br/>    5. All units, including players, can pick up items, have independent archives and will die permanently<br/></li><li> Trading system: You can trade with most NPCs and use currency to exchange for the items you want in their hands.<br/></li><li> Synthesis system: items can be synthesized after obtaining the recipe<br/></li><li> Freely decide the life and death of all NPCs, There are no battles limited by the plot.<br/></li><li> All units have the possibility of actively triggering battles (all units have no camp)<br/></li><li> All units are randomly generated and grow with the growth of the player-controlled character.<br/></li><li> After getting familiar with it, the game time can be controlled within 30 minutes, which is suitable for fragmented time.<br/><br/>Hope you have fun and live a happy life!<br/>The most important thing is: remember to "relax" when you are in a bad mood.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-02-15_洞穴宝箱_all_lan.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-36-44_洞穴中石狮子光影效果_all_lan.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-47-06_生成的副地图中的宝箱_all_lan.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_18-06-05_火焰移情.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_18-25-09.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-13_15-18-56_shadow_out_csve.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-09-20_野怪杀死NPC.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-11-37_野怪拾取情感指示物.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-13_15-16-55_kill_by_moster.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-21-35_野怪冲碎草丛爆金币.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-30-47_交易治疗药水_回血.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-38-40_野怪会首先将攻击它的单位视为索敌目标_勾引野怪互相打斗.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_20-42-51_NPC击杀野怪.gif?t=1710598284"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617300/extras/GIF_2023-12-11_17-59-08_宝箱.gif?t=1710598284"/></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mudoku - next Sudoku</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2860250/Mudoku__next_Sudoku/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2860250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Move + Sudoku = Mudoku !!<br>
<br>
Mudoku is addictive puzzle based on Sudoku.<br>
<br>
Move and slide line to complete Sudoku.<br>
The rules are the same as Sudoku.<br>
<br/>
Fill a 9 × 9 grid with digits so that each column, each row, and each of the nine 3 × 3 subgrids that compose the grid contain all of the digits from 1 to 9.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potato Salad</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2855740/Potato_Salad/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Potato Salad is a collection of 7 games across different genres. Each game covers a potato from a different time period and highlights the never ending battle against The King of Spud Town who is always scheming to get his way.<br/><br/><strong>FEATURES</strong><br/>- 7 unique games across different genres.<br/>- Obtain extras from completing challenges.<br/>- Remastered and formatted to HD resolution.<br/>- Designed with the Steam Deck in mind.<br/>- Play the games in any order you wish!<br/><br/><strong>THE LEGENDARY POTATOES</strong><br/>Below you will find information on the potatoes and types of games contained within this collection:<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/extras/Potato0.png?t=1710591807"><br/>Inspector Smith<br/>GENRE: Point and Click<br/>This potato has always found an explanation to every mystery possible. Until now! At the cost of his sanity, he attempts to solve the case of the missing television.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/extras/Potato1.png?t=1710591807"><br/>Potatoman<br/>GENRE: Platformer<br/>An ordinary potato has his life upended when he is magically transported to a new dimension. In this universe, he is the Potatoman and must save the world.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/extras/Potato2.png?t=1710591807"><br/>Beat Hiratio<br/>GENRE: Beat em' Up<br/>The only justice this potato knows is at the end of his fists. Asked to provide food in exchange for monies, he agrees to make the biggest feast in history.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/extras/Potato3.png?t=1710591807"><br/>Boxer Yakuzomo<br/>GENRE: Boxing<br/>A potato determined to become the strongest punchmaster in all the lands. Win all the belts and claim the championship once and for all.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/extras/Potato4.png?t=1710591807"><br/>Spaceace Alexius<br/>GENRE: Shooter<br/>The legendary spaceace is contracted to obtain an item of great power. The grizzled veteran sets off for one last trip; sure to be the deadliest yet.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/extras/Potato5.png?t=1710591807"><br/>Chaos Vasquez<br/>GENRE: Action<br/>Wandering the wasteland without a cause, a hapless king approaches him with a proposal he can't refuse. Everything he's ever known is about to be tested...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855740/extras/Potato6.png?t=1710591807"><br/>8Bit Potato<br/>GENRE: Arcade Minigame Collection<br/>Trapped in an arcade machine, 8bit potato must beat the high scores to become the ultimate gamer.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Cats in Berlin</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2736480/Hidden_Cats_in_Berlin/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736480/extras/steam_cards_header.gif?t=1710588739"><br/><br/>HALLO! Our cats are now in the awesome city of Berlin! Let's search for them.<br/><strong>A short and pleasant experience in a big and lovely illustration!</strong> Start with a Beautiful monochromatic scenario, relax, and find all the cats to reveal the final colored art.<br/><br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736480/extras/ui-credits-star.png?t=1710588739"><strong>More than 970 hidden objects to find!!!</strong><br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736480/extras/ui-credits-star.png?t=1710588739"><strong>Play through different modes, find special cats, and unlock bonus levels!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736480/extras/modes.png?t=1710588739"><h2 class="bb_tag">NORMAL MODE</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Find 120 cats in fixed positions.<br/></li><li>5 hints.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">ADVANCED MODE</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Find 200 cats in semi-random positions.<br/></li><li> 12 Special cats that unlock Bonus Levels and give hints.<br/></li><li> 20 city people to find and earn hints.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736480/extras/bonus-levels.gif?t=1710588739"><br/><br/>Bonus levels with different sizes and numbers of kittens to find. One use of hint for helping.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Metzgerei:</strong> 50 kittens<br/></li><li><strong>Bäckerei: </strong>50 kittens<br/></li><li><strong>Hauptbanhoff:</strong> 50 kittens<br/></li><li><strong>Berlin Wall:</strong> 75 kittens<br/></li><li><strong>Brauhaus:</strong> 100 kittens<br/></li><li><strong>Tiergarten:</strong> 100 kittens<br/></li><li><strong>Underground Party:</strong> 100 kittens + 100 people</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736480/extras/ui-credits-separator.png?t=1710588739"><h2 class="bb_tag">Accessibility</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dark Mode<br/></li><li>Invert Mouse Zoom<br/></li><li>Mouse Drag Sensibility<br/></li><li>Edge Screen Scrolling<br/></li><li>Color Blindness</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER FURY</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2829060/COMPUTER_FURY/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2829060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							general: Offline For One Player Fighting game like 3rd person challenging fighting game like small computer toys while playing &amp; you can change to you fighter position during fight , special moves , receive score after you win , you can very easily make your any special move or difficult move during fight with any simple keyboard, using keyboard is more fun than x box game pad or pc game pad , but with x box game pad or pc game pad added vibration system , currently there is tow hero characters each character have more than 14 move but soon on new update is coming more characters ,more moves , more enemy &amp; more enemy types<br>
<br>
skills: improve your game skills using keyboard or pc gamepad or x box gamepad , improve your speed , improve your mind memory  <br>
<br>
game play &amp;  story:<br>
when you start play game select start new game , on next scene select your pc game pad or x box game pad or keyboard,  on next scene select your favorite character , on next scene the story is : ( when dark computer team controlled the computers &amp; computer city , so heroes decide to free the computers &amp; computer  city from dark computer team ) , on next scene is map scene for enemy locations the hero should clear all dark computer team from whole computer city so the hero in game chose any plane (randomly) to face dark computer member to fight him on which location should go <br>
<br/>
after loading scene the start actual game scene , start fight dark computer face to face , if you are lose you can continue and no worry about how many time to continue, and if win you will be ready for facing next dark computer member from map scene until facing the boss of dark computer team and facing him , if you win you on boss then you congratulations the computer city is free and cleared from dark computer team.<br/>
<br/>
good luck						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grim Realms</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1522280/Grim_Realms/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1522280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i><strong>A grim world will be generated...</strong></i><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1522280/extras/FlatterDread.gif?t=1710574293"><br/><br/><i><strong>Explore everything from bare deserts...</strong></i><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1522280/extras/FlatterDesert.gif?t=1710574293"><br/><strong><i><br/>... to snow covered mountains.</i></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1522280/extras/FlatterIcetown.gif?t=1710574293"><br/><br/><strong><i>Recruit blacksmiths, brutal pirates, noble intellectuals and everything in between.</i></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1522280/extras/FlatterSmithing.gif?t=1710574293"><br/><br/><strong><i>They will all struggle to survive in a world overrun by the undead...</i></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1522280/extras/FlatterUndead.gif?t=1710574293"><br/><strong><i>... and <u>you</u> will be their guide!</i></strong><br/><br/><strong>A game inspired by Rimworld, Dwarf Fortress and Terraria:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> All humans have unique portraits, different backgrounds and come from distinct cultures. They will develop and age as the seasons change and the years pass.<br/></li><li> They all have different skills and abilities; some will become expert miners, great counsellors, and others master blacksmiths.<br/></li><li> Manage their needs, set their priorities and equip them for war or work. They will eat, sleep, socialize, create art, fight and abandon your faction if pushed too hard. They might return later, but as a friendly visitor or leading an attack? <br/></li><li> Defend your settlement from hordes of undead, bandits, large raiding parties and necromancers.<br/></li><li> Mine for riches deep below the surface, discover ancient shrines and powerful magic.<br/></li><li> Start practicing necromancy, raise the dead and have them work for you - see if you can defend your faction from paladins instead! Or maybe harness the powers of light and try to banish the undead for good!<br/></li><li> Craft a huge variety of weapons, armor and clothes from all kinds of materials.<br/></li><li> Plant crops and later harvest to create food and medicine.<br/></li><li> Hunt animals, or tame them to produce milk and fur.<br/></li><li> Grow your knowledge by plenty of research options. All the way from longbows to muskets and grenades.<br/></li><li> Trade with visiting merchants, convince them to join your settlement or plunder them if you wish!<br/></li><li> Create caravans, travel the world by land or sea; discover new locations and establish new settlements.</li></ul><br/>PS: This game is in the same franchise as Grim Nights. However, <i>this game will focus less on tower defense and much more on your villagers and the management of your growing settlement</i>.<br/>(Also: This game was previously called 'Grim Nights 2'. Long story short: the name was changed because it is too different to easily be considered a sequel.)						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotoko's a Little Weird</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2657710/Kotokos_a_Little_Weird/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2657710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2657710/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1710561616"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2657710/extras/Kotoko_s_a_Little_Weird_Description_1_EN.png?t=1710561616"><br/>Kotoko follows the same routine day after day, trying to be the perfect student and sister. But is that all there is to life? One day, Kotoko decides to spice up her bland routine. Will she end up going back to her old ways, or will she grow into her own person? <br/><br/>Follow Kotoko as she makes new friends and throws herself into some wild situations. Sure, she's a little weird, but that's all part of the fun!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2657710/extras/Kotoko_s_a_Little_Weird_Description_3_EN.png?t=1710561616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2657710/extras/Kotoko_s_a_Little_Weird_Description_01_EN.png?t=1710561616"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blindsighted</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2809170/Blindsighted/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2809170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">A Different Kind of Platformer</h2><strong>Blindsighted</strong> has the player explore levels not by sight but by touch and memory. <strong>Dying is common</strong>, but you'll remember the lay of the land each time. Learn from your mistakes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2>Originally conceived for a <strong>Game Jam</strong> as nothing more than a demo, <strong>Blindsighted</strong> is now a full game!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Lots of unique gameplay mechanics<br/></li><li> Minimalist, but captivating visuals<br/></li><li> Controller support<br/></li><li> 4 original pieces of music<br/></li><li> More than one level! (12 base levels, 3 mastery levels.)<br/></li><li> Level select with best times and best deaths<br/></li><li> Optional timer and death counters<br/></li><li> Accessibility features</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bunny hungry</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667010/bunny_hungry/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							There's only one word that can adequately describe this bunny: hungry. The goal of each puzzle in <i>bunny hungry</i> is to rearrange the terrain so that the bunny has a safe path of grass and dirt to reach the food. Every time you place a piece of terrain, all the tiles interact with their neighbors in consistent ways—but you must discover those ways!<br/><br/>Key features:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 80 original 9-by-9 puzzles<br/></li><li> mouse-based pick-and-place interface<br/></li><li> more than 10 types of terrain to discover<br/></li><li> original music, artwork, and sound effects<br/></li><li> customizable bunny appearance and food types<br/></li><li> unlock-able level editor<br/></li><li> optional move counter<br/></li><li> discord server for community, support, and sharing custom levels</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twilight Manor: Roguelite FPS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2863690/Twilight_Manor_Roguelite_FPS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2863690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2863690/extras/hdsbflkhfdaslkjsfhd.gif?t=1710593138"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fast paced combat! </strong>- Use a wide array of weapons to destroy your enemies! You can even kick enemies and parry their projectiles! <br/></li><li><strong>Advanced Gore System</strong> - Headshot enemies or tear their body to pieces and paint the mansion red! Just better hope it's not your blood being spilled <br/></li><li><strong>Stop time!</strong> - With Twilight Mode, you can use your built up adrenaline to stop time and gain a huge advantage over your foes!  <br/></li><li><strong>Intense boss fights </strong>- Test your skills as you fight through increasingly difficult bosses and uncover the truth about the mansion. <br/></li><li><strong>Upgrade system</strong> - At the end of every boss fight, you get to chose between 1 of 3 upgrades, double damage, 2x reload speed and flight are just some of the abilities you can gain! <br/></li><li><strong>Unlockable difficulties</strong> - Carry over your upgrades and face new difficulty modes you've unlocked!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">STORY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2863690/extras/asdkufygfkajdysgh__1_.gif?t=1710593138"><br/>In Twilight Manor: Roguelite FPS, you play as a woman investigating a mysterious mansion in a futuristic cyberpunk world. As you battle through tough foes, you realize there is more going on here than just some experiments.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloody Hallowfest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1797060/Bloody_Hallowfest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1797060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bloody Hallowfest is a horror game with a retro visual style, inspired by some classic B-series horror films from the 90s.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1797060/extras/BloodyHallowfest_Img1.jpg?t=1710536412"><br/><br/>On the night before Halloween, Maya and her friends gather at the summer camp, eager to set up a special event for the youngsters. Together, they deck out the place and prepare games for Halloween night (kids love hunting for pumpkins and taking a swing at the pinata filled with sweets and candies!). What starts as a fun night takes a horrifying turn when a stranger, wielding a bloodied axe, barges in and snuffs out everyone's lives.<br/><br/>Now, Maya is forced to run for her life. As she unravels the escape plan, she also delves into a sinister secret behind the killer and the motives that led to such a massacre. Will Maya manage to escape the nightmare and confront the truth, or perhaps her blood will mingle with that of her friends on the cold steel of the killer's axe?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1797060/extras/BloodyHallowfest_Gif1.gif?t=1710536412"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Survive the Night: Help Maya navigate through the terrors of the night and escape the bloodbath.<br/></li><li>Unravel the Mystery: Uncover the sinister secret behind the killer and the motives that led to such a massacre.<br/></li><li>Prepare for Halloween: Immerse yourself in the Halloween spirit by helping set up decorations and games for the night.<br/></li><li>Retro Graphics: Experience the nostalgia of classic B-series horror films with the game's retro visual style.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pogo Girlfriend 👧🏼</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2318880/Pogo_Girlfriend/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/developer/JofersGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318880/extras/SteamBanner.gif?t=1710534690"/></a><br/><strong><u>The friendliest rage game!</u></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318880/extras/Jump011.gif?t=1710534690"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318880/extras/SaveYourGirlfriend.png?t=1710534690"><br/>Your having a lovely meal.<br/>You nip out to the loo.<br/>When you return your girlfriend is missing.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318880/extras/RocketGang.gif?t=1710534690"><br/>You run outside, and a rocket ship is flying towards space.<br/>Is your girlfriend in the rocket?<br/>Your only option is to give chase and find out!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318880/extras/Jump011.gif?t=1710534690"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318880/extras/Gameplay.png?t=1710534690"><br/>Use your pogo to navigate the the world.<br/>Find checkpoints located off the beaten track<br/>Each checkpoint can be relocated once to any spot the player choses!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318880/extras/Checkpoint002.gif?t=1710534690"><br/>Can be useful for making the gaps between checkpoints smaller.<br/>But can still be useful in speedruns.<br/>Leaving a checkpoint at a junction you wish to return to quickly later!<br/>Touch the original checkpoint location to reset the flag and allow it to be placed somewhere new.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318880/extras/Jump011.gif?t=1710534690"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318880/extras/PlayWithFriends.png?t=1710534690"><br/>Create lobbies!<br/>And race with against your friends!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318880/extras/PogoTrailer021.gif?t=1710534690"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318880/extras/Jump011.gif?t=1710534690"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318880/extras/Leaderboards.png?t=1710534690"><br/>Can you be the pogo king?<br/>Race against the clock to post times to the global leader board!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318880/extras/LeaderBoards2.PNG?t=1710534690"><br/><br/>If you enjoyed this, please check out my weird none linear cosmic horror game! <br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2444380/Mines_Of_Moritania/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2444380/Mines_Of_Moritania/</a><br/><br/>Or my strange and spooky animal crossing esque multiplayer RPG!<br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2331890/Cozy_Together/" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2331890/Cozy_Together/</a><br/><br/>⭐Follow for more weird stuff!⭐<br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/developer/JofersGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2318880/extras/Following.png?t=1710534690"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMARA</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2829370/SAMARA/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2829370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>SAMARA</strong> is a first person, single player psychological survival horror game. The game unfolds as Player sets out to investigate the mysterious disappearance of his uncle, whom he hasn't heard from in over a year. He has no idea that this seemingly ordinary visit will send him into a terrifying experience beyond his wildest dreams.<br/>Upon arriving at his uncle's secluded estate, the player is greeted by an unsettling silence that hangs heavy in the air. The once-familiar surroundings suddenly feel claustrophobic , as if there were invisible monsters lurking just beyond the shadows.<br/>As he cautiously explores the dimly lit halls and forgotten corners of the house, a sense of foreboding intensifies with every step.<br/>The nightmare begins with the finding of a <strong>lone doll</strong> that appears harmless at first glance. The glassy eyes of the doll seem to follow the player everywhere he goes, and something about it feels inherently wrong. Its presence also evokes an unexplainable feeling of dread.<br/>As the night wears on and the tension reaches its peak, the player finds himself inexorably drawn back to the eerie doll, its presence a constant reminder of the malevolent forces at play. The doll's true nature is exposed in a climactic, terrifying showdown that unleashes a terror beyond description. <br/>The player has to face the deepest recesses of his own mind in order to survive the night and discover the terrifying truth behind his uncle's disappearance, his nerves strained and his sanity on the verge of collapse. However, the doll's eerie stare stays, serving as a disturbing reminder of the horrors that lie just beneath the surface, even as daylight breaks and the nightmare fades.<br/><strong>Game feature:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The game is made in Unreal Engine<br/></li><li>Players must navigate through a series of intricate puzzles scattered throughout the game<br/></li><li>Immersive Realistic Graphics<br/></li><li>Immersive Sound Effects<br/></li><li>Dynamic Gameplay: With a combination of exploration, puzzle-solving, psychological suspense, and chasing sequence the game offers dynamic gameplay that keeps players engaged and challenged from start to finish.<br/></li><li>Atmospheric Environment</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amygdala</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2453920/Amygdala/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2453920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Amygdala | <strong>Synopsis</strong></h2><br/>Welcome to the haunting world of Amygdala, an horror experience that explores the dark depths of the nightmare realm, manifested through incredible and terrifying creatures. <br/><br/>Confront your deepest fears and uncover what lies behind the Amygdala. <br/><br/>Prepare to immerse yourself in the sinister beauty of horror.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2453920/extras/AM1_compressed2.gif?t=1710532920"><h2 class="bb_tag">Wellcome to Amygdala | <strong>Story</strong></h2>Step into the eerie world of Amygdala, a first-person horror game that takes players on an unsettling journey through mysterious dimensions. <br/><br/>Explore a haunting location, uncovering its secrets while encountering terrifying monsters that lurk in the shadows. <br/><br/><strong>Amygdala is the destination of all the entities in the Universe that are lost in the nightmare.</strong> <br/>There are cases in which some entities are allowed to have their own symbolic body as a manifestation of the nightmare; <br/><br/>This is the case for <strong>entities that manage not to succumb to the nightmare but to live through it</strong>, and in the most<strong> formidable cases, to control it.</strong><br/>These individuals are known as <strong>Rulers of Nightmares</strong><br/><br/>If a nightmare for some reason becomes unstable, the <strong>Absolute Judge</strong> takes action takes action through you, and this is where your adventure begin.<br/><br/>You are the nightmare seeker and it is your job to take the eyes of the Rulers of Nightmares.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2453920/extras/AM3.gif?t=1710532920"><h2 class="bb_tag">Terrifying creatures, to be feared or... | <strong>Unique Gameplay feature</strong></h2><br/>Embark on a journey through Amygdala, where monstrous creatures await. Uncover the secrets they hide, the reasons behind their existence, and go into their nightmares.<br/><br/>In Amygdala, you will encounter different creatures, each with unique their nightmares.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Face nightmares and gain the eyes of the Rulers of Nightmare;</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Unique creatures, terrifying but at the same time mysterious;</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Discover mysterious, macabre but at the same time fascinating settings</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Let yourself be drawn into this atypical narrative horror</li></ul><br/>Starting from the Amygdala, the <strong>Main HUB </strong>after the speech of the Absolute Judge, you will be able to freely explore the hub and<strong> freely choose which nightmare to start </strong>from:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>The Nightmare of the Big Head:</strong> Discover what happened inside this nightmare, mysterious rituals, strange creatures within a setting reminiscent of corridors of an ancient hotel now abandoned.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>The Nightmare of Insatiable Knowledge:</strong> Inside a giant vertical bookcase, you will have to feed insatiable creatures by climbing through this bookcase in search of the most... delicious books. But be careful, there are other hungry creatures.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>The Nightmare of Beauty:</strong> A sick and distorted nightmare, where the representation of perfect beauty through mannequins merges with what the media canons impose on us... evolving into a macabre attempt to find beauty... but what is the beauty? You will have to find out within the walls of crumbling laboratories.</li></ul><br/><i>Once you have completed your task you will be able to have an audience with the Great Monolith... some say it can make your nightmares come true.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2453920/extras/AM4.gif?t=1710532920"><h2 class="bb_tag">Unique Creatures | <strong>Monsters shaped by nightmares</strong></h2><br/>Encounter unique creatures, known as rulers of nightmares, entities who have been able not only to withstand the nightmare but to master and shape it according to their desires.<br/><br/>These rulers of nightmares have earned a place within the Amygdala, where the Absolute Judge supervises the stability of these nightmares.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2453920/extras/AM2.gif?t=1710532920"><h2 class="bb_tag">Stunning Nightmare | <strong>Unreal Engine 5</strong></h2><br/>Nightmares connected with a subtle artistic thread that unites the aesthetics enhanced by the Unreal Engine 5 graphics engine. <br/>Immersive lighting rendering to immerse the user in a supernatural experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">Info | <strong>More Info &amp; Social</strong></h2><br/>Amygdala is a solo developer game.<br/><br/>Amygdala was not born with the idea of innovating the gaming industry or being the best horror game ever made, but was born simply to give context and show some creatures created by me connected with the basic idea of expressing different emotions.<br/><br/>I hope these creatures can accompany you in your deepest nightmares.<h2 class="bb_tag">Sensitive Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</h2>Amygdala contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images. This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. <br/><br/>Please enjoy this nightmares.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Song of Yosef</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2853240/Song_of_Yosef/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2853240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Yosef recover all of the letters of his scroll in this fast-paced, retro style "metroidvania" adventure. Inspired by the Commodore64 classics that the author grew up with, Song of Yosef joins platform gaming physics with adventure and exploration. Smash sock puppets and other foes, unlock new areas by collecting abilities and becoming more powerful, and slide your way to victory.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floppa: The Dark Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2854370/Floppa_The_Dark_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You have found yourself alone, in the middle of a vast dark forest. You need to explore this place to find 8 pictures of cats that are hidden somewhere here. But it's not that simple, because in fact there is someone else in this forest besides you, and he doesn't like your presence at all... If your screen gets disturbed, you'd better run away... Find the 8 pictures before Floppa finds you. <br/><br/>In the menu you can choose one of the 10 characters that will chase you in this forest. Big Floppa, Bingus, El Gato, and others.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854370/extras/gifCharacters.gif?t=1710530116"><br/><br/>You can also choose from three levels: This is a forest in summer, fall and winter seasons.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854370/extras/gifLevels.gif?t=1710530116"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirate Dragons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1835120/Pirate_Dragons/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pirate Dragons is a third-person, action RPG where you play a dragon in a world filled with sailing ships, islands, trade routes, pirates, and much more. <br/><br/>Battle against other sailing ships from different factions, grow your dragon's power, learn new breath weapons, build your own sailing fleet, and make your mark!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835120/extras/BreathRedShipNew_.gif?t=1710527683"><br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play a dragon!<br/></li><li>Third-person, high flying, action combat.<br/></li><li>Explore an open world of islands, sailing ships, and piracy.<br/></li><li>Use power-ups to increase your fire damage, heal you, and recharge your breath weapons.<br/></li><li>Level up to learn new breath weapons and other skills.<br/></li><li>Build a fleet of ships to help you trade goods and battle against other factions.<br/></li><li>Upgrade your ships with better crews, sails, cannons, and hulls.<br/></li><li>Complete missions, become a merchant, or engage in piracy!<br/></li><li>An economy that changes based on your actions.<br/></li><li>Events and missions.<br/></li><li>Grow your hoard to become the richest and most powerful dragon ever!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835120/extras/FlyOverTrensec.gif?t=1710527683"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835120/extras/SkelSkullNew.gif?t=1710527683"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835120/extras/IceBreathNew.gif?t=1710527683"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835120/extras/FleetNew.gif?t=1710527683"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Room</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2822210/Next_Room/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2822210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							It is a single-player 3D scene puzzle type game that interacts with objects in a room from a first-person perspective to find a way to the next room. The game is made up of high-quality models, bright skies and warm sunlight, so find your way to the next room in this cozy room!<h2 class="bb_tag"> Foreword</h2><br/>- Welcome to this cozy room, there seems to be a little puzzle here, can you find the puzzle and the puzzle solution?if you can find it, the reward is - the next room.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Gameplay</h2><br/>- Finding the key in the room from a first-person perspective or other method to open the door.<br/><br/>- Have more than 10 playable individual levels (new levels will continue to be made).<br/><br/>- Does not contain horror elements.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Notes</h2><br/>- Please keep the graphics card driver updated so that you can experience the ray tracing function that is turned on by default (if the graphics card driver version is lower, you will not be able to experience the ray tracing function, and there will be a driver upgrade prompt when starting, which can be ignored and will not affect normal play).<br/><br/>- If the frame rate is low, you can try to turn on the window mode and reduce the game window resolution to play.<br/><br/>- There is only a small amount of simple English text in the game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dice-Zee!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2857400/DiceZee/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2857400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dice-Zee! brings back a classic and beloved game that is popular across the world!  <br>
<br>
Dice-Zee! brings you a chill and very casual dice rolling experience where you'll try and score as high of a score as possible on the virtual score card provided to you within the game!<br>
<br>
- Easy to learn and casual game experience<br>
- Hear authentic dice shaking and dice rolling sound effects<br>
- No timers to beat, No way to die, Just addicting dice rolling good times!<br>
<br/>
Dice-Zee! consists of thirteen rounds, each round provides you up to three rolls of up to five dice.  After each dice roll, you'll get to choose which dice you'd like to keep and which dice you'd like to re-roll as you try to score maximum points in all the categories.  Once you've rolled three times without writing a score on one of the categories, you'll have to choose one to place your score.  Never fear making mistakes because you can always back out of scoring and choose a different one instead with the simple to use and user-friendly interface.<br/>
<br/>
After all the categories have been scored, you'll see your final score automatically added up for you and how well you've done!<br/>
<br/>
Can you rank as one of the best dice scoring players in the world?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Park Baseball 25</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384620/Out_of_the_Park_Baseball_25/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_banner_1.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/>We are incredibly excited to announce <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong> - the special 25th Anniversary edition of our award-winning baseball strategy series. Can you believe it's been a quarter of a century? Out of the Park Baseball is not just a game - it's a legacy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_henry.png?t=1710574531"><br/><br/>If it happens in real baseball, it happens in Out of the Park Baseball! Discover new talent, draft the next superstar, negotiate with free agents, enter trade talks with other teams, build your dynasty and guide a franchise into an infinite future! As a manager, dive into the more hands-on management and set your team's lineups, pitching staffs, in-game strategy and call the shots from the dugout. You can oversee your league at a high level, or play out each game in the gorgeous 3D game mode, managing play by play or even pitch by pitch. OOTP has it all covered!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_badge.png?t=1710574531"><br/>Here are just a few of the new features coming to <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong>:<br/><br/><strong>A game-changing new Player Development Lab!</strong><br/><br/>Shape the future of your upcoming stars! You can channel your inner Player Development Director like never before. A modern new Player Development Lab is here for every team that allows you to give players individual programs to work on, developing them how you like. Do you want your hitter to work on improving their baserunning? Bunting? Contact? Would you prefer your pitcher to work on building up their stamina? Developing a new pitch? Velocity? It's all up to you - for each of your upcoming future stars!<br/><br/><strong>Massive Player Ratings and AI Upgrade!</strong><br/><br/>It’s the most comprehensive player ratings upgrade in the 25 year history of Out of the Park Baseball! Batting, Pitching, and Fielding ratings have been painstakingly modified to capture the essence of baseball, with modifications to Contact and Power for hitters, Movement and Stuff for pitchers, the addition of Catcher Framing and Stealing Aggressiveness, and much more. BABIP is now front and center for hitters and hurlers, while new internal ratings updates allow for even more flexibility for Commissioners around the world to adjust the game to their detailed delight. Plus, the AI throughout the game has been improved dramatically to deliver the most challenging OOTP experience ever! <br/><br/><strong>Even More Detailed Player Development Control!</strong><br/><br/>Delegate how each and every player on your team will spend their time day in, day out with coaches at practice. Want your power hitter to worry less about avoiding strikeouts and put that time and effort into working on his home run swing instead? Want your aging starter to spend more time practicing his control instead of spending that time worrying about his stuff? By allocating their time and focus to the areas you want, over time you can influence how players develop, maintain their skillset, and fight the aging curve.<br/><br/><strong>2024 Rosters and Rules!</strong><br/><br/>As always, Out of the Park Baseball features up-to-the-minute 2024 MLB rosters that get updated all season long, with every franchise represented from its big league club all the way down to the low minors, and everywhere in between! Plus, OOTP 25 features officially licensed leagues from South Korea (KBO) and Europe.<br/><br/><strong>Improved Historical MLB Modes!</strong><br/><br/>Set up historical MLB games in an all new streamlined way - and benefit from vastly improved historical player ratings! It’s never been faster or easier to experience the entire history of Major League Baseball, now producing even more realistic outcomes thanks to those comprehensive ratings and simulation engine upgrades.<br/><br/><strong>New Retro Visual Immersion!</strong><br/><br/>Watch games with a variety of experiences, including retro-style black and white, ‘50s-era, and ‘70s-era television presentations. Choose from all of these to play games, watch highlights, or just catch a ballgame from a bygone era!<br/><br/><strong>New Licensed Leagues!</strong><br/><br/>For the first time ever, Out of the Park Baseball features an officially licensed Honkbal Hoofdklasse league from The Netherlands and the British Baseball Federation from the United Kingdom! Look for their official clubs, players, competitions, and more!<br/><br/><strong>For the first time ever - an official partnership with the Baseball Hall of Fame!</strong><br/><br/>What happens when you combine the only game that has the entire history of baseball and the the greatest Hall of Fame in sports? An incredible, year-long journey! Join us as we partner with the Baseball Hall of Fame all season - and beyond. Explore Hall of Fame Plaques, with the official, accurate text for each Hall of Famer. Discover incredible Hall of Fame artifacts, curated and released in fun "exhibits" over the course of the season in concert with the Hall - and more surprises too. It's going to be amazing! <br/><br/><strong>Dozens of upgrades big and small!</strong><br/><br/>--&gt; Updated in-game engine base advancement and camera movements<br/>--&gt; A new manager decision history screen gives you a look back on your best and worst trades and transactions<br/>--&gt; Improved trade packages for prospect packages <br/>--&gt; Updated two-way functionality with injured players<br/>And much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/pt_store_text_banner2.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/><br/><strong>Perfect Team is back - bigger than ever!</strong><br/><br/>It’s an all-new Perfect Team! There’s nothing in the world like the incredible online competitions of Perfect Team. Featuring by far the largest player pool ever, and taking advantage of all the player rating and balance upgrades, this year’s Perfect Team is a whole new ballgame.<br/><br/><strong>Brand New Perfect Team Combinator Series Cards!</strong><br/><br/>Pulled non-live cards have a chance to be a special Combinator Series version of the card! Use other cards that share a link (for example being teammates) with the player to get a chance to boost the raw ratings of the Combinator Series card.<br/><br/><strong>A Perfect Team Tournament Roster Builder!</strong><br/><br/>Want to design rosters for the incredible array of Perfect Team Tournaments - all on your own? For the first time ever, Perfect Team will feature a Tournament Sandbox! You can tinker to your heart's content with varying rosters for every type of tournament, with no pressure. This long-requested feature makes its debut in Out of the Park Baseball 25!<br/><br/>In addition to the brand-new Tournament Roster Builder and Combinator Series, Perfect Team 25 also features:<br/><br/><strong>Team Chemistry</strong> - Players who played together in real life will get extra bonuses when on your roster together. Players gain bonuses for seasons they played together, as well as simply being part of the same team or from the same decades<br/><strong>Perfect Team competitions starting on the first day</strong>, including a huge Opening Weekend of Tournaments with big prizes and Perfect Team Championship Series qualifying from Day One! <br/><strong>New content all season long - and beyond!</strong> All new programs, missions, competitions, and excitement await you every day.<br/><br/>Out of the Park Baseball 25 runs on PC/Mac and features the American League and National League logos, the World Series trophy, official logos and jerseys for all 30 MLB teams and 15 KBO teams, over 150 Minor League Baseball league and team logos, and historical MLB logos.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Circle Tales: Elvenwoods</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2805910/The_Circle_Tales_Elvenwoods/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2805910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Elvenwoods is a story-driven action-adventure game, and the first instalment of the Dark Aeon saga. It is an experimental project made to learn game development, and is now available for everyone on Steam. It will therefore remain completely free. <br/><br/>In the beginning, there was a Source. This Source was the origin of every universe, and the only thing that prevented time and space to collapse. In the year 5000 of the Creation Era, the high priest of the Dead God Tarisdum destroyed the Source, starting a ten-thousand-year prophecy. Its first events take place in Vàlochlin, a young world built by the Warlord Dusnol to hide the skull of the Dead God. You are Imriel of Darkwood, Green Spirit of the Circle, an elf who dreams of exploring the world. After arriving in the Elvenwoods, you begin a quest to slay a resurrected Tarisdum, and to uncover the mystery of the Three Enemies.<br/><br/><br/><strong><u>The beginning of a saga</u></strong><br/>A 10-hour long, fully voiced story. <br/>Elvenwoods is a story-driven game, based on a main questline and seven factions.<br/><br/><strong><u>Epic battles</u></strong><br/>A dynamic sword, bow, and magic combat system.<br/>18 unique boss battles await the players, as well as a trials mode for those who seek a true challenge.<br/><br/><strong><u>A vast open world</u></strong><br/>The world of Elvenwoods expands on three different maps and more than a hundred locations to explore.<br/>Players can travel by foot, on a mount, on a boat, or even by flying.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legends of Alterra</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2663350/Legends_of_Alterra/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2663350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An epic adventure awaits!  A classic RPG experience, with modern game design and deep battle strategy.<br>
<br>
In the mysterious Kingdom of Alterra, a young princess defies her father and makes her own path in the world.  She makes invaluable companions along the way, and learns the truth about the Kingdom she is destined to inherit.  The rich story includes several overlapping narratives, character growth, and twists.<br>
<br>
The game features a dynamic timeline system that determines the order of actions in battle. Character and enemy icons move along a timeline at the top of the screen, showing when each combatant will act. This timeline system adds an element of strategy, as you can delay or interrupt enemies by well-timed actions.  The system also allows for deep character customization, including a job system (with primary classes and subclasses), skill point system (acquire and spend points to learn class-specific skills), and a deep magic system.<br>
<br>
Concoct useful items from ingredients you come across during your journey.  Customize your characters with unique items, equipment, classes and traits!<br/>
<br/>
Zelda-like puzzle solving allows you to manipulate your surroundings and progress through the many dungeons scattered across the world.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grym Wonder</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2243080/Grym_Wonder/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2243080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Grym Wonder</strong> — a time survival game with minimalistic gameplay and roguelike elements.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2243080/extras/gw1.gif?t=1710520023"><br/><br/>Your kingdom has been captured by evil spirits, the last hero has fallen and the enemy is triumphant. Thanks to the Court Mage, you can return to battle countless times in any of the heroic guises and avenge your home. Fight, collect resources, improve skills and weapons for victory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2243080/extras/gw2.gif?t=1710520023"><br/><br/><strong>Court magician's tips:</strong><br/>Time is your main enemy; every minute the enemy becomes stronger and faster.<br/>Fully upgraded weapons and relics in the right combination will give you an incredible advantage in battle.<br/>Runes will strengthen you, and battle cries will help you get more gold.<br/>Reset purchased upgrades to try new combinations - it's free.<br/>Don't lock yourself in tight spaces. More enemies - more experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2243080/extras/gw3.gif?t=1710520023"><br/><br/><strong>Good luck!</strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dusty The Lazy Cat</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2851520/Dusty_The_Lazy_Cat/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2851520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dusty must journey through various worlds and levels, solving numerous puzzles along the way. Some puzzles require him to collect certain items, which he must search for on each island. However, there are obstacles that must be overcome to access each island and enemies that will attempt to eliminate Dusty. Once he has collected the key, he can proceed to the next level.<br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F7k72P6ZPrb" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2851520/extras/About_Section_Banners-4.png?t=1710518442"> </img></a><br/>Don't forget to join my amazing Discord community for even more awesome content!<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2851520/extras/About_Section_Banners-1.png?t=1710518442"><br/>Dusty progresses through a series of levels, each of which requires him to utilize his problem-solving skills to overcome obstacles and challenges. In order to progress through these levels, Dusty must collect a variety of items which are integral to the completion of the puzzles. These collectibles are essential to the successful resolution of each level, and their acquisition is paramount to Dusty's success in the game.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2851520/extras/About_Section_Banners-2.png?t=1710518442"><br/>As you advance through each level, you will encounter increasingly challenging adversaries who endeavor to eliminate you. It is imperative to note that these opponents will become progressively more formidable, thereby intensifying the difficulty of each level. It is recommended that you prepare yourself accordingly and develop strategies to overcome these obstacles.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2851520/extras/About_Section_Banners-3.png?t=1710518442"><br/>As you progress through the different levels, you'll encounter increasingly difficult obstacles that require more skill and strategy to overcome. As you move forward, you'll need to use your reflexes and quick thinking to avoid falling into the water below, which would result in your elimination from the game. The water can be deceptively deep and cold, so it's important to stay focused and alert at all times. With practice and patience, you can learn to navigate each level successfully and move on to the next challenge.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Royale 3D</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2511180/Pixel_Royale_3D/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2511180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to <strong>Pixel Royale 3D</strong>, where you'll embark on an immersive journey into the heart of intense <strong>pixelated FPS</strong> action! Prepare to dive into a world of thrilling gunfights, strategic gameplay, and an impressive arsenal of over <u>40 meticulously designed weapons</u>. With <u>three captivating maps</u> and a constant stream of <strong>bimonthly updates</strong>, this game is sure to keep you on the edge of your seat.<br/><br/><strong>Pixel Royale 3D</strong> offers an extensive collection of uniquely crafted weapons, catering to every playstyle imaginable. From <u>classic firearms to futuristic energy guns</u>, you'll find the perfect tools to dominate the battlefield. Experiment with different weapon combinations, discover your favorites, and unleash havoc upon your adversaries.<br/><br/>But that's not all - <strong>Pixel Royale 3D</strong> takes customization to a whole new level. Express your creativity and <u>design your own character skins</u> (Purchase may be necessary), standing out from the crowd with a personalized touch. Become the envy of both allies and foes as you showcase your unique style and prowess.<br/><br/>Prepare for an intense and action-packed gameplay experience like no other. Engage in heart-pounding battles across <strong>three unique maps</strong>, each adorned with stunning pixel art that creates a visually captivating backdrop for your epic encounters.<br/><br/>With <strong>three separate game modes</strong>, <strong>Pixel Royale 3D</strong> ensures endless variety and re-playability. Dive into <u>Team Deathmatch</u>, where teamwork and communication are paramount. Embrace the chaos of <u>Deathmatch</u>, where survival of the fittest is the ultimate goal. Or test your tactical skills in <u>Duels</u>, where a tense 1v1 situation and pure skill determine the victor.<br/><br/>We are dedicated to providing a phenomenal gaming experience, which is why we deliver <strong>bimonthly updates</strong> packed with exciting new content. From weapons and maps to game modes and thrilling features, we constantly strive to keep the gameplay <u>fresh and engaging</u>. Our team is committed to refining the game and delivering the <strong>best possible experience</strong> to our players.<br/><br/><strong>Pixel Royale 3D</strong> combines the nostalgic charm of pixel art with the adrenaline-pumping mechanics of <strong>FPS gameplay</strong>. Immerse yourself in a dynamic world where bullets fly, strategies unfold, and the thrill of victory awaits. Are you ready to jump into action? Gear up, lock and load, and experience the chaos of <strong>Pixel Royale 3D</strong>!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Air War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2852280/World_Air_War/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2852280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an exhilarating journey into the heart of aerial warfare with World Air War, where the skies are your battleground and adrenaline is your constant companion. Commandeer powerful fighter planes as you take on the role of a seasoned pilot thrust into the midst of a high-stakes conflict for air superiority. Your mission: to soar through the clouds, engage enemy aircraft, and reclaim control of vital military installations from hostile forces. Brace yourself for pulse-pounding dogfights, execute tactical maneuvers with precision, and experience the rush of airborne combat like never before.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
- **Epic Aerial Battles:** Engage in epic confrontations amidst the vast expanse of the sky, where every maneuver counts and victory hangs in the balance.<br>
- **Three Thrilling Game Modes:**<br>
   - **Pacific War:** Dive into the chaos of the Pacific theater, where the clash of mighty air fleets shapes the course of history.<br>
   - **WWII Air Combat:** Relive the iconic battles of World War II, where bravery and skill will determine the fate of nations.<br/>
   - **Avatar Fight:** Unleash your creativity and customize your avatar, then take to the skies in electrifying one-on-one duels against other players.<br/>
- **Immersive Cockpit View:** Experience the action from the pilot's perspective with a dynamic camera angle that puts you right in the cockpit, providing unparalleled immersion and intensity.<br/>
<br/>
Prepare to soar, strategize, and seize victory in World Air War, where the sky is your domain and aerial supremacy awaits the boldest of pilots.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Village Farm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2852290/Village_Farm/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2852290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to "Village Farm," where the art of farming meets the thrill of strategic gaming! Step into the boots of a farmer with a mission to cultivate your land to its fullest potential before the sun sets. Time is your most precious resource, so every decision counts as you race against the clock to maximize your harvest.<br>
<br>
Prepare to be captivated by a gaming experience that seamlessly blends practical farming with delightful challenges. Each level presents a unique puzzle, testing your intuition and logic as you strategically plant crops to optimize your yield.<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br>
- **Over 50 Exciting Levels:** Dive into a world of endless challenges, with each level offering new and dynamic obstacles to overcome.<br>
- **Experience Farm Ownership:** Feel the satisfaction of managing your own virtual farm, where every decision shapes the outcome of your harvest.<br/>
- **Race Against the Clock:** Feel the adrenaline rush as you work against time to meet deadlines and achieve your farming goals.<br/>
<br/>
Hone your farming skills, and immerse yourself in the beauty of agriculture. "Village Farm" promises an unforgettable gaming experience that entertains, educates, and keeps you coming back for more. Are you ready to cultivate success and reap the rewards?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party Friends</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2639500/Party_Friends/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From the charming Farm to the icy thrills of the Winter Resort, and from the sun-soaked Beach to the enchanting depths of the Forest, get ready for a whirlwind of fun, laughter, and competition!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639500/extras/steam-2.gif?t=1710511265"><br/><br/>Grab your friends and family because Party Friends supports both single-player and local multiplayer modes with Remote Play Together support for up to 4 players. Challenge your loved ones in friendly competitions that will have you laughing, strategizing, and celebrating victory together. Easy-to-learn gameplay ensures that everyone can join in on the fun, making it an excellent addition to any social event. Plus, the stunning, colorful visuals will leave a lasting impression on players of all ages.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639500/extras/steam-1.gif?t=1710511265"><br/><br/>Get ready to unleash your inner party animal and embark on a joyous adventure with Party Friends. It's time to create unforgettable memories, share moments of hilarity, and establish yourself as the life of the party. <br/><br/>Let the games begin!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcast - A New Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1013140/Outcast__A_New_Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							20 years after the award-winning action adventure hit, Outcast, pioneered the genre of non-linear open-world games, the long-awaited sequel sees Cutter Slade return to the spectacular alien world of Adelpha. Resurrected by the almighty Yods, he has returned to find the Talans enslaved, the world stripped of its natural resources, and his own past intertwining with the invading robot forces. It's up to him to go on a mission and save the planet again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/flight_8mb.gif?t=1710511218"><br/><br/>The original team behind Outcast 1 has reunited to create this fascinating world, full of dangerous creatures and home to the Talan people – an ancient culture whose fate has become inextricably linked with earth since the events of the first game. You play as Cutter Slade, ex-Navy SEAL, sporting the same dry wit he had back in the 90s – however, the world around him has changed and eventually, so will he.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/combat01_6mb.gif?t=1710511218"><br/> <br/>To save Adelpha, you will … <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>use your jetpack to jump, air-dash, glide, and quickly traverse the fantastic in-game open world <br/></li><li>combine dozens of different modules to create your own personal weapon for taking down the robot invaders <br/></li><li>have total control to approach the story at your own pace in this non-linear world <br/></li><li>explore the world without boundaries, discover hidden temples and dangerous wildlife <br/></li><li>get familiar with the Talan culture while helping them free their villages and gain access to ancient Talan powers that use forces of nature to destroy your enemies <br/></li><li>experience a beautiful, hand-crafted world accompanied by an epic soundtrack by Outcast's original composer, Lennie Moore </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/combat02.gif?t=1710511218"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Sweet Floating in the Void</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2738740/My_Sweet_Floating_in_the_Void/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							# Immerse yourself in My Sweet Floating in the void!<br/><br/>The Game is a philosophical journey toward the betterment of one's being; it is advancement, evolution and rebirth. The more we advance, facing and overcoming the obstacles in our lives, the more we improve ourselves, subsequently achieving a reward, a satisfaction of being, what is called happiness by many!<br/>Each section consists of a labyrinthine system of arrows and numbers; to unlock each section you will have to follow an arrow path to its finish line (remembering the sequence of numbers on your path) and complete each puzzle through a number pad.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738740/extras/My_Sweet_Floating_In_The_Void_24p.jpg?t=1710507235"><br/><br/>To advance and move forward, you will also have to discover the meaning of each symbol and color so that you can complete the puzzles and access all areas of the game. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738740/extras/My_Sweet_Floating_In_The_Void_35p.jpg?t=1710507235"><br/><br/>Get carried away by a new and unique gaming experience for your mind, completely Retro graphics and style, a player control system that is nothing short of unique and equally ingenious, accompanied by extremely strange and difficult Rebuses where not only intellect will be needed to complete them, but also a good memory!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738740/extras/My_Sweet_Floating_In_The_Void_7p.jpg?t=1710507235"><br/><br/>+ GAME PECULIARITIES +<br/><br/>° The player will always be able to float throughout the game without ever falling below the point where he is suspended, except if he ends up in an area marked by a purple border, in which case he will fall by accessing or in the area below, or by teleporting to the next section.<br/>° It contains a labyrinthine rebus system never seen before, that the player will have to complete to unlock the following areas through the interaction of a particular and bizarre numeric keypad (which will also often be decipherable).<br/>° Graphically, the game is totally made with basic color textures and, within many areas, there are many psychedelic parts to make it decidedly more particular, original and captivating.<br/>° The game contains 6 game worlds, each with its own graphic and artistic theme. As you complete more sections, you will be able to return to previous worlds in order to access newly unlocked areas.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738740/extras/My_Sweet_Floating_In_The_Void_9p.jpg?t=1710507235"><br/><br/>+ REPRESENTATION OF GAME WORLDS +<br/><br/>White World:<br/>A strange portal that will take you to a new dimension.<br/><br/>Grey world:<br/>The beginning of the mystery or the end of something... a limbo in which you are sometimes without actually being there, that takes us and sends us further, finally leading us inexorably to itself.<br/><br/>Green World:<br/>Inspired by nature, it is definitely the most structurally weird and psychedelic world; it offers more vegetation and color, along with as many puzzles that will engage the player to make the most of their memory to complete all the puzzles and discover all the secrets.<br/><br/>Orange World:<br/>A arid, desert world, where the few central cubic structures (including those outside) are full of charm and mystery. They will lead you on strange paths and offer you extremely difficult puzzles.<br/><br/>Red World:<br/>A part of the game that approaches an artistically oriental theme, with very complex puzzles that can only be completed by looking beyond the traditional logic. It will offer you a slow descent (or fall) towards something that is there, but until the end it keeps us hidden among the green and bright structures of which it is composed, hiding the occult to itself and to everyone.<br/><br/>Blue World:<br/>Cubes that intertwine logic and mystery, broken castles that offer a new vision of their path and that, thanks to the snow, offer cold and dispersive puzzles, where the common logic will not be enough to complete them, but also a real change of perspective.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738740/extras/My_Sweet_Floating_In_The_Void_36p.jpg?t=1710507235"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreamland</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2544880/Dreamland/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2544880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In Dreamland, you can create personalized avatars that represent your virtual identity within the game. you can explore a vast and visually stunning virtual environment filled with captivating landscapes, fantastical creatures, and intriguing challenges.<br>
Online Adventure<br>
Some games in Dreamland are very difficult. If you encounter difficult levels during the game, you can invite friends to work together to overcome them.<br>
The challenges you will face<br>
• Experience the horror and danger of zombies in ShootTheZombie and OtherShore<br>
• Defeat the evil cowboy in the town in the WesternRanger<br>
• Playing the adventurer in DungeonHunter to explore unknown underground castles<br/>
• Break into the dangerous laboratory in GunHunter and defeat the evil organization<br/>
• Use watermelon and cars to eliminate the threatening enemy in CrazyThrowing<br/>
• Evade the traps scattered throughout LostMaze and find the correct exit<br/>
• Experience real live online shooting battles on ShootingSquare<br/>
• Dream World has now launched 19 different styles of game scenes, including social games, PVP games, and PVE games<br/>
Game List<br/>
Home,Lobby,TheOtherShore,ShootingSquare,TeamBrawl,DesertTown,UndergroundPalace.SpaceSquare,ShootTheZombie,IndividualBrawl,TeamCap,WesternRanger,GunHunter, DungeonHunter,MazeTrial, CrazyThrowing, LoopsFly, LostMaze, GunDuel.<br/>
Dreamland is a world full of imagination and adventure, waiting for you to explore and discover. Join us and embark on your adventure!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhythm &amp; Beats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2858500/Rhythm__Beats/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2858500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>MAIN FEATURES</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play to any audio from your PC including streamed audio</li><li>Add your own .wav/.mp3 audio to play to</li><li>Record your own music with ability to add your own sound effects for the drum sounds</li><li> 5 levels of difficulty, </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Can you keep up with the Rhythm</strong></h2>Play to the rhythm of your favorites songs! You can play to any Live audio sound playing on your PC or jam to downloaded songs.  For the creative type you can add any sound effects to the drums and record your own songs.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PJ Masks Power Heroes: Mighty Alliance</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2223440/PJ_Masks_Power_Heroes_Mighty_Alliance/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2223440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2223440/extras/PJM2_ENG_SteamBanner_v1_1.png?t=1710494683"><br/><br/>Catboy, Owlette, and Gekko are teaming up with An Yu, Newton Star, Ice Cub, Lilyfay, and Bastet to form a Mighty Alliance.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2223440/extras/Team_Up_GIF.gif?t=1710494683"><br/><br/>After a big accident at PJ Power Q scatters valuable pieces of technology and gems across Earth, these extraordinary heroes must rebuild it. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2223440/extras/PJM2_ENG_SteamBanner_v1_2.png?t=1710494683"><br/><br/>Land, sky or sea, the Explorider will get your Power Heroes there.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2223440/extras/Drive_And_Discover_GIF.gif?t=1710494683"><br/><br/>Hop into the Explorider and begin the night-time adventure scouring the deserted streets in The City. You will discover more while exploring the bamboo forests, secret caves, and the sacred temple in Mystery Mountain. Then slide through the Ice World to reach the snowy caves searching for the lost parts. But be quick! Before they get into the wrong hands. Romeo, Luna Girl, and Night Ninja are never too far away and are always ready to cause havoc. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2223440/extras/PJM2_ENG_SteamBanner_v1_3.png?t=1710494683"><br/><br/>Use unique abilities, collect gems, discover secrets, unlock hidden masks, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2223440/extras/BeExtraordinary_GIF.gif?t=1710494683"><br/><br/>Together, these extraordinary kids are bigger and better. Use their unique abilities, from super speed to snowballs, to stop the baddies. Collect gems, discover secrets, unlock hidden masks, and more.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2223440/extras/PJM2_ENG_SteamBanner_v1_4.png?t=1710494683"><br/><br/>Accessible features: simple controls and easy interactions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2223440/extras/FunforeveryHero_GIF.gif?t=1710494683"><br/><br/>You know, night-time is the right time to fight crime! So, leap into this side-scrolling platform adventure, stop the pesky villains in their tracks, and fix the PJ Power Q. You have the power to become a hero.<br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>TEAM UP </strong>- Join Catboy, Owlette, Gekko, An Yu, Newton Star, Ice Cub, Lilyfay, and Bastet.<br/></li><li><strong>DRIVE AND DISCOVER</strong> – Land, sky or sea, the Explorider will get your Power Heroes there.<br/></li><li><strong>BE EXTRAORDINARY</strong> – Use unique abilities, collect gems, discover secrets, unlock hidden masks, and more.<br/></li><li><strong>FUN FOR EVERY HERO</strong> – Accessible features: simple controls and easy interactions.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gnosis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2764110/Gnosis/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Curiosity. Exploration. The opening of the mind, through the process of discovery and revelation. Through whatever means you have found yourself here,  you are welcomed, encouraged, to stay.<br/><br/>By finding this, you have self-selected for a rare program intended to test you. In the course of this examination, you will encounter questions and scenarios designed to open your mind to new possibilities and perspectives. Will you heed the call, and explore what potential may yet await you?<br/><br/>_____________________________________________________________________________________<br/><br/>This is my first ever game, so hello. This game is a love letter to the era of Flash horror, which I used to indulge in heavily. This is, however, not a horror experience. Instead, it is what I shall call "Bizarre" - taking from another medium, a "Bizarre" work is one that implicates a wider world of magic and ritual. It is often, but not necessarily, presented in a dark and atmospheric manner, with a particular focus on narrative and mystery. I repeat: this is not a conventional horror experience. There are no jumpscares, there are no creatures, there is no survival or opposition, and you are free - and encouraged - to explore as you like.<br/><br/>Here's a rough idea of what you're up for:<br/><br/><strong><u>GRAPHICS</u></strong><br/><br/>This experience is largely text-based, but it uses graphics throughout. Animated backgrounds are present throughout, and art is a central part of the experience at several points throughout. All art, static and animation, is hand-drawn, with a stylistic emphasis on muted tones, typically grayscale, and a sketchy or blotty appearance.<br/><br/><strong><u>GAMEPLAY</u></strong><br/><br/>Gameplay consists largely of point-and-click, particularly in a question-and-answer format. There are some typing sections as well. I made this on Ren.py, a visual novel engine, and brute forced it into being more interactive. At several points, you will be asked to take a critical eye to what you are being presented with. Your success or failure in doing so, and the answers you provide, will lead to one of about 60 permutations of ending. Most of the gameplay will remain the same, although it will occasionally remark on your actions.<br/><br/>Skipping through chunks of dialogue, the game can still take an hour to finish. While you can make it run faster, I wouldn't recommend it. The replay value at launch consists of achieving different endings, including the 'ideal' one, and exploring different choices and what the game might react to. If this is not the sort of game you enjoy, I welcome you to try, but cannot advise you to expect something radically different.<br/><br/><strong><u>REQUIREMENTS</u></strong><br/><br/>This game was developed on Ren.py 7.4.11.2266, and should be compatible with most OS platforms of relatively decent modernity. As the game is largely point and click mechanics with premade art, it does not render much, and should be able to run fine on even low-performance computers. Renpy's release for 7.4 states that OpenGL 2, DirectX 9, OpenGL ES 2, or WebGL are required to run programs on that version, if any clarification is needed.<br/><br/><strong><u><br/>ACCESSIBILITY</u></strong><br/><br/>This game's graphics are predominantly in grayscale, featuring white text on dark black and gray backgrounds. At times, it will use purple text instead. At other times, there will be muted red and black on a gray background. So long as you are capable of distinguishing some color from no color at all, the game will be functional for you. While recent Renpy builds have included a self-voicing feature by default, the visual component of this experience is important, and having eyesight is necessary to progress certain sections.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guardian</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2817180/Guardian/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A Human League city has suffered a demonic invasion. Heroes protect the city and fight back against the demons.You need to protect your base and destroy the enemy base.Own hero has four magic, w, s, e, d keys to release magic attack, destroy the enemy's main base you will win to enter the next level. You can also click on the four magic icons on the right to release the magic.The magic attacks are very powerful, and the enemy heroes will get stronger and stronger. As long as the main base is not destroyed, the heroes will come back to life every once in a while.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
