<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Jurassic World Evolution 2: Cretaceous Predator Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2610980/Jurassic_World_Evolution_2_Cretaceous_Predator_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Introduce four ferocious new predators to your parks with Jurassic World Evolution 2: Cretaceous Predator Pack. Manage and control these striking dinosaurs as they fight for dominance in your parks and search for their next meal. Unveil the true power of the Cretaceous period to your park guests.<h2 class="bb_tag">Welcome the following extraordinary species:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Gigantoraptor, whose name means “Giant Thief”, is the largest known Oviraptorosaur from the Late Cretaceous era. Featuring an impressive coat of feathers and large elongated legs, the Gigantoraptor can maintain speed for an extended period of time as it chases down its prey.<br/></li><li>Concavenator has a distinctive narrow hump, formed by two extremely large vertebrae, making its profile instantly recognisable. This agile theropod from the Early Cretaceous period is a fierce hunter that will make an exciting addition to your parks.<br/></li><li>Utahraptor, one of the largest dromaeosaurs, is an intelligent and ruthless predator that is sure to impress your guests. With a stunning feather coat and large scythe-like claws, this predator, hailing from Utah, will stop any prey in its tracks.<br/></li><li>Tarbosaurus, is a gargantuan hunter inspired by the Universal Pictures, Amblin Entertainment and DreamWorks Animation Netflix Show, Jurassic World Camp Cretaceous: Hidden Adventure. This unique Tyrannosaurine theropod will need a secure enclosure to protect guests from its powerful jaws.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEVI</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2230650/TEVI/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FZ9KrdFvNRK" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/JoinUsOnDC.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Action-Packed_Combo_System.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/戰鬥動圖.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>The protagonist Tevi is nimble and agile, wielding both her trusty dagger and an oversized wrench for dishing out melee damage in style. Alongside her, companions Celia and Sable manifest as two floating orbitars, ready to unleash a variety of ranged offensive and supportive magic in battle. Adapt your combat style to suit any situation and bring down foes with flashy, dazzling combos!<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Thrilling_Boss_Battles.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Boss.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Every boss fight is a unique challenge requiring different strategies to tackle, all while you dodge their attacks and look for openings to counter-attack. <br/>As bosses change phases, their attack and bullet patterns become increasingly challenging, and they can even unleash devastating ultimates. Continual offense can submit bosses into a vulnerable BREAK state, during which you can deal massive bursts of damage.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Myriad_Abilities,_Equipment,_and_Exploration.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/badge.jpg?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Scattered across the the expansive world, there are over 300 different items and pieces of equipment waiting to be discovered. These items can enhance your abilities or introduce new ones, allowing you to find more methods of navigating the world and finding secrets. A cornucopia of equippable sigils can be freely configured to create builds tailored to your preferences and playstyle.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/A_Rich,_Expansive_Fantasy_World.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/場景6.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Dive into the vibrant world of Az, in which you will discover various towns, regions, peoples, histories, and civilizations, each with their own tale to tell. Along the way, you'll meet a large cast of strange and colorful characters. As their tales unfold and intertwine, you'll be drawn into a tale full of adventure, friendship, mysteries, and danger... <br/><br/>Get ready to embark on an unforgettable adventure, writing your own epic journey alongside Tevi!<br/><br/><a href="https://youtu.be/psxior_WswQ" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/角色介紹.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tevi（VA: Lynn）<br/></li><li>Celia（VA: Yoko Hikasa）<br/></li><li>Sable（VA: Natsumi Fujiwara）<br/></li><li>Zema（VA: Tomokazu Sugita）<br/></li><li>Vena（VA: Rie Kugimiya）</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Suika - Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2671970/My_Suika__Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A fun watermelon merge puzzle game!<br>
<br>
Think you can get 3000 points in this addictive watermelon puzzle game?<br>
<br>
Combine various matching fruits to help Kyo gather watermelons! Unlock new game modes and new fruit skins by obtaining high scores. Compete against other players on the global leaderboards!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call to Arms - Gates of Hell: Liberation</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2447590/Call_to_Arms__Gates_of_Hell_Liberation/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<strong>“Soldiers, Sailors, and Airmen of the Allied Expeditionary Force: you are about to embark upon the Great Crusade!”<br/>This DLC introduces the western front action in 1944, featuring the US faction, as well as German western front content.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/01Sherman.gif?t=1701279518"><br/><br/>Be among the first to scale the Atlantic wall and fight your way through the Bocage. <br/>Be the spearhead that breaks the stalemate in the battle of the Bulge. <br/>Re-live the rush to the Rhine bridge, on the road into the heart of Germany!<br/><br/>Or, fight for the Wehrmacht and be the one that leads the counterattacks, the one that stops the breakout. In other words; be the one that defends “Fortress Europe” facing all the classic dilemmas that come with it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/02Beach.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Single Player</h2>The single player campaigns focus on four legendary western front units: the “Liberation” campaign has the 2nd Rangers and the 3rd Armored Division on the US side. Beside 6 single player missions, this DLC also offers 4 skirmishes for the US faction, which are part of the campaign storyline.<br/>In all of the missions, you will find yourself in intense battles on iconic battlegrounds, recreated to the last detail; get a taste of the bitter fighting against fanatical opposition, liberating western Europe step by hellish step. The action will be intense and the immersion will be up there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/03Nebel.gif?t=1701279518"><br/><br/>The German campaign,  “Festung Europa”, has the 3rd Fallschirmjäger division and 116th Panzer division on the German side in 6 intense and compelling missions.<br/>Be the one that commands the Wehrmacht forces on the western front from Normandy to the last battles in the Ruhr pocket. In the German campaign you will enjoy a lot of new content as well! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/04Maps.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer</h2>“Liberation” adds the USA to multiplayer with 20 brand new western front MP maps, and all of the new weapons, vehicles and tanks; it also adds a new German late war doctrine.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/05Mist.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Conquest</h2>For conquest, 25 western front maps are included. These, like other maps, use the unique set of assets we have created to immerse you in the western front atmosphere. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/06wespe.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Visuals</h2>Liberation pushes the boundary of the visuals of the Gates of Hell universe to a new standard, with hundreds of highly detailed environment models, improved destruction for buildings and beautiful environments. To ensure the historical accuracy of our content, we have collaborated with WW2 Armor in Florida, who provided us with vast amounts of valuable documentation and knowledge.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/07Logo.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Content</h2>The Liberation DLC contains:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>10 US single player missions, including 4 US skirmishes<br/></li><li>6 German single player missions<br/></li><li>150+  new US and German vehicles, cannon, ships, aircraft and tanks<br/></li><li>50 new small arms<br/></li><li>500+ new humanskins<br/></li><li>20 new MP maps<br/></li><li>25 new DCG (Conquest) maps<br/></li><li>500+ new editor assets for the western European theater.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MULLER-POWELL PRINCIPLE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2155770/THE_MULLERPOWELL_PRINCIPLE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FeY9JWyTaAm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_discord.png?t=1701271403"/></a><br/><br/>It is a sci-fi story that takes place in the near future. You are Harry Herman, an employee of Delta Laboratories who researches interdimensional traveling. You had been participating in a project that was supposed to benefit all humanity, but something went wrong. Through the gameplay, you will solve various physics-based puzzles using an energy-manipulating weapon, travel across space and time to explore surrealistic universes and find out the dark truth about this project and your connection to it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_gameplay.png?t=1701271403"><br/>Solve various puzzles and trick enemies using physics interactions and your special tool - the Portable Energy Manipulator. <br/><br/><strong>PHYSICS PUZZLES &amp; INTERACTIVE ENVIRONMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/gameplay_physics.gif?t=1701271403"><br/><br/>Many objects in the game can be picked up, brought somewhere, or manipulated in other ways. Whether it's a computer terminal, a box you can carry, or a simple mug on a table. Explore various interactive environments to find clues and return to the riddle with a solution, which in some cases may be several. Nothing was made for you to solve, there's no cube dispenser or an obvious exit door at the end. It's all for you to figure out.<br/><br/><strong>PORTABLE ENERGY MANIPULATOR</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/gif_photongun.gif?t=1701271403"><br/><br/>The device you carry throughout the game can absorb different energy types from the environment and use them to perform various tasks.<br/><br/>Absorbing energy from a particular source will give the gun its’ properties. The heat energy from fire and radiators will melt glass, security cameras can be blinded by a beam of light, and for powering generators, you can take hazardous radiation from toxic puddles scattered across Delta Labs facilities. And of course, you will make an encounter with the quantum entanglement energy - the mysterious power capable of opening rifts between worlds. <br/><br/>Apart from solving environmental puzzles, your device can also be used against various creatures you'll meet in parallel dimensions. Most of the time you can't defeat your enemies; instead, you can use the Manipulator to outsmart or suspend them. Some enemies can be frozen in place using the force field energy, while others are sensitive to light and can be distracted by shooting a beam at it in the distance. You will require more advanced strategies and combining various energy types to pass them.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_story.png?t=1701271403"><br/>You find yourself in one of Delta Labs' off-world research facilities in an unknown dimension that looks more like a crashing-down laboratory. Your old friends Eugene and Alex try to connect with you shortly, and with their help, you start a journey through various dimensions. You will learn different physics interactions and meet unusual creatures on your way home. Along this, you have to unveil the mysteries of this project and your past. <br/><br/>Experience a non-linear story where your choice always matters. Can you get to the bottom of this, or just try to escape? Who to listen? Who to trust? Which side will you take? And will you finally “break the Principle”? That depends entirely on you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_setting.png?t=1701271403"><br/>Make your way back to Earth through mysterious parallel dimensions littered with puzzles and secrets, uncover mysterious connections between the worlds you visit, and reveal the dark truth about Delta Labs and your involvement with them. Dare to explore?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_features.png?t=1701271403"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Solve various physics-based puzzles<br/></li><li>Unique gameplay mechanics that involve an energy-manipulating weapon <br/></li><li>A mix of sci-fi with surreal and esoteric themes makes the game setting a unique design. Most of the time you'll spend in bizarre alien dimensions<br/></li><li>Deeply thought-out story and lore. Each location and each character in the game has its own story revealed through various notes, environmental narratives, and characters' conversations.<br/></li><li>The game features multiple endings that can be achieved through different choices </li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn around immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Other</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destiny 2: Season of the Wish Silver Bundle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2218002/Destiny_2_Season_of_the_Wish_Silver_Bundle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2218002/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Purchase the Season of the Wish Silver Bundle and receive the 'Brave Explorer' Legendary Emote along with 1700 Silver (1,000 + 700 bonus Silver) which you can use to purchase Season of the Wish, cosmetics, and more! <br>
<br>
Visit the Seasons tab in-game to use your Silver and buy Season of the Wish.<br>
<br>
To unlock your new Emote, visit the Special Deliveries Terminal in the Tower.<br/>
<br/>
One-time purchase only available during Season of the Wish. Silver is an in-game currency used at the Eververse store.<br/>
<br/>
Season of the Wish not included with purchase.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead by Daylight - Chucky Chapter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2656010/Dead_by_Daylight__Chucky_Chapter/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Main_Banner.png?t=1701272232"><br/> <br/>Meet your new best friend ‘til the end. Dead by Daylight: Chucky brings an iconic horror legend into The Fog with a new Killer: <strong>The Good Guy - Chucky</strong>. Purchasing this add-on unlocks an <strong>exclusive Charm: Good Guys Box.</strong> <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Killer_Power.gif?t=1701272232"><h2 class="bb_tag">CHUCKY</h2>Viciously cruel with a cutting sense of humor, Chucky is a brutally effective killing machine. Using his diminutive frame to his advantage, he’ll pop up when Survivors least expect it, chasing them down and introducing them to his trusty weapons.<br/> <br/><strong>Chucky’s Power: Playtime's Over </strong><br/><br/>The Good Guy is the first Killer in Dead by Daylight to feature a third-person camera.   <br/><br/><strong>Special Ability – Hidey-Ho Mode:</strong> When Chucky enters Hidey-Ho Mode, he becomes Undetectable and generates Map-wide footfalls, disorienting Survivors. Though Hidey-Ho mode can be entered at any time, it does have a cooldown.   <br/> <br/><strong>Special Ability – Scamper:</strong> While in Hidey-Ho Mode, Chucky can Scamper under a downed Pallet or through a Window, allowing him to quickly gain ground.   <br/><br/><strong>Special Ability – Slice &amp; Dice:</strong> While in Hidey-Ho Mode, Chucky can sprint and lunge forward to Slice &amp; Dice Survivors. This attack can be held, but Chucky will be unable to do anything else during this time. If a Survivor tries to Vault a Window or Pallet while you’re charging a Slice &amp; Dice attack, Chucky can quickly chain into a Scamper.   <br/> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Killer_Perks.png?t=1701272232"><br/><br/>Chucky comes with <strong>3 new perks.</strong><br/><br/> <h2 class="bb_tag">Hex: Two Can Play</h2>When a Survivor Stuns or Blinds you a number of times, a Dull Totem becomes a Hex Totem. When that Hex is active, Survivors who stun or blind you are Blinded for 4 seconds. The Hex effects persist as long as the related Hex Totem is standing.<h2 class="bb_tag">Friends ‘Til the End</h2>You become Obsessed with one Survivor. When you Hook a Survivor that is not the Obsession, the Obsession becomes Exposed and reveals their Aura for a brief duration. If you Hook the Obsession, a random Survivor will scream, reveal their position, and become the Obsession.<h2 class="bb_tag">Batteries Included</h2>When within the vicinity of a completed Generator, gain Haste. The movement speed boost lingers for a brief duration after you leave the Generator’s vicinity.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Exclusive_Item.png?t=1701272232"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXCLUSIVE CHAPTER ITEM: GOOD GUYS BOX</h2>The Chucky Chapter includes an exclusive item, the <strong>Good Guys Box Charm</strong>, only available as part of the DLC. Please note that this item cannot be purchased separately.<br/><br/><br/><i>His name is Charles Lee Ray. Chucky to his friends... You’ll be his friend ‘til the end, right?</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1701242352"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1701242352"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1701242352"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noctuary</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2143680/Noctuary/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/英文_大标题.png?t=1701331051"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/1奇光异彩_英文.png?t=1701331051"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/英文_主角介绍.png?t=1701331051"><br/><br/>Noctuary is a dual-protagonist Visual Novel. Players can play the role of the duo, Fancia Dream and Alina Nightsong who have dreams of "becoming Arborangers who protect and serve everyone." Travel through the fairy-tale-like world as the duo, experience their lively daily adventures, and gradually encounter the life story of a mysterious girl who came down from the sky.<br/><br/>Meanwhile, don't forget to fight against the everpresent monsters—"Darkritters!" These dangerous enemies threaten the life of Illuminators constantly. Sharpen your fighting skills, defeat ferocious monsters and ensure peace in your community!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/2华丽战斗_英文.png?t=1701331051"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/ARPG01_英文.gif?t=1701331051"><br/>During your adventure, you will fight against various enemies. You can defeat them with a cascade of powerful combo attacks!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/ARPG02_英文.gif?t=1701331051"><br/>The two main characters master different skills and present various fighting styles, which allows you to win a battle in whichever method you choose. Switch between the two girls in battles to cope with enemies' attacks and finish them off with the powerful On-field Switch skill and the Synergy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/3任务选择_英文.png?t=1701331051"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/Quest01_英文.gif?t=1701331051"><br/>Embark on various missions within Inlixaland and become a unique "Arboranger."! In addition to the main storyline that spans several tens of hours, there are also over 20 side routes and quests featuring different stories and characters to explore. Join forces with diverse Illuminators as companions, cultivate relationships, and earn adventure rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/4祝福标题_英文.png?t=1701331051"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/Blessing01_英文.gif?t=1701331051"><br/>The friendships and blessings you harvest along the journey will strengthen you in battle. Feel free to combine the "Blessing Petals" that are embedded with features of different characters to customize your battle style. In addition, there are many other well-designed cultivation systems that are ready for you to explore!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/感谢尾图_英文.png?t=1701331051"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retro Commander</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/338820/Retro_Commander/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/338820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/338820/extras/icon_and_text_v05_-_600x195px.png?t=1700862195"><br/>Retro Commander is a <strong>post-apocalyptic</strong> real-time strategy wargame (RTS). Take command and fight it out in a world where a cataclysmic timeline has transpired on Mother Earth. Wage wars solo, against the AI, or take on your gaming comrades and friends in cross-platform multiplayer matches. Form teams and clans and fight co-op style with the AI and other players for ultimate victory.<br/><br/>As opposed to other real-time strategy game, Retro Commander tries to focus on both, a fun <strong>single player</strong> and a thrilling <strong>multiplayer</strong> experience. The game strives to be easy to learn with a modern user interface. Single player comes with skirmish matches against the AI as well as a comic-based <strong>story campaign</strong>. Multiplayer can be played cross-platform and includes a ranking and rating system.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u>Post-Apocalyptic</u>: Real-time strategy (RTS) played in a post-apocalyptic timeline on Mother Earth. The environment includes day-night cycles, rain, snow, wind and solar flare activity.<br/></li><li><u>Story Campaign</u>: Deep campaign and story line of humanity after a cataclysmic event. Factions come with their own specialized <strong>technologies</strong> such as stealth, robots, drones or shields.<br/></li><li><u>Single &amp; Multiplayer</u>: A challenging AI for both single and multiplayer matches with co-op play. Cross-platform multiplayer including <strong>LAN</strong>/internet. ONLINE play comes with an award and rating system.<br/></li><li><u>Play Modes</u>: In addition to regular skirmish matches, the game supports missions such as elimination, survival, <strong>capture the flag</strong>, defense and <strong>battle royale</strong>. Available in both single and multiplayer also are escort and rescue missions.<br/></li><li><u>Structures &amp; Troops</u>: Common troops for land, sea and air warfare is available to all factions. Specialized elements such as stealth, shields, <strong>EMP</strong> weapons, nukes, <strong>portals</strong>, orbital weapons, assimilator and other troops and structures provide for additional variety.<br/></li><li><u>Research</u>: A <strong>tech tree</strong> and research options enable to build specialized structures and troops. A <strong>Tech Snatcher</strong> can be used to steal enemy technology.<br/></li><li><u>Modding</u>: A map editor is included allowing for player-modded maps including player-modded campaigns. All elements including troops, structures, as well as graphics and sound effects, can be modded if desired.</li></ul><br/>Although some troops are shared, the game is trying not to be a generic RTS-games. There are <strong>faction-specific technologies</strong> each with their strengths and weaknesses.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u>GRA Technology</u>: gives access to <strong>stealth</strong> and cloaking. Included are cloaked agents and spies as well as bombers with EMP and nuclear weapons. Available also are snipers and heavy airlifts. Can build uranium fabricators.<br/></li><li><u>ELC Technology</u>: provides <strong>robots</strong>, <strong>airships</strong> and robo dogs. Available also are a mechanic and heavy airlift. Can build stationary EMP-field generators.<br/></li><li><u>IDB Technology</u>: provides <strong>hovertanks</strong>, <strong>drones</strong> including EMP-field drones and drones equipped with napalm weapons. Can build fusion generators for power.<br/></li><li><u>Mayan Technology</u>: consists of <strong>decoy</strong> capabilities. Included are hologram tanks, transformers, dogs and dolphins. Can build <strong>portals</strong>.<br/></li><li><u>Ancient Technology</u>: provides <strong>shields</strong>, EMP soldiers, assimilators and napalm tanks. Can build matter fabricators.</li></ul><br/><strong>Free vs Paid (DLC or in-game)</strong>: The free version includes unlimited access to over 12+ multiplayer scenarios and Chapter 01 of the single player campaign. Purchasing the DLC <strong>"All Maps &amp; Modding"</strong> grants full access to the game. It includes everything for single player including the story campaign, skirmishing against the AI, ONLINE multiplayer or LAN-play with friends and family.<br/><br/><strong>No DRM</strong>: There is no DRM in the game. You <strong>don't need to connected to the internet</strong> to play single player games or the campaign. You don't need to be logged in to play LAN games either. You don't need to login either for WAN games (locally hosted games over the internet), but you will have to work out your router settings and do the appropriate port-forwarding so your friends can connect from remote.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Stars And Time</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1677310/In_Stars_And_Time/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FZzFSRUBXEC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/discordbanner620.gif?t=1701180941"/></a><br/><br/><strong>What would you do if you were forced to relive your failures over and over again?</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam5_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> tells the story of Siffrin and their adventurer friends—a found family bound together by fate in order to end the tyrannical reign of an evil king. But as victory is just within the party’s grasp, a tragedy occurs, the clock resets, and <strong>they have to do it all again</strong>. <br/><br/>As Siffrin’s the only one who notices this loop, each new start wears away at his cheerful veneer, yet he keeps going in hopes he can end this temporal tragedy once and for all.<br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> is a <strong>time-looping RPG adventure</strong>. With each loop, Siffrin gains a new perspective on the world around them, opening up new solutions to puzzles and allowing them to make better choices in conversation. Equip memories as armor, pray to the Change God to improve your team’s capabilities each loop, and challenge deadly foes to Rock, Paper, Scissors as Siffrin seeks the truth.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam4_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Our Adventurers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Siffrin (he/they):</strong> Stressed, depressed, and under duress. (Don’t worry about it. They’re doing fine.) The punmaster protagonist of our neverending tale.<br/></li><li><strong>Mirabelle (she/her):</strong> A caring and nervous housemaiden mysteriously blessed by the god she so ardently follows.<br/></li><li><strong>Isabeau (he/him):</strong> Defender with a heart of gold. Cares dearly for his people and his friends.<br/></li><li><strong>Odile (she/her):</strong> The mature and nonsensical researcher studying…something. (No, she will not tell you what it is.)<br/></li><li><strong>Bonnie (they/them):</strong> Wait a minute, who brought this kid along???</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Save the world through the power of Rock, Paper, Scissors in <strong>strategic turn-based RPG</strong> combat encounters.<br/></li><li>Ignore the limits of time and space to <strong>fix your past mistakes</strong> by repeating the same two days over and over again.<br/></li><li>Equip the <strong>memories you have of your friends</strong> to make your party stronger in combat. <br/></li><li><strong>Watch the fate of this world unfold</strong> as you escape the twists and turns of this endless(???) loop.<br/></li><li>Eat <strong>samossas</strong> with your friends!<br/></li><li>Get heckled by a <strong>cheeky ethereal being of infinite starlight</strong>.<br/></li><li>Pray to a god for good luck in your travels. <strong>You’re gonna need it.</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam2_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/>If any of this interests you, you might also want to play the game’s initial prototype, <u><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1691420/START_AGAIN_a_prologue/" rel="" target="_blank">START AGAIN START AGAIN START AGAIN: A Prologue</a></u>. While you don’t need to play it to understand In Stars and Time, it’s fun to see the game’s roots.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 5 Tactica</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2254740/Persona_5_Tactica/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join the Phantom Thieves as they lead an uprising of the heart! Assemble a team of beloved heroes in a brand-new story in this thrilling combat adventure set in Persona’s iconic universe. The Persona 5 Tactica: Digital Deluxe Edition includes the following content:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Repaint Your Heart Challenge Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Weapon Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Picaro Summoning Pack + Raoul Persona</li></ul><br/><strong>Ignite your heart— An emotional uprising begins!</strong><br/><br/>After a strange incident, the Phantom Thieves wander into a bizarre realm where its citizens are living under tyrannical oppression. Surrounded by a military group named Legionnaires, they find themselves in grave danger until a mysterious revolutionary named Erina rescues them and offers an enticing deal in exchange for their help. What truth lies behind Erina and the deal she offers to the Phantom Thieves?<br/><br/>Persona 5 Tactica features an all-new story, the return of fan-favorite characters, and brand-new allies and foes. Join the group as they lead an emotional revolution in this thrilling combat adventure!<br/><br/><strong>An Emotional Revolution</strong><br/>Lead an uprising of the heart in a brand-new storyline that takes place in Persona’s iconic universe.<br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Squad</strong><br/>Assemble a team of beloved heroes to fight oppressive armies in thrilling turn-based combat.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Combat</strong><br/>Overthrow your enemies with powerful Personas, an assortment of weapons, and wipe them out with style!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Early purchase bonus!</strong></h2><br/>Buy now to get the following digital bonuses:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Orpheus Picaro<br/></li><li>Izanagi Picaro</li></ul><br/>Additional Personas will become available to summon in-game. After becoming the Trickster's masks, picaro versions of two Personas will be added to the Persona Compendium.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucky Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2404510/Lucky_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2404510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Lucky Hero: A Fantasy Adventure Weaving Wisdom, Exploration, and Strategy! <br/><br/>Welcome to the world of "Lucky Hero"! This is a deckbuilder game that perfectly combines roguelike adventures and strategy. Engage in battles with a variety of enemies by spinning the wheel of fortune, collecting, and combining various symbols and skills!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2404510/extras/Character.gif?t=1701073211"><br/><br/><strong>Character：</strong><br/>3 distinct characters: the hefty Warrior, the elusive Assassin, and the enigmatic Summoner, offering varied gameplay experiences.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2404510/extras/En战士_9个片段2023108181391.gif?t=1701073211"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2404510/extras/En召唤师_6个片段20231081848273.gif?t=1701073211"><br/><br/><strong>Symbol：</strong><br/>Over 300 enigmatic symbols are to be collected. By purchasing and deleting them, you build your strategies against enemies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2404510/extras/2023-10-08_11-50-4920231081851524.gif?t=1701073211"><br/><br/><strong>Skill:</strong><br/>Over 30 active &amp; passive skills. When matched with appropriate symbols, skills leads to different builds.<br/><br/><strong>Enemy:</strong><br/>Unique enemies and Bosses with diverse abilities are to be challenged! They will relentlessly assail you. Some may hinder you in ways you are unable to expect. Observe, study, then beat them with your wisdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2404510/extras/2023-10-08_11-50-492023108185705.gif?t=1701073211"><br/><br/><strong>Area Effect:</strong><br/>Over 10 effects for different areas provide unique experiences for every run! Some positive area effects may lead to a less bumpy road, but a negative area effect often has rewards in store for the brave The decision is in your hands.<br/><br/><strong>Random Event:</strong><br/>The game teems with random events, providing a plethora of surprises and unforeseen developments. Will you stumble upon overnight riches or get stripped to bare bones? Are you daring enough to take a punt?<br/><br/>Navigate your journey with deliberation, collect gold, strategize your builds, vanquish formidable enemies, and liberate your kingdom! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2404510/extras/lkho_steam_store_asset_spin_effect_en.gif?t=1701073211"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Saga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1320140/Small_Saga/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Venture below the streets of London, and you will find the medieval kingdom of rats, mice, moles, squirrels, and shrews known as Rodentia.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G8.gif?t=1700830017"><br/><br/>If the rodents have a cardinal law, it is this: never attack a god. But Verm never had much respect for the rule of law. His tail was stolen by the Yellow God of Death, and now the mouse will have to fight all manner of beasts and titans on his quest to get it back.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G5.gif?t=1700830017"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G1.gif?t=1700830017"><br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Team up with a colorful cast of misfit rodents.<br/></li><li>Encounter awe-inspiring titans. Clash with a swashbuckling water vole, a pious lab rabbit, a poetry-spewing kraken, and many more.<br/></li><li>Meet the hideous vermin who run society, then overthrow them.<br/></li><li>Brandish your tiny weapons in strategic, turn-based combat. <br/></li><li>There is no grinding. Small Saga is a tightly-focused and boss-oriented adventure.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero's Adventure: Road to Passion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1948980/Heros_Adventure_Road_to_Passion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FFPnrtuXddA" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/JOIN_OUR_DISCORD.png?t=1700823813"/></a><br/><br/>In <i>Hero's Adventure:Road to Passion</i>, you commence your journey as an underdog in the tumultuous Jianghu - a vibrant world teeming with martial artists - and are met with a wide array of choices as you navigate your heroic saga. Whether it’s training under a battle-hardened warrior to become a master of martial arts, or following Taoist rituals to reach self-enlightenment, you’re the hero, and this is your adventure.<br/><br/><br/>Play 1.0 Now!<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>[Unexpected Encounters Await]</strong><br/><br/>Throughout your journey, you will run into scripted and unexpected encounters. Perhaps you'll cross paths with an ambitious lieutenant amidst a power struggle at a humble inn, or you’ll run into a retired kung fu master in a nameless village. These will be the experiences you will learn to expect in the ever-changing Jianghu.<br/><br/>Beware, each encounter might associate and change your relationship with the 30+ factions involved in the power struggle in this chaotic Martial World. And remember: every choice you make, every person you befriend (or offend), and every faction you engage will leave a mark.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/Sparring.gif?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[Become the Master of Martial Arts]</strong><br/><br/>Whether you're decoding ancient techniques off a forgotten scroll, or prefer training with a battle-hardened warrior, there’s no correct solution for mastering martial arts. Choose from a variety of weapon types and explore 300+ martial arts skills, the Jianghu will be yours to conquer.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/High-level_Martial_Arts.gif?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[Explore a Living, Breathing World]</strong><br/><br/>In this Wuxia simulator, you'll get to explore 80 cities and villages that bring wuxia to life. Witness how villagers go about their daily routines, and experience the rhythms of ancient Chinese cities.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/Nameless_Village.gif?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[Craft Your Narrative]</strong><br/><br/>To provide an experience where you can embody your own martial spirit, Hero’s Adventure has over 10 distinct endings. Whether you choose to be a noble swordsman, a guardian of the nation, or an agent of chaos, you'll find an ending that aligns with your chosen path in Hero's Adventure. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/武林霸主_1_.png?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[New features that are added in v1.0:]</strong><br/>- New bondable female characters, boosting the total number to 18<br/>- A Homestead system to better manage your recruited characters, inherit your Martial Art and weapons to another playthrough<br/>- 200+ new narrative encounters, and adjusted 400+ of the existing encounters<br/>- New Jianghu Event system ensures your adventure doesn’t end prematurely with major events<br/>- Added duel option against high-rank NPCs for a test of mettle.<br/>- Enhanced customization and upgrades for team characters.<br/>- Early supporters will discover a special accessory as a token of gratitude.<br/>- Controller and steam deck support.<br/>- Steam Workshop 2.0</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header_alt_assets_2.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astral Ascent</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1280930/Astral_Ascent/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Astral Ascent is a 2D platformer rogue-lite game set in a modern fantasy world. As one of 4 Heroes with very different personalities, you must escape from <i>the Garden</i>, an astral prison guarded by 12 powerful and vicious bosses, the Zodiacs.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CREATE YOUR OWN PLAYSTYLE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Gif_playstyle.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Unlock dozens of unique spells for your 4 distinct characters. Optimize your own build or try out new ones to take down 12 powerful bosses. Get stronger with time to match up with your foes. Each run will test your skills and your reactivity.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TWELVE ALMIGHTY BOSSES TO FACE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Zodiacs.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The Zodiacs are 12 experienced guardians dispatched over 4 gorgeous worlds. They’ll bring to the battlefield unique attacks, abilities, and patterns, backstories to uncover, and reasons to be fighting you. Get yourself warned!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>4 PLAYABLE CHARACTERS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/4_Character_banniere_steam7.png?t=1700851162"><br/><i>Unique characters. Unique weapons. Unique ways to play.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Ayla:</strong> The sole survivor of her guild of assassins, she uses her twin daggers to eliminate her enemies before they can react. Her speed and proficiency are unmatched.<br/></li><li><strong>Kiran:</strong> This orphan learned life the hard way. He uses his strength to deliver attacks powerful enough to create shockwaves. Brutal.<br/></li><li><strong>Calie:</strong> This talented sculptor wants her freedom back. She will use her magical gemstones to pierce enemy defenses and shred them to bits. She is unforgiving.<br/></li><li><strong>Octave:</strong> Trained by a powerful witch, this young fighter summons ethereal guns to attack his foes. When needed, he can conjure bigger weapons as well. Lethal in all cases.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A STORY THAT OPENS UP, ONE PIECE AT A TIME</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/ZimZim2.png?t=1700851162"><br/>Astral Ascent is a rogue-lite infused with narration. Replayability is part of our story which will be unraveled piece by piece. As you get stronger, you will discover more about the characters, their motivations, and the secrets of the world they’re trapped in.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>LOCAL CO-OP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Coop.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The weight of destiny is too heavy to carry by yourself? Don’t worry and bring a friend to play in our <strong>two-player co-op</strong> mode. Fight and crush your enemies together in local co-op or online using the <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/remoteplay?snr=1_614_615__1601" rel="" target="_blank"><strong>Steam's Remote Play Together</strong></a> feature.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A VAST, COLORFUL FANTASY WORLD WAITING TO BE EXPLORED</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Panning.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Dash across gigantic landscapes. Explore original and hand-crafted areas. Discover the world created by our artists, with a gorgeous art and frame-by-frame animation.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirate Fighting Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186400/Pirate_Fighting_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pirate Fighting Simulator is a free multiplayer PVP game developed in Unreal Engine 5 in which you fight other players using typical pirate weaponry. There are also cosmetics that you can unlock, these cosmetics can be either hats, weapon skins or in the form of a title that sits underneath your username. The game also includes emotes so you can absolutely boogie down silly style after destroying an enemy gamer. There are also two gamemodes one being TDM (Team Death Match)) and the second being FFA (Free For All).						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1699642767"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1700646226"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colony Ship: A Post-Earth Role Playing Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/648410/Colony_Ship_A_PostEarth_Role_Playing_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/voyage.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/><i>It is the Year of Our Lord 2754…<br/><br/>You will never feel the sun’s warmth under a blue sky, never hear the wind in the branches of a tree, and never swim in the ocean, all because you had the misfortune to be born on the Ship, chained to a fate you didn’t choose. You have never seen Earth and you’ll never see Proxima Centauri either. You’re doomed to live and die on the Ship in the name of the Mission, like your father before you, like his father before him.<br/><br/>The Ship is old. She had already been twenty years in service when she was rechristened Starfarer - a pretty name for a retrofitted interplanetary freighter. No one is certain the Ship will actually reach its destination, and nobody much cares, since no one alive now will live to see it. Might as well get on with your life and try to make the best of it.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/features_header.jpg?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>Colony Ship is an isometric, party-based RPG inspired by Heinlein’s Orphans of the Sky. Your character's world is a “generation ship,” a massive spacecraft on a centuries long voyage to colonize a distant planet. The Ship's original government has been disbanded following a violent mutiny and you must negotiate a treacherous path among your fellow passengers and the contentious factions striving to dominate the Ship. Your choices will determine who your friends and enemies are.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/explore.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/Pit.gif?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>Your adventure starts in the Pit - a sprawling heap of vacant cargo containers slowly getting filled up with those who couldn't afford to stay in the Habitat or needed to get away from its bosses and factions. Out here, folks live free and die fast...<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><i>You open your eyes to a grey hull-metal ceiling, one panel of which flickers yellow, indicating dayshift. You overslept, not that it matters. With a grunt you roll off your stained mattress and open the "window" to let some fresh air in. Like everything else around here, fresh is relative. The Ship does its best to recycle air and water, but cargo holds aren’t high on Her priority list. You breathe in metal and burning oil and look up. Four of the bridge's six projectors are still operational, shining dully down on the container towers of Cargo Hold 3, better known as the Pit, the Free City.<br/><br/>Calling the Pit a city is a bit of a stretch, but so is calling this reddish-brown liquid water. You've read that water is supposed to be clear and cities are supposed to be big, but no ship-born has ever seen either. Maybe in another hundred years water will look and taste like oil and people will be talking about the good old days when it was the color of rust and tasted refreshingly bitter and tangy. That's the kind of optimism that keeps you going.<br/><br/>The elevator crawls up a groove in the cargo hold's wall like a black steel bug that's worn a path traveling to the bridge and back. It’s time to get up there and earn a few credits, but first you need a drink.</i><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/Hydroponics.gif?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>Once tasked with adapting Terran plants and grasses to the alien environment of Proxima Centauri, Hydroponics was abandoned during the Mutiny. Quickly overwhelmed by out-of-control mutant vegetation, it more closely resembles deep jungle than a research complex. In addition to the abnormal plants, oversized pest control species –bioengineered to safeguard the colony's farmlands– are also on hand to punish the careless.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><i>Plants were sacred to the Founding Fathers. They represented our connection to Mother Earth, our sustenance, and our future. Picture rippling fields of wheat, rye, and barley to the horizon, mighty oaks and cedars, children eating apples right from the tree. That was the vision for Proxima.<br/><br/>But they didn't anticipate how many seedlings would fail in the Ship's simulated environments. And unless they found a way to make good those losses, it would be catastrophic. Alien fauna and poor soil were deemed the biggest threats, so they matched the most important plant species with customized, symbiont fungi. The latter were meant to act as pest killers. Unfortunately, the fungus did its job a little too well. We’re the pests now.</i><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/Habitat.gif?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>Before the Mutiny, the rooftops of the Habitat supported a sprawling amusement park. There, the people of the Ship could experience at least a few of the novelties they would never enjoy on Earth or Proxima: walk barefoot on real green grass – courtesy of Hydroponics – or soft, red-tinted 'Proxima' sand; sit under tall, artificial trees; and watch the sunrise on gigantic screens suspended all around. This last was said to be indistinguishable from the real thing, not that anyone aboard had ever seen it.<br/><br/>Nowadays, the three remaining rooftops are heavily fortified platforms, patrolled by armed guards. The sky-screens went dark long ago, a frivolous luxury in a decaying world. The grass underfoot and simulations of golden fields have likewise vanished, replaced by watchtowers and checkpoints. With enemies on all sides, cheap entertainment is a useless distraction from reality and its harsh demands.<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/Mixed.gif?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>The Armory - Among the stars, the children of Earth wish most of all for peace. Nevertheless, the wise prepare for every eventuality – we should not survive long without the means to protect our territory and interests, with violence if every other method is exhausted. To that end, the Ship launched with a wide assortment of peacekeeping weapons and armaments, most of it looted and spent during the Mutiny and the hundred lesser skirmishes that followed.<br/><br/>Mission Control - The century-old wreckage of the Ship Authority government complex that once controlled every aspect of life on the Ship. Now scavengers infest this ancient seat of power, a grim reminder that nothing lasts.<br/><br/>The Shuttle Bay - Noah relied on doves to find a landing place, the Ship carried twelve survey shuttles for that same purpose. Even though the Shuttle Bay survived the Mutiny intact, it was looted in the interim, the life support systems and emergency supplies stripped, and the shuttle interiors used by generations of squatters. <br/><br/>The Factory - An abandoned industrial complex that once worked 'round the clock to produce tools for the Ship and the future colony. Why squander your precious shekels on second-hand Earth machinery, when your captive workforce will have three hundred years to manufacture everything you need?<br/><br/>And many others.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/gain.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/Combat.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>Combat is difficult. You’ll be outnumbered and outgunned, so you’ll have to figure out how to even the odds or avoid fights you can't win. There are 3 main factors determining the difficulty of any combat encounter and your character's life expectancy: Accuracy, Evasion, Damage (both dealt and taken). To succeed in combat, you must learn to control these factors. <br/><br/>Accuracy = 50 + bonuses from (stat + skill + feat + implant + helmet/goggles + weapon). You can easily neglect a couple of items from this list and still be a competent fighter, meaning you don't need to min/max your stats because it's only 1 item out of 6. The attacker's accuracy is further modified by the attack type (different attacks have different pros and cons), the weapon's gun's effective range, and inflicted penalties.<br/><br/>Evasion = bonuses from (stat + skill + feat + implant + armor handling – armor penalty). The defender's evasion is further modifier by cover (the exact bonus depends on the angle), gadget bonus (i.e., using a Disruptor Field), and smoke/spore cloud (smoke grenades and certain critters). More detailed information can be found on the character and inventory screens (which show your accuracy and evasion), and in combat, where you can press ALT when targeting while targeting to learn what is affecting the accuracy of a particular attack.<br/><br/>The damage depends on both the weapon and the target's defense. Incoming damage is reduced by damage resistance (feat + implants + armor) and energy shield (gadget and/or energy armor). Weapons with good penetration and/or aimed attacks can reduce enemy's damage resistance, dealing more damage.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/Stealth.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>When you enter the stealth mode all tiles are automatically assigned detection values, determined by the distance from the guards, which way they're facing, their Perception, and thermal vision gear, if any. Green - safe (you remain undetected), yellow - risky (if you end your turn there, you'll be spotted), red - instant discovery. High sneaking ability (modified by skill, feats, gear) turns more tiles green and opens up more options, whereas a low level thief might see nothing but yellow and red tiles. <br/><br/>Each step and action (lockpicking, climbing, using computers, killing guards in stealth mode, etc) generates noise. Not a whole lot of noise to instantly alert the guards the moment you do something, but enough to add up over time and raise the guards' suspicions. The higher the guards' Perception, the faster the alert bar is filled. An alerted guard turns towards the last noise generated, meaning a lot of safe tiles will turn red and if you're in the line of vision you'll be instantly discovered. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/Dialogue.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>If fighting isn't you thing, you can avoid ALL combat by relying on speech skills: Persuasion, Streetwise, and Impersonate. Not every solution is in your face, but it is there. We check stats, skills, reputation, deeds, and track your choices to deliver appropriate consequences. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/friends.png?t=1701168231"><br/>Ten party members (max party size is 4) and well over a hundred different characters, some less friendly than others. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/001.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/002.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/003.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/005.jpg?t=1701168231"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/008.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/007.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/015.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/006.jpg?t=1701168231"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/harbinger.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/009.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/012.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/010.jpg?t=1701168231"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/016.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/013.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/004.jpg?t=1701168231"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/017.jpg?t=1701168231"><br/><br/><i>Lord's Mercy was her given name. Though he wasn't a priest, her father had called himself a Man of Scripture, and never tired of reminding his only child of God's wrath, His vengeance, His untiring thirst for retribution. If that’s what her name meant, Mercy did her best to live up to it.</i><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><i>"Are you now?" Bartholomew looks at you with interest. "I assume you were on your way to the Habitat, but now you're stuck here...  Your odds aren't looking good, my friend,” he gives you a salesman's smile. “Attacking the Black Hand's stronghold is suicide, with or without our help. If Stanton loses...” He makes a pause, letting you work it out on your own.</i><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><i>“You may address me as Harbinger. I no longer have a name." The bitterness in her voice is unmistakable. She must not have been doing this Harbinger thing for long. One of the guards removes his helmet to reveal an oddly leathery face with deep-sunk eyes and a lipless mouth. He grins as he savors your discomfort.<br/><br/>“I wonder if the Neanderthals were as shocked by your outlandish appearance,” the woman says. “I wonder if they foresaw their own doom.”</i><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/join.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>A generation ship is a perfect ant-farm where different societies can coexist within a limited space, influencing and affecting each others' development while fighting for that limited space, which adds 'the end justifies the means' pressure. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/protector.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>The Protectors' one truth is the Mission, and the sole way to ensure successful completion of the Mission is to follow the Old Ways. The ways of the fathers, forefathers, and Founding Fathers are together the beam upon which the Ship travels to our ultimate destination. The mutiny, which through their steadfast and timely intervention was thankfully aborted, was the ultimate betrayal of the Old Ways, of everyone who had come before, the nullification of every sacrifice and every life dedicated to the Mission.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/brotherhood.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>The Brotherhood was formed to liberate the people from the iron shackles of the Ship Authority. Though their first sally -which the fossils of the old world denigrate with the term "mutiny"- failed to completely achieve this aim, the Brotherhood was successful in establishing themselves as a power to be reckoned with. The Brotherhood's initially pure goal, to free the enslaved wherever they may be, has unfortunately been sullied by the practical concerns of democracy. To bring freedom to the Ship entire must involve war, and no war may be won without sacrifice, nor may battles be managed by committee.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/church.png?t=1701168231"><br/><br/>As inevitably happens in dark and challenging times, some citizens turn to God for reassurance, the promise of an end to pain and hunger. Or failing an end, at least a purpose. The Church of the Elect rejected both the Protectors of the Mission and the Brotherhood of Liberty as worldly fools distracted by politics and their own egos. Teaching their adherents that they were chosen by God, the Church frames the journey of the Ship as a centuries-long test of faith. When the Ship arrives at her destination, Judgment Day awaits every citizen. The righteous will be welcomed into the Promised Land of Proxima Centauri, while the unrepentant will be returned to the Hell from which we fled - Earth - to suffer for all eternity.<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"/><br/>Plus lesser factions and groups: People of the Covenant (the mutants), the House of Ecclesiastes, formerly known as ECLSS - the Environmental Control and Life Support System, the Pit's Freemen, Thy Brother's Keepers, the Grangers, Jackson's Riflemen, and more!<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/648410/extras/123.png?t=1701168231"/> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobalt Core</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2179850/Cobalt_Core/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_1.gif?t=1700087396"><br/><br/>Cobalt Core is a sci-fi roguelike deckbuilder with a unique single-axis combat system that will throw you for a loop. Many loops! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_2.gif?t=1700087396"><br/><br/>Give orders to your crew by playing cards: Will you <strong>raise shields</strong> to protect your ship, <strong>dodge</strong> incoming missiles and cannon fire to avoid damage outright, or <strong>strike</strong> preemptively to disable your enemy’s weapons? Outmaneuver your foes to stay just ahead of impending calamity, and reach the Cobalt Core!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/characters.png?t=1700087396"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fresh new spin on tactics –</strong>  dodge attacks and target weak points in this unique single-axis take on tactics combat. Outwit the enemy in a high stakes game of cat and mouse!<br/></li><li><strong>Customize your deck –</strong> hundreds of cards and split upgrade paths means no two runs will be the same. Find that perfect combo that brings your deck from powerful to overpowered.<br/></li><li><strong>Get to know your crew –</strong> each character comes with a completely unique playstyle and their own personal story. Bring 3 along, mix and match their decks, and see how these little goobers get along with each other.<br/></li><li><strong>Tons of replayability –</strong>  hundreds of different character+ship combinations before you even hit “start run”. Crank up the difficulty and really test your skills!<br/></li><li><strong>Forward momentum –</strong> untangle a narrative and unlock more playstyles as you go. Is there any escape from this time loop?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/grandma_cookies.gif?t=1700087396"><br/><br/>By the makers of <i>Sunshine Heavy Industries</i>, recipient of IGF's <strong>Honorable Mention for Excellence in Design 2022</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nickelodeon All-Star Brawl 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2017080/Nickelodeon_AllStar_Brawl_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/ReviewScores.jpg?t=1700669221"><br/><br/><strong>Nickelodeon All-Star Brawl 2</strong> lets you duke it out with the biggest and best fighting character roster yet, including all new characters like SpongeBob SquarePants, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, Squidward Tentacles, Jimmy Neutron, and more!<br/><br/>Choose your favorite brawlers, master their unique move sets, and use all-new powerful Supers to land the finishing blow with friends or across a unique, roguelike player campaign!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/General_GIF-Optimized.gif?t=1700669221"><br/><br/>Featuring:<br/>• <strong>New Single-Player Campaign:</strong> Put your skills to the test as you fight to stop Danny Phantom archvillain Vlad Plasmius from taking over the Nickelodeon universe!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/Campaign_GIF-Optimized.gif?t=1700669221"><br/><br/>• <strong>All-New Gameplay:</strong> New and revamped visuals meets new audio, animations, modes, stages, mechanics, taunts and move sets for all levels of play!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/GameplayRevamp_GIF-Optimized.gif?t=1700669221"><br/><br/>• <strong>Cinematic Supers:</strong> Power up your fighters with incredible new animated supers to deal devastating blows to your opponents!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/CinematicSupers_GIF-Optimized.gif?t=1700669221"><br/><br/>• <strong>New &amp; Improved Brawlers:</strong> Nickelodeon All-Star Brawl 2’s roster is better than ever, with even more variety in how each unique character plays. Battle with brand new Nickelodeon fighters as well as returning fan favorites!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/NewBrawlers_GIF-Optimized.gif?t=1700669221"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658820/Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							10 possible fruits and one goal, reach the Watermelon.<br/>Your job is to combine matching fruits to evolve them to the next one and eventually reach the coveted Watermelon.<br/>To help you, you have 3 different abilities at your disposal. But watch out, using these will cost you some of your points. Be smart about when you use them to get the highest score!<h2 class="bb_tag">GET THE WATERMELON</h2>How many Watermelons can you combine before your basket overflows?<h2 class="bb_tag">USE YOUR ABILITIES</h2>Power, level up and destroy — These abilities will help you reach the Watermelon, using any of those will also allow you to angle your aim.<h2 class="bb_tag">GOLDEN FRUIT</h2>If luck is on your side, you might even see the mysterious Golden Fruit. Find it and witness its effect firsthand.<h2 class="bb_tag">STATISTICS</h2>Track your progress with in-depth statistics. Visit the menu to see the number of fruits you've combined, your ability usage, and much more.<h2 class="bb_tag"></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.codecks.io%2Fwatermelon-game" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/extras/Roadmap_Banner.png?t=1700532981"/></a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football Manager 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2252570/Football_Manager_2024/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2252570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a real boss and write your own football story in Football Manager 2024, the most complete edition in the series yet. <br/><br/>Whether you’re a manager who likes to build from the bottom or prefers to chase immediate glory, the perfect challenge awaits. The arrival of the new Meiji Yasuda Insurance Ltd J. League licence unlocks J1 League, J2 League, J3 League for the first time ever, giving you the opportunity to explore new horizons in Japan.<br/><br/>Wherever you manage, it's up to you to build a team capable of competing with the world's elite.<br/><br/><strong>Game Description </strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Continue your relentless journey to the top of the footballing world by using the new ability to import your existing career from Football Manager 2023.<br/></li><li>Craft a winning tactical approach, incorporating modern football’s most popular systems and cutting-edge positional innovations to deliver victories on the pitch. <br/></li><li>Master the transfer market, using new ways to shape your side to cultivate a squad capable of achieving your goals. <br/></li><li>Level up your players on the training field, developing the mentality and teamwork needed to transform contenders into champions. <br/></li><li>See your tactical vision come to life on Matchdays, with every game elevated by improvements to ball and player movements.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">NEW FOR THIS SEASON</h2><br/><br/><strong>TRUER FOOTBALL MOTION</strong><br/><br/>Enhancements to player animations, ball physics and lighting deliver the most immersive Match Engine in Football Manager history. Move to the cutting edge of football by using the new Inverted Full-Back player role, while more intelligent player rotational movements add more fluidity to every highlight. <br/><br/><strong>DOMINATE FROM SET PIECES</strong><br/><br/>Make an impact at both ends of the pitch with an overhauled Set Piece Creator. Lean on the expertise of brand-new Set Piece Coaches to develop winning routines in every scenario that will help you to outsmart your rivals. <br/><br/><strong>BRACE FOR TRANSFER BATTLES</strong><br/><br/>Showcase your squad-building skills in our most refined transfer market yet. You’ll face a trickier battle for talent as your rival opposition managers are now more strategic than ever in their recruitment decision-making. <br/><br/><strong>NEW AGENTS TO BUILD A DREAM SQUAD</strong><br/><br/>Better shape your perfect squad with the introduction of new Intermediaries that will help you offload surplus players for a cut of the final transfer fee. Additional functionality for existing Agents and the debut of TransferRoom, a football marketplace for transfers in real life, gives you more real-world powered tools than ever to build an elite team and dominate the competition.<br/><br/><strong>ELEVATE PERFORMANCES WITH TARGETS</strong><br/><br/>Motivate your team to achieve more on and off the field by setting them individual Targets. Whether you’re focusing on goals scored in a season or average training performances, challenge your star players and top prospects to maximise their ability. <br/><br/><strong>A HOST MORE ADDITIONS</strong><br/><br/>Enjoy greater variety in every career with the arrival of two new game modes. Real World mirrors when players actually joined your club. Your World sets club squads and budgets at the day your career starts, meaning that only players who joined before that date will be in your squad, giving you the opportunity to rewrite your team’s transfer window.<br/><br/>Elsewhere, you can look to dominate international management and plan for your country's future with a revamped National Pool that gives you a better overview of the talent at your disposal. Match preparation and briefing meetings deliver you winning insights before each fixture. <br/><br/>That’s not all though, with many more changes waiting for you to discover in every career.<br/><br/><i>This version contains information that is still under approval process by rights holders and may contain data that does not, at this time, accurately reflect real world data. For context, some club and player assets may be absent during this version.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MalovMetaArt Metaverse</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2224020/MalovMetaArt_Metaverse/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2224020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							MalovMetaArt is a metaverse of world art, a digital museum that allows you to view the digital twins of world masterpieces that are identical to their physical counterparts.<br>
<br>
The key distinction among MalovMetaArt and similar projects is the 100% accurate replication of artworks. Using photogrammetry and laser scanning techniques, we have created a way to create precise digital twins of the masterpieces of world art you see in the app. You can even touch, zoom and examine the artworks from all sides. In virtual space, you can hold an item (which is not allowed in a real museum) or get up close to unique paintings, so close that they can see the texture of each touch of the genius’s brush.<br>
<br>
Non-traditional exhibition galleries are another feature of MalovMetaArt. Here you may admire glass artworks exhibited under the starry sky of faraway planets, as well as masterpieces of painting in a subway hall of mid-20th century.<br>
<br>
Many of us don't frequently visit regular museums. So, give a go to a virtual one. You'll like it. Furthermore, MalovMetaArt Metaverse is better and more convenient than a traditional museum in many aspects.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beacon Patrol: First Horizons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2554990/Beacon_Patrol_First_Horizons/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2554990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Beacon Patrol: First Horizons is a <strong>relaxing</strong> strategy game with endless possiblities.<br/><br/>Steer your Coast Guard ship and build your own coastal map one tile at a time.<br/><br/>Get more tiles by exploring and keep building indefinitely as long as you can keep scoring.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2554990/extras/description_header_01_en.png?t=1701345756"><br/>Start with your ship at the Coast Guard HQ and you build your map from there.<br/><br/>On your turn you place up to three tiles, connecting to the tile your ship currently occupies. Tiles must not be rotated and all their edges have to match.<br/><br/>After placing a tile you immediately move your ship onto it. By spending one of your tokens you can take an additional movement to a connected tile.<br/><br/>You score points for each tile that is connected to other tiles on all four sides. For scored points you receive new tiles to continue your journey.<br/><br/>The game ends after allavaialble tiles have been played.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2554990/extras/description_header_02_en.png?t=1701345756"><br/>Beacon Patrol: First Horizons combines the look and feel of a board game with the endless posibilities of a digital experience.<br/><br/>Experience this cozy and strategic game at any time.<br/><br/>The clear and cute art style lets you enjoy the coast and the sea from where ever you are.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siheyuan</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2239360/Siheyuan/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2239360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							SIHEYUAN is a single and local co-op action-puzzle game of few words, but lots of tiles. Move the falling blocks, pass them and pass them again to fill the grid, in this minimalistic test of coordination for 1-4 players of any age, inspired by the tradition of "siheyuan", historical courtyards of Beijing, China.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2239360/extras/How_it_works_small.gif?t=1701344776"><br/><br/>Juggle tiles between the 4 game areas in single-player mode, or pass them to your friends in multiplayer mode (up to 4P), talking, collaborating, and sharing (or shouting) your strategy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2239360/extras/Maschere_small.gif?t=1701344776"><br/><br/>• 13 different levels to unlock<br/>• 13 special modifiers, changing the game's pace from meditative to hectic<br/>• Unique minimalistic abstract design inspired by Chinese traditional architecture, color theory, opera, and games.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hand In Hand</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1209510/Hand_In_Hand/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1209510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Hand In Hand is a 2D split screen puzzle platformer, where the player can control two characters at once, or two players can play in co-op mode on one device.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A TOUCHING STORY</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1209510/extras/History.gif?t=1701341865"><br/>Two soulmates live in a fairytale world. But when evil came to their world, they lost each other. Now both of them need to head towards each other, facing many difficulties and dangers along  the way. And only by finding a fragile connection between one another and going hand in hand will they be able to defeat evil and meet again. It's a story about how we can help one another even when you're apart, and be far from one another even when you're nearby. It's a story about the importance of relationships and mutual support. But every story has an even deeper meaning...<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SPLIT SCREEN</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1209510/extras/SplitScreen.gif?t=1701341865"><br/>The game works in splitscreen mode, with one character on each screen in their respective locations. The game has two modes. The first is single-player mode, where one player simultaneously controls both characters with one joystick. In this mode, the player must demonstrate sophisticated controller skills. The second is local co-op mode, where two players control the characters using two joysticks. Here, both players control their respective characters. Each mode has its advantages. Single-player mode requires you to show great dexterity and reaction speed, and co-op mode allows you to feel the joy of playing the game with your family or friend. Try both game modes, we hope you'll like it and enjoy completing it.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>THE CHARACTERS INTERACT WITH AND HELP EACH OTHER</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1209510/extras/Interaction.gif?t=1701341865"><br/>Each character has their own part of the level in a common location. However, some parts of the level are interconnected. This means that the characters can interact and help each other complete the level. Characters can move keys and objects from one part of the screen to another, and most puzzles are need to be solved by both characters working together, connecting parts of the screen and solving puzzles together.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>EPIC BOSSES</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1209510/extras/Boss.gif?t=1701341865"><br/>The game has epic boss battles. Each boss represents the world of shadows that has invaded this fairytale forest and wants to plunge all the inhabitants of this fairytale world into the horror of eternal darkness. Our brave heroes, Lina and Minho, must defeat each of the bosses so that peace and prosperity will once again reign in the fairy forest. Boss battles take place without splitscreen, and are designed to be played by just one of the characters, so each character must defeat their evil shadow bosses.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>PUZZLES</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1209510/extras/LightPuzzle.gif?t=1701341865"><br/>On their way through the collapsing fairy-tale world, the characters will constantly encounter various puzzles like closed doors, laser beams with reflectors, ancient mechanisms and ruins, labyrinths, and caves full of dangers. Our heroes will be able to overcome all difficulties, but each will have to make every effort to pass these trials and help their companion.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rock Simulator 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1949770/Rock_Simulator_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1949770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME WHAT YOU HAVE IMAGINED</h2>Earn, find, and collect over 100 unique rocks!<h2 class="bb_tag">LEVELING</h2>Increase your leveling speed by unlocking and leveling up your rocks!<h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLAYER</h2>Relax with friends in any environment to enjoy the sunset together!<h2 class="bb_tag">WEATHER</h2>Create your own custom weather presets to create the exact mood you want to enjoy!<h2 class="bb_tag">AMBIENCE</h2>Listen to the rain or groove along to your meditative music tracks!<h2 class="bb_tag">LEADERBOARD</h2>Who will exist the longest? Idle your way to the top of the leaderboard and show off your hard-earned levels!<h2 class="bb_tag">PUZZLES</h2>What are the rocks hiding? Be the first to find them to get to the top of the leaderboard!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOKI</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2585380/BLOKI/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>BLOKI</strong> is an educational game about residential architecture from the Soviet era. It aims to make people aware of the important function of the colors of buildings, as well as to encourage reflection on the spaces around us. The game also allows you to signal your own needs related to the aesthetics and functioning of these estates while showing the consequences of their implementation.<br/><br/><strong>Work plan at the estate:</strong><br/>1. Prepare a facade design for two residential buildings. Use the color palette and available geometric patterns. Follow the instructions to earn as many aesthetic points as possible.<br/>2. Get to know the elements of the surroundings available in the Służew nad Dolinką estate. Choose environmentally friendly, look after social initiatives, and the necessary elements of small architecture. Earn points for aesthetics, sustainability, and functionality.<br/>3. Share your vision with us - share your design on Instagram with #BLOKIgame.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bug Bash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2586680/Bug_Bash/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2586680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Get ready to unleash your inner exterminator in Bug Bash! In this thrilling and interactive game, players wield a virtual flipflop to squash pesky bugs as they scuttle across the screen. With each squashed bug, you'll earn points and face even more challenging critters. Fast-paced and full of fun, Bug Bash offers endless entertainment for all ages. Whether you're a seasoned gamer or just looking for a way to pass the time, Bug Bash will have you hooked from the first smash. Join the action now, and see how many bugs you can bash!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarmhunters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2621670/Swarmhunters/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2621670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Features</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A simple and casual action shooter: your weapons will automatically aim and shoot!<br/></li><li>Dash between bullets and kill your way out of numerous enemies!<br/></li><li>Four selectable characters, tens of unique weapons and upgrades!<br/></li><li>Non-static builds. You may play as you like on the battlefield!<br/></li><li>No need to unlock anything. Your knowledge is your best weapon!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ecdysis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1842880/The_Ecdysis/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1842880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>THE ECDYSIS</strong> is an episodic Action/ Adventure game that immerses players in the life of Robin Jr., a professional photographer, guiding them through the thrilling adventures and enigmatic mysteries he experiences on his journey.<br/><br/>Play as Robin jr, a professional photographer who embarks on a journey to his dream place to experience and capture the nature and wildlife <br/>but you know... not everything works as planned. As a number of mysterious events occur, robin has to investigate and find out what's happening around him.<br/><br/><strong>GRIPPING STORYLINE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1842880/extras/Untitled_2.9.1.jpg?t=1701333084"><br/>-Engage in an exciting contemporary narrative and endeavor to piece together the clues to the fullest extent possible.<br/><br/><strong>CINEMATIC PLAYTHROUGH</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1842880/extras/Untitled-1.jpg?t=1701333084"><br/>-Embark on a cinematic adventure as you delve into the game, immersing yourself in its stunning visuals and captivating storyline.<br/><br/><strong>GO FOR A LONG DRIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1842880/extras/gif32.gif?t=1701333084"><br/>-Get your truck ready and gear up for an epic expedition to conquer the heights of the mysterious Mt. Mare's Nest.<br/><br/><strong>FIGHT FOR YOUR LIFE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1842880/extras/sxcs.jpg?t=1701333084"><br/>-Prepare to confront and overcome those who oppose your progress.<br/><br/><strong>ORIGINAL SOUNDTRACK</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1842880/extras/GIF6.gif?t=1701333084"><br/>-Enjoy a distinct original soundtrack and background score created by Kingsley Roy, an independent musician.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPIRITUS 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2695850/SPIRITUS_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2695850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Albert and Rose return in SPIRITUS 2. The Book of Rites has been used to build an army and has wiped out the city of London. Together, they must stay together to stay alive and venture to the very depths of evil to prevent the end of the world from happening. With a huge roster of new enemies to fight, challenging bosses, and labryinth areas to solve, SPIRITUS 2 is this year's survival horror classic.<br>
<br>
Presented in wonderful 3D HD graphics with awesome PSX style retro effects, SPIRITUS 2 is the definite survival horror experience.<br>
<br>
GAME FEATURES<br>
-Take  arms and shoot monsters, explore and manage a limited inventory in this  3D survival horror with static camera angles and classic tank controls.<br>
-Explore the City and it's dark depths with Lovecraftian influences.<br/>
-Investigate the story with cinematic sequences and found note storytelling<br/>
-Quality of life engine upgrades - Shoulder camera toggle added for easier navigation through static camera angles<br/>
<br/>
PRESENTATION<br/>
-A game presented in classic 3D survival horror with fixed camera angles adding to the suspense<br/>
-PSX Style rendering which takes players back to the best days of survival horror.<br/>
<br/>
SOUNDTRACK<br/>
-Immersive sound effects and chilling soundtrack that immerses the player in the horror.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scary School Simulator 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667850/Scary_School_Simulator_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dive into the spine-chilling world of Scary School Simulator 2, where the serene facade of Sakura High School conceals dark secrets and eerie mysteries. Immerse yourself in this heart-pounding anime horror simulation that combines the thrill of high school life with the terror of a yandere ghost's obsession. Unravel the mysteries, survive the doki-doki moments, and escape the sinister ghosts.<br>
<br>
Play the game as Sakura and her friend Sara, the Japanese schoolgirls on livestream that trapped in a cursed and abandoned academy, where you must navigate the dark corridors of a haunted school, solve chilling mysteries, and survive terrifying encounters with spooky creatures and zombies.<br>
<br>
🌟 Key Features:<br>
<br>
🔪 Survive the Haunted School: Navigate the spooky halls of Sakura High School, where creepy ghosts lurk around every corner, ready to haunt you into a world of terror. Can you escape their killing desires and survive the nightmare?<br/>
<br/>
🌸 Explore Sakura High School: Discover the hauntingly beautiful 3D surroundings of Japanese high school, complete with swimming pool, art club, and abandoned classrooms. But beware, as darkness hides behind every corners.<br/>
<br/>
👧 Interact with Friends: Meet with a variety of students, each with their unique personalities and secrets. Build love relationships or face the consequences of rejection, as the yandere ghost are always watching you.<br/>
<br/>
👹 Evil and Angry Teacher’s Wrath: The beautiful teacher is not what they seem. Avoid seek their attention, scare her by prank teachers, solve puzzles, and escape their evil plans to trap you in the haunted high school forever.<br/>
<br/>
🎮 Realistic Simulator Experience: Experience the thrill of a realistic high school simulator with a terrifying twist. Attend classes, prank your friends, and interact with stuff, all while being on the lookout for popping jump scares.<br/>
<br/>
😱 Heart-Pounding Doki Doki Story: Feel your heart race during intense chapters, where your choices could mean the difference between survival and death. Can you keep your composure and outwit the evil ghost trying to kill you?<br/>
<br/>
👻 Anime Horror Atmosphere: Immerse yourself in the captivating anime horror game atmosphere of Scary School Simulator 2. The chilling soundtrack, eerie jumpscare, and unsettling ambiance will keep you on the edge of your seat.<br/>
<br/>
🏃 Escape the Horror: Your last goal - escape from Sakura High School with your boyfriend before it consumes your soul. Use your eyes, mobile phone, and playtime to find a way out of this nightmare.<br/>
<br/>
Survive the horror school, outsmart your pursuers, and escape Sakura High School before it's too late. Can you evade the hordes of the supernatural being in this terrifying anime horror simulation game?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Isekai: Legends of Nipponia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2589290/American_Isekai_Legends_of_Nipponia/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2589290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							250 years ago, on the world of Nipponia, twin siblings Taneela and Tanaka seek to become Adventurers like their father. On the day of their registration, they are contacted by Mavis, the Crystal being and guardian of the world. Can they gather enough forces to stand against the rising evil in their world? <br>
<br>
This is the story of how two unlikely heroes set off to save a world, and how the story of American Isekai began. <br>
<br>
The game features several mechanics not found in the Prologue game including:<br>
<br>
80-120 hours of gameplay depending on the player.<br>
<br/>
Equipment upgrading.<br/>
<br/>
Monster Taming.<br/>
<br/>
Class change.<br/>
<br/>
Enemies level up with you, and learn new skills at higher levels.<br/>
<br/>
Rank up in the Guild to get stat boosting cards.<br/>
<br/>
A massive world map with several methods of travel including Airship, Teleportation Items, and a Guild Teleporter.<br/>
<br/>
Quest Notes for tracking side and main quest objectives.<br/>
<br/>
A World Map and a Local Map to track your position in the world for easier travel.<br/>
<br/>
Learn skills from Skill Cores instead of through leveling.<br/>
<br/>
A difficulty option for those that want to sail through the game, and those that want an extra challenge.<br/>
<br/>
And much more!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Paupers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2683200/The_Paupers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2683200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2683200/extras/paupers-1__1_.png?t=1701331818"><br/><strong>Step into a world between worlds</strong>, where the ethereal and the earthly collide in a whimsical yet haunting adventure. In <i>The Paupers (formerly Dziady)</i>, players assume the enigmatic role of a spectral custodian, tasked with aiding lingering souls' transition to the afterlife. This game ventures into the surreal, guiding players through a spectral realm teeming with lost spirits.<br/><br/>In <i>The Paupers</i>, players immerse themselves in the art of spectral listening, tuning into the peculiar requests of these ghostly inhabitants. The challenge lies in fulfilling their varied and often bizarre needs, whether it's an alcoholic beverage or a long-forgotten comfort food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2683200/extras/paupers-gif-5.gif?t=1701331818"><br/>The journey through <i>The Paupers</i> is a delicate balance of empathy, wit, and a touch of spookiness. Engaging with these lost spirits unveils layers of stories and unmet desires, each request illuminating a fragment of their past lives.<br/><br/>The game's unique charm lies in serving these spectral needs while exploring the intricate stories behind the spirits' presence. It's not merely about supplying items - it's about connecting with these lost souls, understanding their wishes, and ultimately guiding them toward peace in the afterlife.<br/><br/>But don't think it's too serious! It's a Halloween-themed spooky fun game, blending eerie encounters with delightful humor for an entertaining gaming experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2683200/extras/paupers-gif-4.gif?t=1701331818"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Dynamic Spirit Encounters:</strong> Engage with a variety of spirits, each with unique needs, personalities, and requests.<br/></li><li> <strong>Quest-Driven Gameplay:</strong> Embark on quests to gather the required items for the spirits, navigating through stylized environment and avoiding supernatural dangers.<br/></li><li> <strong>Mysterious Atmosphere:</strong> Explore an atmospheric world filled with eerie yet captivating visuals and an immersive soundtrack, creating an intriguing and mysterious ambiance.<br/></li><li> <strong>Halloween-Themed Spooky Comedy:</strong> Embrace the Halloween spirit with a balance of spine-chilling atmospheres and humorous encounters, blending spooky elements with lighthearted and funny interactions with the spirits, creating an entertaining and uniquely themed gaming experience.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pingo Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2015830/Pingo_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2015830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">About</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2015830/extras/pingo_blinking_cropped.gif?t=1701331315"><br/>Pingo Adventure is a <strong>cute</strong> 3D platformer in a <strong>physics simulated</strong> world with jiggly plants, bouncy bridge, springy rope etc.<br/><br/><strong>Explore</strong> the adorable &amp; interactive 3D world from rainforest, ancient ruins to dungeon filled with hot lava and <strong>solving puzzles</strong> designed for the physics simulated environment.<br/><br/>But that’s not all, there are <strong>mini games</strong> in between the platforming level which can be unlocked and played in the “arcade mode”.<br/><br/>And don’t forget to <strong>customize</strong> your own Pingo with all the costumes that can be unlocked from the adventures.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2015830/extras/intro_short_optimized_cropped.gif?t=1701331315"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><strong>Physics Simulation</strong> - Immerse in the physics simulated cute world with jiggly plants, bouncy bridge, springy rope and more...<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2015830/extras/platformer1_optimized_cropped2.gif?t=1701331315"><br/><br/><strong>Puzzles</strong> - Solving puzzles designed for the physics simulated environment<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2015830/extras/lava_lever_optimized_cropped2.gif?t=1701331315"><br/><br/><strong>Mini Games</strong> - Collect replayable mini games from adventures<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2015830/extras/mini_games2_cropped2.gif?t=1701331315"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2015830/extras/mini_games1_cropped2.gif?t=1701331315"><br/><br/><strong>Camera Mode</strong> - Capture the cute moments of your adventures from different angles<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2015830/extras/camera_mode1_cropped2.gif?t=1701331315"><br/><br/><strong>Character Customization</strong> - Customize your own Pingo with various costumes that you can unlock from the adventures<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2015830/extras/customization_cropped.gif?t=1701331315"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Cafe</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2409360/Pixel_Cafe/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2409360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Welcome to Pixel Cafe</strong></h2>Dive into this captivating blend of an arcade time manager and visual novel. Help a small-town girl navigate life in a big city, and take part in her coming-of-age story as she forges connections, overcomes difficulties, and struggles to find her worth.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2409360/extras/Nowy_projekt__52_.png?t=1701331242"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Uncover Hidden Tales</strong></h2>Explore Karstok, a city stuck between a socialist past and a capitalist future. Go on an emotional journey as you form connections with your bosses and clients in this beautifully crafted pixel art world.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2409360/extras/Nowy_projekt__53_.png?t=1701331242"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Master the Art of Coffee and Cooking </strong></h2>Perfect your coffee-making and cooking skills on your professional journey through 10 wildly different bars. Keep your customers satisfied as you learn new recipes and adapt to sub-optimal working conditions. Sounds too easy? Challenge one of the 50 optional Nightmare levels. Their hellish difficulty will surely hunt you in your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2409360/extras/Nowy_projekt__2_.jpg?t=1701331242"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Decorate Your House</strong></h2>Breathe new life into your Grandma's old house. Buy furniture and unlock posters to decorate it and truly make it your own.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2409360/extras/Nowy_projekt__4_.jpg?t=1701331242"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Experience the Emotional Journey</strong></h2>Witness an emotionally gripping narrative that spans three generations. Explore both the past and present through Pixel's eyes and see how memories of her Grandparents shaped her life.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2409360/extras/Nowy_projekt__5_.jpg?t=1701331242"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Unique Soundtrack</strong></h2>Immerse yourself in the game's atmosphere while listening to the captivating, original soundtrack by Arkadiusz Reikowski, featuring a diverse range of genres and emotions.<br/><br/>Embark on a heartfelt journey and discover the essence of Pixel Cafe, where the emotional story unfolds one cup at a time.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yard Sale Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2416350/Yard_Sale_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2416350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this immersive simulation you will go from a novice trader to a highly respected business person. Start off living in the shame of poverty and use what little you have to make your start as an entrepreneur in the yard sale world.<h2 class="bb_tag">Buy</h2> Buy items from various places around town. Find great deals at yard sales. Visit the flea market for rare finds. Learn how to spot a deal or a fake.<h2 class="bb_tag">Clean Dirty Items</h2>Some items are in rough shape but its nothing a good cleaning won't fix. Dirty items are harder to inspect but often come at a discount. Make them shine to attract new customers.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2416350/extras/CleanTV-gif.gif?t=1701330835"><h2 class="bb_tag">Repair Damaged Items</h2>You got your new item home to clean up but oh no it's damaged. Have no fear. With the right tools and know-how you can fix that up no problem.<br/><br/> <strong>Repair cracked items with our easy to use system. With just a can of putty and a little know-how you can have it fixed up in  a jiff.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2416350/extras/PuttyTV.gif?t=1701330835"><br/><br/> <strong>Maybe your new item is a little dented, grab your self a dent puller and pop that dent out in no time.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Rank Up Your Skills</h2>Gain experience as you fix up items allowing you to use the best tools in town. <br/>Buy and sell to gain experience unlocking  more business opportunities.<h2 class="bb_tag">Satisfy Customers Anyway You Wish</h2><br/><strong>Get your first yard sale going to make your start.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2416350/extras/startsale.gif?t=1701330835"><br/><br/><strong>Invest in better locations and items to grow your empire.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2416350/extras/standbuy.gif?t=1701330835"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hazelnut Hex</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2474690/Hazelnut_Hex/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2474690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Rescue breakfast in this arcade-style bullet hell shoot 'em up!<br/><br/>A strange curse falls across the land! Breakfast everywhere has disappeared, and it's up to you to save the most important meal of the day! Blast your way through 5 colorful stages jam-packed with dangerous enemies, elaborate bullet patterns, and ruthless bosses to rescue breakfast once and for all!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2474690/extras/steamgif1.gif?t=1701320512"><br/><br/>Release the shoot button to charge a powerful piercing shot! Hit multiple enemies for extra points and stars!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2474690/extras/steamgif2.gif?t=1701320512"><br/><br/>Collect stars to fill your Superbeam meter! Unleash your Superbeam in dense bullet patterns for huge bonuses!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2474690/extras/steamgif3.gif?t=1701320512"><br/><br/>Save Nat's buddy, Sam, for extra firepower!<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>5 Exciting Stages!<br/></li><li>Over 50 Unique Enemies!<br/></li><li>3 Powerful Magic Types!<br/></li><li>2 Challenging Difficulty Modes!<br/></li><li>about 30 minutes of gameplay</li></ul><br/><i>Cover art by the talented MisMash!</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Highrise</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1273480/The_Highrise/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1273480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The first alien beings did not fall from heaven. <br/><br/>They come from beneath the ground.<br/><br/>They destroyed everything on the earth on their first appearance.</strong><br/><br/><br/><i>THE HIGHRISE</i> is a first-person survival game set in a high-rise building that has been sealed off by an alien monster invasion. Gather resources to make fighting weapons and survival tools. You must find and send a rescue signal at the end of your desperate survival.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Feel the void and abandoned highrise building</strong></h2><br/>Prior to this apocalyptic era, facilities such as shopping malls, offices, and residences, which were previously crowded with people, were very familiar and friendly spaces to us. But, now, they will inspire fear in a sense of emptiness and heterogeneity that no one can find. Furthermore, it is a space created by inspiring real skyscrapers, and the space that is vacated or omitted has been minimized. Players will feel that every floor and facility in the building will have the appearance of a very real space.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SHHH! Beware of noise caused by carelessness.</strong></h2><br/>The monster sniffers responsible for humanity's extinction have a highly developed sense of hearing and smell. They can detect even the smallest movements, coughs, and gurgling sounds from your stomach. Moreover, if there is a loud noise, such as glass breaking or falling from a great height, the sniffers will rush to the player.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>GO DOWN AND DOWN! Find out more and better resources.</strong></h2><br/>To avoid the monster sniffers, the last survivor stayed near the top floor of a building. The player used to be a linker, connecting these survivors to the food court in the building's basement. Use this knowledge to your advantage. The lower floors you go, the more resources you have and the more efficient you are. However, as they get closer to the ground, the monsters become more powerful and the number of monsters increases. But you never know; you may find any hints to help you escape from the downstairs.<br/><br/><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">KEY FEATURES</h2></strong><br/><br/>* Hunger and thirst must be controlled. However, be cautious of food poisoning. Food poisoning survivors are likely to be pursued by sniffers.<br/><br/>* You can obtain resources by destroying most of the building's furniture. For a much more efficient acquisition, use tools that are specific to the material of each piece of furniture. <br/><br/>* Make and install the tools required for survival. You can carry a still to purify dirty water, a cooktop to boil food, and a workbench to craft survival tools.<br/><br/>* You can avoid monsters by sneaking between them, but you can also create weapons to fight them. Crafting each appropriate tool and weapon for combat and infiltration allows you to work more efficiently. <br/><br/>* A ventilation system connects all of the building's floors and rooms. This is the only safe zone from the group of monsters, and it is entirely up to the player. Remember the layout and flow of this area.<br/><br/>* There are a total of 6 playable characters, each with different stats and passive skills.<br/><br/>* Single-player and multiplayer for up to 4 players (up to 8 players in custom mode) are available. In multiplayer, there will be balance adjustments based on the number of players.<br/><br/>* There will be Sandbox mode, Survival mode, and Custom mode. In Sandbox mode, infinite lives are guaranteed, and there will be resource respawns. However, in Survival mode, you can experience the true challenge of the game with limited resources and a one-time life. In Custom mode, you can configure various options according to the difficulty level you desire.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape Quiz</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1432410/Shape_Quiz/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1432410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2308240" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2308240</a><h2 class="bb_tag">Welcome to Shape Quiz - Unleash Your Inner Detective!</h2><br/>Embark on a captivating visual adventure where shapes take the spotlight. Can you discern the shapes hidden within intriguing outlines? Put your perception and speed to the test in this exhilarating quiz game!<h2 class="bb_tag">🌟 Shape Exploration:</h2> Delve into the world of shapes as they gradually unfold on your screen. Can you identify them all correctly?<h2 class="bb_tag">🌟 Race Against Time:</h2> Quick thinking is key! Identify the correct shape swiftly to earn stars and dominate the global leaderboard.<h2 class="bb_tag">🌟 Daily Challenge:</h2> Challenge yourself daily with a unique set of 10 shape-based puzzles. Can you outperform others who are shown the exact same shapes?<h2 class="bb_tag">🌟 Diamonds:</h2> Earn diamonds as rewards! Get 5 diamonds for every 5 correct answers in standard mode. In Daily Challenge mode, receive a diamond for each correct answer.<h2 class="bb_tag">🌟 Game Over:</h2> In the event of an incorrect answer, the round gracefully concludes, affording you the chance to restart and redeem yourself.<h2 class="bb_tag">🌟 Information &amp; Settings:</h2> Access game instructions and the development version in this section.<br/><br/><strong>Shape Quiz</strong> is your opportunity to prove your shape recognition skills. Rise through the ranks and become a star collector. Get ready to embark on this visual journey today!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PODCAST VS VIEWER 《主观争霸》&amp;《主播vs观众》</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2127830/PODCAST_VS_VIEWER_vs/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2127830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The game is an auxiliary software game tool specially created for the podcasts and podcast viewer fans playing online live broadcast on major live broadcast platforms in minutes, integrating interactive communication and gameplay.<br>
The main gameplay of the game is to interact with the podcaster and the viewer to report numbers and the podcaster controls and clicks on the number slots of themselves and the viewer to compete in the game. The viewer rounds to the number by sending numbers to the podcaster in the chat comment area of ​​the live broadcast software on the live broadcast platform, so that the podcaster can manually perform the game number for the audience when the viewer takes turns, so as to interact with the game.<br>
At the same time, the game also provides message and chat boxes to facilitate podcasters and viewers to leave messages and chat. There is no need to switch to the chat area of ​​the live broadcast platform to type every time, preventing podcast replies from being overwhelmed by viewer replies in the comment area.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALACTIC FIELD 《银河领域》</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1253440/GALACTIC_FIELD/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1253440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a brand new space sci-fi flight shooting game. The story of the game takes place in a distant future world, which is about an interstellar war between three different factions. Players can choose the spaceship pilot status of any faction faction to join the interstellar war of these factions. At the same time, players can also control various types of spaceships to fight with the frontline enemies. In addition to advocating fast-paced competitive flight shooting gameplay, the game also provides a variety of personalized modes and gameplay details setting functions. It is especially suitable for live streaming. The host can easily interact with the audience anytime while playing. In addition, the game is non-violent and suitable for players of any age, especially those who like sci-fi warfare and space flight. Right now, the game is a basic version, and more modes will be added in the future. Due to limited resources, there are only single-player and double-player modes. However, you can get free updates. Hope you will like and support this game!<br>
Game Features: Fast-paced, exciting, shooting, sci-fi, space<br>
<br>
Reminder - the game has many customizable mode options. It is recommended that players adjust and play in their own favorite mode. The official default mode may not be suitable for every player's preference.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Walker: Dark World</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2093910/Time_Walker_Dark_World/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FMap4E2Reav" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/DISCORD.png?t=1701339617"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/分割线1.png?t=1701339617"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/组合技能eng.png?t=1701339617"><br/><strong>Lead four Time Walkers to torture the Dark Lord and his subordinates with more than 40 skills. Match different skill builds without class limits. Archer healer, assassin tank or wizard warrior? All up to you.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/打斗.gif?t=1701339617"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/组合职业eng.png?t=1701339617"><br/><strong>Choose four Heroes before battles, match them with different abilities to produce amazing chain reaction. Create your unique Time Walker every time you start!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/组合职业-选英雄eng.gif?t=1701339617"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/组合资源eng.png?t=1701339617"><br/><strong>Manage the resources you collect in every battle. Merge to get advanced abilities or Reforge to your luck.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/组合资源-重铸eng.gif?t=1701339617"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/解锁天赋eng.png?t=1701339617"><br/><strong>Never ignore Talents. Unlock new heroes and abilities to give Dark Lord’s subordinates an impressive lesson.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/天赋解锁eng.gif?t=1701339617"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/进阶强化eng.png?t=1701339617"><br/><strong>Looking for more power? Try Advanced Heroes and EX Abilities! Merge three same basic hero items into an advanced one! Merge two Level III abilities into a moer powerful EX ability.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/进阶强化-合成英雄英语.gif?t=1701339617"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/进阶强化-合成技能eng.gif?t=1701339617"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/揭秘陰謀eng.png?t=1701339617"><br/><strong>Time Walkers power will be stronger and stronger during the war against Dark Lord. Take them to the deep side and reveal Dark Lord’s plots!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/揭秘阴谋-剧情对话eng.gif?t=1701339617"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/揭秘阴谋-四个同职.gif?t=1701339617"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093910/extras/eng分割线愿望单.gif?t=1701339617"><br/><br/>Please join our Discord to meet more penguins!Welcome to join our <strong>DISCORD: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FMap4E2Reav" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/Map4E2Reav</a></strong> to meet more adventurers！						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEVI</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2230650/TEVI/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FZ9KrdFvNRK" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/JoinUsOnDC.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Action-Packed_Combo_System.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/戰鬥動圖.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>The protagonist Tevi is nimble and agile, wielding both her trusty dagger and an oversized wrench for dishing out melee damage in style. Alongside her, companions Celia and Sable manifest as two floating orbitars, ready to unleash a variety of ranged offensive and supportive magic in battle. Adapt your combat style to suit any situation and bring down foes with flashy, dazzling combos!<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Thrilling_Boss_Battles.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Boss.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Every boss fight is a unique challenge requiring different strategies to tackle, all while you dodge their attacks and look for openings to counter-attack. <br/>As bosses change phases, their attack and bullet patterns become increasingly challenging, and they can even unleash devastating ultimates. Continual offense can submit bosses into a vulnerable BREAK state, during which you can deal massive bursts of damage.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Myriad_Abilities,_Equipment,_and_Exploration.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/badge.jpg?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Scattered across the the expansive world, there are over 300 different items and pieces of equipment waiting to be discovered. These items can enhance your abilities or introduce new ones, allowing you to find more methods of navigating the world and finding secrets. A cornucopia of equippable sigils can be freely configured to create builds tailored to your preferences and playstyle.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/A_Rich,_Expansive_Fantasy_World.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/場景6.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Dive into the vibrant world of Az, in which you will discover various towns, regions, peoples, histories, and civilizations, each with their own tale to tell. Along the way, you'll meet a large cast of strange and colorful characters. As their tales unfold and intertwine, you'll be drawn into a tale full of adventure, friendship, mysteries, and danger... <br/><br/>Get ready to embark on an unforgettable adventure, writing your own epic journey alongside Tevi!<br/><br/><a href="https://youtu.be/psxior_WswQ" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/角色介紹.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tevi（VA: Lynn）<br/></li><li>Celia（VA: Yoko Hikasa）<br/></li><li>Sable（VA: Natsumi Fujiwara）<br/></li><li>Zema（VA: Tomokazu Sugita）<br/></li><li>Vena（VA: Rie Kugimiya）</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metro PD: Close to You</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2581210/Metro_PD_Close_to_You/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2581210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a Steam version of a hit visual novel game released on the mobile reader app Love 365: Find Your Story by Voltage Inc. It is a collection of romantic, richly illustrated interactive stories with the following premise:<br/><br/>In Metro PD: Close to You, join an elite group of detectives at the Metropolitan Police Department. Partner up with a handsome senior detective to go on undercover investigations and solve dangerous cases such as serial bombings - and of course, overcoming these life-or-death situations will bring you two closer together... Experience a world straight out of a procedural drama, as thrilling as it is romantic.<br/><br/>An opening movie and adventure feature have been added to the Steam release, so even players that have previously read the app version will discover more things to enjoy.<br/><br/><strong>The Story:</strong><br/>"You're my partner as of today."<br/><br/>You're a rookie detective. Your training? <br/>Trial by fire, solving a dangerous case together!<br/><br/>Get yourselves out of tight binds<br/>and discover an even stronger bond with each other.<br/><br/>Will you catch the real culprit?<br/>And will your case come to a romantic conclusion?<br/><br/>A lethal love where you watch each other's backs.<br/>What will come of your dangerous and thrilling romance?!<br/><br/>Whether on the job or in love,<br/>there's never a dull moment!<br/><br/><strong>Characters:</strong><br/>Hiroshi Kirisawa     "The Rugged Boss"<br/>Kazusa Hanai    "The Perfectionist Detective"<br/>Yutaka Tennoji         "The Unmatched Senior Detective"<br/>Tadanobu Nomura      "The Flirty Deputy Chief"<br/>Masashi Himuro      "The Ruthless Coroner"<br/><br/><strong>Contents:</strong><br/>Includes Main Stories from the app Love 365: Find Your Story up until "24 Hours and Counting" (Except Nomura)<br/>*His PoV Stories are counted as Special Stories and thus not included						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>犬神ディフェンダーズ / Soul Dog TD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2093970/__Soul_Dog_TD/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">"One More Game" will Turn into a Hundred!</h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Overview</h2>Fight off hoards of foes with the titular Soul Dog and six units in this tower defense game.<br/>Defeat enemies before they reach your leader and collect the souls they drop.<br/>Use those souls to upgrade your units and take down all 30 waves!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093970/extras/steam_doganime.gif?t=1701306677"><h2 class="bb_tag">The Soul Dog, a.k.a. "Inugami"</h2>The Soul Dog possesses the unique ability to collect spirits that appear when you defeat enemies.<br/>Make sure to collect every last soul, as they can be used to strengthen your army!<br/>However, while you collect souls, your army will be left defenseless. Timing is key!<h2 class="bb_tag">Soul Boons</h2>When picking up a soul, you will get to choose one of three random items known as Soul Boons.<br/>Choose the items best suited to your units and make your army a force to be reckoned with!<h2 class="bb_tag">Know When to Strike</h2>Your army consists of six units, each of whom can switch between <strong>attacking</strong> and <strong>training</strong>.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093970/extras/levelup.gif?t=1701306677"><br/><br/><br/><strong>Attack Mode</strong><br/>Units will attack automatically.<br/><br/><strong>Training Mode</strong><br/>Units will gain EXP and level up. However, they cannot attack while training.<br/><br/>Learn to attack with exactly the right number of units to defeat the enemy while the rest train and level up. Striking the right balance between attacking and training will be vital to your victory!<h2 class="bb_tag">The Skill Tree</h2>Money earned from battle can be used to increase your army's strength via the skill tree.<br/>Acquire useful and powerful skills to buff up your units!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2093970/extras/steam_skillboard.gif?t=1701306677"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive 30 waves of enemies by learning the ins and outs of battle, training your units, and collecting souls!</h2> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Punch Jump</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667240/Punch_Jump/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Punch Jump is a Foddian Platformer, which means progress is difficult and not guaranteed.<br/><br/>The central mechanic is throwing around Carl, who is an NPC<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667240/extras/throwing_carl.gif?t=1701305978"><br/>The goal of the game is to get him to the end of the level.<br/><br/>The art-style is minimalist and the in-game radio system plays a large variety of music from royalty-free authors.<br/><br/>The platforms and particles in the game flash to the beat of the music currently playing.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667240/extras/music_change.gif?t=1701305978"><br/>If you are confident in your skills at platforming type games, then this game will humble you.<br/><br/><br/>Join our Discord!<br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FUbtKc9NFcd" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667240/extras/icons8-discord-144.png?t=1701305978"/></a> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Suika - Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2671970/My_Suika__Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A fun watermelon merge puzzle game!<br>
<br>
Think you can get 3000 points in this addictive watermelon puzzle game?<br>
<br>
Combine various matching fruits to help Kyo gather watermelons! Unlock new game modes and new fruit skins by obtaining high scores. Compete against other players on the global leaderboards!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Piece</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684940/The_Piece/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>“The Piece” is a simple &amp; fun block puzzle game, it’s a fun way to train your spatial ability!</strong><br/> - Simple game-play: Drag blocks to fill up the puzzle board in correct position!<br/> - Simple game play but somehow you trapped by tricky pieces!<br/><br/>Get into block Puzzle’s fun world &amp; visual pleasure!<br/> - Normal levels: Over 540+ puzzles are full of fun to train your brain!<br/> - Special levels: Collecting 60 marvelous pictures by completing special levels!<br/> - “The piece” gives you the visual pleasure of seeing beautiful pictures along with fun of solving the puzzles!<br/><br/>Gallery: Stunning pictures!<br/> - 15 different themes of gallery: Big, Beauty, Happy, Nature and more fun themes.<br/> - Various shapes of puzzle will be placed in different sections.<br/> - Try to find out SPECIAL pictures through the game play! Beautiful puzzle pieces will appear in special level!<br/> - Complete special level to collect pictures and fill up your beautiful gallery!<br/><br/>So simple!<br/> Quick into the game play! Do not need to sign in and any other unnecessary steps!<br/> Do NOT need network connection! Do NOT worry about your data issue!<br/> Even airplane, you can enjoy the game!<br/><br/>“The Piece” is a simple &amp; fun  block puzzle game, train your spatial ability!<br/>- Complete the puzzle by colorful pieces to fit in correct position!<br/>- Collecting marvelous pictures to complete your gallery!<br/>- The piece puzzle that make you smarter!<br/><br/>* Challenge with over 600 fun stages!<br/>* Collecting 60 marvelous pictures to complete the gallery!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adhd Arena</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2623080/Adhd_Arena/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2623080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Let your ADHD run wild and stack gems to accumulate points, get to higher more rewarding tiers and get the highest score you can by pushing gems around to organize and combine them, get lost in the joys of creating chaos and then putting it to order.<br>
<br>
Choose your own playstyle, scores are not affected by playtime, play fast then tidy up, or plan out your placements and keep it organized from the begining, it's up to you.<br>
<br>
Some runs can get long, that's why you can quit the game and pick back up where you left last time! no pressures.<br>
<br>
Every three months a new season will drop, bringing new game feel/mechanics and shapes to keep it fresh, new rewards for the top 20 players in the global rankings and new content for all players.<br/>
<br/>
Side note: This is the first game I've ever finished, I hope you enjoy playing it as much as I did making it :)						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trophy Hunt</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658260/Trophy_Hunt/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Trophy Hunt is a silly multiplayer game all about stealing and defending trophies from your friends! With Trophies in the center of the map, its an all out rush to bring them back to your base. Use your sword to trip others and steal their trophies! Use power-ups to boost your speed, turn invisible, plant traps and more! <br>
<br>
Play any setup from 1v1, 2v2 or 4 player free-for-all while asserting dominance with your trophy hunting skills!						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escape the Farm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2660710/Escape_the_Farm/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2660710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take on the role of an intrepid chicken in Escape the Farm, a 3D puzzle platformer that offers an escape room experience with a farmyard flavour.<br/>Plot and execute daring escapes from a variety of farms, taking advantage of full dynamic physics to cook up the best-laid plan for success.<br/><br/>Run, jump and glide through increasingly treacherous farmyards, using what you’ve learned from each new flight to break away from the confines of your oppression.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2660710/extras/description-chicken.png?t=1701293800"><br/><br/>Whether your style is sneaky or berserk, your plucky hen will find the right tools for the job. You might find yourself using an axe to smash a wooden fence, a lantern to navigate a dangerous forest, or an explosive barrel to blow everything sky high. And remember - the obvious path isn’t always the easiest route to liberty.<br/><br/>Good cluck - you’ll need it!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On The Brink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2347350/On_The_Brink/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2347350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use Capri's gravity manipulation to slingshot across the universe as she embarks on a mission to liberate a forgotten dimension from the clutches of an all-powerful being. Solve puzzles, uncover mysteries, and shatter space-time itself in this snappy sci-fi action platformer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2347350/extras/DescriptionBanner_01.png?t=1701302267"><h2 class="bb_tag">What lies in the dimensions above our own?</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> An original sci-fi narrative set in the far reaches of the universe following Capri's fight to right cosmic wrongs and save <strong>PROJECT: Almagest</strong>.<br/></li><li> High-speed movement is interwoven with unique puzzle mechanics sure to engage hypothalamuses and prefrontal cortexes alike.<br/></li><li> Galaxy distribution across the universe is dynamic and infinite. Stay conscious, or be lost in the infinite aether.<br/></li><li> <i>On The Brink</i> has subtitles available alongside controller support for both Windows and Mac OSX. <br/></li><li> Recommended for third-dimensional beings. Playable in the second dimension, with decreased performance.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stream Slugger</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2218430/Stream_Slugger/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2218430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							This desktop application is a transparent application.<br/>Which will entertain you while working.<br/>Together with an active Twitch account you can let friends spawn their 3D character on your desktop.<br/>Even when you aren't live on Twitch just use the chat.<br/>This can lead in hilarious situations and you will never feel alone when streaming or working for school.<br/>During a live stream the characters can fight or just hang out on your screen.<br/>Level them up  so the characters get super powers!<br/><br/><strong>Please note:</strong> that this program utilizes an API from Twitch.<br/>Before using the program, please review Twitch's API policies and guidelines at:<br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fsafety.twitch.tv%2Fs%2Farticle%2FCommunity-Guidelines" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://safety.twitch.tv/s/article/Community-Guidelines</a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2Fp%2Fen%2Flegal%2Fprivacy-notice%2F%23authentication-and-log-data" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.twitch.tv/p/en/legal/privacy-notice/#authentication-and-log-data</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kraken Odyssey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2112260/Kraken_Odyssey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2112260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2112260/extras/texte2.png?t=1701274360"><br/>Dive headfirst into this 3D action/racing game, run at full speed, jump to avoid dangers and hit the finish line! More than thirty different levels await you, with missions and medals to earn at each level. You won't be short of challenges!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2112260/extras/2023-05-17_16-19-20.gif?t=1701274360"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Help Voulpy in his adventure! </strong></h2>His little brother has been kidnapped and it's up to you to travel through various worlds to find him! Beaches, jungles, snowy mountains, flaming dungeons, but be careful not to end up as crab bait...<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2112260/extras/course.gif?t=1701274360"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Become the coolest kraken on the islands!</strong></h2>The game has a multitude of costumes to unlock, pirate or unicorn - it's up to you to choose.<br/>So if you love octopuses, the beach, and adventure, set out on an adventure in Kraken Odyssey!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2112260/extras/skins.gif?t=1701274360"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2112260/extras/essai.png?t=1701274360"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flat Spot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2459820/Flat_Spot/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the <strong>casual motorsport management</strong> game of the year!<br/><br/>Experience motorsport like never before: <i>very simple</i>. In this exciting, fast-paced management game you can be team principal of your own team, <strong>upgrade</strong> your car with newly built parts and <strong>sign new drivers</strong> to compete in races and win the championship. Use your drivers <strong>special abilities</strong> to gain an advantage over other drivers on track and leave them in the dust.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Build <strong>randomly generated car parts</strong> that suit your purpose! </li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459820/extras/FlatSpot_CreateCarPart_RearWing_480px.gif?t=1701272955"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Customize</strong> your car for each race! </li><li>Handle <strong>fun encounters</strong>off-track! </li><li><strong>Special abilities</strong> and strategy decisions, all in <strong>your hand</strong>!</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459820/extras/FlatSpot_UseSpecialAbility_AdrenalinRush_480px.gif?t=1701272955"><br/><br/><strong>See you on track!</strong> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All of Us Are Dead...</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2177170/All_of_Us_Are_Dead/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2177170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							All of Us are Dead - The Visual Novel<br>
An interactive, visual novel based on the hit webcomic series. <br>
<br>
◆ Story <br>
Summer. July. Zombie virus breaks out in Hyosan High. Friends and teachers become infected, and many can't bring themselves to take down the infected. They were friends and teachers, after all. Soon, the entire school is infested with zombies with no way of escape. <br>
Experience the struggles of ordinary students as they juggle extraordinary challenges. Join the jocks as they face overwhelming odds while fighting for their survival. Be wary of the terror that lies within the school for zombies were not the worst of their troubles. See how each and every one survives in their own, unique way.<br>
<br>
◆ All of Us are Dead: The Visual Novel <br/>
- Based on the hit webcomic of which the live-action drama series 'All of Us are Dead' is based on. Discover wholly new content untold in other adaptations! <br/>
- All new events, endings, and more! Watch where your decisions take you and see how they unfold. <br/>
<br/>
◆ Artworks <br/>
- All new character artworks are made to reflect every character's individual personality. <br/>
- Persistent artwork. Any encounters or events that affect the character persist in the artwork, even as the story progresses!<br/>
<br/>
◆ High Quality Illustrated Events<br/>
- 100+ high-quality illustrations for maximum drama.<br/>
- Animated events!<br/>
<br/>
◆ Fully voiced in Korean<br/>
- 12+ hours of fully voiced scenarios.<br/>
- Voice-over<br/>
Lee Bohee, Park Seongyeong, Ryu Seung Gon, Lee Kyung Tae, Song Harim, Mun Yujeong, Kim Na Yul, Seo Da Hye, Kang Si Hyun, Ahn Hyomin, Kim Young Sun, Kim Hye Sung, Jang Mi, Choi Seunghun, Jang Ye Na, Shin Beomsik, Park MinGI, Bang SiU, Kim Jin Hong, Lee Eun Jo, Jung Eui Jin, Lee Myounghwa, Sung Ye Won, Jung Ui Taek						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
