<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Solium Infernum</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1893810/Solium_Infernum/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare yourself for Solium Infernum, the grand strategy game of politics, intrigue and betrayal, set in the ultimate arena of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingDarkSide2.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_IndulgeYourDarkSide_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Satan's mysteriously vanished and Hell is in an uproar. Play as one of eight all-powerful and menacing Archfiends and indulge your Machiavellian dark side. Command legions, enlist champions, cast sinister rituals, and trick, rob, and insult your rivals to be crowned Hell’s new Dark Majesty.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingStrategy2.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_StrategyFromHell_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Experience Solium Infernum's legendary devilish political machinations. Requiring nerves of steel and a true heart of darkness, every order you give will have lasting consequences. Get into the minds of your rivals, second-guessing their every move both on the map and on the floor of Hell’s parliament as you sling insults and demands in the only truly political strategy game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Eight playable Archfiends<br/></li><li>Eight single-player Chronicles<br/></li><li>Single-player Skirmish mode<br/></li><li>Revelations Tutorial Scenario<br/></li><li>Sessional and Asynchronous 2-6 player Multiplayer<br/></li><li>Dozens of Infernal Legions, including unique enormous Titans. <br/></li><li>Champion Praetors and dark Artifacts fit for any Archfiend!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingMulitplayer.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_InfernalMultiplayer_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Play 2-6 player multiplayer games with your soon-to-be ex-friends in a single session of deceit and politics, or put your friendships to the test in quick daily bursts with Solium Infernum’s infamous asynchronous multiplayer for a truly harrowing scheme-in-your-sleep experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/Heading_DarkArt2.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_DivineMadness_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>If you love dark art, you’re in the right place. Brimming with striking visions of Hell unlike anything you’ve seen before, Solium Infernum is an infernal feast for the eyes with multitudes of individual dark paintings to enjoy. Every item of the game is accompanied by mind-blasting artwork, a feat declaring Solium Infernum a winner of the 2022 Game Makers Sketchbook.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingRessurect.gif?t=1708670283"><br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_CultClassic_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Originally inspired by Milton’s epic poem, Paradise Lost, League of Geeks’ (known for seminal digital board game Armello) sophomore title is a re-imagining and modernisation of Vic Davis’ critically acclaimed cult-classic of the same name, hailed as a masterpiece of strategy game design. <br/><br/>Once again, prepare to lose yourself within ‘the cold glory of a difficult decision’ as we resurrect Solium Infernum from the depths of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/label_praise.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Note: The following quotes refer to the original Solium Infernum (2009) by Vic Davis.<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum is a political wargame set in hell… The game is now finished, and none of the friends survived. By which I mean, we all hate each other now.”</i> <br/>- Rock Paper Shotgun<br/><br/><i>“It’s a game about playing other people, in both senses of the word…. This is game design based on psychology as much as rules.” </i><br/>- Quarter to Three<br/><br/><i>“More than any game I've played in years, Solium Infernum nails the sensation of staring at a screen and losing yourself in the cold glory of a difficult decision.”</i><br/>- Game Developer (formerly Gamasutra)<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum kicked my knees out from under me ... this game took my past experience with strategy games and threw it, like a pro basketball player, into a bin eighty feet away.”</i><br/>- Eurogamer<br/><br/><i>“One of the best games of the year.”</i><br/>— Three Moves Ahead<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_toReign.png?t=1708670283"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inkulinati</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/957960/Inkulinati/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/957960/header_alt_assets_5.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Inkulinati</strong> is a turn-based strategy game inspired by medieval manuscripts. Draw your army of Beasts, and spill the ink of your enemy, defeat medieval superstars and collect perks to unleash hidden powers. Being a master of the quill isn’t easy, so make sure you’re focused and plan every move wisely. Embark on your journey and become the greatest Inkulinati of all time!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/957960/extras/steam_tittle_2_CTBS_EN.png?t=1708623493"><br/>Don’t let the looks fool you. Inkulinati is a game of nuance and brain-sizzling challenge that will test even the most hardened strategists. And as every hardened armchair general knows, it all starts with your units, which we call Beasts. There are multiple deadly (and bizarre) <strong>Beasts</strong> to unlock. They all have their special individual skills, as well as class-specific abilities causing different effects. And when these Beasts work in unison, a symphony of destruction, death, until the literal apocalypse will endure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/957960/extras/BEASTS_v2.gif?t=1708623493"><br/><br/>It’s not just your Beasts that can cause havoc and damage. There are special, battle tide-turning actions performed by the <strong>Inkulinati Masters</strong> themselves - such as yourself! Use your unique Hand Actions to smash your opponent's units, draw obstacles to create barriers, relocate your units with a move of your finger, or explode your troops to create pure, pure chaos. Just remember - your opponent can do it too. And to keep it more interesting, each Inkulinati Master can have their own set of Talents too that can help win the battle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/957960/extras/HANDS_v2.gif?t=1708623493"><br/><br/>But wait, there’s more. You will need to adapt your tactics to every battle. Each Battlefield is its own domain, with its own particular dangers that you should watch out for, and opportunities that you can use. Look out for objects that are scattered all over the <strong>Battlefields</strong>, such as exploding Pots of Beans, travelling Hell’s Maws, Clouds of Blessings, and use them to your advantage. <br/><br/>And just when you think you have a handle on the battle, an <strong>Apocalyptic event</strong> can come in and flip all of your plans upside down. We’re talking fires, plagues, and the Memento Mori itself. However, when all hope is lost and you’re on the ropes, an Apocalypse might be just what you need to turn the tide in your favour.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/957960/extras/BATTLEFIELDS_v2.gif?t=1708623493"><br/><br/>There are different difficulty levels to choose from depending on your cunningand know-how, so even younglings will be Inkulinati-Masters in due time. And for those that want to know the ins and outs, you can learn how to master it all in our <strong>Academy mode</strong>, where we teach you step-by-step all the nuances to win every battle. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/957960/extras/steam_tittle_1_SPC_EN.png?t=1708623493"><br/>Uncover the mystery and secrets of the Inkulinati and face such opponents as Hildegard, Dante Alighieri, and more. Go out into the world and start your adventure! Fight the biggest Inkulinati masters in the land, tame the untamed Beasts, build your ultimate army, try to bring back your Master from the clutches of death, and most importantly, finish your grand quest with the biggest party that the middle ages have ever seen! <br/><br/>The best adventures are those of your own. In Journey mode you will create and develop your own character. As any aspiring Inkulinati Master, you will get to create your own Inkulinati character. During your journey you will learn the secret techniques of drawing new Beasts and Inkulinati Hand Actions, allowing you to choose the composition of your army. You can be a brave knight that has no fear or a nun who with the power of prayer can confuse her enemies and heal thy own servants. Those styles, and more, are waiting to be discovered and made your own. Express yourself!<br/><br/>On your journey you won’t just battle against other Inkulinati Masters. You will face untamed Wild Beasts, go against Beast Lairs, meet interesting characters such Bards and talking Geese, visit shops, scriptoriums, and loads more. It is one heck of an adventure!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/957960/extras/CAMPAIGN_MAP_v2.gif?t=1708623493"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/957960/extras/steam_tittle_3_PVPM_EN.png?t=1708623493"><br/>Inkulinati will bring you back to the Golden Era of hot-seat mode. Face your friends, family, or foes, and decide who is the greatest Inkulinati Master in the house!<br/><br/>Choose your Army, Talents, Inkulianti Master, the Battlefield, and other criteria and options, and face a battle that will be remembered for the ages.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/957960/extras/DUELS.gif?t=1708623493"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/957960/extras/steam_tittle_4_IRLM_EN.png?t=1708623493"><br/>700 years in the making, finally these bizarre art pieces can come alive in a video game and show that medieval people also had their “memes” and that they laughed from the same silly things that we do today. You’ll see sword-wielding rabbits, dogs with spears, trumpets lodged in bottoms, human-eating snails, and more. Much, much more…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/957960/extras/DECK.gif?t=1708623493"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/957960/Inkulinati/" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/957960/Inkulinati/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regency Solitaire II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2137470/Regency_Solitaire_II/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2137470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Revisit romantic Regency Britain and build a glorious garden, in this charming solitaire sequel. Brought to you by the creators of the hit casual card game, <strong>Regency Solitaire</strong>. <br/><br/>Play your cards right as you tour must-see locations around Britain, from grand houses to vast landscaped gardens and cultural hotspots. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2137470/extras/600x137_map_zoom.gif?t=1708620328"><br/><br/>Resolve a tangled web of family secrets to help Bella silence the gossips, and host the season’s most anticipated soiree.  <br/><br/>Unlock gameplay features with your makeover project, and reveal bonus 'Collector's Edition' levels and a love story. Don't miss the party everyone's talking about!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2137470/extras/marietta_page.gif?t=1708620328"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2137470/extras/Collector_s_Edition_Label.png?t=1708620328"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2137470/extras/Features_text.png?t=1708620328"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Smooth, satisfying solitaire gameplay.<br/></li><li>'Collector's Edition' bonus content.<br/></li><li>Transform Bella's garden and costume.<br/></li><li>Sumptuous art and romantic storyline.<br/></li><li>New characters, and some old favourites.<br/></li><li>Standalone story in the world of Regency Solitaire.<br/></li><li>160 unique levels spread over 18 chapters plus 66 bonus levels!<br/></li><li>Unlock dozens of exciting gameplay upgrades.<br/></li><li>Normal and Hard modes.<br/></li><li>Specially-composed, classical music.<br/></li><li>Extra Regency romance story to unlock.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garden Life: A Cozy Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1915380/Garden_Life_A_Cozy_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/MASTER_GIF.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE1_EN.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF1.gif?t=1708616161"><br/> <br/>Plant and nurture your dream garden using gardening techniques based in real life and adapted for everyone to enjoy:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Plant seeds, leaving them enough space to thrive<br/></li><li> Water, fertilize, and clip your plants to enhance their natural beauty and nurture them to health<br/></li><li> Discover different colourful varieties and unlock the full potential of each plant<br/></li><li> Pull out all weeds or choose to leave some to protect plants from pests<br/></li><li> Admire your plants in full bloom even through the changing seasons : in Garden Life, all plants thrive no matter the time of year!<br/></li><li> Play the story mode or the creative mode</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE2_EN.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF2.gif?t=1708616161"><br/> <br/>You are in charge of an abandoned community garden and decide to roll up your sleeves to restore it to its former glory. Complete tasks given to you by your neighbours to earn rewards, unlock new tools, seeds, ornaments and areas of the garden, and learn more about what lies behind this secluded spot.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE3_EN.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF3.gif?t=1708616161"><br/> <br/>Instantly unlock every corner of your garden, including all the seeds and ornaments, and give free rein to your creativity: in this restriction-free mode, you can bring your dream designs to life!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE4_EN.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF4.gif?t=1708616161"><br/> <br/>Procedural growth simulation developed specifically for the game ensures each plant grows in its own way! Each and every plant grows procedurally, and some even adapt to their environment by climbing if planted close to certain objects.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE5_EN.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF5.gif?t=1708616161"><br/> <br/>In Garden Life, you are not restricted by a grid: place plants and objects freely to create your designs!  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE6_EN.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF6.gif?t=1708616161"><br/> <br/>Head to the village square to sell flowers and bouquets at your stall and use the earnings to buy new seeds, ornaments and tools in the shop. You can also donates flowers to help create huge floral sculptures in the pavilion and win adorable prizes! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE7_EN.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF7.gif?t=1708616161"><br/><br/>Add Garden Life to your wishlist, follow us, and join our discord community so you don't miss out on any news!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rail Route</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1124180/Rail_Route/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1124180/header_alt_assets_7.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ever dreamed of designing your own railway network? Building it from scratch, adding more stations, taking on more contracts, watching your small network grow into a complex, thriving rail system? Rail Route makes this dream a reality!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1124180/extras/june23_gif1.gif?t=1708684230"><h2 class="bb_tag">Master the art of automation</h2>Start with a few stations, design your first railway lines, and experience the joy of your first train completing its route. Take on contracts to earn money and upgrade points, unlocking new technologies that introduce more trains and automation tools into your network. With each added station and contract, the complexity grows, but so does your mastery. Experience the thrill of watching your railway network evolve from a few simple lines to a bustling, automated operation. Automation in Rail Route isn't just a feature - it's a complex, rewarding challenge. As your strategy unfurls, every signal placement and contract planning decision adds another gear in the intricate machine of your network. And when the trains glide smoothly through the tracks, operating flawlessly on their own, you'll feel that unparalleled satisfaction - not just of a job well done, but of mastering a world of your own creation.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1124180/extras/june23_gif2.gif?t=1708684230"><h2 class="bb_tag">Unleash complexity in simplicity</h2>Navigate the charming minimalism of the design, reflecting the familiar screen of a train dispatcher yet imbued with a unique twist. It presents an intuitive interface at a glance - a system that can be understood in minutes. However, beneath this simple surface, a world of intricate mechanics awaits, revealing itself as more stations are added and more contracts are undertaken. Each new layer of complexity maintains the design's authenticity, capturing the essence of real-world rail management.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1124180/extras/june23_gif3.gif?t=1708684230"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your network, your rules</h2>The freedom is yours: build from scratch, gradually unlocking technologies and resources to create your ultimate rail network across real-world city maps. Experience the satisfaction of perfect scheduling, ensuring a smooth and efficient flow of trains that reflects your strategic acumen. Or maybe the thrill of high-pressure, time-sensitive scenarios calls to you, where quick decision-making is key and wave after wave of challenges keep you on your toes.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1124180/extras/june23_gif5.gif?t=1708684230"><h2 class="bb_tag">Join a world of creators and enthusiasts</h2>Join a vibrant community that contributes to an ever-expanding universe of maps.  A community of creators and railway enthusiasts, coming together to design, share, and explore maps that span the globe. Each addition is a new adventure, a new challenge to conquer.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1124180/extras/Maps.gif?t=1708684230"><br/><br/><strong>So, what are you waiting for? Embrace your inner train enthusiast and plunge into the world of Rail Route – make the traffic flow and the network grow!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruindog:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802430/RuindogPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 4 are available in the official version.<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 4 in the official version<br/>Weapons: 3 in the prologue, 26 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/11z.jpg?t=1708686134"><br/><strong>A long, long time ago, in a solar system not so far away, alien bugs invaded Earth, but they were soon beaten back home, and by the way, their home planet was blown up. After centuries of being invincible, it became popular for humans to watch live alien hunting shows, participate in alien hunts, save up money, equipment, and use the various loot they found to keep going to new maps and defeating more powerful enemies. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1y.png?t=1708686134"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1z.gif?t=1708686134"><br/><strong>Enemies will come at you from all sides on every level, proceed with caution or you'll be torn to pieces in an instant</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3y.png?t=1708686134"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3z.gif?t=1708686134"><br/><strong>Each character has a different growth path and active skills, utilize these skills and choose the most appropriate item for the current hero to achieve the mission objective</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5y.png?t=1708686134"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5z.gif?t=1708686134"><br/><strong>Earn more resources and achieve various mission objectives to unlock different maps/difficulties and even new map mechanics!<br/>Each map has very different mission objectives and combat mechanics, so choose the one that better suits the current mechanic to win the game</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yohane the Parhelion - NUMAZU in the MIRAGE -</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2459750/Yohane_the_Parhelion__NUMAZU_in_the_MIRAGE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A deckbuilding roguelite played using magical cards!<br/>Another Yohane story is here!!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/InGame_EN_02.gif?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■『Yohane the Parhelion - NUMAZU in the MIRAGE -』<br/>Yohane the Parhelion is an official spin-off of ""Love Live! Sunshine"". 『Yohane the Parhelion - NUMAZU in the MIRAGE -』 is a deckbuilding roguelite set in that world.<br/><br/>While working as a fortune teller in Numazu, Yohane spends her days with her friends.<br/>By chance, she comes into possession of an old mirror.<br/><br/>Worried that her fortune-telling isn't accurate, Yohane decides to perform ""Magic Mirror Fortune-Telling"" using it.<br/>Suddenly, the mirror begins glowing, and sucks Yohane in!<br/><br/>What she finds in the mirror is ""Reverse-Numazu,"" which is a reversed replica of the real Numazu!<br/>Moreover, in that mysterious world, magic could be used with the power of cards.<br/>At the same time, strange things begin happening to her friends in the real world, one after another.<br/>In order to save them, Yohane must go through ""Reverse-Numazu""!<br/>What awaits her?<br/><br/>A mysterious mirror world that changes each time it's entered.<br/>After countless choices, what future will Yohane choose?<br/>A new story begins in the other Numazu!<br/><br/>■Deckbuilding and card battles in ""Reverse-Numazu"" where magic can be used!<br/>Adventure through Numazu in the mirror.<br/>Aim for the deepest level of the ""Reverse-Numazu"" by making full use of the cards you have obtained!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/Head_EN.jpg?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■A wide range of deck construction with more than 150 types of cards!<br/>Collect cards as you adventure through ""Reverse-Numazu"" and build powerful decks of your own creation!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/Select_1_card_EN_02.gif?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■Summon your trusty friends with Summon Cards!<br/>You can summon powerful friends in ""Reverse-Numazu"".<br/>Summon Yohane's friends to help you out in a pinch!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/Summon.gif?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■Prepare for your next adventure at the Fortune-Telling Shack!<br/>By completing quests in your adventures, you can power up Yohane!<br/>Also, in the 'Closet', you can change into various costumes. <br/>By changing initial cards and charms this way, you can acquire abilities that are different from your usual outfit!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/Closet_EN.gif?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■Endlessly replayable layout-changing maps! There's infinite strategies!?<br/>Once cleared, the map changes its layout every time you enter.<br/>A bargain system that lets you play forever!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/MAP_Mix.jpg?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■Charms to make you stronger than the strongest! Create your strength with Cards x Charms!<br/>""Charms"" are items with powerful effects.<br/>Combine them with your cards to become more powerful than the strongest!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myth of Empires</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1371580/Myth_of_Empires/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Embark Upon a Thrilling Journey</h2>Explore a land with diverse landscapes, ecologies, and weather, as well as a realistic day/night cycle. The v1.0 release of Myth of Empires also features a new map – Dongzhou Island, offering new adventures and challenges.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/11111探索之旅，发现新世界的惊险旅程.gif?t=1708657778"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Own Empire From the Ground Up</h2>Myth of Empires features sandbox gameplay with a high degree of freedom; the game has 1300+ different crafting recipe, allowing you to build your own empire. The v1.0 release adds new recipes, including mechanical tools and base defenses, as well as a new planting system. The possibilities are endless.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/22222自由创造，打造你的帝国.gif?t=1708657778"><h2 class="bb_tag">Recruit NPCs, Tame Wildlife</h2>In-depth taming and training systems allow players to recruit or subdue additional forces to aid them in combat and production. The v1.0 release adds new boss NPCs and powerful beasts. In addition, smaller types of animals can be used to help power your base’s defenses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/333333驯服万物，NPC、马匹与野生动物.gif?t=1708657778"><h2 class="bb_tag">Wage Epic Wars on Ancient Battlefields</h2> Myth of Empires features hundreds of different weapons, armor, and large-scale engineering equipment. Pick the weapons that best suit your playstyle, or utilize your strategic capabilities to build an army. The v1.0 release introduces powerful mechanical base defenses, wooden oxen, and other new combat equipment to further enrich the game’s deep war experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/444444史诗战争体验，挑战百变的古代战场.gif?t=1708657778"><h2 class="bb_tag">Engage in Cross-server Battles </h2>Establish administrative regions, fight for the position of county magistrate, and compete to expand your territory through Fortress Battles. Craft the perfect guild and utilize your diplomatic prowess to ensure its long-term stability.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/555555跨服征战，共同创造历史.gif?t=1708657778"><h2 class="bb_tag">Write Your Own Legend </h2>With 25 different development paths, a 16-level title system, and more than 100 achievements, you have complete freedom in growing your character. Become a legendary military commander, or content yourself with the life of a simple farmer – the choice is yours.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/666666传奇生涯，定制独特的人生.gif?t=1708657778"><h2 class="bb_tag">Play Multiple Gameplay Modes Offering Endless Possibilities </h2>Myth of Empires supports official servers, custom servers, as well as solo and hosted modes. Creative players are also able to use the game’s robust mod editor to tailor the game to their dream experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/no7多样玩法.gif?t=1708657778"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Epoch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/899770/Last_Epoch/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Epoch combines time travel, exciting dungeon crawling, engrossing character customization and endless replayability to create an Action RPG for veterans and newcomers alike. Travel through the world of Eterra’s past and face dark empires, wrathful gods and untouched wilds – to find a way to save time itself from The Void.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Gameplay.gif?t=1708534852"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>15 Mastery Classes</strong><br/>Embark on your adventure as one of five powerful classes and, through your journey, ascend into a unique Mastery Class that unlocks more specialized abilities and build-options. <br/></li><li><strong>120+ Skill Trees</strong><br/>Every skill has its own augment tree that will allow you to control, alter, and empower your playstyle. Transform your skeletons into archers, your lightning blast into chain lightning, or make your serpent strike summon snakes to fight alongside you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Nodes.gif?t=1708534852"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Hunt Rare &amp; Powerful Loot</strong><br/>Fill your arsenal with magic items that you may craft to perfection, change the rules of your build with powerful unique and set items, and always have that next upgrade just on the horizon with Last Epoch's deep and randomized loot system.<br/></li><li><strong>Rewarding Crafting System</strong><br/>The items you wield are yours to forge! Last Epoch’s community-revered crafting system allows you to control your character's power progression, featuring robust and deterministic upgrade mechanics.<br/></li><li><strong>Uncover the Past, Reforge the Future</strong><br/>Travel to different moments of time where you will discover the many factions and secrets that exist within the world of Eterra and fight to set the timeline onto a new path.<br/></li><li><strong>Endless replayability</strong><br/>With a wealth of classes and skills to customize, deep game systems, randomized loot, and continuing development, Last Epoch is a game that will keep you coming back for years to come.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Monolith.gif?t=1708534852"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Easy to Learn, Hard to Master</strong><br/>We’re committed to making gameplay approachable for new and veteran players alike by allowing you to jump into the fray quickly and providing many in-game resources. Though don’t be fooled, Eterra has many dangers waiting for you that require a mastery of combat and build-crafting.<br/></li><li><strong>Zero Pay-To-Win</strong><br/>Last Epoch will never offer gameplay advantages by being able to spend real money. We believe in creating a fair environment for all players. </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bandle Tale: A League of Legends Story</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1759380/Bandle_Tale_A_League_of_Legends_Story/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1759380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							One little Yordle, one humongous problem.<br/><br/>From Lazy Bear, the studio that brought you Graveyard Keeper, comes Bandle Tale: A League of Legends Story™. Jump into this delightful crafting RPG set in the magical world of Bandle City, home of the furry and fun-loving yordles.<br/><br/>You are a shy yordle living in Yarnville, a cozy but isolated island obsessed with all things knitting. When your 101-year-long apprenticeship ends, you want nothing more than to see what lies beyond the portals that connect the rest of Bandle City. But when a party you attend goes horribly wrong, the portals collapse and everything is thrown into chaos!<br/><br/>With your unique knitting magic and unflappable spirit, enlist the help of new friends, restore the portals, and reunite Bandle City once more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1759380/extras/BandleTale_Steam-Breaker-Image-616x100.jpg?t=1708535596"><br/><br/>BEYOND THE BANDLEWOODS<br/>In Bandle Tale, experience a never-before-seen look at life beyond the bandlewoods. Encounter curious critters, gather materials to make impossible crafts, and awaken magical portals as you move between five unforgettable new islands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1759380/extras/BandleTale_Exploration.gif?t=1708535596"><br/><br/>PARTY ON, BANDLE CITY!<br/>A good life in Bandle City hinges on one thing: beet soup! Wait, no, having fun! Throw festivals to ensure that your fellow yordles are happy and entertained. Cultivate your green thumb and cook farm-to-table dishes for your guests, or flex your engineering prowess and build gadgets to delight them.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1759380/extras/BandleTale_Party.gif?t=1708535596"><br/><br/>MEET THE CHAMPIONS<br/>Befriend colorful characters and make League of Legends Champions your allies as you unravel the mysteries around you and mend your community, one magical stitch at a time.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1759380/extras/BandleTale_Champs.gif?t=1708535596"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminator: Dark Fate - Defiance</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1839950/Terminator_Dark_Fate__Defiance/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif1.gif?t=1708701023"><br/><strong>Terminator: Dark Fate – Defiance</strong> is a <strong>real-time strategy game</strong> based on the Terminator: Dark Fate universe that follows the war between humanity and Legion's synthetic intelligent machine network.<br/><br/>In the<strong> single-player campaign</strong>, you take the role of a commander in the Founders, a force made up of the remnants of the US military and guide your army in an attempt to foil Legion's plan to exterminate the last remnants of humanity. In skirmish and multiplayer modes, play as three very diverse factions: Founders, Movement and Legion.<br/><br/>Take control of an army carried over from mission to mission on a series of large strategic maps. Make decisions about unit placement, battle tactics and abilities so that you don’t just survive but can become the leader of the resistance against the machines. Hone your skills and military expertise by replaying and achieving the best possible outcomes.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic battlefields: realistic tactics and consequences</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif2.gif?t=1708701023"><br/>Engage in complex, realistic battles where your <strong>tactical decisions</strong> are vital to your survival and ultimate victory. Use a variety of military equipment, vehicles and ammunition types in your battles against the enemy. Recruit and train new units, assign new skills and acquire new weapons and equipment to continue the resistance.<br/><br/>Encounter tense battles. Your battlefield tactics and choices have deep consequences that will impact through the campaign, with other factions and characters either joining you or fighting against you, and with certain missions being available or not depending on your actions. <br/><br/><strong>Your resources are limited</strong> and you must protect your army. Weapons of war receive damage through a modular component damage system where armour characteristics, component malfunctions and hull structure all affect if your troops survive.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Lead the survival of mankind</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif3.gif?t=1708701023"><br/>Recruit others to your cause and <strong>grow your army</strong>. Mix and match the composition of your troops to fit your preferred battle tactics. Use infantry units, heavy armoured military vehicles, plasma cannon technology, drones and other flying units and even human skirmishers to achieve victory.<br/><br/>Use the battlefield to your advantage! <strong>Physics-based building demolition</strong> lets you generate a realistic set of tactical consequences, especially in urban areas.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer Mayhem: Skirmish and Online Battles</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif4.gif?t=1708701023"><br/>The excitement amplifies in <strong>skirmish and multiplayer modes</strong>, where <strong>you can play as three distinct factions</strong>: Founders, Movement, and Legion. <br/><br/>Engage in epic battles across vast strategic landscapes, testing your skills and military expertise. Every decision matters, impacting alliances, missions, and the overall survival of mankind.<br/><br/>Challenge your skills in skirmish and online multiplayer matches, facing off against AI or real-life human opponents in intense 1v1 and 2v2 battles.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penny’s Big Breakaway</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1955230/Pennys_Big_Breakaway/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ready. Set. YO! - Join Penny &amp; Yo-Yo in a kinetic 3D-platformer bursting with innovative gameplay! Showcase your catalog of tricks and chain impressive combos to deliver Penny &amp; Yo-Yo's perfect breakout performance. Take the stage with this vibrant pair in Penny’s Big Breakaway.<br/><br/>Penny is a street performer with big dreams; she has her own spin on what it takes to be a star! When Eddie the Emperor calls for new Palace Court Performers, Penny gets herself tangled in an audition she’ll never forget. A strange encounter with a Cosmic String transforms Penny’s Yo-Yo into a living creature with an appetite for snacks— and mayhem! Use Yo-Yo to help Penny clear her name, outrun the Emperor’s penguin army, and unravel the mystery of the Cosmic String. <br/><br/>Burst onto the scene in the fluorescent world of Macaroon, home to this over-and-under escape! Discover your true star power in this easy-to-play, difficult-to-master challenge. Penny’s Big Breakaway is the debut title from Evening Star.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-01-Supertitles.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Key Features: <br/><br/>Walk the Dog: Yo-Yo’s big appetite will earn an even bigger reward with snack power-ups! Use these tasty treats to temporarily transform Yo-Yo, granting it the abilities to improve movement speed, protect Penny from harm, and much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-02-WalktheDog.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Around the World: Flee from Eddie the Emperor’s massive penguin army as they chase you clear across the planet! These clumsy flightless birds patrol the halls, come bursting through walls, and will stop at nothing to seize you! Help out friendly denizens along the way and make use of your spectacular surroundings to evade your capturers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-03-AroundTheWorld.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Encore Stage: Play your way with multiple game modes! Show off your skills as you chain awesome combos and rack up multipliers in Story Mode. Take on the ultimate speedrunning challenge and dominate the leaderboard in Time Attack Mode. Redeem coins for bonus items, secret stages, and more unlockable extras.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-04-EncoreStage.gif?t=1708524042"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slave Zero X</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1903910/Slave_Zero_X/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/01_Intro_Banner.png?t=1708520359"><br/><br/>From the top of Megacity S1-9, the Sovereign Khan rules with fists of iron and flesh. Beneath the city’s rotting foundations, a vengeful warrior embarks on a journey to murder him. 4 years prior to the events of Slave Zero, Slave Zero X brings new life to a world where horrific, living machines known as Slaves are primed to become the latest tools of war in humanity’s long and bloody history. A secret band of warriors known as The Guardians hope to stop these biomecha from being unleashed upon the world, but one swordsman among their ranks has a different idea: use the enemy’s own weapon against them. By merging with a stolen Slave Unit Prototype, Shou will become a furious Devil in pursuit of killing a false God.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/02_Features_Banner.png?t=1708520359"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/03_Killer-Combos.gif?t=1708520359"><br/><strong>KILLER COMBOS:</strong> Use swift swordplay, explosive ordnance, and stylish combos against an army of meat and metal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/05_Death-From-Above.gif?t=1708520359"><br/><strong>DEATH FROM ABOVE:</strong> Air juggling, dashes, and frequent target switching allow for you to take down foes of any size while wall-jumping and platforming can help you outmaneuver your enemies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/Graffiti_row_01.png?t=1708520359"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/07_Fight-For-Your-Life.gif?t=1708520359"><br/><strong>FIGHT FOR YOUR LIFE:</strong> Conquer mini-bosses, set pieces, and climactic 1-on-1 encounters that offer intense challenges against unforgettable villains.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/09_Strength-is-Nothing.gif?t=1708520359"><br/><strong>STRENGTH IS NOTHING WITHOUT CONTROL:</strong> Use the Training Room to hone precise and powerful moves to string together devastating attack sequences.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/Graffitti_Row_02.png?t=1708520359"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/11_Battle-to-the-Beat.gif?t=1708520359"><br/><strong>BATTLE TO THE BEAT:</strong> A 90s-inspired soundtrack features heavy Drum’n’Bass and funky industrial music that adds to the thrill of combat.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/13_Feast-Your-Eyes.gif?t=1708520359"><br/><strong>FEAST YOUR EYES:</strong> A unique visual aesthetic combines nostalgic 2D sprites with an advanced lighting system and stylized 3D environments.<br/><br/><strong>THE END IS NEVER THE END:</strong> After completing the campaign, further challenges await in an expansive and frenetic ‘Crimson Citadel’ procedural challenge tower with an online high score leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/15_Footer_Banner.png?t=1708520359"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2379780/Balatro/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Balatro is a poker-inspired roguelike deck builder all about creating powerful synergies and winning big.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Endless_Possibility.gif?t=1708683444"><br/><br/>Combine valid poker hands with unique Joker cards in order to create varied synergies and builds. Earn enough chips to beat devious blinds, all while uncovering hidden bonus hands and decks as you progress. You’re going to need every edge you can get in order to reach the boss blind, beat the final ante and secure victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Jokers_Clean_Thin.gif?t=1708683444"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The definitive poker roguelike experience.<br/></li><li>Endless possibilities - every pick-up, discard and joker can dramatically alter the course of your run.<br/></li><li>In-depth campaign mode complete with 8 difficulties, as well as challenge, daily and seeded runs. </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Break_The_Game.gif?t=1708683444"><br/><br/>Deftly deploy an array of potent tools: different Decks, Jokers, Tarot cards, Planet cards, Spectral cards, and Vouchers. Use these versatile instruments to ignite a combo frenzy and turbocharge your poker hands, crafting electrifying, adrenaline-fueled synergies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro_5_Aces_GIF__HQ_.gif?t=1708683444"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 Jokers, each with their own unique abilities<br/></li><li>15 Decks with distinct modifiers to choose from for each run<br/></li><li>5 potential variants of each Joker which add further abilities<br/></li><li>22 Tarot cards variants that can enhance your regular playing cards<br/></li><li>11 Planet cards that help level up your possible poker hands<br/></li><li>32 Voucher cards to help provide permanent buffs for your current run</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Find_Your_Flow.gif?t=1708683444"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in Balatro’s distinctive psychedelic world. Let the synthwave soundtrack wash over you -  wind down, escape the daily grind and prepare to enter the ultimate roguelike flow state.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improve your collection and discover new cards and secrets with every single run.<br/></li><li>Make use of the in-depth stats screen to study your best hands, most used Jokers, and more!<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the CRT fuzz and enjoy detailed, hand-crafted pixel art.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Spectral_Pack.gif?t=1708683444"><br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F5mH3dNhjx2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro-join_the_discord.png?t=1708683444"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Stars: The Ur-Quan Masters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2645580/Free_Stars_The_UrQuan_Masters/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">You are the captain</h2><i>Free Stars: The Ur-Quan Masters</i>® is a classic space game that captures the charm of retro science-fiction, space combat, and high adventure. Your story begins as the captain of the last human starship, with Earth trapped under a hostile forcefield. You are the last hope for humanity in a fight for control of the galaxy, as you explore thousands of unknown worlds and get dozens of quirky aliens to help.<h2 class="bb_tag">Meet fascinating alien characters</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_alien_dialog_optimized-loop-count.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>​The galaxy is thriving with alien species, each with unique mysteries and motives. Meet an eclectic cast of characters, brought to life with full English voiceover. Ask sharp questions, make new friends, and exchange colorful insults.<h2 class="bb_tag">Adventure through HyperSpace</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_explore_hyperspace.gif_scaled-loop-count.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>Discover a vibrant galaxy filled with wonder, terror, and absurdity. Explore thousands of uncharted worlds across hundreds of stars, and gather important resources and technology.<h2 class="bb_tag">Battle your rivals in starship combat</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_super_melee_scaled-loop-count.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>Build your fleet and battle enemy starships, facing off against friends or the computer-controlled AI. Play action-packed Super Melee as its own mode, or as part of the single-player adventure – or choose automated combat to stay focused on the story.<h2 class="bb_tag">Experience a sci-fi classic – for free!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_precursors_intro.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>As a celebrated piece of gaming history, <i>Free Stars: The Ur-Quan Masters</i>® has also received wide acclaim for its story, characters, and setting. It was created as a love letter to classic science fiction like Douglas Adams, David Brin, and Jack Vance. In turn, its setting inspired a new wave of game creators, including the visionaries behind <i>Mass Effect</i>, <i>No Man’s Sky</i>, <i>Subnautica</i>, <i>Starfield</i>, <i>Fallout</i>, and <i>Stellaris</i> – to name just a few.<br/><br/>In 2002, the game was released under an open source license thanks to the generosity of Paul Reiche and Fred Ford. It continues to be available to play as a free download, for game historians and fans to enjoy.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Experience an open-world adventure, venturing through space to defeat the invading Ur-Quan and its hierarchy of battle thralls.<br/></li><li>Travel through extra-dimensional HyperSpace and discover nearly 500 unknown star systems filled with alien worlds.<br/></li><li>Fight enemies in fast-paced space battles with 25 different starships, each with its own unique attacks and powers.<br/></li><li>Befriend, threaten, or fight a diverse cast of aliens with unique personalities, from scary, to funny, to just plain weird.<br/></li><li>Explore thousands of planets, collecting resources and technology to upgrade your flagship and grow your fleet.<br/></li><li>Play standalone Super Melee to practice space combat against AI opponents or to duel against a friend.<br/></li><li>Mod and tinker with freely available, open-source code and content.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please, Touch The Artwork 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2600140/Please_Touch_The_Artwork_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Disclaimer:</strong><i> This is a short game made in</i> <strong>6 months</strong><i>. It's</i> <strong>100% FREE</strong><i>(no ads, no dlc's), made by a </i><strong>solo dev</strong><i> in honour of James Ensor’s 75 year remembrance.</i> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/extras/Steam3DRoomGIF_Wide.gif?t=1708440801"><br/><br/>Touch the artwork and help a lost skeleton artist find its way home in a surreal, hand-painted universe. <br/><br/>Collect hidden objects for its quirky inhabitants, solve casual puzzles, and restore cracks in the fabric of the paintings. <br/><br/>This slow paced relaxing adventure was carefully crafted from works by James Ensor, a Belgian pioneer in the world of Modern Art.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Hidden object adventure<br/></li><li>5 unique worlds<br/></li><li>Hints when stuck<br/></li><li>Casual point &amp; click gameplay<br/></li><li>Zoom-in for extra details<br/></li><li>Real hand-painted art<br/></li><li>Atmospheric relaxing sound<br/></li><li>Silly and quirky<br/></li><li>Slow-paced &amp; relaxing<br/></li><li>Fit for ages 12-99</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Small Mazes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2570630/20_Small_Mazes/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2570630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a puzzle game with twenty small mazes. If you solve the mazes, you beat the game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>It's about 1-2 hours long, maybe.<br/></li><li>You need a keyboard and mouse to play it. One person played through the whole game on the Steam Deck, but I tried it and think it's better on PC.<br/></li><li> A few puzzles require knowledge of English. No puzzle requires sound or audio to solve it. No puzzle requires being able to recognize different colors.</li></ul> <br/>I hope you enjoy it. <br/> 						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708702172"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708702172"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708702172"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708702172"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smalland: Survive the Wilds</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/768200/Smalland_Survive_the_Wilds/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>"Before the time of the giants, we lived freely under the Sun and Moon. Centuries have passed, but those stories of the surface world have been passed down through the generations. Now the giants are gone, and you, Vanguard, must venture out into the wilds once more, on an urgent mission. Be brave, and do not falter…"</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/TreeLookingup.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the vast “Land of the Small" </h2>Traverse lake sized puddles, scale skyscraper sized trees, scramble through cavernous cracks in roads, as you experience a huge open world from a new perspective. Explore dense forests, hazardous swamps and strange ruins left over from the time before. Uncover lore and knowledge from hidden NPCs scattered throughout the world and learn to survive in this vast wilderness. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Land_of_Small.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Tame and ride creatures</h2>Uncover recipes that will let you tame and ride an array of critters. Leap huge distances on the back of a Grasshopper, zoom around on a Damselfly, scurry from place-to-place on a Spider. This world and its inhabitants are yours to conquer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Mounts.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive together</h2>Play alongside friends with support for up to 10 players in multiplayer. Explore together, fight together, build together and survive the wilds as a team.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Together.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build encampments on the ground or amongst the trees</h2>Scavenge or refine resources to build your encampment with multiple material tiers, from leaves and twigs to sturdy stone. Pick your favourite spot in the world and build, or scale vast trees and claim your own settlement at the top.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Housing.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Craft powerful armour sets</h2>Collect powerful armours that provide you with resistances and abilities and mix them up to personalise your appearance. Glide through the skies in winged armour, swing from tree to tree with the grappling hook and many more. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Armors.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive the Wilds</h2>Most of the creatures you encounter will see you as lower on the food chain – Ants, Cockroaches, Beetles, Wasps, and Spiders all view you as a potential meal. Weather conditions and seasons are in constant flux so if you want to survive for another day, preparation is key.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Survive_the_Wilds.gif?t=1708514975"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider I-III Remastered Starring Lara Croft</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2478970/Tomb_Raider_IIII_Remastered_Starring_Lara_Croft/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2478970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover Lara Croft’s Original Adventures, Lovingly Restored</h2> <br/>Play the Original Three Tomb Raider Adventures: For the first time ever, play the complete experience with all expansions and secret levels on modern platforms in this definitive collection.<h2 class="bb_tag">Included Game Titles</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tomb Raider I + Unfinished Business<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider II + Golden Mask<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider III + The Lost Artifact</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><strong>Solve Ancient Mysteries</strong>: Uncover treasures of the ancient world by solving puzzles and unraveling mysteries lost to the ravages of time.<br/><br/><strong>Globe-trotting Adventure</strong>: Follow Lara Croft around the world and face off against deadly foes and dangerous myths.<br/><br/><strong>Lovingly Restored</strong>: Experience the classics boasting upgraded graphics, with the option to switch to the original polygon look at any time.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultros</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2386310/Ultros/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You wake up stranded, after seemingly crashing your ship on The Sarcophagus — a giant, space-drifting, cosmic uterus holding an ancient demonic being known as ULTROS. Trapped in the eternal loop of a black hole, you will have to explore The Sarcophagus and meet its inhabitants to understand the part you play. <br/><br/>Are you the gruesome breaker of this cycle, or can you become a link from destruction to rebirth? <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat1.png?t=1708612006"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat1.gif?t=1708612006"><br/>ULTROS is set in a multifaceted realm - a vast alien landscape teeming with life. Grounded in science fiction, ULTROS comes wrapped in an eccentric art style and a mystical soundtrack from the visionary El Huervo, renowned for his work on Hotline Miami. ULTROS explores meta-themes of mental health, life, death, and karmic cycles through deep lore and environmental storytelling.       <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat2.png?t=1708612006"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat2.gif?t=1708612006"><br/>Experience brutal, intimate, close-quarter combat with cosmic lifeforms, driven by a sense of urgency – where precision is paramount and every cut of your blade counts. Yet this intense combat is juxtaposed with cultivating the greenery and tending to plant life in The Sarcophagus, providing precious moments of contemplation and peace. In turn, this grants deeper access to obscured paths.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat3.png?t=1708612006"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat3.gif?t=1708612006"><br/>The rich world of ULTROS holds many secrets for those curious enough — and fearless enough — to seek them out. A unique loop-based mechanic will allow you to start over at key moments in the story, providing opportunities to unfold such secrets, unlock different areas of the world and new abilities on a branching skill tree. Experiment with and master your own specific fighting style as you explore the world of ULTROS. Each loop brings you closer to the truth...						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Will:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802530/Space_WillPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 10 in the prologue, 59 in the official version<br/>Galaxy: 2 in the prologue, 6 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><strong>Sixty basic cores, hundreds of base station equipment, and thousands of chips, you can freely cooperate and shoot through the dual-angle joystick operation in a survival Roguelike game! Explore the sci-fi space and build your strongest battleship!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Step 1: Choose a "core" as your basic role<br/>Step 2: Choose a "crew" as your initial weapon<br/>Step 3: Select a galaxy for exploration</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game will continuously collect new "units" or "chips" during the exploration process<br/>Using "crew" can expand weapons and enhance combat effectiveness for your warship<br/>Using "chips" can enhance various abilities of your warship</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Each "core" or "unit" has a maximum of 4 interfaces. When the interfaces are used up, you cannot equip more parts, but you can also infinitely increase the number of your interfaces!<br/>Each "crew" can use the right mouse button to rotate and adjust the optimal angle for combat</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game features dual joystick shooting, with the keyboard moving and the mouse aiming at the enemy. Of course, there are many weapons that can automatically attack or be placed in the scene as traps for use~</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_TITLE_FULLSCREEN.gif?t=1708080818"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_1.png?t=1708080818"><br/> <br/>In New Eden, 1695, communities of settlers are plagued by a dreadful curse. As Banishers, step into their lives, investigate the source of evil, unravel chilling mysteries, explore diverse landscapes, and interact with unforgettable characters whose fate lies in your hands.<br/><br/>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden is an all-new title crafted by renowned studio DON'T NOD, known for their acclaimed titles such as Life is Strange and Vampyr. Immerse yourself in an intimate narrative Action-RPG, taking you on an exhilarating journey between life, death, love and sacrifices.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_2.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_FANTASY.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Play as a couple of Banishers, Red and Antea, experienced spirit hunters entrusted with the daunting task of dispelling a malevolent curse through powerful rituals. Protect the living from the threat of lingering ghosts and specters, and become a beacon of hope in a world consumed by darkness.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_3.png?t=1708080818"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_NARATION_LOVE.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Experience a heart-wrenching love story between Antea Duarte and Red mac Raith. When Antea is killed and turned into a spirit, you find yourself facing a choice. Will you uphold your oath and ascend her soul, or will you sacrifice the living in the hope of bringing her back? Your decisions will shape the fate of New Eden’s inhabitants - may they be living or dead, and determine the end of your journey.<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>BLAME</strong> the living and sacrifice their lives, holding them responsible for their actions<br/></li><li><strong>BANISH</strong> souls of the departed, condemning them to eternal suffering<br/></li><li><strong>ASCEND</strong> souls, liberating them from eternal sorrow and granting them serenity</li></ul><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_4.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_COMBAT.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Banishers are specialized in combat against undead creatures, such as specters or ghosts. Combine Red's physical arsenal with Antea's supernatural powers in a dynamic combat system. Find your own style by mixing weapon attacks and spiritual abilities. Powerful synergies will lead you to defeat New Eden’s most dangerous enemies and bosses.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_6.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_SKILL.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Unleash the full power of the Banishers by unlocking new gear and supernatural abilities. By exploring New Eden, you will find ancient artifacts, trinkets and valuable resources to enhance your equipment in preparation of future fights. In addition to your arsenal, progress in Antea’s skill trees to upgrade her devastating spectral powers and unseal new combos.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_5.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_EXPLORATION.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Investigate haunting cases in a mystical world full of dark secrets. Discover New Eden, a North America settlement marked by terrible stories and secrets of its tormented inhabitants. Understanding each resident’s motivations will be essential to guide your decisions throughout the game.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_7.png?t=1708080818"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Ninja Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_9" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🥋🐾 WELCOME TO 100 NINJA CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🗡️</h2>🗡️Join the cutest adventure in the Ninja world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of ninja themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game.<br/>😊Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x200.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Ninja Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Extra.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816000/100_Ninja_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815980/100_Ninja_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Artbook.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x1.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_10" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_11" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Tales</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1465070/Legendary_Tales/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_07.gif?t=1707433150"><br/>Are you ready for adventure? Collect loot, destroy enemies, learn magic, craft your own items and head out on epic quests to conquer the evil that lurks beneath the earth. Play Alone or with friends; Legendary Tales is the ultimate fantasy VR experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/00.Steam_MiniTitle_RPG.png?t=1707433150"><br/>Grow your own unique character through gameplay and work your way through an extensive skill tree.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/01.Steam_MiniTitle_Multiplayer.png?t=1707433150"><br/>Supports Up-to 4 player Co-op<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/02.Steam_MiniTitle_Magic.png?t=1707433150"><br/>Master the art of magic and destroy enemies with fire, ice and lightning.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/03.Steam_MiniTitle_RNGItems.png?t=1707433150"><br/>Collect an almost limitless amount of items thanks to random number generation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/04.Steam_MiniTitle_Physics.png?t=1707433150"><br/>An amazing physics based fighting system with destructible objects and scenery.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/05.Steam_MiniTitle_Crafting.png?t=1707433150"><br/>Craft your own items,potions and upgrade crafted items with an in depth crafting system.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/06.Steam_MiniTitle_AboutLT.png?t=1707433150"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_05.gif?t=1707433150"><br/>Are you ready to step down into the darkness? Explore winding roads and ruined castles that will take you down to the heart of the underworld, to defeat the evil corrupting the land. But be careful down there, the road is dangerous so you best bring a friend. Traverse the landscape, Bludgeon, slice and decimate skeletons with melee weapons, sneak up on a goblin with ranged weapons or destroy a demon from afar with destructive magic.<br/>Physics based melee combat, Improved Ai, an immersive crafting system, a myriad of weapons and up to 4 player co-op; this is an RPG, fantasy, adventure that is waiting for you to create your own Legendary Tales.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/07.Steam_MiniTitle_Generation.png?t=1707433150"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/08.Steam_MiniTitle_VR.png?t=1707433150"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_04.gif?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">Built from the ground up for VR; Legendary Tales will throw you into an immersive fantasy world, suitable for any PCVR platform with customisable graphics settings to ensure you get the smoothest possible experience.</ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/09.Steam_MiniTitle_Mutiplayer.png?t=1707433150"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_03.gif?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">Up to 4 players can play Legendary Tales in co-op mode. Grab some friends, trade some items, and head down into the dungeon to fight your way through the darkness together.</ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/010.Steam_MiniTitle_Physics.png?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">The physics in Legendary Tales was built to mimic the way real weapons feel and act as close as possible while still being fun to play. Weapons have their own weight so that larger swings will do more damage. Not only that but enemies and destructible items also react to how hard you hit them for a truly engaging experience. </ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/011.Steam_MiniTitle_Items.png?t=1707433150"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_06.gif?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">Want to try sneaky kills with a dagger? Hit your enemies from afar with a bow? Or just mash some faces with a morning star? There are a host of different weapon types to suit your play style so find what works for you! And for every weapon type you will find so many variations on their stats thanks to random number generated items. The items are classed into five categories ranging from normal to Legendary. which not only look awesome but have special abilities. What abilities? You’ll have to get one for yourself to find out.</ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/014.Steam_MiniTitle_Skilltree.png?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">As you fight your way through the world, your character will grow based on how you play. But there’s more to growth than just how you fight, work your way through the magic and skills available to truly bring your character to the next level.</ul><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/012.Steam_MiniTitle_Combatskills.png?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">Weapons are fun and all but through the skill tree you can improve your abilities with combat skills or find yourself a Legendary item with their own special abilities and even more, you can upgrade their skills! </ul> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/013.Steam_MiniTitle_Crafting.png?t=1707433150"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_02_new.gif?t=1707433150"><br/>If hunting for weapons in the dungeons isn’t for you then we have good news! You can create your own weapons with ingredients found on your adventures, or by honing the weapons you’ve collected. You can also make potions to prepare deep dungeon crawling and disassemble items you found during your adventures to get ingredients and enhance your crafted weapons or potions with them.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_01.gif?t=1707433150"><br/>Get ready for an epic adventure in VR! Put on your headset, find some friends and head into the dungeon to start creating your own Legendary Tales.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1708019001"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal Richards (formerly of Echos)</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1708019001"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about the future of Sheepy, limited edition merch and more.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soak &amp; Splash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2051500/Soak__Splash/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2051500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the Soak &amp; Splash! Get ready to sweat, socialize, and have a blast with your friends in this unique game that combines the best of traditional sauna culture with modern party fun.<br>
<br>
First, step into the steamy sauna and feel the heat and humidity envelop your body.<br>
<br>
Once everyone is inside, it's time to start the fun. You can start by whisking each other with broom.<br>
<br>
Feeling competitive? You can also fight with other players with sauna equipment. Or you can simply relax and enjoy the company of your friends, chatting, singing, or telling jokes.<br>
<br/>
Finally, when you've had enough of the sauna, you can cool off in the nearby pool or shower.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, this game is all about having fun, bonding with your friends, and experiencing the unique benefits of sauna culture. So why wait? Download game and get ready to sweat, laugh, and enjoy life to the fullest!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/315210/Suicide_Squad_Kill_the_Justice_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Rocksteady Studios, the creators of the Batman: Arkham series, Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is a genre-defying third-person action shooter where the ultimate band of misfits must do the impossible to save the world: Kill the Justice League.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/SSKTJL_Intro.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Join the newly “recruited” members of Amanda Waller’s infamous Task Force X (aka the Suicide Squad), Harley Quinn, Deadshot, Captain Boomerang and King Shark, as they set out on an impossible mission to Kill the Justice League. Drop into an expansive and dynamic open-world Metropolis ravaged by Brainiac’s invasion and terrorized by the heroes who once protected it. <br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/Traversal_2.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Each Squad member brings their own traversal mechanics to help them navigate a sprawling and battle-torn Metropolis, combining free-roaming exploration and combat verticality for an unforgettable experience. Players are free to experiment with a variety of different play styles to unleash maximum damage on their enemies. Whether in single player or online with up to three of your friends, players can take on this suicide mission their own way.<br/><br/>Post-launch, players can expect a continuously evolving Metropolis with free new playable villains, environments, weapons, in-game events, and more, all included with purchase of the base game.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788630/Nothing_Together/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play together. Maybe.<br/><br/>Just do Nothing as the timer goes up and climb the leaderboards. If you do Something, you lose.<br/><br/>Play in <strong>Together </strong>mode, where up to 20 players unite to do Nothing, or compete with other players in <strong>Battle Royale</strong> to find out who's the best at doing Nothing!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161700/Persona_3_Reload/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a transfer student thrust into an unexpected fate when entering the hour "hidden" between one day and the next. Awaken an incredible power and chase the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fight for your friends, and leave a mark on their memories forever. <br/><br/>Persona 3 Reload is a captivating reimagining of the genre-defining RPG, reborn for the modern era.<br/><br/>Key Features: <br/>- Experience the pivotal game of the Persona series faithfully remade with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, and signature stylish UI. <br/><br/>-Fully immerse yourself in an emotional, gripping journey with new scenes, character interactions, and additional voiceover.<br/><br/>- Choose how to meaningfully spend each day through various activities, from exploring the Port Island to forging genuine bonds with beloved characters.<br/><br/>- Build and command your optimal team to take down otherworldly Shadows and climb closer to the truth.<br/><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Deluxe Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook: Filled with 64 pages of character art, concept art, backgrounds and other illustrations from the game!<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack: Listen to newly arranged tracks from the original Persona 3 plus all-new tracks from Persona 3 Reload, presented by the Atlus sound team for a total of 60 new songs.</li></ul><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Premium Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack<br/></li><li>Persona 3 Reload DLC Pack:  P5R Phantom Thieves Costume Set, P5R Shujin Academy Costume Set, P5R Persona Set 1, P5R Persona Set 2 , P5R BGM Set, P4G Yasogami High Costume Set, P4G Persona Set</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1131620/Dominion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Expand a small kingdom to a mighty Dominion!  <br/><br/>Play the Spiel des Jahres winning boardgame beloved by millions around the world. This is the officially licensed implementation.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Reigning.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Discover the game that defined a genre, Dominion was first to popularize deck-building and remains a staple of tabletop. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/GrowYourKingdom.png?t=1707010484">Collect as many Victory Points as you can by building a powerful deck. Your deck starts out a small sad set of Estates and Coppers, but you hope that by the end of the game it will be brimming with Gold, Provinces, and the inhabitants and structures of your kingdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/BuildEngine.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Choose wisely among the 10 cards available in the tableau to create the strongest combos to dominate your opponent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CollectAllExpansions.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Make your games more exciting with additional cards and rules from up to 15 expansions including the recent Plunder expansion! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/NearInfiniteVariety.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Over one hundred thirty-two septillion possible Kingdom combinations, 500+ cards, 15 and counting expansions, and ongoing promo packs make Dominion one of the most extensive and replayable boardgames in the hobby. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CompeteComputer.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Sharpen your skills with solitaire style solo play against a robust AI, with four levels of difficulty. Our innovative AI learns through self-play. Earn Achievements and win in Recommended Sets against each AI level. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/PlayWithFriends.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Join up to 6 players online through your device or pass and play among your friends. Play ranked or unranked matchmaking, with realtime and asynchronous modes. Set up a private table for a family game, challenge a stranger in the lobby, or invite a friend!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Daily.png?t=1707010484"><br/>A daily ritual to relax with over a cup of coffee. Try the Daily Dominion, a free puzzle level available to players around the world. Practice your strategy to keep up a winning streak and climb the leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CrossPlatform.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Play from any supported device, whenever you want, after verifying your email in-game. Join games with opponents on platforms other than your own to enjoy the largest possible multiplayer pool and speedy matchmaking. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/JoinCommunity.png?t=1707010484"><br/>With an active Discord and online community, make new friends or challenge new people to a game. Export and share kingdoms and game summaries to compare strategies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/FreeToPlay.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Download the game that started it all for free! The base set of Dominion is available at no charge. Try the rotation of expansion cards in the Daily at no cost once per day. Jump into a lobby game with expansions enabled to try before you buy. Only the host needs to own the expansions.    <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Intro.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Learn the ropes in this easy to pick-up, hard to master title. Play one of the most highly regarded strategy tabletop games of all time through our simple tutorial.  The core loop is easy to follow, but offers a wealth of strategy to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>1-6 player</strong> support<br/></li><li><strong>500 </strong> plus <strong>cards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Solo play</strong> against four AI difficulties<br/></li><li><strong>Async </strong>&amp; <strong>real-time</strong> multiplayer<br/></li><li><strong>Ranked</strong> &amp; <strong>unranked</strong> matchmaking<br/></li><li><strong>Lobby</strong> &amp; <strong>Private game</strong> tables<br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform multiplayer</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform purchases</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Daily challenge</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Challenging AI</strong> that learns through self-play<br/></li><li><strong>Recommended Sets</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Customize</strong>, save &amp; share <strong>Kingdoms</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Achievements</strong>, <strong>Stats </strong>&amp; <strong>Leaderboards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Pass &amp; Play</strong> mode<br/></li><li>Automated <strong>score-keeping</strong> &amp; hints<br/></li><li><strong>Smart-play</strong> options to streamline gameplay<br/></li><li><strong>Jumbo mode</strong> for readability on phones<br/></li><li><strong>Turbo mode</strong> to zoom through games quickly<br/></li><li><strong>Tutorial</strong> &amp; <strong>Rules</strong><br/></li><li><strong>4 languages</strong>: English, Japanese, German, French<br/></li><li><strong>15 expansions</strong> plus three promo packs </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Awards for the Boardgame</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Awards.png?t=1707010484"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/881020/Granblue_Fantasy_Relink/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/881020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Story<br/>
Granblue Fantasy takes place in the Sky Realm, a world where myriad islands float in a great blue expanse. Take your role as captain of a skyfaring crew, joined by a scrappy little dragon named Vyrn and a young girl with mysterious powers named Lyria. Together you sail with a colorful cast of crewmates, including kings and misfits alike, for Estalucia, a fabled island beyond the end of the skies.<br/>
<br/>
In the Zegagrande Skydom, islands are guarded by powerful creatures known as primal beasts and winds carry tales of a secretive organization known as the Church of Avia. Unveil a web of intrigue reaching far beyond the borders of Zegagrande and engage in a battle for the fate of the Sky Realm itself.<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay<br/>
Engage in real-time combat with a party of four in this character action RPG—choose from a diverse roster of skyfarers, each with their own unique weapons, skills, and combat styles. Teamwork makes the dream work with party-based mechanics such as Link Attacks and Chain Bursts to help you crush foes in spectacular fashion. Tackle quests solo or with the help of others for up to 4-player co-op and take down treacherous foes to score rare loot to further enhance your gear. Every enemy and party formation has its own strengths and weaknesses—the key to victory lies in working out how these pieces fit together.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced combat not your thing? Assist modes can provide accessibility for gamers of all skill levels. Toggle on Full Assist to have all actions performed automatically during battle!<br/>
<br/>
The Sky Realm is rich in lore and history. Browse Lyria's journal at any point during the game to access a trove of writings on the world's peoples, places, and more. In addition to the wealth of side quests available, Fate Episodes allow you to delve into the backstories of each member of your crew!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stranded</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2636410/Stranded/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Stranded is a 2D game with procedurally (randomly) generated levels. Heavily inspired by exploration, creation and character development games, such as Forager, Don't Starve Together and Stardew Valley.<br/><br/>An action roguelike with a lot of collecting and creation, start with absolutely nothing and using the resources available, build bases, improve your equipment and skills by facing hordes and villages of enemies, go as far as you can, but remember: Once dead, you will have to start everything from <strong>ZERO</strong>!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital of the Undead</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2778880/Hospital_of_the_Undead/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Hospital of the Undead is an indie horror survival game viewed from a first person perspective. Explore an abandoned hospital for useful items that help you progress while avoiding a number of zombies waiting to catch you.<h2 class="bb_tag">Details</h2>You wake up in a dizzy state only to find yourself in a nightmarish hospital overrun by a number of zombies. You need to find the keys to the front door to escape. Search the hospital for keys, equipment and consumables that could be helpful for advancing. Your sanity is affected by darkness so avoid spending too much time in unlit areas. Shoot or run from zombies to prevent getting caught.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778880/extras/SS1.png?t=1708704454"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>Explore the hospital. Unlock doors and search the furnishings for useful inventory items such as <i>keys, weapon, ammunition, batteries, medicines</i> etc. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778880/extras/DrawerSS.gif?t=1708704454"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778880/extras/KeySS.gif?t=1708704454"><br/><br/>Explore unilluminated rooms by finding something that helps you see in the dark. Avoid spending too much time in them to preserve your sanity.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778880/extras/NVDSS.gif?t=1708704454"><br/><br/>Shoot zombies to prevent them from catching you as it leads to an instant death. Shooting without an aim reduces accuracy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778880/extras/SS.gif?t=1708704454"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maze Time</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2823360/Maze_Time/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2823360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Maze Time is a simple 3D walking simulator.Your task in it is to look for a way out in the mazes to go to another level.<br>
In this game you will have to wander through the mazes to find a way out.This is a simple and relaxing game that will help you pass the evening.<br>
<br>
Key features :<br>
<br>
1) 12 levels<br>
2)Relaxing gameplay<br/>
3)pleasant soundtrack						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHERNO</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2640250/CHERNO/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2640250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Game based on the creepy pasta "The Russian Sleep Experiment", tells the story of an intern who needs to do his internship in a clinic in the Soviet Union, while an explosion occurs that leaves them without electricity. With a flashlight and the help of his supervisor he will try to escape without being devoured by the experiments.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2640250/extras/descripcion_gif_1.gif?t=1708703874"><br/><br/>You must look for all the clues that the doctor has left you to go down each floor and thus be able to get out. But it won't be easy since you shouldn't let yourself be touched by the experiments that are found in each room of the building.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2640250/extras/descripcion_gif_2.gif?t=1708703874"><br/><br/>The game has 5 levels where you will enter the mysterious building where the Russian experiments are located, use your detective skills to escape from each level and thus leave the clinic alive. In each level you will find clues that will be part of the key to get out. Show your ingenuity to be able to escape without being touched by the experiments.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2640250/extras/descripcion_0.png?t=1708703874"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Jump Guys</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2757810/The_Jump_Guys/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a physics-based platformer. It consists of 40 levels of a platformer that can be played like one player or with friends up to 4 players and a variety of 12 arenas where you will fight with your friends as a team or against each other. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757810/extras/v_1.gif?t=1708701038"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757810/extras/v_2.gif?t=1708701038"><br/><br/>A platformer as a part of the game consists of locations with different physics obstacles. 1 - the main obstacle is a trampoline. 2 - the main obstacles are an ice, a sled, snowballs. 3 - the main obstacles are a rope and logs on the water. 4 - a jetpack. Each location has a candy which you have to carry to the finish of the level. You can pass a level without a candy, by doing a speedrun only but you have to keep in mind that a candy and speedrun give you stars which you can use to open new levels. These levels will be passed by you or you with your friends by a network multiplayer or local multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757810/extras/v_3.gif?t=1708701038"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757810/extras/v_4.gif?t=1708701038"><br/><br/>The game has 12 different arenas also.<br/> - basketball<br/> - football<br/> - soccer<br/> - volleyball<br/> - the last life<br/> - boxes to one row<br/> - collecting<br/> - death match<br/> - catch up<br/> - obstacle course<br/> - holding a flag<br/><br/>Have fun with friends as you like. These arenas have a jetpack which changes the gameplay radically<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757810/extras/v_5.gif?t=1708701038"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757810/extras/v_6.gif?t=1708701038"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I commissioned some mice 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2798300/I_commissioned_some_mice_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2798300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A hidden object game where you must find all the mice and cheese to complete each level.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key features:</h2>🖼️ 15 Unique artworks<br/>❓ 1500+ Hidden objects total<br/>🐁 750+ Mice<br/>🧀 750+ Cheese.<br/>💡 ∞ Unlimited hints if you get stuck<br/>♻️ Restore a small number of hidden objects to a painting so you can find them again!<br/>🎵 Music and ambiance for each artwork<br/>⌨️ Use your keyboard to move/zoom in if you have no scroll wheel<br/>💾 3x save slots<br/>🗑️ Reset progress entirely and play again<br/>🕒 Timer included to show how long you took to complete each level<h2 class="bb_tag">Context:</h2>The brief was simple. I commissioned artists to create a fantasy world, and hide as many mice and cheese as they can inside it. Now it’s your job to find them all! With 15 art pieces to choose from, and 1500+ hidden objects you will have a lot of searching to do.<h2 class="bb_tag">Controls:</h2>Use your mouse to move around the image and zoom in / out. When you find a hidden object, click it and it will disappear. You can also use WASD to move and the arrow keys to zoom.<h2 class="bb_tag">Difficulty:</h2>A full range of difficulty is included, but all levels start unlocked, your progress is saved as you play, and you can use hints if you get stuck.<h2 class="bb_tag">Get immersed:</h2>Each painting has its own music and ambiance to help you connect with the world, as you search for everything.<h2 class="bb_tag">Replayable</h2>You can restore a small number of hidden objects back into a painting so you can find them again! It’s much harder when there are only a few hidden objects left (especially randomly). You can also use up to 3 save slots so you can replay without progress loss. Alternatively, you can reset your progress for the entire game if you’d like to start over.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eternal Burden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2744070/Eternal_Burden/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In Eternal Burden you play as William, a restless soul trying to go back in time to get rid of his burdens, symbolized by a metal ball chained to his body. Use the ball to your advantage to get over obstacles and to solve the physics based puzzles that block your path to liberation.<br/><br/>-Change the ball's size as you deem fit in order to overcome any obstacle<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744070/extras/ball_small_616.jpg?t=1708696819"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744070/extras/ball_big_616.jpg?t=1708696819"><br/><br/>-Solve a unique set of physics based puzzles<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744070/extras/balance_616.jpg?t=1708696819"><br/><br/>-Use your brain to place the correct amount of weight on each scale in order to open the door<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744070/extras/scale_616.jpg?t=1708696819"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save Giant Girl from monsters 4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2830690/Save_Giant_Girl_from_monsters_4/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2830690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A flight simulator game.<br>
Save the giant girl from the monsters attacking her using a helicopter.<br>
<br>
Compete with other players to see who can score the most points and last longer while save the girl.<br>
<br>
You control helicopter on WASD.<br>
And shoot bullets on the left mouse button or rockets on the right mouse button.<br>
<br/>
Your task is to destroy all the enemies attacking the giant girl.<br/>
<br/>
The game has achievements and a leaderboard.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neon Fuga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668070/Neon_Fuga/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Shoot'em up, inspired by old games, which can be played on the difficulty that the player likes. Do you just want to relax after encountering minor difficulties? Or test yourself by breaking through waves of strong and tenacious enemies?<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
<br>
- control the ship as it is convenient: with one mouse, gamepad*, keyboard.<br>
- 30 types of enemies. Each species is represented in 5 subspecies, with a characteristic manner of movement.<br>
- 5 bosses.<br/>
- a personal music track for each enemy.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
*A computer mouse is required to navigate the pause menu						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mika's Battle S</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2817550/Mikas_Battle_S/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Mika's Battle S is a 2D platform action game based on the story of a warrior who has been commanded to defend Sunshineland territory against the attacks from the enemy soldiers belonging to the Rogho Corporation.<br/><br/>Mika, one of the best warriors of the Sunshineland which is famously known as the land of sunflowers, has been commanded to defend the Eastern border area of the territory while other members of the group were taking care of the Northern and Western Sunshineland border areas. Rogho Corporation is one of the Evil organizations which toppled the previous Government of Rogholand. They took full control over the territory of Rogholand and its people. <br/><br/>Since the Rogho Corporation took over the territory there have been reports of border clashes frequently. After a few months of coming to power, they went a bit too far by declaring a war against Sunshineland. So, the Sunshineland warriors, a group of five formidable female super soldiers, have been commanded by the leader of Sunshineland Army to fight against the intruders and to protect the territory at any cost. Rogho Corporation deployed the formidable human as well as robot warriors around the border areas. Moreover, the enemies took a few civilians as hostages. They started launching multiple missiles towards the Sunshineland territory which had reportedly destroyed some of the agricultural fields, a few buildings, and a few sunflower gardens. There were no reports of military or civilian casualties. Most of the civilians of the Sunshineland were taken to the underground Bomb shelters temporarily for their protection.<br/><br/>You play as Mika, one of the strongest Sunshineland warriors and your mission is to protect the Eastern border area of your territory and defeat the enemy forces while rescuing the civilians. Will you be able to accomplish your mission?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817550/extras/mbr_gif_01.gif?t=1708698921"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>15 Levels with stunning visuals!</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Lots of formidable enemy soldiers having different kinds of weapons!</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>2 Boss Battles!</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Lots of deadly traps which includes saws, spikes etc.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>3 Firing modes which includes machine gun, laser and missile launcher modes!</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Ability to double jump.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Collect items like health box, ammo, blue gems, crown etc. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Story Driven. Anime aesthetic, and animated cut-scenes! </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Challenging situations!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817550/extras/mbr_gif_5.gif?t=1708698921"><br/><br/>Note: I am a solo game developer and I have done all of the graphics, artwork, character design, animation, programming except for the music. I hope you will enjoy the game.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817550/extras/mbr_gif_03.gif?t=1708698921"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinbot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2826410/Pinbot/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2826410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Synopsis</h2>Arks, mammoth interstellar vessels, usher hordes of Earth’s inhabitants away from the overpopulated confines of their homeworld, embarking on epic odysseys towards distant extrasolar colonies. These voyages span decades, with the colonists slumbering in cryogenic stasis, tended to by a myriad of machines. A diverse array of robots tirelessly manages everything from crafting essential commodities to constructing prospective settlements and safeguarding the colossal spacecraft.<br/>Contrary to the vast cosmic emptiness previously assumed, the void is teeming with robotic entities that thrive on consuming metallic remnants—relics of vanished extraterrestrial civilizations. However, the arks are fortified with an intricate network of defense mechanisms, among which the most intriguing is the Pinbot. This enigmatic guardian combines curiosity and efficiency, embodying an unparalleled fusion of technology and artificial intelligence.<h2 class="bb_tag">The game</h2><strong>Pinbot reimagines the timeless breakout game in an immersive 3D setting</strong>. Traditional brick formations now morph into incubators nurturing alien robots, demanding swift destruction! In this robotic realm, every element is mechanized—be it the player’s paddle, the antagonizing entities, or the enticing power-ups. Amidst the chaos, a series of relentless machines persist in their tasks, inevitably hindering your progress and adding an extra layer of challenge to your quest for dominance.<br/><strong>Embark on a journey through five distinct levels, each housing a series of rooms. Encounter a total of 53 unique rooms, each presenting its own set of challenges and surprises</strong>. To progress from one level to the next, conquer all rooms within that level in a single game. Brace yourself for a dynamic encounter where every aspect pulsates with robotic vitality, amplifying the thrill of the classic breakout concept.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kitt's Quest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2806870/Kitts_Quest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2806870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take the role of Kitt, a young warrior fox, in a fight to save her land from the evil invaders! Kitt's Quest is a 3D platforming adventure where you must fight enemies, solve puzzles and defeat bosses to learn new powers, unlock costumes and discover new areas. Explore 6 worlds through over 20 levels, find the Soul Crystals to increase your health and spellpoints, unlock armor and staff sets that grant you upgrades like more health, stronger spells and more!<h2 class="bb_tag">The Story</h2><br/> As a child, Kitt witnessed the invasion of her homeland, powerless, she was taken in by Cato, the village's old wizard. Cato took care of Kitt and taught her how to use magic spells. Now grown up and stronger, Kitt seeks to defeat the invaders and free her village.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban Chase</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2700550/Urban_Chase/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Urban Chase" immerses players in a lively city chase between police and mischievous thieves. In this whimsical world, players take on the role of a police officer, engaging in thrilling pursuits to apprehend playful troublemakers.<br/><br/>Currently, players can exclusively experience the game from the perspective of a skillful police officer. Utilize your running skills to navigate the charming low-poly cityscape and apprehend the mischievous thieves who are up to playful antics.<br/><br/>Features:<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700550/extras/Urban_Chase_Official_Trailer.gif?t=1708698867"><br/>Cute 3D Low Poly Graphics: Immerse yourself in a charming world with adorable characters and a visually appealing low-poly art style.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700550/extras/Urban_Chase_Official_Trailer__1_.gif?t=1708698867"><br/>Diverse Stages: Thanks to the 12 stages that become progressively challenging and entertaining, there is no room for boredom.<br/><br/>Running and Capture: Chase down the mischievous thieves by showcasing your running skills, adding a dynamic element to the pursuit. Enhance your pursuit with boosters and handcuffs, special items designed to aid in the capture.<br/><br/>Playful Thieves: The thieves in "Urban Chase" are full of mischief, making each pursuit a delightful and unpredictable experience.<br/><br/>Single-player Focus: As of now, players can exclusively enjoy the game in single-player mode, taking on the role of the police officer.<br/><br/>"Urban Chase" offers a delightful and lighthearted experience as you dash through the city streets, chasing down playful thieves in this whimsical 3D low-poly world. Get ready for a charming adventure where cuteness meets crime-fighting fun!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 257th Element</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2648640/The_257th_Element/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2648640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							◇◇◇◇◇The 257th Element◇◇◇◇◇<br/><br/>SYNOPSIS<br/><br/>    A time not too far from now. To find a solution for the food problem caused by a growing population, every country has been investing huge budgets into scientific research to increase every single mass with as limited time and energy as possible. As a result, new elements the 119th and beyond were discovered and created one after another, and finally, a genius scientist in Tokyo named Hikojuro Araki succeeded in creating the 256th element, Araraginium, which is a dreamy element that creates every being out of nothingness.<br/>   However, at the very moment when the first experiment in the world to create Araraginium just began, by an unexpected accident, it diffused all over Tokyo and disappeared.<br/>   A few days later, appalling incidents started happening all of a sudden, all-over Tokyo; people who were thought to be dead started emerging back to life as if they had never been dead, not even once. They all had a memory before their death, and actually, were those who passed away during the time period between the accident and 72 hours before that.<br/>   Due to their relevance with the accident, those people were called Araragi Human.<br/>This story takes place several years after this in Tokyo…<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2648640/extras/ヘッダー3.png?t=1708693194"><br/><br/><br/>＞＞＞Tokipedia<br/><br/>◇Shinsei Shonogamigakuen High School<br/>The school where Tokimune and his friends go to. It has a conspicuous interior with contemporary and futuristic designs. There are classrooms, cafeteria, and rooftop where students can go. The rooftop is covered with futuristic invisible walls to prevent anyone from falling out, and a lot of students come and hang out there during lunch break.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2648640/extras/私立新生床之上学園高等学校.png?t=1708693194"><br/><br/>◇The Island Where Dreams Come True<br/>An island that has emerged in the Pacific Ocean out of nowhere after the Araraginium experiment and accident. It has become a tourist attraction as a miracle island. There are forests that look like mangrove jungles on this island, which offers a scenery that you rarely or never find in the coastal waters of Tokyo. Besides resort facilities, it also has camping facilities for students.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2648640/extras/夢の成り島.png?t=1708693194"><br/><br/>◇Cafe CHIENYAROU<br/>A cafe where Tokimune and his friends go very often. You can play all the retro games and read all the manga books as much as you would like. It even has a space with a bowling alley. There is a Japanese-style space in this cafe, where you can enjoy its Japanese afternoon tea.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2648640/extras/喫茶　ＣＨＩＥＮＹＡＲＯＵ.png?t=1708693194"><br/><br/>◇Araragi Human<br/>People who passed away during the time period between the accident and 72 hours before the Araraginium experiment. They are just the same as normal human beings, except that they will disappear if no one (besides Araragi Humans) recognizes them. In other words, if no one sees them, they will disappear instantly. <br/>Therefore, the government has installed and placed a small, invisible camera device for observation, so called “Invisible Watcher” on the majority of Araragi Humans. They are monitors 24x7 by the government’s monitoring organization (the Araragi Watcher) through footages sent from the device. This prevents Araragi Humans from disappearing.<br/><br/>◇“Elements” in this story<br/>When we talk about “elements” in this story, it doesn’t mean an atom. “Element” is used as an abstract concept that contain properties. For example, Araraginium is not an atom that has 256 protons. Elements beyond the 200th are something completely different from atoms which are described by the number of protons and neutrons. Many of them are constituted by minuscule elements smaller than protons and invisible elements. To sum it up, those elements are called the Gaia elements. Detailed explanation about the Gaia elements is too hard to comprehend for high school students, so we will not touch on that in this story. Yet, it seems like Hamakado has got most of the idea. Therefore, if you are ever interested, we would recommend you ask her.<br/><br/>◇CAUTION<br/>Streaming of this game and monetization of this game play videos are strictly prohibited.if you want to know more,please check our thread.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tap Drift Car</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2821810/Tap_Drift_Car/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2821810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a game to control the car drifting through the corner, simulate the real drifting.Higher levels of cars can be got by merge,that have better handling.A variety of different cool cars waiting for you to collect, 3000 different game tracks waiting for you to challenge one by one.<br>
<br>
The game starts, the car will automatically advance.press the mouse and turn the car right,release the mouse and turn the car left.So easy.<br>
The game has a large number of levels, the difficulty gradually increases. <br>
The game automatically generates a large amount of gold each day, which is used to purchase cars that can be merge into higher level cars and challenge more difficult levels.<br>
The excitement and thrill of racing can be experienced in the game.<br>
The game is simple and very decompress, so come and enjoy the immersive gaming experience.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the Breach</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2752930/Beyond_the_Breach/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2752930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2752930/extras/Interact.gif?t=1708690024"><br/>Beyond The Breach is a 3D, sci-fi, single-player, first-person, narrative, puzzle where you as a player will take on the role of an AI robot who is undergoing a seemingly ordinary test in a dystopian world, only to realize that you exist in a society where they mistreat robots who defy their rules. This leads you to become a deviant robot who will gain special abilities like detecting electrical energy, hacking into scientists, and controlling them to aid your escape. Your mission is to break free from this oppressive environment and rescue other robots like yourself who are also imprisoned. The game combines stealth and puzzle gameplay, presenting players with the challenge of escaping from society while also giving them the responsibility to save other robots.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RplGen Studio</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2550090/RplGen_Studio/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2550090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							RplGenStudio is a specialized video production software designed for creating videos similar to galgames, tabletop game replays, and audio-visual novels.<br>
<br>
These types of videos are characterized by their fixed structure and lengthy duration, which means that using traditional video editing software to create them would involve a tremendous amount of repetitive work. As a result, RplGenStudio was developed. RplGenStudio was primarily designed to assist content creators in crafting their video stories as easily as writing a document, allowing them to dedicate more of their energy to the creation of visuals and content rather than getting bogged down in the intricate and tedious process of video editing.<br>
<br>
Why choose RplGenStudio?<br>
<br>
1. Maximum Customization: Unlike conventional tabletop game replay video production software, RplGenStudio allows users to highly customize their visuals. In addition to the typical combination of character illustrations and speech bubble frames, it also supports chat window-style performances resembling instant messaging apps. All visual elements can be freely moved and configured with transition animations and text effects, maximizing design flexibility. RplGenStudio also includes practical dice rolling and hit point animations, with plans for future updates to cater to various tabletop game replay video needs.<br/>
<br/>
2. Professional Exporting: RplGenStudio supports built-in MP4 video export, eliminating the need for screen recording software and the hassle of replaying the performance for preview. This ensures stable video quality without stuttering or dropped frames, even on less powerful computers. On high-performance computers, NVIDIA GPU hardware acceleration can be utilized for faster video exporting, minimizing waiting time. To meet the needs of professional video creators, RplGenStudio not only exports MP4 videos but also offers the option to export scripts as XML project files compatible with Adobe Premiere Pro. The project files retain separate layers and tracks, allowing for customized post-production effects.<br/>
<br/>
3. Efficient Project Management: RplGenStudio provides a systematic project management mode, supporting batch import and manipulation of images, audio, and font media. Users can easily transfer projects to other disks or computers and continue editing seamlessly, greatly optimizing the experience of collaborative editing.<br/>
<br/>
4. Rich Text-to-Speech Sources: RplGenStudio integrates over 200 text-to-speech voice sources from multiple services, along with system-embedded voices and typewriter sound effects that can be used offline. This ensures a wide range of audio options to fulfill users' audio requirements in video production.<br/>
<br/>
5. User-Friendly Interface: In the Project View of RplGenStudio, most functions offer convenient keyboard shortcuts, including but not limited to save, copy, paste, find, replace, delete, and sort operations. With abundant audio and video features, the script editing process is straightforward and user-friendly. The built-in script editor in RplGenStudio 2.0 provides professional text editing capabilities. All commands related to parameter settings, character selection, and media switching can be auto-completed using the text suggestion engine of the script editor, allowing users to focus on their storytelling.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roofcats Band - Suika Style</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748050/Roofcats_Band__Suika_Style/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ever wondered what mischief cats get up to on the roof? Well, they're not just lazing around – they're hosting the ultimate rooftop jam session! Picture this: jazz, rock, samba and a whole lot more. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748050/extras/roof.gif?t=1708689032"> <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Innovative features like adaptive music, different game modes and a dog that mess the things up.<br/></li><li>Classic mode, Dog Challenge mode, High Score or Low Score modes.<br/></li><li>Dynamic, interactive songs that evolve with the gameplay, composed exclusively for the game.<br/></li><li>Four different levels with unique and original music.<br/></li><li>Hand-drawn artwork and animations for a visually captivating experience.<br/></li><li>Global leaderboards.<br/></li><li>Challenging achievements.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748050/extras/wish.gif?t=1708689032"><br/><br/>Your mission is to skillfully match the feline musicians, summoning new talents while dodging overflow and contending with an occasional canine disruptor. Oh, and the climax? Brace yourself for a mind-blowing guitar solo on the final cat. Are you up for the challenge? The purr-fect musical adventure awaits!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marzia lost in space</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815210/Marzia_lost_in_space/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2815210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A short story about Marzia shipping cargo to some port,<br/>she decides to take a short break after going FTL for a while.<br/><br/>This is a short visual novel I made as an attempt to make a game for steam.<br/>This story is not based on reality, but more of what it is like to live a life in the future,<br/>and what may happen in the future, as in this character Marzia has to live the struggles of<br/>trying to pay her bills while not getting killed by atleast anything.<br/><br/>I tried my best to make this game as artistically pleasing and good enough<br/>to understand the story, I hope you will enjoy it!<br/><br/><br/><strong>Features[/i]</strong><br/> &gt; The gameplay time may be a little short (5-15 minutes)<br/> &gt; A story with at least 3 endings<br/> &gt; And nothing else...						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoversteppers: Zone 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2777190/Hoversteppers_Zone_1/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2777190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>This is a free prologue for Hoversteppers, and it includes:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>2 stages<br/></li><li>2 Characters, and the starter hoverboard<br/></li><li>10+ Challenges</li></ul><br/>Hoversteppers is a freestyle hoverboard skating game. Explore stages, complete challenges against the clock, or freestyle your own way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2777190/extras/steamGif2.gif?t=1708688865"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>5 unique stages<br/></li><li>Over 50 challenges to complete<br/></li><li>Unlockable characters, boards, and cosmetics<br/></li><li>A rich soundtrack of jungle / drum and bass, by talented artists Mr. Wax, Lunanescence, and Snowdream<br/></li><li>Multiple achievements to unlock</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escape from Bytesville</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2825910/Escape_from_Bytesville/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is an action, quest and platformer single player game set in the town of Bytesville!<br/><br/>You've woken up in Bytesville hospital with memory loss and a strange feeling that you have to get out of this town! Interact with over 60 unique NPCs, earning money and upgrading your weapons to help eliminate the evil agents.<br/><br/>Can you discover the sinister secret in <strong>Escape from Bytesville</strong>?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Altitude's Toll</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2719980/Altitudes_Toll/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2719980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Altitude's Toll is a short single-player walking simulator mystery set in Himalayas.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Introduction</h2>Matt, a 27 year old sherpa, is solving a mystery with his dispatcher about a magnetic repulsion in Himalayas. The dispatcher is thinking about leaving the job as it isn't fulfilling enough; on the other hand, Matt is enjoying it...<br/>...until something unsettling happens on his final ascend.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2719980/extras/snow_gif.gif?t=1708686013"><h2 class="bb_tag">Content</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Pretty and colorful nature<br/></li><li> Slow immersive gameplay<br/></li><li> Wildlife reacts to the players presence<br/></li><li> Delivering packages<br/></li><li> Handmade level design<br/></li><li> Explorable world</li></ul><br/>Playtime 30-60 minutes						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ice Land</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2681650/Ice_Land/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2681650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a game centered around surviving in a harsh, cold environment, offering you the ultimate test of survival.<br>
<br>
In the game, you will tackle the following primary tasks:<br>
Mining and logging: Gather resources to sustain survival and craft various items using these materials to create a habitable environment.<br>
Crop cultivation: Cultivate crops in adverse conditions to meet food requirements.<br>
Animal husbandry: Acquire additional food and resources through animal breeding.<br>
Recruiting NPCs: Employ assistants to help you complete various tasks and work.<br>
<br>
You will need to carefully modify the environment, using a heating system to ensure a comfortable living environment for both yourself and the NPCs. However, you must also be mindful of the pollution generated by the heating system to maintain a delicate balance.<br/>
<br/>
Additionally, the game provides main storyline missions to guide you to explore the game world more deeply, but these missions are not mandatory.<br/>
<br/>
The game offers both single-player mode and local network multiplayer mode, enabling you to cooperate with friends to face the challenges of this cold world together and create even more excitement and enjoyment.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God's Plan</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2435220/Gods_Plan/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2435220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Welcome to Purgatory</strong>!<br/><br/>- This bluish, ice-cold realm lies between hell and heaven, where souls become trapped awaiting their final judgment. You will wander through this maze until you have endured enough suffering.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2435220/extras/Gif1.gif?t=1708685000"><br/><br/><br/>- You are not alone in this place. Your memories are almost real, but somehow not as you remember them. Other suffering souls accompany you through this journey—souls that you may have harmed, perhaps.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2435220/extras/Gif2.gif?t=1708685000"><br/><br/><br/>- There are four levels, each with a painting inside, each corresponding to the curse applied to you. Each painting reveals fragments of the story; however, it is your imagination that will bring it to life. Keep an eye out for Easter eggs, as they can help you build it up.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2435220/extras/Gif3.gif?t=1708685000"><br/><br/><br/>- Some levels require you to find objects to proceed, but you will encounter obstacles along the way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2435220/extras/Gif4.gif?t=1708685000"><br/><br/><br/>The sundered world is neither above or under us, it's inside our minds. <br/><br/>It's us who choose it, even if it's called God's Plan...						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shockwaves</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2824500/Shockwaves/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2824500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Shockwaves redefines the puzzle genre with its unique gameplay. Your goal: strategically place numbers to unleash powerful shockwaves, merging and pushing numbers together. Navigate through an endless mode or tackle 25 mind-bending puzzles.<br/><br/><strong>FEATURES:</strong><br/><strong>ENDLESS MODE:</strong> Dive into a continuous challenge, creating shockwaves to achieve the highest score.<br/><br/><strong>PUZZLES:</strong> Solve 25 intricate puzzles, each requiring strategic moves and clever thinking.<br/><br/><strong>LEADERBOARDS:</strong> Showcase your skills on integrated leaderboards.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hero We Need</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1584820/The_Hero_We_Need/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1584820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1584820/extras/websitecontent.png?t=1708684206"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1584820/The_Hero_We_Need/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1584820/The_Hero_We_Need/</a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Rose</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2799490/Project_Rose/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2799490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							· This is a third person shooter role-playing game!<br>
The player takes on the role of a sexy, beautiful woman on death row who is given a contract by a mysterious organization to continue living under a new identity in exchange for working for the organization.<br>
· Rich plot: Assisting the police, shooting criminals, defusing bombs, rescuing hostages.<br>
· Unique third-person shooting feel.<br>
· 3D model.<br>
· The beautiful female protagonist is waiting for you!						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOD-1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2830060/BOD1/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2830060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Exploration and Survival: Players will explore their home, which has become a trap between worlds, and search for ways to escape this nightmare.<br/>Puzzles and Riddles: Unravel the secrets of the otherworldly realm by solving various puzzles and riddles that stand in the way of salvation.<br/>Atmosphere of Horror: A deep atmosphere of horror is created through ominous music, sounds, and visual effects that emphasize tension and horror with every step.<br/><br/>Unexpected Plot Twists: Immerse yourself in an exciting plot with unexpected twists, revealing the secrets of the protagonist's past and the nature of the otherworldly force.<br/><br/>The gameplay includes tense survival moments as players must navigate through dark corridors, avoiding traps, and evading attacks from otherworldly forces. Discover new areas of your home, explore surrounding objects, collect clues, and solve puzzles to uncover the secrets of this otherworldly realm.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2830060/extras/Bod1_2024.02.06_-_15.20.01.02.gif?t=1708681371"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promenade</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1781260/Promenade/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1781260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Oh no! The Great Elevator has been broken and its cogs have been scattered all around the world!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1781260/extras/Promenade_cogCollect.png?t=1708681263"><br/><br/><br/>Travel the world with your poulp using a dynamic moveset<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1781260/extras/Promenade_Moveset.gif?t=1708681263"><br/><br/><br/><br/>Interact with colorful characters and solve puzzles<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1781260/extras/Promenade_Puzzle.gif?t=1708681263"><br/><br/><br/><br/>Explore dungeons and face the bosses that dwell there<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1781260/extras/Promenade_Boss.gif?t=1708681263"><br/><br/><br/><br/>Use to your advantage the different objects and their properties<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1781260/extras/Promenade_objectProperties.png?t=1708681263"><br/><br/><br/><br/>Collect the lost cogs, repair the Great Elevator and unlock new levels in this collectathon directly inspired by 3D platformers, such as Mario 64, Banjo-Kazooie, Spyro and, more recently, Mario Odyssey<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1781260/extras/Promenade_wholesome.png?t=1708681263"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A fascinating story : Wedding Night</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2736210/A_fascinating_story__Wedding_Night/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736210/extras/主宣传图.png?t=1708675433"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game background</h2>This is just a story that happened in the past. It has long passed now, but it really happened. It is a story that changed Do Yeon’s life.<br/>She once had a very smooth life, a delicate and pleasant appearance, a financially superior family background, and a decent job. No, she just successfully arrested the most difficult criminal this month, perfectly breaking the rumors. It's a pity that she chose to marry her subordinate when she was about to be promoted.<br/>However, they have been in love for many years and their relationship is very stable.<br/>And tonight was their wedding night's carnival party~ Of course she wouldn't miss it, so she dressed up and went with her husband.<br/>But no one expected that the two policemen would be retaliated by their enemies... It was difficult for her to fight with her four fists. On this night, she was about to spend the darkest night in her life...<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>This is a very simple card flip game where you turn over a card and then try to find another card that matches it.<br/>You only need to click on the card to find the same card as the image that appears, and the identical ones will be eliminated. After all the cards are eliminated, the heroine's story can be unlocked...						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last of the Noticers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2730120/Last_of_the_Noticers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							For the past few years, you've noticed things, things about life, things about others, things about the world and about geopolitics. And none of it is adding up. Today, you woke up and decided to do something about it. Or will you?<br/><br/><strong>Choose the path you will take during this non-linear FPS</strong><br/><br/>- Walk through life as a good little NPC, interacting with your fellow NPCs along the way, and avoid succumbing to the monotony of it all<br/><br/><strong>OR</strong><br/><br/>- Reach into your bag and become the main character for a change<br/><br/><strong>DURING THE ADVENTURE:</strong><br/><br/>- Liquidate any denizen or fed that gives you trouble<br/><br/>- Generate as much (or as little) social credit as possible to justify your rating as a person<br/><br/>- Unlock weapons with different effects depending upon your social credit score<br/><br/>- Partake in the use of inhalants to ensure today's adventure is as long and as amusing as you want it to be <br/><br/><strong>How will you spend this day you woke up to?</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sling Puzzle: Golf Master</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2685630/Sling_Puzzle_Golf_Master/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Have you ever imagined what happens to the world when gravity is not always downward? In an inverted city, you will walk over walls and fall into the sky. Space is no longer limited to flat ground and the movement of things will become truly different. This game constructs a special gravity space. In the game, you will explore in the intricate gravity space, discover golf like movement, break the traps, solve the puzzles, and discover the path to the end.<br/><br/>Roll your character through a maze of challenges, solving puzzles to reach the finish point. Precision and wit will be your allies on this exhilarating rolling adventure!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685630/extras/1.gif?t=1708672685"><br/><br/>Crash into the pyramid of cans for a smashing good time in our puzzle arcade game. Roll your way to bonus points as you skillfully break down the pyramid and conquer the challenge!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685630/extras/6.gif?t=1708672685"><br/><br/>Roll with precision and master the art of timing to overcome the sophisticated obstacles that lie ahead. Only the most skillful players will conquer this thrilling and demanding test of wit and reflexes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685630/extras/5.gif?t=1708672685"><br/><br/>Take careful aim to hit the pyramid of cans, breaking it with finesse. Show off your accuracy and puzzle-solving prowess in this exhilarating level!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685630/extras/4.gif?t=1708672685"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Exquisitely designed levels<br/></li><li>Hundreds of mind-blowing puzzles with hidden paths and well-designed traps<br/></li><li>Nice and simple sling game, golf mechanics<br/></li><li>100% real physics<br/></li><li>Collect and upgrade various characters and trails<br/></li><li>Three different game modes<br/></li><li>Level mode: reach the final point of each level within a limited number of moves<br/></li><li>Capture mode: no limit on the number of moves, you need to capture all chickens in the shortest time<br/></li><li>Treasure mode: discover and collect the hidden treasures in the level<br/></li><li>Comfortable and relaxing music and sound<br/></li><li>Easy to control, golf mechanics, fun to play</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aim Trainer - Shooting Range</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626780/Aim_Trainer__Shooting_Range/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Aim Trainer - Shooting Range</strong> is a casual shooting game that includes a variety of exciting and fun game modes and a extensive weapon upgrade system. Train your shooting skills, collect different types of weapons, and become an excellent shooter elite!<br/><br/>Experience the thrill of precision marksmanship, hone your shooting skills, aim for perfection, and hit your targets dead center!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626780/extras/5.gif?t=1708672641"><br/><br/>Step into the great outdoors and embrace the explosive power of the shotgun!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626780/extras/2.gif?t=1708672641"><br/><br/>Prepare for long-range dominance as you venture into the open expanse of our virtual world!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626780/extras/4.gif?t=1708672641"><br/><br/>Embark on an epic hunting adventure in the wild, where time slows down as your bullet sails towards your prey!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626780/extras/7.gif?t=1708672641"><br/><br/>Get ready for heart-pounding shotgun action in the great outdoors. Your first shot may miss, but the second shot is right on target!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626780/extras/6.gif?t=1708672641"><br/><br/>Step into the dimly lit indoor shooting range and test your reflexes as glass bottles pop up one by one!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626780/extras/3.gif?t=1708672641"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Game features:</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Abundant task levels: Train and improve your shooting skills step by step!<br/></li><li>Various of weapons: Different kinds of weapons bring different shooting experiences! Upgrade your weapons to get more powerful equipment!<br/></li><li>Realistic shooting experience: Physics-based shooting simulation that recreates a real-world, authentic shooting experience!<br/></li><li>Multiple game modes: Contains training levels, clay pigeon shooting, hunting, and other game modes, a variety of different shooting scenarios simulation!<br/></li><li>Hunting mode: Realistic hunting scenario simulation, conquer the wild animals in the forest with a sniper rifle!<br/></li><li>Offline Games: Play a few rounds anywhere, anytime!</li></ul><br/>The game mainly trains three types of weapons: pistols, shotguns, and sniper rifles.<br/>Pistol - Train the reaction speed, aiming speed, and the rapid-fire ability for close-range shooting.<br/>Shotgun - Training accuracy and speed of aiming at medium distance.<br/>Sniper - Training ultra-long-range shooting accuracy and aiming ability.<br/><br/>Skeet Shooting and Trap Shooting: Simulate skeet shooting to train your reaction speed and shooting accuracy.<br/>Hunting Mode: Realistic simulation of the forest ecological environment, animals will avoid each other, attack, foraging. You use a sniper rifle to survive in the forest, the longer you survive, the more rare species you will encounter and the more difficult challenges you will face. Try to survive in the forest to the end!<br/><br/>Come and download the game, train your shooting skills and experience the realistic shooting environment!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Motel</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2800680/Death_Motel/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2800680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I'm Joe Salinger, a dedicated paranormal investigator. I couldn't resist delving into the rumors circulating about ghostly sightings at Crimson Motel.<br>
<br>
The unsettling news revolves around a chilling incident from several months ago: a maniacal psychopath brutally murdered two teenagers within the hotel's walls.<br>
<br>
In response, the management abruptly shut down the motel, citing "renovations" as a cover.<br>
<br>
During the supposed renovations, a wave of eerie occurrences unfolded. Construction workers reported encountering apparitions, and some even suffered severe mental distress, compelling them to abandon their work at the site.<br>
<br/>
The enigma shrouding Crimson Motel piqued my curiosity; it's precisely the kind of mystery I thrive on.<br/>
<br/>
Armed with my investigative prowess, I am determined to gather concrete evidence within the hotel's haunting confines. Backed by my comprehensive computer setup in the van, I will meticulously process all the information I collect. My ultimate goal is to capture undeniable proof of these spectral entities on video camera.<br/>
<br/>
If I manage to record any ghostly apparitions, that would be my invaluable contribution to unraveling the secrets veiled within the Crimson Motel.<br/>
<br/>
*Short, can be completed under 1 hour.<br/>
*Has running key, you can run around fast, although we suggest you walk around and explore the background story.<br/>
*Solve simple puzzles using your inventory and your equipment in the back of your van.<br/>
*Collect evidences regarding the paranormal events of this Motel.<br/>
*Hunt down ghost sightings.<br/>
*Has jumpscares.<br/>
*Ominous background music and soundscapes.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP / Maya Prophecy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2741000/MP__Maya_Prophecy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2741000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world view is derived from the parallel timeline of a personal novel.<br/><br/>In a parallel timeline in 2012, the Maya Prophecy of the world's end came true, not due to meteorites or floods, but because a small number of humans awakened superpowers. These abilities were potent enough to shake the entire world, leading to a war between the awakened, referred to as the "New Human," and the non-awakened, known as the "Old Human," sparking a global conflict.<br/><br/>The game emphasizes challenging battles, with every fight, except the first one, being winnable. If unable to win, players can study tactics for improvement. JP points earned from defeating monsters can be used to enhance character attributes.<br/><br/>Speed is crucial in the game, as having a lower speed may result in enemies taking action twice. Additionally, there is an equipment enhancement system where scrolls for strengthening attributes can be acquired through battles or purchased from shops. Equipment can be strengthened in the menu, but this decision is irreversible.<br/><br/>The current version of the game features only six playable characters, with three starting characters and the others joining after battles.<br/><br/><br/>Game Features:<br/><br/>●Each boss battle presents a high level of difficulty.<br/>●Diverse skills can be obtained through battles or by purchasing skill books from the shop.<br/>●There is no limit to the attributes of all characters.<br/>●The unique JP system allows self-enhancement through battle rewards.<br/>●Various abnormal states add challenge to battles.<br/>●Equipment enhancement system.<br/><br/><br/>Change language<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2741000/extras/01.png?t=1708669819"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2741000/extras/02.png?t=1708669819"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super RPS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2634770/Super_RPS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2634770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Super RPS is a tactical strategy game in which two players have a series of Rock, Paper, Scissors matches on 5 fields concurrently. Each player has a secondary deck of "Field Cards" that have special abilities that can turn the match in your favor.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2634770/extras/Discord.png?t=1708668013"><br/>Join the official BlueExabyte Discord and YouTube, linked both in game, as well as in the links to the right!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2634770/extras/Features.png?t=1708668013"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Online Multiplayer (1v1) play against your friends on Steam or against random players online!<br/></li><li> Offline VS Bot - sharpen your skills against the bot with the scariest Artificial Intelligence: randomization<br/></li><li> Strategize to beat players, select the best combo to outsmart your opponents and win<br/></li><li> Customization colors to change the mood of the game<br/></li><li> In game chat to talk to your friends while you play</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2634770/extras/Fields.png?t=1708668013"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Rock++</strong> - Rock beats Paper and Scissors<br/></li><li> <strong>Paper++</strong> - Paper beats Rock and Scissors<br/></li><li> <strong>Scissors++</strong> - Scissors beats Rock and Paper<br/></li><li> <strong>Rock--</strong> - Rock loses to Paper and Scissors<br/></li><li> <strong>Paper--</strong> - Paper loses to Rock and Scissors<br/></li><li> <strong>Scissors--</strong> - Scissors loses to Rock and Paper<br/></li><li> <strong>Reverse</strong> - Cards have reverse win conditions (i.e. Paper beats Scissors)<br/></li><li> <strong>Equal Balance</strong> - The match on this field results in an automatic draw<br/></li><li> <strong>Ultimate Draw</strong> - If there is a draw in this match, the Player who owns the field wins (CPU results in normal draw), other conditions are normal<br/></li><li> <strong>Scapegoat </strong>- Auto draw, but points will randomly be assigned to a match on the field<br/></li><li> <strong>Shuffle </strong>- The enemy's RPS card will be switched with another of theirs<br/></li><li> <strong>Dud </strong>- No field effect</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
