<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Ingression: The Portal Trial</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2761970/Ingression_The_Portal_Trial/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an intergalactic adventure as Rina, a cunning thief in the year 2442 within the corrupt Galactic Empire. Get a preview of the game's start and tackle some tricky levels. Can you beat the challenges and triumph in this futuristic journey?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761970/extras/IGS_GIF_1.gif?t=1705681045"><br/>Get ready for a wild ride in a tricky platformer with mind-bending challenges and seamless portals that'll keep you on your toes!<br/><br/>Check out Ingression: The Portal Trial - free prologue with 25 levels to get a feel for what the game is all about!<br/><br/>Stay grounded as you navigate through the mind-bending levels that play tricks on your sense of direction.<br/><br/>Race against the clock as you tackle challenging levels – can you beat the timer?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761970/extras/IGS_GIF_2.gif?t=1705681045"><br/>Easy-to-use controls – just jump, use portals, think ahead, and climb. Yet, beneath the simplicity lies layers of expressive depth to master, turning every death into a valuable lesson. Swift respawns ensure you're back in action in the blink of an eye, always ready for another go.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intravenous 2: Mercenarism</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2651330/Intravenous_2_Mercenarism/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Wishlist_Game.png?t=1705699394"><br/><br/>Step into the shoes of Gideon, a ruthless mercenary who cares about nothing but his wealth. Set two months before the events of Intravenous 2, you will take on seemingly simple jobs, the effects of which will ripple out and affect the main game's protagonist. But why should Gideon care? He's just in it for the money.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Stealth_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Stealth or Firepower:</strong> the choice is yours. Sneak through shadows, turn off the lights, pick doors, or unleash a hail of bullets. The game will adapt to your play style.<br/></li><li> <strong>Customize Your Skills:</strong> develop your skills the way you want to, whether it's mastering the art of stealth or becoming a gunslinging virtuoso.<br/></li><li> <strong>Bullet Time:</strong> Gideon is no stranger to stimulants that enhance his cognitive abilities - bending time to give him the edge in tense situations.<br/></li><li> <strong>Vast Arsenal:</strong> choose from firearms, gadgets, and a variety of ammo types to creatively tackle the challenge<br/></li><li> <strong>Weapon Modification:</strong> personalize each firearm with suppressors, laser sights, and more, tailoring your arsenal to the task at hand.<br/></li><li> <strong>Responsive AI:</strong> engage in intense combat with enemies that react to your actions, take cover, use tactics and call for backup.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Action_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fling to the Finish</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1054430/Fling_to_the_Finish/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/header_alt_assets_8.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/smallMontage.gif?t=1705671800"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_WhatIsIt.png?t=1705671800"><br/>In Fling to the Finish, teams of two players race through colorful, chaotic obstacle courses while tethered by a stretchy elastic rope. <br/><br/>When you and your friends first pick up the game your rope will get tangled in practically everything you pass. But as you quickly improve your communication skills you'll learn that the rope is your biggest asset. <br/><br/>Experienced players can use the rope to swing around perilous obstacles, and fling their partner up ledges before they fall to their doom. When partners master using their rope, they're capable of acrobatic feats unachievable in any other platformer!<br/><br/>Teams can show off their skills by competing in online or local races with a bunch of other players!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_WaysToPlay.png?t=1705671800"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/ways2play.png?t=1705671800"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_Courses.png?t=1705671800"><br/><br/>Every course in Fling to the Finish has a unique theme and style. Race through floating parks, giant casinos, and even worm filled asteroid fields to reach the finish line! We designed every obstacle to force you to use the rope in a new way, so every second is filled with new surprises and memorable moments. The race track even evolves to challenge you as you play, so every race is a nail biter. You'll never know what weird obstacle you'll find next. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Fling_Golf.gif?t=1705671800"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_Attacks.png?t=1705671800"><br/><br/>Opponents battle back with hails of plungers, sinking weights, and evil lasers if they fall behind. Our items keep the races interesting, and help even the score if one player has more experience than another.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/NAdC5A8_-_Imgur.gif?t=1705671800"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_Characters.png?t=1705671800"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/smallerCharRotate.gif?t=1705671800"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/Steam_SectionTitles_EN_ShareController.png?t=1705671800"><br/>Because you're literally attached to your partner, Fling to the Finish is a truly cooperative experience. If you want, you can even play through Fling to the Finish by sharing a controller with your partner. <br/><br/>This control scheme is great for local co-op, and adds an extra dimension to the game. While you push and pull each other in game, try not to do the same in real life!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1054430/extras/optimizedShareGif.gif?t=1705671800"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turnip Boy Robs a Bank</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2097230/Turnip_Boy_Robs_a_Bank/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2097230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2097230/extras/AboutBanner.png?t=1705590256"><br/><br/>Turnip Boy is ready to commit more felonies in this comedic action-adventure game with roguelite elements. This time the career criminal is teaming up with the fearsome Pickled Gang to plan and execute the weirdest heist of all time! Shake down hostages, steal precious valuables, and explore the deep, dark depths and history of the Botanical Bank.<br/><br/>To pull off the perfect heist, you’ll need to purchase an array of dangerous and wacky tools from the dark web, including a diamond pickaxe, C4, and… a cardboard box? However, bank robbing isn’t easy, so be prepared for intense shootouts with security guards, the fuzz, elite swat teams and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2097230/extras/FeatureBanner.png?t=1705590256"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A thrilling single-player adventure full of bank robbing, dark web browsing, and fuzz fighting.<br/></li><li>Roguelite elements to turnip the action.<br/></li><li>A big ol’ bank to explore and loot.<br/></li><li>An array of wacky weapons.<br/></li><li>Take on whoever the bank throws at you in intense shootouts, from security guards to elite veggie swat teams!<br/></li><li>A large cast of quirky food-based characters, including some familiar faces and new citizens with their own stories and problems.<br/></li><li>Earn collectable hats to wear and new banger tracks to blast.<br/></li><li>Discover a deeper history of Turnip Boy’s world and how it became what it is.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Kingdoms Zhao Yun</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2201710/Three_Kingdoms_Zhao_Yun/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							- Dive into 12 complete story chapters <br/>- Choose from 3 difficulty levels, with a minimum of 30 hours experience of main storyline.<br/>- Master 4 distinct weapon systems: spears, bows and arrows, swords, and steeds, supplemented by equipment systems like crafting, sets, refinement, and enchantment.<br/>- Explore no fewer than 30 expansive maps.<br/>- Encounter dozens of well-known Chinese historical figures, who will either fight by your side or become your adversaries.<br/>- Enjoy a wide range of visually striking outfits for the protagonist and companions.<br/>- Engage in several large-scale, renowned battles that truly capture the essence of the Three Kingdoms atmosphere.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/战场.gif?t=1705736926"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/连招1.gif?t=1705736926"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/大招.gif?t=1705736926"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2201710/extras/射箭.gif?t=1705736926"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immortal Life</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1201230/Immortal_Life/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Immortal Life is a captivating life simulation game where you strive to restore the Guiyun Sect after its near-total destruction – all while you try to achieve immortality through spiritual cultivation.</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/漫步乡野.gif?t=1705714837"><br/><br/>Decided to help your new brothers and sisters make this settlement grow and flourish into a prosperous village, you will work relentlessly with them to restore the Misty Valley by farming, cooking, and crafting decorations for your new home. As you strengthen your bonds with them, you will learn more about their lives, stories, and motivations. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/师兄弟.gif?t=1705714837"><br/><br/>As you work and improve your skills, you will ascend in your cultivation journey; and your adventures will take you far from your Misty Valley. One day you will rebuild the strength of the Guiyun Sect and restore the glory of the Misty Valley. And maybe even achieve immortal life yourself…<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Farm with Spells</h2>Roam through the countryside, using your magic to cultivate fields, and taking care of crops with enchanted tools. Manage your own farmland amidst changing seasons and weather.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/仙法种田.gif?t=1705714837"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cultivate your way to immortality</h2>Master various skills such as fishing, cooking, crafting elixirs, or making furniture. Remember, every skill is important to help you restore the Misty Valley and cultivate your soul and powers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/生活技艺.gif?t=1705714837"><br/><br/>Train your abilities and attend classes before submitting yourself to the tests that allow you to reach a new step in your cultivation journey. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/修仙生活.gif?t=1705714837"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Mystic Realms</h2>Travel to distant lands, uncover treasures and use your magic to defeat mythical creatures. There are more than 10 different Mystic Realms and you’ll have to master different abilities and strategies to find the crafting items that you need from each territory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/秘境战斗.gif?t=1705714837"><h2 class="bb_tag">Fellowship within the Sect</h2>Get to know your brothers and sisters and help them with their daily struggles to strengthen your bond. Each character has their own personality and interests in cultivation. By helping them, you’ll learn more about their lifes and motivations – and receive new items, missions, and skills. You can also invite them to share your dwellings.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/同门.gif?t=1705714837"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Home</h2>Acquire spirit stones, unlock new territories, and initiate construction projects to establish a tranquil sanctuary in the valley of your homestead. With your crafting skills and the help of your brothers and sisters, you will get new decorations and magic tools for your farm and house.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201230/extras/仙府建设.gif?t=1705714837"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Cut: Samurai Duel</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2193490/First_Cut_Samurai_Duel/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A high-intensity arcade sword-fighting game where <strong>every strike is lethal</strong>. Slash, clash, parry, dodge and watch limbs fly in the atmosphere of historical feudal Japan. Choose your move carefully - <strong>the first cut is also the last.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/stg1.gif?t=1705515941"><br/><br/><strong>A refined and intuitive fighting system</strong> - Aim your sword to block attacks and strike around your opponent's guard. Parry their attacks with your own, dodge to close the distance, and interrupt them with a well-timed shove. It takes a minute to learn, and a lifetime to master.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/jan7.gif?t=1705515941"><br/><br/><strong>Customize your fighter</strong> - An array of different options to wear. Choose and colour each piece separately to make each character your own.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/stg2.gif?t=1705515941"><br/><br/><strong>Dueling with deadly results</strong> - Send heads and limbs flying as blood rains down and stains the characters and environment. Chop your opponent to pieces, or equip a wooden sword instead for a little mercy and possibly a concussion.<br/><br/>Duel your friends in <strong>local multiplayer</strong>, fight custom <strong>AI opponents</strong>, try to stay alive in <strong>Survival mode</strong>, or hunt down enemies in the <strong>Scenario mode</strong> campaign. <br/>Play with friends remotely using <strong>Steam Remote Play Together.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Bonus modes</strong> - Laser swords, custom blood, floating weapons, zombies, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2193490/extras/jan12.gif?t=1705515941"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEST TEST TEST</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667690/TEST_TEST_TEST/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667690/extras/2023_08_02_Teaser.gif?t=1705552043"><br/><br/>TEST TEST TEST is a retro pixel-art point-and-click puzzle adventure where you must escape a time loop as an overworked office employee.<br/>Find clues, gather information, and solve cryptic puzzles with alternate reality game elements.<br/>Will you able to release yourself from the clutch of time itself? Or will you be stuck in this reality forever?<br/><br/> ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟<br/>                                                                 FEATURES<br/> ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟ ͟<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore various areas, from your own apartment room to the big corporate office building.<br/></li><li>Non-linear puzzle with Alternate Reality Game elements<br/></li><li>15 minutes time loop<br/></li><li>Hand-drawn retro pixel-art aesthetic with modern touches</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominions 6 - Rise of the Pantokrator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2511500/Dominions_6__Rise_of_the_Pantokrator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2511500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are a God! You are master and ruler of a loyal nation. You have unimaginable powers at your disposal. You have claimed this world as yours. But there are others who stand in your way. You must defeat and destroy these pretenders. Only then can you ascend to godhood and become the new Pantokrator.<br>
<br>
Dominions 6 is a turn based 4x strategy game suitable for both play vs AI, player vs player.  Team play vs AI or players also works great as everyone can do their turns at once.  The game has a huge variety of units, spells, magic items and different nations to play.<br>
<br>
In Dominions you take control of a powerful being that rules a nation and aspires to godhood. The type of Pretender Gods can vary from magically powerful arch mages to huge titans or large monuments. The pretender gods have different strengths dependent on what kind of god you choose and what nation you play.<br>
<br>
When you start the game you decide what kind of god you are and how your Dominion affects your lands, followers and sacred soldiers. It is an expression of your divine might and the faith of your followers. If your dominion dies, so do you. Your dominion also inspires your sacred warriors and gives them powers derived from your dominion.<br/>
<br/>
In order to win and become the one true god you have to defeat your enemies one of three different ways: conquer their lands, extinguish their dominion or claim the Thrones of Ascension.<br/>
<br/>
Dominions is set in a fantasy world that draws inspiration from historical nations, cultures and myths. You will not encounter the elves of conventional fantasy in this game. Instead you might lead a nation of vanir from old norse myth. Aztecs, romans, israelites, greeks, kievian rus and lovecraftian horrors are just a few of the inspirational sources of the game.<br/>
<br/>
The first Dominions game was released in 2002 and was well received by strategy gamers. Since then Dominions has been much refined and Dominions series is still actively played making it one of the longest running 4x turn based strategy games.<br/>
<br/>
----------<br/>
<br/>
Dominions 6 is scaled up compared to Dominions 5 and armies are larger. We wanted to tweak the balance between conventional armies and magic. To accomplish this a couple of changes are introduced. Incomes and resources are increased, while mages are more expensive. Battlefield-wide spells are more difficult to cast and there are instead more mid-tier spells. There are some other changes with the same aim.<br/>
<br/>
The second and probably most influential change is the addition of a new magic path. No longer are illusions the domain of Air magic. Instead illusions, phantasms, dreams and the stuff of forgotten legends are manipulated with the path of Glamour. This has resulted in many new spells, items and sites being added to the game. <br/>
<br/>
A third massive change is the separation of mounts and riders. Riders and mounts now have separate stats and can be targeted individually. This change probably has less impact on gameplay than the previous one, but will still have an impact on cavalry and nations using mounted units.<br/>
<br/>
Dominions 6 features a number of new nations as well. The addition of the Glamour path has also affected several of the old nations. <br/>
<br/>
There are also a number of changes intended to ease gameplay.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Safety Hotline</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2357910/Home_Safety_Hotline/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/RuntimeLabel-HSH-Dark.png?t=1705432881"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/ShinyLogoOnlyGIF.gif?t=1705432881"><br/><br/><strong>Hearing noises? Seeing things? Call Home Safety Hotline! Our operators are standing by, waiting to give you the answers you need to protect your home from all manner of pests and household hazards.</strong><br/><br/>Home Safety Hotline is an analog horror inspired telephone operator simulator where you answer incoming callers' questions about what's inside their home. Read through a vast catalog of common pests and household hazards, and do your best to become an expert in home safety. You will be held responsible for what happens.<br/><br/>A new horror experiment from Nick Lives, the creator of <i>NiGHT SIGNAL</i> and <i>A Wonderful Day For Fishing</i>. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Navigate a vast catalog of safety information using the latest in 90's technology.<br/></li><li> Listen to original jazzy lo-fi music by David Johnsen while you place callers on hold.<br/></li><li> Correctly deduce what's in your callers' homes or else leave them to suffer the consequences.<br/></li><li> Learn about the various untold horrors that live inside your home.<br/></li><li> "Phobia Toggles" - An accessibility option that allows you to disable in-game images for common phobia triggers including arachnophobia and more.<br/></li><li> Unlockable Art Book detailing the game's development history.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/NumberOnlyGIF.gif?t=1705432881"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2744170/Artifact_SeekerPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/DS.png?t=1705638389"/></a><br/>The difference between the prologue version and the official version<br/>There is a special artifact in the prologue<br/>Characters: 2 in the prologue, at least 5 in the official version<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 3 in the final version.<br/>Systems: Tavern, Marketplace, and Endless Mode will be added to the game.<br/>Artifacts: More artifacts will be added to the game.<br/>Skills: More skills will be added in the official version.<br/>Words: More words will be added in the official version.<br/>Encounters: There will be more interesting encounters in the official version.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/11y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1z.gif?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/2y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/gif1.gif?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.gif?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong>[/b]<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.gif?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.gif?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><strong><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.gif?t=1705638389"><br/>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </img></img></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Hoplite: Arachne’s Trial</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2738430/Legendary_Hoplite_Arachnes_Trial/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Try out the free prologue to get a taste of the exciting gameplay and easily transfer your progress to the full game.<br/><br/><strong>Transfer your progress to the main game</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_04.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>The main game offers three acts, 38 areas, mini-games, and a lot of gear options for your hero. Progress seamlessly transfers from the prologue to the main game.<br/><br/><strong>Face 10 Levels and 2 Boss Battles</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_02.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>Face the challenge of 10 distinct levels, each filled with hordes of mythic monsters. Try 6 different armies and test your skills against Arachne at the end of the prologue.<br/><br/><strong>Customize Your Build and Power Up Your Army</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_01.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>Customize your build by trying out various gear combinations you come across. Find the perfect match for your playstyle as you explore. Strengthen your army by upgrading them and merging with the Hero to amplify your power, ready to face and conquer the enemy.<br/><br/><strong>War technique</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_03.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>Elevate your armies with War Technique—a fresh way to upgrade. Experiment with various combos and effortlessly switch up your enhancements for effective improvements.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frostrain</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735630/Frostrain/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/01_Thumnail.png?t=1705651196"><h2 class="bb_tag">Roam the frozen world</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Roam_the_frozen_world.gif?t=1705651196"><br/>Climate change has turned the world white and frozen, and the only thing moving on the planet is you, your passengers, and your train. It's a dead world, but ironically, it's all the more fascinating for it. A vivid landscape awaits you to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Keep your passengers happy</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Keep_your_passengers_happy.gif?t=1705651196"><br/>The passengers on your train will work diligently at your command, but be careful: if you don't manage their happiness properly, they might throw you off the train.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build your own train with card decks</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Build_your_own_train_with_card_decks.gif?t=1705651196"><br/>Each time you pass through a city, you'll be able to add new train cars by launching a heavy lift drone. Be careful with each choice you make. If you are lucky, you'll be able to build a better, more synergized, happily-ever-after train deck, but it won't always go as you planned.<h2 class="bb_tag">Reach the Promised Land</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Reach_the_Promised_Land.gif?t=1705651196"><br/>Lead your passengers in search of the Promised Land, somewhere on the eastern edge of the world. But the journey to the Promised Land isn't all smooth and pleasant. You'll have to pass through toxic areas, and a severe storm is brewing behind you. Pay attention to your passengers' happiness levels and lead them safely to the Promised Land. The journey is in your hands.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoardLand</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735620/BoardLand/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Create your own strategy with the dice</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/extras/Cardnals_1.gif?t=1705310503"><br/><br/>The dice is rolled!<br/>Are you going to move? Are you going to act?<br/>Different effects are applied to each die, and the numbers determine your behavior.<br/>How do you combine numbers to get the best results?<br/>Every time you pick a number, you'll have to choose carefully.<h2 class="bb_tag">Make a powerful board by strengthening the tiles.</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/extras/Cardinals_2.gif?t=1705310503"><br/><br/>Tiles get more and more powerful!<br/>Every time you act on a tile, the tile gains experience, and the tile with enough experience is upgradeable.<br/>Combine tiles with multiple properties to create the best strategy, your own board<h2 class="bb_tag">Defeat the monsters and bosses</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/extras/Cardinals_3.gif?t=1705310503"><br/><br/>Monsters disturb you!<br/>Monsters can summon Fireballs, or they can curse and cause obstacles to certain tiles.<br/>You have to move and act with the dice, avoiding these patterns every time.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Flame: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517810/The_Last_Flame_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_1.png?t=1705541234"><br/>The Last Flame is a roguelike auto-battler which focuses on build creation, strategy and decision making. Recruit special heroes, fight deadly encounters, loot and craft powerful gear, discover and create unique synergetic builds! Every run, you will need to create powerful builds that will take down your foes!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_A3.gif?t=1705541234"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_2.png?t=1705541234"><br/>The Last Flame offers an incredible amount of build diversity. Combine heroes, items, relics and origins together to create amazing builds! Hero and team building have been designed with flexibility and freedom at their core which allows you to discover and create unique synergetic builds every single run!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Builds.gif?t=1705541234"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_3.png?t=1705541234"><br/>In between the automated combats, you will have to cleverly guide your heroes through the adventure by making the smart decisions! Manage your resources, choose the optimal path in the map, make powerful builds, and strategically position and plan the combat phase!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Tactical.gif?t=1705541234"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/comingToFullVersion.png?t=1705541234"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get access to a lot more stuff! Make amazing builds with 300 items, 58 heroes, 125 relics and 60 origins.<br/></li><li>Continue the adventure in the third act, and meet the final boss in a special act!<br/></li><li>Face 30 challenging enemies and 10 bosses!<br/></li><li>Progress through 5 difficulties which will challenge your knowledge and strategy!<br/></li><li>Push your builds to their limit in the endless mode, a mode where you try to reach the highest floor!<br/></li><li>Experience the game in diverse and fun new ways with the challenge modes!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_ENDLESS.gif?t=1705541234"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summoners War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2426960/Summoners_War/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2426960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>▶Features</strong><br/><strong>[Tactical RPG play]</strong><br/>Witness the dazzling display of each monster 's unique skills.<br/>23 different Rune sets to pick and choose additional abilities for your monsters!<br/>Come up with the best strategy to win battles in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[Endless Fun]</strong><br/>Decorate your Village, battle other summoners , explore dungeons , fight in PvP battles , expand your collection, train monsters , and more.<br/><br/><strong>[The Key of Colletion RPG : Massive Collection]</strong><br/>Fire, Water, Wind, Light and Dark!<br/>5 different attributes, and 1500 different monsters!<br/>Collect as many monsters as you can and win battles with your own decks .<br/><br/><strong>[Real-time Raid]</strong><br/>Battle as a team with your greatest monsters !<br/>A real-time battle with 3 users!<br/>Defeat the boss with your fellow Summoners using various tactics.<br/><br/><strong>[Homunculus]</strong><br/>The Forbidden Summoning Magic has finally been revealed!<br/>You can Evolve the skill of your choice with this special monster.<br/>Summon Homunculus and show off your strategy in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[All about Turn-Based RPG : World Arena]</strong><br/>Enjoy a real-time battle with Summoners worldwide!<br/>Experience a breathtaking battle that starts from Pick &amp; Ban.<br/>Reveal your unique strategy to the world and win battles .<br/><br/><strong>[Guild Content]</strong><br/>A sensational Guild PvP battle in the Isle of Conquest!<br/>Explore the Tartarus' Labyrinth and dungeons with Guild Members.<br/>Make your Guild the greatest of all.<br/><br/><strong>[Dimension Hole]</strong><br/>Fight against the ancient power emerged from a new dimension!<br/>Defeat the Ancient Guardians and meet the powerful monsters with new awakening power.<br/><br/><strong>[Artifact]</strong><br/>Artifacts are now dropped with MAX power-up levels!<br/>Summoners , fight against the powerful bosses and acquire Artifacts!<br/>Enhance your monsters with various sub properties of Artifacts.<br/><br/><strong>[Progression and Farming Structure Revamp]</strong><br/>Summoner progression structure renewed and content reward greatly improved!<br/>Dive into Summoners War and experience the enhanced progression system!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portal: Revolution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/601360/Portal_Revolution/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Portal: Revolution is a fan-made mod for Portal 2 which plays before the events of Portal 2 in the dead and decaying Aperture facility.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/ezgif-7-f507c3c464_1_.gif?t=1705083406"><br/><strong>Over 40 new puzzles</strong><br/>The campaign contains 40 brand new puzzles making use of new test elements and presents existing mechanics in a new way not seen in Portal 2.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resurrected "Pneumatic Diversity Vent" element<br/></li><li> New laser cube variant<br/></li><li> Over 15 puzzles using only the blue Portal-Gun<br/></li><li> Gel Cleansing Field</li></ul><br/><strong>Difficulty</strong><br/>Portal: Revolutions puzzle difficulty starts where Portal 2 stops, but fear not. All new mechanics and advanced portal tricks are taught to you. We have ensured through rigorous playtesting that every player can solve the puzzles. Although very few chambers require portals to be fired mid-air, no puzzles require advanced tricky movement.<br/><br/>Depending on your experience with Portal 2 mechanics, you can expect about 5 to 7 hours of playtime.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/banner_story_2.gif?t=1705083406"><br/>Set inbetween Portal and Portal 2, Portal: Revolution tells a brand new story using new characters. You play as a test subject who is awoken by a personality sphere called Stirling and join his mission to find a powerful device capable of restoring Aperture to its former glory.<h2 class="bb_tag">ENGINE</h2>Portal: Revolution uses a modified version of Portal 2: Community Edition's engine, which is a custom version of the Counter-Strike: Global Offensive Source Engine branch using licensed source code provided by Valve Software.<br/><br/>This allowed us to introduce many mechanics and improvements to the engine to create an experience which would be impossible in Portal 2.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Esports Godfather Origin</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2739460/Esports_Godfather_Origin/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/游戏简介英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/>"Esport Godfather" is a management simulation card game that revolves around the theme of MOBA esports. In this game, you will assume the role of a coach in an esports club and personally build your own team! Starting from scratch, what kind of playstyle will you devise for your team? In a constantly evolving meta, can you derive a unique understanding of what it takes to win? How will you unlock the potential of your handpicked athletes and mold them into superstars?<br/><br/>Ultimately, will you be able to become a legendary figure in the esports industry, crafting your own esports story and lifting the championship trophy?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/选手培养英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/>Each athlete is unique! They all have their own strengths and weaknesses.<br/>If an athlete's efficiency in earning money increases over time, they are undoubtedly a skilled late-game specialist.<br/>Successful ambushes can unlock hidden potential, propelling some athletes onto the path of godlike.<br/>As a coach, it's your responsibility to analyze each athlete's characteristics, devise training plans tailored to their needs, and guide them on their journey to becoming superstars!<br/><br/>· Every athlete possesses distinct abilities that will impact their performance on the battlefield!<br/>· An athlete's hero pool is crucial for Ban &amp; Pick strategies!<br/>· The tactic cards utilized by athletes in matches serve as the foundation of all strategies!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/版本变更英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/>The meta environment is ever-changing!<br/>Changes in the equipment pool, the structure of economic income, and the source of decisive advantages, even slight alterations to the rules can drastically shift the priorities of Ban &amp; Pick and alter the strategic approach!<br/><br/>· Equipment will be added or removed as the versions change!<br/>· The timing of crucial team fights will shift with each version update, making team composition crucial!<br/>· Does harassment grant more gold? Do kills damage towers? Each gameplay rule brings a fresh experience!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/指挥战斗英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/>You have the power to command the battlefield, with athletes attentively listening to your orders.<br/>Should you play it safe and focus on farming under the towers, or launch aggressive assaults and initiate attacks?<br/>Perfect team composition requires perfect leadership! The game is ever-changing, and you must face your opponents head-on!<br/><br/>· Each hero and athlete possesses their own tactic cards. It is through creative combinations and strategic application that they become unstoppable!<br/>· Offense or defense? Aggression or caution? The outcome rests in your hands. Formulate strategies and implement tactics!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/其他内容英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/>· Over 50 unique heroes in the starting lineup, each with their own special abilities!<br/>· 200+ tactic cards, granting you control over the battlefield!<br/>· Diverse athlete training options! As a mentor, it's important to tailor your teachings to each individual!<br/>· Unearth young talents and cultivate new forces in the youth training camp!<br/>· Choose sponsors, a top-tier club deserves the support of top-tier sponsors!<br/>· Trash-talking sessions, asserting dominance is a must before crucial matches!<br/>· Abundance of events, includes unexpected occurrences, athlete communication, team pep talks!<br/>· Training match plans, knowing your opponents inside out ensures victory after victory!<br/>· Regular season, playoffs, transfer periods—different decisions await you at different times!<br/>· When athletes reach their limits, you must help them break through and reach new heights!<br/>· Create a custom team logo for your club!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/工作室LOGO英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowbreak: Containment Zone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668080/Snowbreak_Containment_Zone/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Snowbreak: Containment Zone is a 3D sci-fi RPG-shooter powered by the Unreal Engine 4 that offers a next-gen, cross-platform gaming experience, sharing your progress across all of your devices. <br/><br/>The Descent of the Titans turned a once-vibrant city into the devastated wasteland of Containment Zone Aleph. As the Adjutant of Heimdall Force, bravely undertake missions alongside Manifestations with the powers of gods and unique personalities, seeking to bring this bitter winter to an end...<br/><br/>[Enjoy Hybrid Combat]<br/>Snowbreak's weaponry injects realism into a sci-fi setting, with designs closely simulating future firearms technology. This combines with the otherworldly, RPG-like skill mechanic to create a refreshing combat experience.<br/><br/>[Take on Titans]<br/>The Descent of the Titans completely changed the world, and the battlefield. Feel the thrill of battling giants in this dystopian future!<br/><br/>[Befriend Operatives]<br/>Spend time with your Heimdall Force companions in the Base system. Decorate, chat, and give gifts to grow closer!<br/><br/>[Play Co-Op in Gigalink] <br/>Tired of exploring alone? Join up with friends and fight enemies together!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703868247"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1705734315"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1705734315"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1705734315"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1705734315"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1705734315"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1705734315"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1705734315"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1704804364"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1705439381"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1705439381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1705439381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1705439381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1705439381"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1703186631"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1705229288"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1705229288"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1705229288"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1705229288"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1705229288"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1705229288"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1704392583"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1704392583"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1704392583"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pepa's Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2745900/Pepas_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2>The paper fairy Pepa lived harmoniously with the book fairy Lex.<br/><br/>However, one day, the scissor fairy Slash intruded into their home and snatched away pages from Lex's book.<br/><br/>Deprived of strength, Lex returned to being a silent book. <br/>To reclaim the stolen pages, Pepa rises to the occasion.   <br/><br/>Using the power to manipulate paper freely, Pepa embarks on a journey to the scissor fairy's lair, overcoming various challenges along the way.<h2 class="bb_tag">About this game</h2>Pepa's Adventure is a point-and-click picture book made with papercut art.<br/>The story unfolds through pictures alone, progressing the narrative without words.<br/><br/><strong>Characters and backgrounds are crafted from handmade papercut art.</strong><br/><br/>Embark on an adventure with Pepa, meeting the enchanting inhabitants of the papercut world along the way.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hakuba School ! Hunting Prey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2625900/Hakuba_School__Hunting_Prey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2625900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Welcome to Hakuba!</h2><br/>Immerse yourself in the extraordinary world of Hakuba School, where every students are unique animals. In this emotionally charged visual novel game, you'll embark on a thrilling journey that combines humor, darkness, intrigue and heartwarming friendships. Uncover the hidden pasts of your friends, explore a multitude of dialogue choices, and navigate around the school.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Vibrant Cast:</h2>Encounter a diverse and colorful cast of over 20 characters, each with their distinct personalities. Form meaningful connections with these students, unraveling their unique backgrounds, personalities, and struggles.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Twisted Tale:</h2>Delve into a story that balances humor and darkness, keeping you on the edge of your seat. As you navigate the halls of Hakuba School, choices you make will shape the fate of not only the protagonist but also the lives of those you encounter.<h2 class="bb_tag">Unlocking Hidden Pasts:</h2>Dive deep into your captivating backstory and those of your friends, peeling away the layers of mystery that shroud their lives... Aside from the central mysteries, Hakuba School is brimming with hidden stories, conspiracies, and personal journeys, ensuring 3-4 hours of gameplay.<h2 class="bb_tag">Go around the school !:</h2>Explore Hakuba School! Roam freely through the school's hallways, classrooms, and hidden corners.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2625900/extras/Characters3.png?t=1705778058"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DarkStorm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748470/DarkStorm/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Long ago, humanity was ambushed by a mysterious alien race. Many perished—while those who survived were forced to find refuge in the mountains. Many years have passed, and the survivors cannot continue their refuge in the mountains. They must return home...<br>
<br>
Play as MARS (Machine of Absolute Retaliation and Safeguard), a robot programmed to exterminate the treacherous aliens who have taken over Razor City. As MARS, you must free Razor City from its domination in order to save  the survivors from their doom.<br>
<br>
In DarkStorm, you must fight endless waves of aliens. As you pass each wave, the map grows larger, allowing you to explore more. Random collectibles will be spawned throughout the map, including health, ammo, weapon upgrades, and random weapon crates. There are three types of enemies, a Bat, Brute, and Crab. Each enemy has a special set of skills, so you have to watch out as you fighting them. The game includes only one gamemode, which is the endless wave. Once you pass wave 8, the map is completely open for you to explore.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kitten Burst</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1592360/Kitten_Burst/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1592360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1592360/extras/200x_bump_sm.png?t=1705768637"><br/>Hapi, a down on their luck racing cat, teams up with a hacker named S4br aboard the cybership “The Eternal September”. Together they travel to abandoned sites, siphoning energy to power their ION Drive. Can the team pull off their scheme, or will the future of cyberspace be controlled by the megacorp PANDO?<h2 class="bb_tag">WHISKERS </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1592360/extras/whiskers.gif?t=1705768637"><br/><i>[Width/Height Intersect Sensing Kinetic Energy Recovery System]</i> Generate <i>Burst</i> energy by flying close to walls and obstacles. Surf through levels to set quicker times.<h2 class="bb_tag">BOSS BATTLES</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1592360/extras/bulletheaven.gif?t=1705768637"><br/>Challenge a cast of boss characters to battle. Survive an onslaught of attacks long enough to drain their energy.<h2 class="bb_tag">CIRCUITS</h2>Scattered throughout the sites are circuits to race in. The quicker your time the more IONs each circuit generates. Plan out and perform the fastest lines through the world.<h2 class="bb_tag">CATS ARE SOLID/LIQUID</h2>Shift your state of matter to alter your burst power. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Solid: Increase your acceleration and top speed<br/></li><li>Liquid: Slow down time and increase maneuverability.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cube War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748100/Cube_War/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cube War is an exhilarating 2D shooter set in the depths of space. Players take on the role of galactic nomads tasked with exploring and defending a galaxy teeming with enemies composed of various geometric shapes.<br>
<br>
In Cube War, the adversaries come in the form of unique geometric shapes. Triangular warships, square tanks, and even round drones present players with a variety of strategic challenges.<br>
<br>
Controls<br>
<br>
Movement: W/A/S/D<br/>
<br/>
You fire automatically.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
By defeating the enemies, you will increase your level and fight more challenging and more enemies and try to reach the highest level.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoHeroes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2403940/AutoHeroes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2403940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>There's no matchmaking with random opponents! </strong><br/><br/>You can play solo, accompanied by three AI-controlled heroes whose difficulty can be adjusted. Alternatively, <strong>if you invite Steam friends to join, each friend will replace one of these AI heroes</strong>. You also have the flexibility to rearrange teams and create alliances among all the heroes.<br/><br/>You can try the demo version - it is similar to the main game, except that you cannot choose heroes. <strong>You can also play the demo version with friends from Steam.</strong><br/><br/>AutoHeroes is a ‘one hero’ autobattler with elements of roguelike and the ability to play in multiplayer. Control one of the four heroes who fight each other for the throne on random maps - both as each for themselves and as part of teams. Manage your hero through priority setting, as well as skill and equipment upgrades. Study your enemies and counter them with your plan!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2403940/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__3_.gif?t=1705784028"><br/><br/>The kingdom has lost its king and is in turmoil - no one understands what will happen next. Will the kingdom fall into the hands of a good hero, who will inspire the guard to serve him as the new king? Will the supporter of the dark forces, who prefers to rule the kingdom of the dead, prevail? Or maybe it will be that hero who combines both good and evil?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2403940/extras/ezgif.com-crop.gif?t=1705784028"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Auto-battler: no rush during the game. <br/></li><li>One hero: no armies, no "deck-building"​ - focus only on your hero.<br/></li><li>Flexible settings: customize AI strength and teams, or invite friends to play PvE or PvP. <br/></li><li>Priority system: regulate which objects and which enemies interest you first, and which last. <br/></li><li>Skill wheel: choose skill schools and master them. Experiment and look for the best combinations. <br/></li><li>Kindness or Malevolence: Persuade guards to join your cause or compel them to battle on your behalf even after their demise.<br/></li><li>Assassin or Tactician: Choose to be an aggressor who strikes enemy heroes at the first chance or a strategist who benefits from prolonging each round.<br/></li><li>Scouting: play for fun or seriously worry about countering your opponents.<br/></li><li>Four heroes to choose from: warrior, archer, fire mage, or dark mage.<br/></li><li>Random maps filled with enemies - each map is different from the previous one!<br/></li><li>Fight with formidable opponents - dark knights, ghosts, even dragons!<br/></li><li>Finally, fight your main enemy and main threat in all game modes - other AutoHeroes.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2403940/extras/ezgif.com-crop__1_.gif?t=1705784028"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UpWorld - Multiplayer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2625330/UpWorld__Multiplayer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2625330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Are you ready to rise to the challenge and become the hero you were born to be?<br>
<br>
Embark on a breathtaking journey unlike any other in "UpWorld - Multiplayer," a parkour adventure that will challenge your skills, your heart, and your sense of wonder. Reach for the skies as you scale towering cliffs, navigate treacherous chasms, and defy gravity in your quest to reach the mythical Upworld.<br>
<br>
You are the chosen one, entrusted with the sacred "Celestial Relic" - a mission that will take you through a world teeming with wonder and enchantment. Encounter a cast of mystical creatures and characters who will aid you on your journey, from wise guardians to imprisoned angels, all of whom have destinies entwined with yours. As you ascend, you won't just face challenges; you'll forge deep connections. You will also challenged by some Puzzles.<br>
<br>
Discover hidden powers and abilities as you progress, enhancing your parkour skills and empowering you to overcome even the most daunting obstacles. otherworldly landscapes will leave you in awe, from lush, magical forests to towering, crystalline spires. Your adventure begins now in "UpWorld - Multiplayer," where the fate of a world rests on your shoulders.<br/>
<br/>
Are you ready to rise to the challenge and become the hero you were born to be?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robo Rob</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2291910/Robo_Rob/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2291910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Welcome to Robo Rob! </strong><br/><br/><strong>Robo Rob</strong> is an intensively challenging puzzle game crafted to push your patience to the limits. Start your journey with 21 intricately designed levels that promise to deliver both frustration and triumph. But that's just the beginning – we regularly roll out new batches of maps, each set ramping up the difficulty and fun factor. Are you ready to take on the ever-evolving challenges of <strong>Robo Rob</strong>?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runaway bride</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2757570/Runaway_bride/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In a world where acceptance and understanding are still evolving, lives a young woman named Rachel.<br>
Rachel is a lesbian who proudly embraces her identity and love for another woman. However, her family, bound by tradition and societal expectations, insists that she marry a man. Rachel's heart sank as she faced the daunting prospect of a loveless marriage that would rob her of her true self. She struggled with conflicting emotions, torn between her own desires and the need to obey. Despite the enormous weight on her shoulders, Rachel decided at the last minute to find a way to live life on her own terms. With unwavering determination, Rachel decided to run away from her wedding. Rachel's journey won't be without its challenges, so help her through with perseverance and determination. Challenge society's expectations and prove that true happiness can only be found when you truly live.<br>
<br>
The main idea of the game is that you, as bride, has to run away from the wedding. 10 different people, like family members and friends will do their best to catch you, so you must be very quick and careful. To be able to pass to the next level you have to take the key which randomly appear on the scene. At this moment, the game has 10 different levels. If you have been caught you are going back to the first level.<br>
<br>
Each character has its own, unique story which you can read.						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jelly Belly</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2762750/Jelly_Belly/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2762750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Jelly Belly - is an exhilarating action arena shooter where players engage in relentless combat against an endless stream of diverse monsters. In this dynamic game, you'll face a constant challenge as the number of enemies and damage levels steadily increase. Your goal is survival and complete annihilation of enemies using a varied arsenal.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Endless Waves of Monsters</strong>: Battle against constantly increasing numbers of unique and dangerous monsters to test your skills and endurance.<br/></li><li><strong>Progressive Damage Levels:</strong> The game's difficulty continually rises, escalating tension and demanding strategic thinking and quick reactions from players.<br/></li><li><strong>Diverse Arsenal</strong>: Utilize a wide selection of unique weapons to deal with various types of monsters. From exploding projectiles to powerful energy waves, you have everything you need to survive.<br/></li><li><strong>Upgradable Weapons</strong>: Improve your weaponry as you play, enhancing effectiveness and adding tactical variety.<br/></li><li><strong>Arena Panic</strong>: The dynamic atmosphere creates a sense of constant danger, compelling players to act decisively to stay alive and complete each wave of monsters.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Curse3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735840/School_Curse3/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Game Title: School Curse 3<br>
<br>
Genre: Horror<br>
<br>
Overview:<br>
<br>
A girl wakes up in a school one day. However, this is not her usual school, but a strange dimension filled with mysterious monsters. The girl must collect 10 magical books to escape this dimension.<br/>
<br/>
This dimension was once a place where an evil power was sealed. However, the seal was broken, and the evil power has returned, causing the dimension to reappear.<br/>
<br/>
The girl must escape this dimension.<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay:<br/>
<br/>
The game is played from a third-person perspective. The player controls the girl as she collects the magical books.<br/>
<br/>
If the girl is spotted by a monster, she will be attacked and the game will end.<br/>
<br/>
The game ends when the player collects 10 magical books. Once 10 books have been collected, the girl can escape the dimension.<br/>
<br/>
The player can avoid monster attacks by hiding in a moving locker.<br/>
<br/>
Features:<br/>
<br/>
This is a horror game set in a strange dimension filled with mysterious monsters.<br/>
<br/>
The player can experience a thrilling escape game as they collect magical books.<br/>
<br/>
The game is full of tension as the player avoids monster attacks and searches for magical books.<br/>
<br/>
As the third installment in the School Curse series, the game features connections to the previous games.<br/>
<br/>
Target Audience:<br/>
<br/>
All ages<br/>
<br/>
Number of Players:<br/>
<br/>
1<br/>
<br/>
Playtime:<br/>
<br/>
About 5 minutes<br/>
<br/>
Difficulty:<br/>
<br/>
Intermediate<br/>
<br/>
Release Date:<br/>
<br/>
February 2024						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Curse2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2730660/School_Curse2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Title: SchoolCurse2<br>
<br>
Genre: Horror<br>
<br>
Release Date: January 2024<br>
<br>
Platform: PC<br/>
<br/>
Description:<br/>
<br/>
A sequel to the popular short horror game, SchoolCurse.<br/>
<br/>
In a cursed school, you must collect 10 magical tomes to break the curse.<br/>
<br/>
But be careful, the school is crawling with alien-like monsters.<br/>
<br/>
Explore the school, find the tomes, and escape the curse.<br/>
<br/>
Two modes are available: Normal and Hard.<br/>
<br/>
Normal mode is similar in difficulty to the original game.<br/>
<br/>
Hard mode provides a more challenging experience.<br/>
<br/>
This game is recommended for fans of the original SchoolCurse and horror games in general.<br/>
<br/>
Target Audience:<br/>
<br/>
Fans of the original SchoolCurse<br/>
Horror game enthusiasts<br/>
Overview:<br/>
<br/>
SchoolCurse2 is a short horror game that is the sequel to the popular game SchoolCurse.<br/>
<br/>
The game is set in a cursed school at night.<br/>
<br/>
The player controls a girl named Sakura who must collect 10 magical tomes to break the curse.<br/>
<br/>
The game is played from a third-person perspective.<br/>
<br/>
Players must explore the school to find the tomes.<br/>
<br/>
However, the school is also home to alien-like monsters.<br/>
<br/>
If the player is caught by a monster, they will be killed.<br/>
<br/>
The game features two modes: Normal and Hard.<br/>
<br/>
Normal mode is similar in difficulty to the original game.<br/>
<br/>
Hard mode provides a more challenging experience.<br/>
<br/>
SchoolCurse2 is a great choice for fans of the original game.<br/>
<br/>
It is also a good option for horror game enthusiasts who are looking for a short and challenging game.<br/>
<br/>
Review:<br/>
<br/>
SchoolCurse2 is a more challenging game than the original, but it is still a lot of fun.<br/>
<br/>
The atmosphere of the school is creepy, and the monsters are scary.<br/>
<br/>
Normal mode is a good challenge for fans of the original game.<br/>
<br/>
Hard mode is a good choice for players who are looking for a more difficult experience.<br/>
<br/>
SchoolCurse2 is a great choice for fans of the original game or horror games in general.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>雪鹰领（Cultivating Immortals）</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2664950/Cultivating_Immortals/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2664950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Everyone yearns for immortality, and for ordinary people, the most coveted place is undoubtedly the Cultivating Immortals, a place of cultivation. It is said that the Cultivating Immortals was divided into eighteen territories by demon forces, where fairy grass was everywhere and demons were rampant. Therefore, this place became a paradise for cultivators. There are often powerful cultivators here who practice hard and eventually soar to the sky. This place not only contains treasures left by the ascending sages, but also those cultivators who bravely died here for immortality. Perhaps you will bravely kill demons due to a spiritual herb, a secret script, or a relic, or compete with your companions for resources. No matter what method you choose, you will embark on an unprecedented adventure where you will learn about Taoism, practice demon killing, and treasure hunting, all for the ultimate goal of immortality. Let's jointly uncover the veil of this mysterious land!<br>
<br>
Cultivating Immortals is a multiplayer cultivation competition game.<br>
<br>
The current version has launched single person cultivation mode and multi person interaction scenes. Including: lifespan system, realm system, combat system, magic system, boss system, drop treasure system, Chat system, legacy system, and multi scenario PVE.<br>
<br>
In the later stage, it will be open: mount system , multi scenario PVP, larger magical system, weapon system, equipment system, managed auction house, alchemy system, sect system, multi universe system, creation of small world system, etc<br/>
<br/>
This is currently the first version, and the game will be updated five times to present exciting content to players.<br/>
<br/>
Current version: Mainly aimed at improving cultivation by collecting herbs, eliminating low-level monsters to obtain fairy magic secrets, learning advanced fairy magic, and then going to eliminate high-level monsters.<br/>
At present, the multiplayer mode has poor support for non China regions, which may result in inability to connect to the server, causing both parties to be invisible.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death of Marionette</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2618380/Death_of_Marionette/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2618380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2618380/extras/STORY.png?t=1705719969"><br/>Sawyer and her friends arrive at a ruined factory to prepare an event. While everyone’s busy, Sawyer experiences something strange inside the building.<br/>Sometime later, Huck Finn, Sawyer’s boyfriend, arrives at the factory with some friends after receiving a text message from her...<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2618380/extras/FEATURES.png?t=1705719969"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>An RPG Maker style adventure game with real time combat - clear your path with your trusty Steel Pipe. Enhance yourself and your weapons with items found on your adventure.<br/></li><li>Beautiful illustrations and pixel sprites - Enjoy tens of pictures made by the main artists LuB2an and Coinman.<br/></li><li>Moody piano music - 22 soundtrack pieces written by the artist Antler and the developer Gustav</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZAKESTA-Z</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2695830/ZAKESTAZ/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2695830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Shootung fights on all 5 sides with normal shots that power up by 5 stages and sub-weapons that power up by 3 stages.<br/>You can consume a gauge to generate a circle called "Z-ZONE", and items captured within that range can be turned into high-scoring items.<br/><br/>*Select from 3 modes: "NORMAL", "ZOGEN" where the game rank changes, and "ZUTTOZ" where the highest rank is fixed.<br/><br/>*6 types of sub-weapons<br/>[0] Fires a bullet that attacks in the opposite direction of your aircraft's movement.<br/><br/>[1] Emits a huge laser.<br/><br/>[2] Damages enemies and enemy bullets with a barrier.<br/><br/>[3] A ball rotating around your aircraft deals damage to enemies and enemy bullets.<br/><br/>[4] Fires a bullet that explodes when it hits an enemy.<br/><br/>[5] Fires a bullet that guides the enemy.<br/><br/>*Detailed explanation can be found in the Community Hub guide.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake Crush</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2574030/Snake_Crush/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2574030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Ghost Dragon has truly been killed, and the spiritualized dragon vein once again rises into the sky, tearing a passage between reality and the spirit world. A massive influx of spiritual energy and sinister forces floods into the magic city, empowering countless monsters and demons, causing them to wreak havoc in the human world once again. <br/>The Investigation Bureau has no choice but to dispatch their staff members who are most capable of withstanding the dragon's power, a group of rational serpent demons, to deal with this anomaly.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2574030/extras/titleen01.png?t=1705716039"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2574030/extras/吃球.gif?t=1705716039"><br/><br/>Let your hungry little snake devour the elements it meets like a greedy snake<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2574030/extras/三消.gif?t=1705716039"><br/><br/>Consume three identical elements to unleash skills to clear enemies<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2574030/extras/titleen02.png?t=1705716039"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2574030/extras/天赋.gif?t=1705716039"><br/><br/>Gain experience, Level up, Acquire enhancements and Create your  unique build<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2574030/extras/titleen03.png?t=1705716039"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2574030/extras/潮水.gif?t=1705716039"><br/><br/>Confront the waves of monsters and persevere until the end of the mission<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2574030/extras/titleend.png?t=1705716039"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TERMINAL22</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2704020/TERMINAL22/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i><strong>Take back what they stole from you.</strong></i><br/><br/>You are part of the temporary testing team for project BEYOND and have been provided with a machine that can hack into any device in the world. You are asked to hack into devices and gather information to test the capabilities of this machine.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704020/extras/ABOUT.png?t=1705704543"><br/>TERMINAL22 is a mix of bullet hell and puzzle gameplay, utilizing the aesthetic of an old operating system terminal. Hack into any system you can find, dig around in the files and uncover the secrets about your identity, the testing program, project BEYOND and the company behind it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704020/extras/main_1.gif?t=1705704543"><br/><br/>...before long you may realize that you might not be the only one looking into this.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704020/extras/gameplay.png?t=1705704543"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704020/extras/hackingSub2.png?t=1705704543"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>One of the two main elements of gameplay is hacking. Through the game you will need to hack into many different devices. This is done through a navigating your way through a bullet hell arena and finding all of the "Security Nodes" in order to break the security of the machine and access it.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704020/extras/main2.gif?t=1705704543"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704020/extras/discoverySub2.png?t=1705704543"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Once getting into the machines, you will partake in the second major part of the gameplay, the discovery. Dig through the system by using terminal commands, discover files, go through them to learn the necessary information to progress further in the game.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704020/extras/main3.gif?t=1705704543"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abyss School</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2473710/Abyss_School/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2473710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2473710/extras/Story.png?t=1705725619"><br/>Yuhee is an ordinary girl who attends a private school.<br/>While waiting for her school bus, she picked up a bright purple conch shell on the beach.<br/>She fell asleep on the bus due to unbearable drowsiness. What unfolded in front of her when she woke up was a school that had sunk into the deep sea and an abyss of followers following the high priest.<br/>She solves puzzles prepared by Abyss Followers, avoids terrible monsters, and begins a journey to escape this Abyss School and return to her original world.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2473710/extras/How_to_Play.png?t=1705725619"><br/>Solve hidden items and puzzles<br/>while avoiding abyss zombies and traps at school.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2473710/extras/Game_Features.png?t=1705725619"><br/>▷ Charming characters<br/>▷ Tense gameplay<br/>▷ Simple controls<br/>▷ Various skins and cutscenes unlocked as you play						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets Under Eco</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2751850/Secrets_Under_Eco/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2751850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Secrets Under Eco is a story driven first person metroidvania with a unique spin on fps combat. Explore the military base of Melior and its surrounding area while collecting equipment and powerful upgrades.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fully Voice Acted Story: Melior is about to win the war against The Others. Ready to fight with his people, Jay wakes up alone in a jail cell in his own military base. Labeled a spy, and with an unknown voice in his head, will Jay be able to escape his captors he once called his friends?  <br/></li><li>Unique First Person Shooter Combat: Enemies take damage by slamming into walls and obstacles. Defeat combatants by launching them into whatever you can using your equipment and wits.<br/></li><li> Exploration: Search for a way out of Melior's expansive military base. Find equipment, vending machines, audio diaries, and combat boosting upgrades along the way.<br/></li><li> Visuals: Secrets Under Eco features a pleasing low poly, mostly grayscale art style. </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes Of Memes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2761080/Eyes_Of_Memes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							One day you had the bad luck to fall through from your reality into some otherworld. Such incidents sometimes happen and now it has happened to you. From now on you have only one task - to find 8 pictures and leave this strange place. <br/>In terms of gameplay Eyes Of Memes is a classic indie horror in which you have to explore the location in search of pictures.  You don't have any weapons, you are always defenseless against the inhabitants of the place and if you encounter them, running away is the only way to escape.<h2 class="bb_tag">Levels</h2>You just went to sleep in your cozy bed in your home and when you wake up you find that you are in some dark creepy place... There are 6 levels available to you in the game: Morgue, School, Basement, Game Room, Backrooms and Desert. Visually all levels look different, but your goal is always the same - explore the location and collect all the pictures.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761080/extras/1.gif?t=1705698665"><h2 class="bb_tag">Hazards</h2>Watch out if you hear strange noises or notice something moving in the dark. The inhabitants of this world only at first glance look funny and ridiculous, but they are not! Run. Don't stop, don't try to hide, just run! The creatures that inhabit this place are far more terrifying than anything you've seen before.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761080/extras/2.gif?t=1705698665"><h2 class="bb_tag">Eyes</h2>While wandering through this strange place, you can discover mystical eye pills that allow you to look through the monster's distorted minds.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761080/extras/3.gif?t=1705698665"><h2 class="bb_tag">Progression</h2>For successfully completing levels, you will earn experience points that can be spent to unlock new levels and enemies. Playing on a higher difficulty level will require more effort, but you will gain twice as much experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761080/extras/4.gif?t=1705698665"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Familiars.io</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2619250/Familiarsio/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">what is this game?</h2><br/>it's a compact monster-catching fest in an online multiplayer world. It also has some optional hard stuff for people who like a challenge.<h2 class="bb_tag">what's it like to play?</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 1 battle = 1 levelup, and the max level is 15. I don't want to waste your time with rpg grinding<br/></li><li> with only 20 Familiars in the game, you can max-out and understand all the familiars in the game within a few hours<br/></li><li> ... and then you're ready for the hard stuff<br/></li><li> find hidden portals to other dimensions, where you must manage your familiars' HP and your potion supply in a slew of battles against fairly smart CPU opponents<br/></li><li> or, if you want, fight other players you meet in the world to test your mettle</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">what else is there to like?</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> it's extremely easy to pick up, play a bit, and put down<br/></li><li> the only way to communicate with other players is by pressing the "howdy" button repeatedly, or running around in circles<br/></li><li> I think the soundtrack is pretty nice<br/></li><li> it's free btw</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">it's free?</h2><br/>Yeah this is just a hobby project made by one person. I don't need to make this my job, I just like it when people play my game lol!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Climbers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2590080/Two_Climbers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2590080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>NOTE: This game requires  <u>2 separate players who own the game</u> to play!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Journey to the top!</h2><br/>Two Climbers is a two player platformer where you and a buddy work together to climb a top Mount Teawok.<br/>Filled with puzzles and platforming challenges, explore the different parts of Mount Teawok on your way to the top!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2590080/extras/Overworld_Gif.gif?t=1705745364"><h2 class="bb_tag">Work Together</h2><br/>Utilize unlockable skills that allow you and your teammate to combine your efforts to accomplish tasks that are impossible alone!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2590080/extras/MiniGif.gif?t=1705745364"><h2 class="bb_tag">Find Secret Collectables!</h2><br/>Hidden Moons can be found throughout Mount Teawok!<br/>Can you find them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2590080/extras/Secrets_Gif.gif?t=1705745364"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who do you want to date? professional girls сollection</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653080/Who_do_you_want_to_date_professional_girls_ollection/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653080/extras/vvv.png?t=1705687599"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653080/extras/1-1_1.gif?t=1705687599"><br/>A confident policewoman, a tough military woman, a flirtatious tennis player, or a gentle artist? Or maybe someone else? Who do you want to date?<br/><br/>Easy win: Keyboard <strong>Сtrl+D</strong> - Complete Level<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653080/extras/1-1_2.gif?t=1705687599"><br/><br/>In the game, your goal is to collect the puzzle in order to restore the pictures. (◕‿◕)♡<h2 class="bb_tag">Special Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎾   Animation scenes<br/></li><li>👮‍♀️   CG Gallery Mode<br/></li><li>🧹   Relaxing music<br/></li><li>👩‍⚕️   Puzzle game</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jumpfox: Always Running</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2703790/Jumpfox_Always_Running/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Jumpfox: Always Running" is a precision platformer that pushes the boundaries of your skills and patience. In this game, control is a unique twist – you don't control the running. Your character is in perpetual motion, always running forward, bouncing off walls to change direction. Your task is to master timing and reflexes, using only two actions: jump and dash.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703790/extras/gif2.gif?t=1705686977"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Highlights:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Automatic Running Mechanic: Experience the uniqueness of a platformer where the running is automatic, adding an extra layer of challenge and strategy to your gameplay.<br/></li><li>Diverse Difficulty Modes: "Jumpfox: Always Running" features variations of the same map, each tailored to a different level of difficulty. From casual players to hardcore enthusiasts, the game scales its challenges to suit your skill level, ensuring an engaging experience for every type of player.<br/></li><li>Solo and Multiplayer Fun: Whether you're looking to test your own limits in solo play or engage in exhilarating local multiplayer battles, "Jumpfox: Always Running" offers something for everyone.<br/></li><li>Local Split-Screen Play: Dive into the split-screen mode for an intense competitive or cooperative experience with friends right in your living room.<br/></li><li>The game's design focuses on minimalist graphics that highlight the gameplay mechanics, ensuring that your focus remains on the challenge at hand. The intuitive controls make it easy to pick up, but the game's difficulty curve ensures that only the most dedicated players will master it.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703790/extras/gif1.gif?t=1705686977"><br/><br/>"Jumpfox: Always Running" isn't just a game; it's a test of determination, reflexes, and sheer willpower. Are you ready to take on the challenge?"						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far Lands</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1500940/Far_Lands/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1500940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Get on the official Far Lands Discord Server:<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FvPcQa2xWBG" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1500940/extras/small_logo_white_RGB.png?t=1705732566"/></a><br/><br/><br/><strong>Far Lands is a lightweight survival open-world game.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Lore:</h2>You wake up and find out you are not home. In fact, what was home? There is no memory of that.<br/><br/>You are on a strange island and there is no time for panicking. Surviving is your only option. You start gathering food, crafting tools and building a base until you encounter something nobody sees every day.... A ZOMBIE! He starts attacking and you do too. He's dead for now... but who can assure he was the only one?<br/><br/>To find answers you start exploring more and more of the island, but the you only get more questions. Why are there are human build areas? Why there is no human life signs if there are human build areas? What was that skeleton?<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Character hunger and thirst mechanics<br/></li><li>Crafting<br/></li><li>Gathering resources<br/></li><li>Vehicle transportation (Buggy and MiniCopter)<br/></li><li>NPC companion for Gathering Resources<br/></li><li>NPC merchant<br/></li><li>Procedural Spawning of resources and loot<br/></li><li>Electricity<br/></li><li>Hunting wildlife and fighting creatures<br/></li><li>Base Building<br/></li><li>Farming crops<br/></li><li>Day/Night Cycle<br/></li><li>Weather changes</li></ul><br/>The game is lightweight on mechanics because I feel the player would enjoy the adventure and having fun more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gordian Rooms 2: A curious island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1528220/Gordian_Rooms_2_A_curious_island/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1528220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1528220/extras/NewWorld.gif?t=1705684155"><br/>The Isle of Lye is a specially constructed testing ground for the Gordian Society, and as fate would have it, you have ended up here. <br/><br/>It is up to you to rise to the challenge and find a way out of this place, all the while competing to become a full fledged member of this enigmatic organisation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1528220/extras/GI_2_616_35compression.gif?t=1705684155"><br/>As you explore the island, you will get to know the quirky Lye family and their numerous associates. From servants to family members, everyone is more than they let on.<br/><br/>Can you find the black sheep of the family or the traitor in the mansion?<br/>Or perhaps you'd prefer to search for someone else's carefully hidden treasures...<br/>Will you get to the bottom of every mystery?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1528220/extras/GIF_WISHLIST.gif?t=1705684155"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ingression: The Portal Trial</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2761970/Ingression_The_Portal_Trial/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an intergalactic adventure as Rina, a cunning thief in the year 2442 within the corrupt Galactic Empire. Get a preview of the game's start and tackle some tricky levels. Can you beat the challenges and triumph in this futuristic journey?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761970/extras/IGS_GIF_1.gif?t=1705681045"><br/>Get ready for a wild ride in a tricky platformer with mind-bending challenges and seamless portals that'll keep you on your toes!<br/><br/>Check out Ingression: The Portal Trial - free prologue with 25 levels to get a feel for what the game is all about!<br/><br/>Stay grounded as you navigate through the mind-bending levels that play tricks on your sense of direction.<br/><br/>Race against the clock as you tackle challenging levels – can you beat the timer?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761970/extras/IGS_GIF_2.gif?t=1705681045"><br/>Easy-to-use controls – just jump, use portals, think ahead, and climb. Yet, beneath the simplicity lies layers of expressive depth to master, turning every death into a valuable lesson. Swift respawns ensure you're back in action in the blink of an eye, always ready for another go.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intravenous 2: Mercenarism</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2651330/Intravenous_2_Mercenarism/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Wishlist_Game.png?t=1705699394"><br/><br/>Step into the shoes of Gideon, a ruthless mercenary who cares about nothing but his wealth. Set two months before the events of Intravenous 2, you will take on seemingly simple jobs, the effects of which will ripple out and affect the main game's protagonist. But why should Gideon care? He's just in it for the money.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Stealth_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Stealth or Firepower:</strong> the choice is yours. Sneak through shadows, turn off the lights, pick doors, or unleash a hail of bullets. The game will adapt to your play style.<br/></li><li> <strong>Customize Your Skills:</strong> develop your skills the way you want to, whether it's mastering the art of stealth or becoming a gunslinging virtuoso.<br/></li><li> <strong>Bullet Time:</strong> Gideon is no stranger to stimulants that enhance his cognitive abilities - bending time to give him the edge in tense situations.<br/></li><li> <strong>Vast Arsenal:</strong> choose from firearms, gadgets, and a variety of ammo types to creatively tackle the challenge<br/></li><li> <strong>Weapon Modification:</strong> personalize each firearm with suppressors, laser sights, and more, tailoring your arsenal to the task at hand.<br/></li><li> <strong>Responsive AI:</strong> engage in intense combat with enemies that react to your actions, take cover, use tactics and call for backup.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Action_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Social Engineer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2746510/The_Social_Engineer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Become the next top agent with <i>The Social Engineer</i>: explore companies, exploit vulnerabilities, deceive employees, and prevent dangerous attacks. As a Social Engineer Agent, conduct various targeted assaults on companies to uncover faulty security mechanisms. With diverse open-world settings and realistic virtual reality controls, an exciting and immersive experience awaits you, all without weapons and violence. The integrated Education Mode allows <i>The Social Engineer</i> to be used as a tool for training purposes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746510/extras/The_Social_Engineer_-_Trailer.gif?t=1705679745"><br/><br/><strong>Game Concept</strong><br/><br/>In <i>The Social Engineer</i>, assume the role of a Social Engineer Agent with the aim of protecting companies and businesses from catastrophic attacks. Learn various Social Engineering techniques, apply them independently in different companies, and thereby expose dangerous vulnerabilities before criminals can exploit them. Spy in various departments, sneak into secret rooms, and uncover sensitive information about employees by using publicly available information and deceiving people, all without resorting to violence or weapons. Master the training to earn the title of a professional Social Engineer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746510/extras/The_Social_Engineer_-_Trailer__1_.gif?t=1705679745"><br/><br/><strong>Missions</strong><br/><br/>The game features 13 exciting missions in different settings and difficulty levels. From introductory missions to challenging ones:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Infiltrate a business meeting of an advertising agency as a purported businessman<br/></li><li>Pose as a police officer and steal a laptop from a police station<br/></li><li>Deceive a dock worker to operate a crane unnoticed<br/></li><li>Disguise yourself as a janitor to take pictures of secret photoshoots<br/></li><li>and much more</li></ul>No prior knowledge or technical expertise is necessary for the missions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746510/extras/The_Social_Engineer_-_Trailer__2_.gif?t=1705679745"><br/><br/><strong>Social Engineering Techniques</strong><br/><br/>Utilize a constantly expanding repertoire of different Social Engineering techniques to achieve your goals.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Disguise yourself and pretend to be someone else<br/></li><li>Sneak into monitored rooms<br/></li><li>Explore private social media pages<br/></li><li>Execute baiting attacks with QR codes<br/></li><li>Hack into computers using manipulated USB sticks<br/></li><li>Search trash bins for information<br/></li><li>Use websites and public notices<br/></li><li>Deceive employees in personal conversations or calls</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746510/extras/The_Social_Engineer_-_Trailer__3_.gif?t=1705679745"><br/><br/><strong>Game Mechanics</strong><br/><br/><i>The Social Engineer</i> is a roomscale VR game, allowing you to freely move through the game world. Additionally, there's a teleportation function for covering long distances or moving between floors. Use the controllers as virtual hands to interact with objects, doors, and people. Your tablet contains essential information and apps such as a Social Engineering Wiki, a browser, a phone app, a building plan, a photo app, and a help app. There's also a Mission Instructor to assist you in missions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746510/extras/The_Social_Engineer_-_Trailer__4_.gif?t=1705679745"><br/><br/><strong>Learning While Playing</strong><br/><br/><i>The Social Engineer</i> is a Serious Game based on typical cases in real Social Engineering security audits. It can be used for training to understand Social Engineering attacks and increase awareness of Social Engineering in both private and professional settings. The game concept was developed in collaboration with an IT security firm and scientifically accompanied. The special Educational Mode allows querying learned knowledge directly in the game.<br/><br/><br/><strong>Safety Guidelines</strong><br/><br/>This game includes fast movements and on-screen text that may cause discomfort or eye strain in a few individuals. Take a break if you feel uneasy or experience symptoms of motion sickness, simulator sickness, or eye strain!<br/><br/>All locations, company names, logos, and individuals in the game are fictional. Similarities to real places, companies, or persons are unintended and purely coincidental. All Social Engineering attacks presented in the game are merely gameplay mechanics and should only be carried out in the real world by trained security experts.<br/><br/><strong>About the Developers</strong><br/><br/>We are <i>zefwih</i>, a small development studio from Germany. Although we may not compete with major providers, we develop all our games with attention to detail and great care. If you have suggestions, issues, praise, or feedback, feel free to reach out to us!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Social Engineer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2746510/The_Social_Engineer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Become the next top agent with <i>The Social Engineer</i>: explore companies, exploit vulnerabilities, deceive employees, and prevent dangerous attacks. As a Social Engineer Agent, conduct various targeted assaults on companies to uncover faulty security mechanisms. With diverse open-world settings and realistic virtual reality controls, an exciting and immersive experience awaits you, all without weapons and violence. The integrated Education Mode allows <i>The Social Engineer</i> to be used as a tool for training purposes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746510/extras/The_Social_Engineer_-_Trailer.gif?t=1705679745"><br/><br/><strong>Game Concept</strong><br/><br/>In <i>The Social Engineer</i>, assume the role of a Social Engineer Agent with the aim of protecting companies and businesses from catastrophic attacks. Learn various Social Engineering techniques, apply them independently in different companies, and thereby expose dangerous vulnerabilities before criminals can exploit them. Spy in various departments, sneak into secret rooms, and uncover sensitive information about employees by using publicly available information and deceiving people, all without resorting to violence or weapons. Master the training to earn the title of a professional Social Engineer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746510/extras/The_Social_Engineer_-_Trailer__1_.gif?t=1705679745"><br/><br/><strong>Missions</strong><br/><br/>The game features 13 exciting missions in different settings and difficulty levels. From introductory missions to challenging ones:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Infiltrate a business meeting of an advertising agency as a purported businessman<br/></li><li>Pose as a police officer and steal a laptop from a police station<br/></li><li>Deceive a dock worker to operate a crane unnoticed<br/></li><li>Disguise yourself as a janitor to take pictures of secret photoshoots<br/></li><li>and much more</li></ul>No prior knowledge or technical expertise is necessary for the missions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746510/extras/The_Social_Engineer_-_Trailer__2_.gif?t=1705679745"><br/><br/><strong>Social Engineering Techniques</strong><br/><br/>Utilize a constantly expanding repertoire of different Social Engineering techniques to achieve your goals.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Disguise yourself and pretend to be someone else<br/></li><li>Sneak into monitored rooms<br/></li><li>Explore private social media pages<br/></li><li>Execute baiting attacks with QR codes<br/></li><li>Hack into computers using manipulated USB sticks<br/></li><li>Search trash bins for information<br/></li><li>Use websites and public notices<br/></li><li>Deceive employees in personal conversations or calls</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746510/extras/The_Social_Engineer_-_Trailer__3_.gif?t=1705679745"><br/><br/><strong>Game Mechanics</strong><br/><br/><i>The Social Engineer</i> is a roomscale VR game, allowing you to freely move through the game world. Additionally, there's a teleportation function for covering long distances or moving between floors. Use the controllers as virtual hands to interact with objects, doors, and people. Your tablet contains essential information and apps such as a Social Engineering Wiki, a browser, a phone app, a building plan, a photo app, and a help app. There's also a Mission Instructor to assist you in missions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746510/extras/The_Social_Engineer_-_Trailer__4_.gif?t=1705679745"><br/><br/><strong>Learning While Playing</strong><br/><br/><i>The Social Engineer</i> is a Serious Game based on typical cases in real Social Engineering security audits. It can be used for training to understand Social Engineering attacks and increase awareness of Social Engineering in both private and professional settings. The game concept was developed in collaboration with an IT security firm and scientifically accompanied. The special Educational Mode allows querying learned knowledge directly in the game.<br/><br/><br/><strong>Safety Guidelines</strong><br/><br/>This game includes fast movements and on-screen text that may cause discomfort or eye strain in a few individuals. Take a break if you feel uneasy or experience symptoms of motion sickness, simulator sickness, or eye strain!<br/><br/>All locations, company names, logos, and individuals in the game are fictional. Similarities to real places, companies, or persons are unintended and purely coincidental. All Social Engineering attacks presented in the game are merely gameplay mechanics and should only be carried out in the real world by trained security experts.<br/><br/><strong>About the Developers</strong><br/><br/>We are <i>zefwih</i>, a small development studio from Germany. Although we may not compete with major providers, we develop all our games with attention to detail and great care. If you have suggestions, issues, praise, or feedback, feel free to reach out to us!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHINORUBI</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1665900/SHINORUBI/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1665900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1665900/extras/shinorubi_bullet_4k_120fps_vignette.gif?t=1705750561"><br/><strong>SHINORUBI is a Bullet hell style game up in the tradition of japanese Danmaku games.</strong><br/><br/>SHINORUBI offers a <strong>fast-paced arcade action pack with great replayability</strong> thanks to the many available difficulty levels, arrange modes, different spaceships, online leaderboards and achievements. This is also one of a rarest <strong>vertical shooter</strong> entirely designed and optimized for widescreen monitor!<br/><br/><strong>#1 Rule:</strong><br/>Only the very centre of the player's craft is vulnerable to enemy fire. You better avoid the mass of bullets aiming at you and destroy everything between you and your mission. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1665900/extras/shinorubi-GIF-ANIME-titre-BULLET-HELL-GAME.gif?t=1705750561"><br/><strong>CLASSIC/ORIGINAL MODE</strong><br/>Complete all 5 levels with 3 starting lives to pass the 1CC (credit clear) challenge. You may add a few credits to help you to finish the game. 5 difficulty levels, including the easy mode with auto-bomb, or enemy shoots being canceled if you manage to destroy the shooter.<br/><br/><strong>BOSS RUSH MODE</strong><br/>Fight only Bosses! Choose from 3 levels of difficulty.<br/><br/><strong>SCORING SYSTEM</strong><br/>The scoring system is based on several parameters that provide you with point multipliers. Survive the barrage of enemy fire, destroy your enemies and collect stars and medals. All this while using your bombs as little as possible.<br/><br/><strong>WORLDWIDE LEADERBOARD &amp; ACHIEVEMENTS</strong><br/>A world wide leaderboard for each game modes with Steam Leaderboards, a personal leaderboard with all your scores per mode, and Steam Achievements.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1665900/extras/shinorubi-GIF-ANIME-02.gif?t=1705750561"><br/><br/><strong>FEVER</strong><br/>When your FEVER charge bar is full, it automatically triggers to <strong>cancel enemy shots on screen</strong> and improve your points. The side effects are boosted weaponry and improved bonus stars when you destroy your enemies.<br/><br/><strong>CONTROLS AND DISPLAY</strong><br/>You can play SHINORUBI using a <strong>keyboard</strong>, a <strong>joystick</strong>, or an <strong>arcade controller</strong>, Steam Remote Play, and customize all the action buttons.<br/>Made with an in-house super optimized, multi-threaded engine, this is not your average 2D shoot them up, it is a full grade PC game optimized, <br/>in Ultra HD, with uncapped frame-rate support, super resolution support and 8K textures, That's why an Direct3D API Level 11 video card or Vulkan 1.1 is required.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1665900/extras/shinorubi-GIF-ANIME-titre-MANY-ARRANGE-MODES.gif?t=1705750561"><br/>Same game levels as the classic mode but with different rules.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>SHIELD:</strong> Use a shield to protect against the enemy bullets. <br/></li><li><strong>CANCEL:</strong> Destroy marked spaceships to clear all shots on the screen.<br/></li><li><strong>LASER / SHOT</strong>: Alternate between laser and classic shots only when it is told!<br/></li><li><strong>JOURNEY:</strong> Get ready for a long journey with several game loops.<br/></li><li><strong>PINK PIG:</strong> Collect those pesky pigs before they left the screen while shooting the enemies.<br/></li><li><strong>SUPER RANK:</strong> The better your play, the higher the difficulty will change.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1665900/extras/shinorubi-GIF-ANIME-05.gif?t=1705750561"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1665900/extras/shinorubi-GIF-ANIME-titre-CHOOSE-YOUR-PILOT.gif?t=1705750561"><br/>Select a pilot and his spaceship with unique weapons and characteristics among the 3 already available.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1665900/extras/shinorubi-GIF-ANIME-pilote-01.gif?t=1705750561"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1665900/extras/shinorubi-GIF-ANIME-titre-STORY.gif?t=1705750561"><br/>For 1000 years, the BAÄA family has reigned as despots on planet SHINORUBI. This planet is the source of the "R-R" substance which offers infinite power and exceptional longevity to its owners. For 150 years, the king of SHINORUBI, R.LOYD III, and his 6 sons have gone to war across space against the TRADDESS and ZOOGT empires, leaving his cruel daughter Nemesis and 5 generals to guard the planet.<br/><br/>A unique alliance of 8 experienced mercenaries will attempt to put an end to the dictatorship of the BAÄA family and its hold on the "R-R" compound by taking advantage of a singularity of the planet SHINORUBI which takes place once every thousand years. The endless night is coming on Kaddin, the capital of SHINORUBI, as spaceships are approaching.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1665900/extras/shinorubi-GIF-ANIME-logo-01.gif?t=1705750561"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Station 13</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2407460/Station_13/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2407460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The AI of Station 13 LAH 13000 is defective and does not accept other forms of life. Run, jump and dodge in this 2D pixel art style precision platformer with<br/>side-scrolling to get out safely from the deadly trap that the ship has become.<br/><br/>■ Single player space adventure.<br/>■ Limited time to get out of each room.<br/>■ Retrieve the keys and go back to open new doors.<br/>■ Defeat AI-controlled machines.<br/>■ Find the secret capsules scattered throughout Station 13.<br/>■ Get to the evacuation ship to leave Station 13 and return home.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2407460/extras/gif6_616x348_15fps.gif?t=1705678511"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2407460/extras/gif8_616x348_15fps.gif?t=1705678511"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2407460/extras/gif7_616x348_15fps.gif?t=1705678511"><br/><br/>The controls and gameplay are easy to learn: jump, run to get further when jumping, lean on walls to climb and slide. If you die, you quickly respawn to keep moving forward.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swing Solver</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2669240/Swing_Solver/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Control the swing at will and aim for the goal! Fascinating trajectories drawn by a pendulum. "Swing Solver" is an easy yet profound physics action puzzle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669240/extras/SwingSolverGimmickGif_180.gif?t=1705676461"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Easy yet profound action using swing. All you need to do is click and release. But the actions are infinite! </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Acceleration tiles, moving platforms, warp gates, and other obstacles that can drastically alter the ball's movement. If you can't control them, you'll hit a saw! </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Replays show the beautiful trajectory drawn by the pendulum after each success. The cooler the success, the more beautiful the trajectory! </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Simple graphics highlight the beautiful orbit of the pendulum. The world made of blue squares and round balls looks like a physics notebook. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Calm sounds that match the graphics. </li></ul><br/>The only actions used are firing and disconnecting the wire. It is a simple operation, but difficult to master. Where do you connect the wire? When to disconnect? Watch the movement of the pendulum and control the ball perfectly with a single wire!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Stuff: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2647860/Star_Stuff_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Star Stuff: Prologue</strong> is a sneak peek into Star Stuff, a galactic blend of automation and strategic action! Join Mija on their first day working at a star factory! Program unique bots and work together in-time with them to solve thoughtfully-curated challenges and space-bending puzzles.<br/><br/>Key Features:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Automation: Program bots with a user-friendly interface, each with different skills to assist you like lifting, lasering, and more.<br/></li><li>Strategic Action: Work together by performing actions in sync with your bots to solve puzzles and if you fail, brush off the stardust and try again!<br/></li><li>High-Level but Low-Tension: Don’t stress while on the job! You can always restart, undo, and try puzzles again without getting fired.<br/></li><li>Break Time: Head to the cozy lobby where you can interact with gizmos of the cosmos and chat with your fellow co-workers from across the galaxy!<br/></li><li>Prologue only: Learn how to automate bots and get familiar with the world of Star Stuff!</li></ul><br/><strong>Disclaimer:</strong> Kindly be aware that certain SFX, music, and assets showcased here might differ from the final build of the main game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roles &amp; Dice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2560120/Roles__Dice/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2560120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Roles &amp; Dice is a meticulously crafted online virtual tabletop game, where imaginations run wild, and epic adventures await! Tailored for fans of tabletop RPGs, this game enables you to load any image file to construct immersive maps and draw your friends into exciting worlds, all from the comfort of your home!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/>🗺 <strong>Versatile Map Integration:</strong><br/>Load any image file as a map, allowing boundless possibilities to explore and create intricate worlds, designed by your imagination.<br/><br/>🎮 <strong>Distinctive Game Modes:</strong><br/>Engage in the Exploration mode where players control their characters in real-time, uncovering the realms set by the Game Master, or dive into riveting turn-based battles, strategizing every move.<br/><br/>💼 <strong>Dynamic Role-Playing:</strong><br/>One player takes on the role of the Game Master, orchestrating the universe's destiny, while others immerse themselves as characters in the unfolding tale.<br/><br/>🧙 <strong>Character &amp; Group Creation:</strong><br/>Game Masters can forge characters, assemble groups, and craft maps, which can be saved and swiftly loaded to streamline gameplay during campaigns.<br/><br/>👥 <strong>Multiplayer Interaction:</strong><br/>Play with friends and experience collaborative storytelling, all while forging memories and facing challenges together.<br/><br/>🎢 <strong>User-Friendly Interface:</strong><br/>Designed with players in mind, Roles &amp; Dice provides an intuitive and seamless experience, allowing easy navigation and game setup.<br/><br/>📜 <strong>Campaign Saving:</strong><br/>Save your meticulously created characters, maps, and groups for quick load and play, ensuring smooth transitions between sessions.<br/><br/><strong>Engage in Unparalleled Adventure:</strong><br/>Whether you're exploring uncharted territories, battling formidable foes, or immersing yourself in stories untold, Roles &amp; Dice provides the ultimate virtual tabletop experience, allowing you and your friends to create and live out your fantastical tales.<br/><br/><strong>Embark on your journey in Roles &amp; Dice and unravel the realms of endless possibilities!</strong> 🌌						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coloring Game: Studio</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2231040/Coloring_Game_Studio/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2231040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Coloring Game: Studio is now not only paint by numbers, but also a small graphics editor. You can not only get rid of stress by painting pixels, but also show your creative nature by changing the base pictures.<h2 class="bb_tag">The game includes:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 pictures;<br/></li><li>3,600,000px;<br/></li><li>Image editor;<br/></li><li>Uploading your own images.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
