<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Voice Love on Air</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2321120/Voice_Love_on_Air/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2321120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2321120/extras/无背景kv.png?t=1711591213"><br/><i>Voice Love on Air</i> is a BL Dating Sim Game centered on voice recording sessions for Radio Dramas.<br/>The protagonist Aki has the ability to hear a person's true feelings from their voice to uncover truths and lies.<br/>He started a recording studio of his own but ran into some business difficulties.<br/>To ease his financial situation, he agreed to help a friend in the sound recording for BL dramas.<h2 class="bb_tag">[Start Recording from Scratch]</h2>Take on different drama genre projects, study, and collect materials.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2321120/extras/（英）插图1.png?t=1711591213"><h2 class="bb_tag">[Do Your Best for Every Drama]</h2>Choose your favorite voice actor to work closely with in voice direction.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2321120/extras/（英）插图2.png?t=1711591213"><h2 class="bb_tag">[Get to know them… better]</h2>Meet up with your love interest on the weekends and hear his story.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2321120/extras/（英）插图3.png?t=1711591213"><h2 class="bb_tag">[Make Your Own Voice Love Story]</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2321120/extras/主角团2.png?t=1711591213"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Necrosmith 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2277320/Necrosmith_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2277320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The necromancer simulator is back. Assemble your undead from different body parts, combining the abilities of various fantasy races. Upgrade your tower and give it a unique look. Fight your way through hordes of enemies in a procedurally generated world and take titans under control.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2277320/extras/1_lab_framed.gif?t=1711557491"><h2 class="bb_tag">Undead with Superpowers</h2>Assemble your undead from the body parts of various fantasy races, unlocking countless combinations of attacks and skills. Give them the ability to overcome obstacles, whether it be towering mountains, full-flowing rivers or lakes of red-hot lava. Under the cover of darkness, your undead are stronger, so do your best to prepare for the dangers of the day.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2277320/extras/2_undead_framed.gif?t=1711557491"><h2 class="bb_tag">Unique Necromancer Tower</h2>Upgrade the tower with various add-ons and give it a unique look. Build necro labs for growing body parts and technomagic devices that will give you powerful spells and enhance your undead warriors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2277320/extras/3_tower_framed.gif?t=1711557491"><h2 class="bb_tag">Procedurally Generated World</h2>Explore dozens of biomes in a procedurally generated world and view the conquered territories on the map. Use suitable body parts when creating the undead, so that they can handle the high mountains, squelchy swamps and dense forests. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2277320/extras/4_world_framed.gif?t=1711557491"><h2 class="bb_tag">Attack of Titans</h2>This time you'll have to face new monsters of gigantic size that can easily destroy your tower. But you also have the chance to create titans and fight back.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2277320/extras/5_titans_framed.gif?t=1711557491"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2277320/Necrosmith_2/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2277320/Necrosmith_2/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warframe: Dante Chronicles Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2882060/Warframe_Dante_Chronicles_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2882060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<strong>This pack features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Dante Warframe<br/></li><li> Ruvox Melee Weapon<br/></li><li> Rencowl Syandana<br/></li><li> Oranist Armor<br/></li><li> Dante Cantist Helmet<br/></li><li> Dante's Delight Glyph<br/></li><li> Dante's Noctua Sigil<br/></li><li> Observant Vitreum<br/></li><li> 125 Platinum</li></ul><br/>This pack may only be purchased once per account.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Magical Mixture Mill</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1883800/The_Magical_Mixture_Mill/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FjZUUaZkUGP" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/extras/tmmm_store_discordbanner.png?t=1711604226"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/extras/Banner2.0.png?t=1711604226"><br/><br/>Any adventurer will tell you that <strong>Griselda’s Magical Mixtures</strong> is the go-to shop for travelers and heroes in search of performance-enhancing concoctions; be it to obtain mighty strength, incredible intelligence, enviable beauty or... less heroic needs.<br/><br/>Griselda, an elderly mushroom-loving witch, has always run the business with great dedication but time has taken its toll, and it's time to train someone who can replace her. In short, her knowledge must be handed down and <strong>YOU</strong> - a former adventurer whose career was cut short by mixture intolerance - <strong>will be the perfect candidate</strong>!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/extras/MMM-CLIP-Mix-1.gif?t=1711604226"><br/><br/>Together with your goblin assistant, <strong>build automated production lines of alchemical workstations</strong> to provide potent mixtures to the local heroes, assisting them in their epic quests, and making you their favorite potion supplier. <strong>Explore</strong> diverse biomes and use your remaining adventuring abilities to <strong>gather and research exotic ingredients</strong>, leading to new mixing opportunities. Get ready to face all the “<i>wax on, wax off</i>” challenges Griselda throws at you to bring the shop back to its former glory!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/extras/Magical_Features2.0.png?t=1711604226"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>• Accessible, automated potion brewing</strong></h2>Create fully automated production pipelines from a varied catalogue of workstations to produce potions. Balance liquid ratio, maximize potency, pick the right ingredients, balance flavors and pour it all on the fanciest bottle you can craft to create the potion!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>• A Vibrant, Cozy, and Colorful world!</strong></h2>A mix of colorful illustration designs with a pinch of cheeky classic fantasy humor but still an alchemically-cozy experience. Different environments to explore and gather your ingredients. But be careful! Some flora and fauna will fight back…<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>• Happy customers always come back! Especially if they are “hooked”</strong></h2>Not all heroes want the same potions, so take your time to get to know your customers. As they level up, their demand for stronger and more advanced mixtures grow, turning them into very loyal customers - and turning your pockets heavy with coins!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/extras/MMM-CLIP-Mix-2.gif?t=1711604226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/extras/guide_mixedPotion_small.png?t=1711604226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1883800/extras/Bar2.0.png?t=1711604226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distant Bloom</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1450250/Distant_Bloom/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to <strong>Distant Bloom</strong>, a <strong>cozy management and exploration game</strong> far away from home!<br/><br/>After a long expedition through space, you and your crew land on an alien planet with the critical mission of establishing a new home for your species. But this place is very different from the vision you saw through your telescope. What happened to the verdant life of this world? <i>And what will happen to you?</i> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/extras/DBGIF1.gif?t=1711545126"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Explore</strong> a desolate world and <strong>restore </strong>its blooming past with the power of plants!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/extras/DistantBloom_newGIF1.gif?t=1711545126"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Nurture new life by learning how to care for an amazingly varied alien flora.</strong> Play around with plant structures and create <strong>a thriving ecosystem!</strong><br/></li><li>Turn your harvest into<strong> recipes, tools, and items</strong> that you can use to build and <strong>improve your homebase.</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/extras/DistantBloom_newGIF2.gif?t=1711545126"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Reunite your scattered crew</strong> into a community where each member has their <strong>own story to tell.</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Explore the wilds to uncover the history of this strange planet.</strong> What <i>–or who–</i> left behind the puzzling ruins scattered across the land?<br/></li><li><strong>Change the world!</strong> Your actions will impact not only nature but also the <strong>future of your crew.</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/extras/DistantBloom_newGIF3.gif?t=1711545126"><br/><br/>Distant Bloom is an <strong>accessible and rewarding game</strong> that offers a <strong>warm, sheltered, and intimate experience.</strong> Explore, create, and bring nature <strong>closer to home!</strong><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FygVMn2Yser" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1450250/extras/discord_banner_DB.png?t=1711545126"/></a> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE FINALS - Bank Rabbit Set</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2897810/THE_FINALS__Bank_Rabbit_Set/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2897810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							The Season 2 Bank Rabbit bundle includes:<br>
<br>
- Bunny Outfit<br>
- Hide Easter Egg Emote<br>
- 2 400 Multibucks						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>River Town Factory: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2847250/River_Town_Factory_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							River Town Factory: Prologue vs. Official Version Differences<br/>*Special Note: Prologue save data can all be transferred to the official version.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>In the Prologue version, players can increase the favorability of all romanceable NPCs up to 4 hearts.<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, players can increase the favorability of all regular NPCs up to 4 hearts.<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, players can access up to T1 node in the Oracle Temple.<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, 15% of buildings and technologies are available.<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, players can explore the Central Region, including martial arts and relic caves within the region.<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, players can reach a maximum of Level 2 on the SwordWay Sect and River Town Bounty Board (Somewhat Famous).<br/></li><li>In the Prologue version, players can participate in the Spring Festival, including the Flower Festival and Qingming Festival.</li></ul><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FwNSHHEB2EJ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/discord.jpg?t=1711550847"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/en1.png?t=1711550847"><br/><br/>Create automated production assembly lines, from wooden planks to circuit boards, design every step of your production line.<br/>Unlock future technologies gradually, from silicon purification to photovoltaic power generation, and build your futuristic workshop.<br/>Use inter-district teleportation stations to receive products at various levels, expanding your factory's territory to the entire continent.<br/>From brewing and oil pressing to manufacturing ovens, even producing watches and antibiotics, astound ancient people with your futuristic goods!<br/>Reinforced concrete, rubber, and large-scale computers, these will be the mass-produced materials you use in the ancient times, a thousand years ago!!!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/steamgif.gif?t=1711550847"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/en2.png?t=1711550847"><br/><br/>There are 12 characters that can be pursued in the game - the royal, the martial arts world, the merchant, etc. Unlock the secrets of each character and pursue the friendships and romances you desire. Choose your partner and discuss marriage, and together move into the workshop where they will provide powerful assistance. Make connections with nearly 30 historical figures, each with their own changing schedules throughout the four seasons. Participate in their lives and use modern knowledge to solve their problems. In the River Town, everything happens naturally, and you have the final say on when to work, explore, and engage in romantic pursuits.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/rwall.gif?t=1711550847"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/rwstory.gif?t=1711550847"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/en3.png?t=1711550847"><br/><br/>A fast-paced combat system that is easy to pick up, combining evasion and offense to defeat your enemies through strategic maneuvers. Whether through formal training or adventures in the martial arts world, master more than 40 martial arts techniques including external skills, internal skills, light skills, and hard skills, allowing you to dominate the martial arts world.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/4zd.gif?t=1711550847"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/en4.png?t=1711550847"><br/><br/>Explore the four major villages on the map, complete village quests, and uncover their secrets.<br/>Explore the mystical realms left behind by ancient predecessors, delve deep into them, and defeat bizarre creatures.<br/>Explore the entire continent, discover treasures, explore bat caves, and punish bandits for the people.<br/>Sign contracts with mine owners throughout the entire map, allowing ancient people to work for you.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/5zddd.gif?t=1711550847"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/en5.png?t=1711550847"><br/><br/>Be a skilled craftsman or a social butterfly? Become the top martial artist or a versatile expert in everyday life? It's all up to you to decide.<br/>Craft spiritual medicines, weapons, and clothing, becoming a master of ancient craftsmanship.<br/>Create over 20 different dishes with various enhancements, such as Five Treasures Stew and Snowy Sunset Soup... Make them in your kitchen!<br/>Fill the Heavenly Workshop with the products you create, allowing ancient people to visit and witness modern technology.<br/>Utilize the power of future technology to repair the time machine and fulfill a mission that only you can accomplish.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847250/extras/6zd.gif?t=1711550847"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulwark: Falconeer Chronicles</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/290100/Bulwark_Falconeer_Chronicles/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/titleBannerDescr.png?t=1711475617"><br/>Bulwark: Falconeer Chronicles is an open world builder with freedom and expression at its core, allowing players to build sprawling towns, spires, and fortresses that become hubs for trade, or rallying grounds for conquests. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/building.gif?t=1711475617"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_2-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Reforge a world shattered by the decisions of those who came before you, tower by tower, wall by wall, sculpting from the daunting cliffs and perilous waters of an unforgiving landscape that refuses to be tamed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_3-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Devastated by the aftermath of a war 40 years prior, you are in command of creating the last great settlement upon the Great Ursee - a vast, fantastical oceanic world filled with lost myths, breath-taking vistas and danger. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_4-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Starting with humble docks and wooden jetties, you will scavenge resources and grow your settlement as your population and creations grow ever grander, sculpting monumental stone towers and battlements that scrape the skies, where airships and giant warbirds rule.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_5-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>Create trade routes and strike alliances with other factions scattered across the waves, acquiring powerful Captains and Commanders to protect your creations and utilise their aid in exploration -  or muster your own battlegroup to strike at them, waging war upon your ancient enemies. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/BW_Banner_6-EN.jpg?t=1711475617"><br/>This world and its choices are yours to make - what legacy will you leave behind? What creations will bear your name?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/combat.gif?t=1711475617"><h2 class="bb_tag">Rediscover The Great Ursee </h2>The next instalment in the series which started with the award-winning 2020 aerial combat game, ‘The Falconeer’, taken into a completely new genre.<h2 class="bb_tag">A World of History and Violence </h2>An open world, full of opportunity. Explore the widest reaches of the Ursee in search of resources and engage with splintered factions - allying with them to acquire their aid, or sending your own warband to raid their settlements.<h2 class="bb_tag">Defend Your Bulwark </h2>Recruit powerful Captains and Commanders, used to provide powerful units, shore up your defences and adorn your settlement with their own architecture and style.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build Without Limits</h2>Enjoy a cosy ‘Freebuild Mode’, devoid of the conflict and challenges present in standard play, you can build without the need for resources or upgrades.<h2 class="bb_tag">Chaotic Creativity </h2>Immerse yourself in building mechanics inspired by 3D modelling software and kitbashing, for a building experience that focuses on experimentation.<h2 class="bb_tag">Transcendental Soundtrack </h2>Award-winning composer Benedict Nichols returns to craft an eclectic soundtrack like no other, sculpting the audible landscape of the Ursee along with your creations.<h2 class="bb_tag">Share Your Creations </h2>Utilise an intuitive, flexible camera mode and time lapse replay feature to watch your unique creations grow brick by brick, then share them with the world<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Ffalconeer" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/290100/extras/Bulwark-Discord.png?t=1711475617"/></a><br/><br/>Secret Code -&gt; 20TSFCBW24AW						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1268590/Millennia/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fmillennia" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/616x152.png?t=1711472688"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Store_Page_City_Growth_animation_Steam-Loop.gif?t=1711472688"><br/>Create your own nation in Millennia, a historical turn-based 4X game that challenges your strategic prowess across 10,000 years of history, from the dawn of humanity to our possible futures.  Set the course of history and experience different timelines in every playthrough as you write an epic story through your actions.  Lead your people through times of crisis and ages of discovery, face great challenges and opportunities, and build a civilization that prospers through the ages.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Guide_Your_Nation.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Dictate the course of history across ten ages, from the first cities to space travel.  Accomplish certain objectives and you can move time into a Variant Age - an alternate history with new rules, new technologies, and new units.  But beware Crisis Ages; following a path of chaos and disorder may plunge the world into a future filled with war, sickness or ignorance.  Then again, a wise ruler can always turn a crisis into an opportunity....  Choose the path with care, as the ages you pass through will have a lasting impact on your people and the world.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Choose_What_You.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Customize your nation by adopting unique Nations Spirits over the course of your game.  Will you be a nation of warriors or explorers?  Are your people lead by a Great Khan or a builder of monuments?  Are you known for defining  pop culture or for dominating global finance?  What parts of your culture will reverberate across history?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Master_a_Deep.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Manage your economy with care and create a juggernaut of growth and construction.  Start with basic resources to gain food, wealth, and production.  As your advance, decide how to best convert these simple goods into more valuable products through research and improvements.  Specialize your regions, turning iron into weapons or tools, wood into paper or lumber, gold into coin or jewelry.  Ship surplus goods where they are needed, allowing the breadbasket of your empire to feed far-flung colonies or your industrial heartland to supply troops near your enemy.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Unlock_Technologies.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Pursue knowledge to research scientific and cultural advances, unlocking new units, buildings, and improvements to grow your cities or strengthen your armies.  Research Defense to train the first archers, Smelting to master iron production, or Guilds for making wine.  Variant and Crisis Ages feature unique alternatives, introducing everything from Cloud Estates in the Age of Aether to underwater cities in the Age of Utopia.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Achieve_Victory.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Achieve your ultimate success through a Victory Age.  Toward the end of the game (or earlier if your strategy is sound), dominance allows a nation to dictate the winning conditions.  The rest of the world must decide if they will struggle to achieve victory before the leader ... or oppose the leader's attempt.  Risk everything to take victory in the Renaissance or carefully plan for triumph in the modern era.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Millennia: Premium Edition includes the following content:</h2><br/><strong>Wolfpack Warband &amp; Eagle Archers cosmetics</strong><br/>Elevate the presence of your units in Millennia with the exclusive Wolfpack Warband and Eagle Archers clothings. Available instantly with the Premium Edition, this clothes pack unlocks unique wolf skin clothing for your Warband. Your Archer Unit receives eagle-inspired clothes, symbolizing their precision and keen sight.<br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Ancient Worlds</strong><br/>Take your first uncertain steps in a new era for humanity in Millennia: Ancient Worlds. Take control of your people before their first settlement, while they still wander as nomads.  Includes a new nomadic game start option, a new National Spirit, a new economic Good, and new Nation starting bonuses. <br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Atomic Ambitions</strong><br/>Unlock the mysteries of the atom and change the world forever in Millennia: Atomic Ambitions. The Premium edition adds ways to harness the power of the atom for the good of all humankind, but, there are also ways to turn the planet into a fallout-filled wasteland if you aren’t careful. Includes two new Ages, a new National Spirit, and nuclear options for the Strategic Warfare System.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1268590/Millennia/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fmillennia" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/616x152.png?t=1711472688"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Store_Page_City_Growth_animation_Steam-Loop.gif?t=1711472688"><br/>Create your own nation in Millennia, a historical turn-based 4X game that challenges your strategic prowess across 10,000 years of history, from the dawn of humanity to our possible futures.  Set the course of history and experience different timelines in every playthrough as you write an epic story through your actions.  Lead your people through times of crisis and ages of discovery, face great challenges and opportunities, and build a civilization that prospers through the ages.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Guide_Your_Nation.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Dictate the course of history across ten ages, from the first cities to space travel.  Accomplish certain objectives and you can move time into a Variant Age - an alternate history with new rules, new technologies, and new units.  But beware Crisis Ages; following a path of chaos and disorder may plunge the world into a future filled with war, sickness or ignorance.  Then again, a wise ruler can always turn a crisis into an opportunity....  Choose the path with care, as the ages you pass through will have a lasting impact on your people and the world.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Choose_What_You.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Customize your nation by adopting unique Nations Spirits over the course of your game.  Will you be a nation of warriors or explorers?  Are your people lead by a Great Khan or a builder of monuments?  Are you known for defining  pop culture or for dominating global finance?  What parts of your culture will reverberate across history?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Master_a_Deep.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Manage your economy with care and create a juggernaut of growth and construction.  Start with basic resources to gain food, wealth, and production.  As your advance, decide how to best convert these simple goods into more valuable products through research and improvements.  Specialize your regions, turning iron into weapons or tools, wood into paper or lumber, gold into coin or jewelry.  Ship surplus goods where they are needed, allowing the breadbasket of your empire to feed far-flung colonies or your industrial heartland to supply troops near your enemy.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Unlock_Technologies.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Pursue knowledge to research scientific and cultural advances, unlocking new units, buildings, and improvements to grow your cities or strengthen your armies.  Research Defense to train the first archers, Smelting to master iron production, or Guilds for making wine.  Variant and Crisis Ages feature unique alternatives, introducing everything from Cloud Estates in the Age of Aether to underwater cities in the Age of Utopia.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1268590/extras/Achieve_Victory.png?t=1711472688"><br/>Achieve your ultimate success through a Victory Age.  Toward the end of the game (or earlier if your strategy is sound), dominance allows a nation to dictate the winning conditions.  The rest of the world must decide if they will struggle to achieve victory before the leader ... or oppose the leader's attempt.  Risk everything to take victory in the Renaissance or carefully plan for triumph in the modern era.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Millennia: Premium Edition includes the following content:</h2><br/><strong>Wolfpack Warband &amp; Eagle Archers cosmetics</strong><br/>Elevate the presence of your units in Millennia with the exclusive Wolfpack Warband and Eagle Archers clothings. Available instantly with the Premium Edition, this clothes pack unlocks unique wolf skin clothing for your Warband. Your Archer Unit receives eagle-inspired clothes, symbolizing their precision and keen sight.<br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Ancient Worlds</strong><br/>Take your first uncertain steps in a new era for humanity in Millennia: Ancient Worlds. Take control of your people before their first settlement, while they still wander as nomads.  Includes a new nomadic game start option, a new National Spirit, a new economic Good, and new Nation starting bonuses. <br/><br/><strong>Millennia: Atomic Ambitions</strong><br/>Unlock the mysteries of the atom and change the world forever in Millennia: Atomic Ambitions. The Premium edition adds ways to harness the power of the atom for the good of all humankind, but, there are also ways to turn the planet into a fallout-filled wasteland if you aren’t careful. Includes two new Ages, a new National Spirit, and nuclear options for the Strategic Warfare System.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTH PARK: SNOW DAY!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1214650/SOUTH_PARK_SNOW_DAY/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1214650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From South Park Digital Studios, the studio that brought you South Park: The Stick of Truth, South Park: The Fractured but Whole, and South Park: Phone Destroyer comes the next chapter in the journey of the New Kid.<br/><br/>Join Cartman, Stan, Kyle, and Kenny, in three-dimensional glory, to celebrate the most magical day in any young child’s life - a snow day! A massive blizzard has thrown the town into chaos and, more importantly, canceled school.<br/><br/>Play with up to three friends, use matchmaking, or solo the game with ally bots and battle through the snow-piled town of South Park. Engage in frenetic, action-packed combat against warring factions in an all-new story where you make the rules. Equip unique weapons and deploy devastating, upgradable special abilities on a new adventure to save the world and enjoy a day without school.<h2 class="bb_tag">It’s a snow day, dude!</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle your way through the snow-covered town of South Park in this all-new 3D co-op game.<br/></li><li>A blizzard of epic proportions has blanketed the town of South Park and it’s up to Cartman, Stan, Kenny, Kyle, and you, as the New Kid, to save the town from an endless winter.<br/></li><li>Experience cooperative gameplay for the first time ever in a South Park game with up to three friends or ally bots - unleashing powerful, coordinated attacks on your foes.<br/></li><li>Equip and upgrade devastating melee and ranged weapons. Deploy special abilities and powers that will bring hordes of enemies and epic bosses to their knees.<br/></li><li>Use a wide range of iconic cosmetics and customize your New Kid with endless possible combinations from beanies to Cheesy Poof T-shirts to chin balls.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DORONKO WANKO</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2512840/DORONKO_WANKO/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							『DORONKO WANKO』 is a <strong>DORONKO Action</strong> Game.<br/>In this game, you can become a cute, innocent pomeranian.<br/>And you can make your master's home messy and dirty.<br/>Let's explore this beautiful house and make it dirty and muddy at will!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Action_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Action.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>Pomeranian can get muddy by "rubbing"  against the "mud" spread on the floor.<br/>Spread out the mud with "splash"!<br/>Let's make the whole area muddy and messy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Goal_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Goal.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>Sometimes you can find "hidden pome" when you are spreading mud all over the house.<br/>When you find all the "hidden pome", the "Good Smell Room" 's door will open.<br/>(Let's go inside quietly before others notice!)<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Damage_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Damage.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>More mud, more damage!<br/>You can check the total amount of damage you have caused from the ending “Receipt”.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Present_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Present.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>When you cause enough damage, you will receive a “gift”?!<br/>They will help Pome’s exploration by making it easier to splash mud and obtain key items.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Gimmick_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Gimmick.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>A little action can cause a huge damage?<br/>Use personal appliances and toys to get even muddier.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Badge_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Badge_EN.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>The Pomeranian's adventures will remain as a "badge of memory".<br/>A random move may get an unexpected badge.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamBanner_Customize_EN.png?t=1711439792"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2512840/extras/POME_SteamGIF_Customize.gif?t=1711439792"><br/>"Put on" the "Goods" and make your Pomeranian more pretty.<br/>Don't forget the special goods that can release mud!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2510720/Artifact_Seeker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/DS.png?t=1711367082"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/11y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>The unique “Artifacts sharing code function” allows you to share the Artifacts you collect with your friends! !<br/>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/1y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/1z.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/2y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/gif1.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/3y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/3y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/4y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/4y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/5y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/5y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/6y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/6y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living With Sister: Monochrome Fantasy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2429860/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1711168850"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_1__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/>Living in a fantasy world, it's always been your dream to grow up to be a famous adventurer just like your father. Reality proves to be more boring than fiction, however, as your days are mostly spent doing odd jobs for the villagers. With your friends by your side, you enter the Tournament of the Eights and strive for something greater: the chance to become the top guild in the country. Will you realize your ambitions, or will your hopes slip through your fingers and doom you to a life of monochrome monotony?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_2__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/>As a member of your town's Adventurers' Guild, it's your job to protect the townsfolk. Go on hunts, kill dangerous beasts, and hone your abilities to better tackle whatever challenges tomorrow brings.<br/><br/>Once you get home from work, you'll have your sister to attend to. She's a very sickly girl who needs a lot of help. Manage your household finances well, build up your relationship with your sister, and who knows, perhaps you might even be able to solve the mystery behind her illness.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_3__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Big_Brother_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Little_Sister_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Kana_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Yui_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Kasumi_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Yukari_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Akatsuki_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_4__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><strong>Hand-Drawn Monochrome Art</strong><br/>Though it may lack color, this game's world is anything but colorless! The stunning black-and-white art is chock-full of personality and is sure to leave you with plenty of marvelous monochrome memories!<br/><br/><strong>Unique Combat System</strong><br/>With tons of bizarre and ferocious monsters to fight and dozens of unique skills to unlock, your adventures are sure to be full of challenge and excitement!<br/><br/><strong>Charming Characters</strong><br/>Build up your relationships with your guildmates and your sister to learn about what makes them tick and unlock character-specific abilities to further assist you in your quest to become the top guild in the country!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Chilla's Art] Shinkansen 0 | 新幹線 0号</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2793370/Chillas_Art_Shinkansen_0___0/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2793370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Shinkansen 0 | 新幹線 0号 is a game set in Japan where players are tasked with finding anomalies in the Shinkansen. (Japanese bullet train)<br/><br/><i><strong>Supporter content can be turned on and off at the title screen. (It is on by default) </strong></i><br/><br/><i><strong>Motion Blur and Headbob is turned off by default.</strong></i><br/><br/><strong>Controls:<br/><br/>WASD - Move<br/>Left Click - Interact　<br/>Right Click - Zoom<br/>Shift - Run<br/>ESC - Options</strong><br/><br/>Easy mode - There is an easy mode in the mainmenu available for everyone to enjoy<br/><br/>Auto-save: auto-save for each chapter<br/><br/>Endings: There are two endings<br/><br/><strong><i>If you encounter any technical issues, do the following:<br/><br/>-Update GPU driver<br/>-Lower the Graphics settings/Screen resolution<br/>-Update Windows OS<br/>-Check if your anti-virus software is blocking the game or its save data. (Save Data location: C:\Users\[YOURUSERNAME]\AppData\LocalLow\Chilla's Art, LLC\Shinkansen0)<br/>-Delete save, then try again (Save Data location: C:\Users\[YOURUSERNAME]\AppData\LocalLow\Chilla's Art, LLC\Shinkansen0)<br/>-Check if your PC meets the system requirements</i></strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2054970/Dragons_Dogma_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Note: There are other sets that include this item.<br/><br/>Set forth on your grand adventure, Arisen!<br/><br/>Dragon’s Dogma is a single player, narrative driven action-RPG series that challenges the players to choose their own experience – from the appearance of their Arisen, their vocation, their party, how to approach different situations and more. Now, in this long-awaited sequel, the deep, explorable fantasy world of Dragon’s Dogma 2 awaits.<br/><br/>On your journey, you’ll be joined by Pawns, mysterious otherworldly beings, in an adventure so unique you will feel as if accompanied by other players while on your own adventure.<br/><br/>All of these elements are elevated further through physics technology, artificial intelligence (AI) and the latest in graphics, to create a truly immersive fantasy world in Dragon’s Dogma 2.<br/><br/><br/><strong><u>Action that challenges your creativity </u></strong> <br/><br/>Wield swords, bows, and chant magick.<br/>The vocations in Dragon's Dogma 2 give you the ability to approach combat the way you want.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_01.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Company in your single-player experience </u></strong> <br/><br/>Players can customize their own main Pawn, who will always accompany your Arisen, <br/>and enter a covenant with up to 2 additional Pawns from other players through the network. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_02.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Facing the monsters in this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Beyond the town borders, you will encounter diverse monsters that inhabit the lands. <br/>You will need to decide between engaging in battles or finding alternatives; <br/>so be aware of your party’s setup, the terrain around you, and the monsters you face.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_03.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Inhabitants of this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Travelers, merchants, soldiers and other folk go about their daily lives. <br/>Preoccupied by their own objectives and motives, they all exhibit different emotions.<br/>At times, they may lead you to a quest by approaching you and asking for a favor. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_04.gif?t=1711067553"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cureocity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2612680/Cureocity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							We are "Bread On Board," a collective of independent game developers spread across four countries, united by our passion and meeting during a GameJam. <br/>Our game demo was born in the "BOOOM CHALLENGE", a GameJam by GCORES. With only 21 days, we created a game based on a given theme. After the competition, we even won the "Most Popular Game" award at an Online Game Trial Event.<br/>The full playthrough of our game will take about an hour. We hope to give you a short, but super heartwarming and loving adventure❤️.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/1.奇幻而治愈（英文）.png?t=1711531628"><br/>A rookie adventurer fresh on the scene and a former mercenary who was transferred into an adventurer due to injury. Two protagonists with contrasting personalities will embark on an adventure of fantasy and healing together. In the mysterious ruins of an underground dungeon that lies in the depth of a jungle, what awaits them will be...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1711531628"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/2.两位冒险者（英文）.png?t=1711531628"><br/>According to the tavern's adventurer logs, the team heading into the dungeon features a rookie adventurer and an ex-mercenary who is now working as a healer. The adventurer looks as charming as a doll, and the enthusiasm never disappears; the healer is cool and a bit traditional, acting as a guiding figure for their adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1711531628"><br/><br/>What stories have unfolded between these two contrasting characters, and what challenges will they face together in this adventure? The continuation of this adventurous story is yours to discover.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/3.注重手法的回合制解谜（英文）.png?t=1711531628"><br/>"People think battles need powerful weapons, but strategy at hand is key." <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_3_en.gif?t=1711531628"><br/><br/>In "Cureocity," the power of your strategy is materialized as the numerical values of your hands in combat. You can swap different weapons or items held in your left and right hands to alter your character's attack and defense stats. You may also change "gestures" to focus attacks or land heavy blows on specific enemies.As you delve deeper into the dungeon, you will take the unique traits of monsters into consideration and discuss strategies with your allies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/4.你的选择决定冒险归途（英文）.png?t=1711531628"><br/>In this adventure, you'll discover not only the secrets hidden within the dungeon, but also the truths about the world and the  characters themselves. When faced with contaminated monsters, you can choose to either fight them or attempt to purify them. Of course, you also have the option to let things take their own course.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_4_en.gif?t=1711531628"><br/><br/>With each decision,the fate of the protagonists may change. The end of this adventure... is yours to decide.<h2 class="bb_tag">About the Publisher</h2>GCORES PUBLISHING is an independent game publishing venture formed by GCORES, committed to bringing you more outstanding indie games from the BOOOM CHALLENGE.<br/>Feel free to follow our <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/44750639" rel="" target="_blank">publisher webpage</a> for future updates.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midnight Ghost Hunt</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/915810/Midnight_Ghost_Hunt/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/915810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>MIDNIGHT GHOST HUNT IS A <i>PETRIFYING</i> PROP HAUNT GAME TO PLAY WITH PALS! </strong><br/><br/>Lying in wait across a series of cursed locations, relentless spirits stalk the halls. Assigned to eliminate them are the Ghost Hunters, armed to the teeth with the ghoul-busting tech to banish them to another realm! Play both Ghost and Hunter in a chaotic 4v4 struggle between the living and the dead.<br/><br/><strong>TONGUE-IN-CHEEK HIDE-AND-SEEK</strong><br/>As a Ghost, conceal yourself inside seemingly harmless pieces of furniture to evade preying Hunters… but when their backs are turned, turn the environment against them with telekinetic bombardment. No chair, lamp, or grandfather clock is innocent in this hijinks-heavy frenzy.<br/><br/><strong>MIDNIGHT MAYHEM</strong><br/>The fun isn’t over yet...when the clock strikes twelve, the witching hour begins, and the Hunters become the Hunted. The tables turn and Ghosts become supercharged, giving Hunters a limited amount of time to survive their vengeful wrath.<br/><br/><strong>MURDEROUS 4v4 MULTIPLAYER</strong><br/>Play together and communicate with your team and ensure a triumphant victory, giving each other pointers on the paths enemies tend to tread. Create synergies with your team's abilities to outthink and outwit your opponents.<br/><br/><strong>HARNESS SUPERNATURAL ABILITIES</strong><br/>The restrictions of reality don’t apply to Ghosts, of course. Claim your supernatural powers, which include turning invisible, causing furniture to float, and conjuring a dangerous Ghostly miasma. Ghosts can even hide in plain sight by masquerading as a Hunter’s doppelgänger!<br/><br/>Ghostly Perks include dramatically increasing your weight, extending your possessing range, the ability to see nearby Hunters through walls, and much more. <br/><br/><strong>ARMED AND READY</strong><br/>Hunters must choose their weapons from a full range of hi-tech gadgets designed to cast out Ghosts from our plane of existence. Detect ghostly presences with the Spectrophone, Radar and Pathfinder, capture them with a Trap, and suck up their spectral remains with the Vacuum – or just blast them to smithereens with the Spectral Cannon, sledgehammers, harpoons, salt-spewing shotguns, and more.<br/><br/>Hunters can also select Perks to give them a special boost. Choose from an extra burst of speed, health-replenishing capabilities and a host of other powers to get ahead of the game.<br/><br/><strong>A BEVY OF BLOOD-CURDLING MAPS </strong><br/>Explore ten unsettling locations, including an abandoned theatre, eerie mansion and cursed carnival. Each map brings with it different tactical considerations and items to throw about… as well as plenty of opportunities to play tricks on the enemy.<br/><br/><strong>FRIGHTENING NEW FEATURES</strong> <br/>As it crept through Steam Early Access, Midnight Ghost Hunt picked up a gaggle of game-changing features, built on the feedback of its community of Ghosts and Hunters.<br/><br/>Dedicated servers and host migration support make setting up matches a breeze, while the Progression Tier and Challenge systems bring added competition to the hunt. Looking for less of the silly and more of the scary? The Experimental Darkness game mode lends a chill to the chaos. Not to mention crossplay, full controller support, and even the GhostMaster minigame to pass the time during the van ride to your next match!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horizon Forbidden West™ Complete Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420110/Horizon_Forbidden_West_Complete_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/extras/horizon_forbidden_west_cinemagraph_610x610.gif?t=1711473066"><br/><br/>Join Aloy as she braves a majestic but dangerous new frontier that holds mysterious new threats. This Complete Edition allows you to enjoy the critically acclaimed Horizon Forbidden West on PC in its entirety with bonus content, including the Burning Shores story expansion that picks up after the main game.<br/><br/>Explore distant lands, fight bigger and more awe-inspiring machines, and encounter astonishing new tribes as you return to the far-future, post-apocalyptic world of Horizon.<br/><br/>The land is dying. Vicious storms and an unstoppable blight ravage the scattered remnants of humanity while fearsome new machines prowl their borders, and life on Earth is hurtling toward another extinction.<br/><br/>It's up to Aloy to uncover the secrets behind these threats and restore order and balance to the world. Along the way, she must reunite with old friends, forge alliances with warring new factions and unravel the legacy of the ancient past.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>See every gameplay detail with Ultrawide 21:9 and Super Ultrawide 32:9 resolutions, as well as 48:9 triple monitor support.*<br/></li><li>Witness the Forbidden West coming to life, with NVIDIA DLSS 3 upscaling and frame generation, image enhancing NVIDIA DLAA and latency reducing NVIDIA Reflex. AMD FSR and Intel XeSS are also supported.**<br/></li><li>Customize graphic settings to your preference, with the potential for unlocked frame rates.**<br/></li><li>Take control with full support for the DualSense™ controller, including haptic feedback and adaptive trigger functionality.*** </li></ul><br/>* Compatible PC and 4K display device required. <br/>** Compatible PC required. <br/>*** Wired connection required to experience the full range of in-game controller features.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age of Water: The First Voyage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2841350/Age_of_Water_The_First_Voyage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The First Voyage is the very beginning of your Age of Water experience. Jump right into the intense naval combat, craft your first boats, explore the waterworld and get a good idea of what Age of Water is about. Don’t forget to wishlist the full game now!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_ship_anim.gif?t=1711025025"><br/><br/>Become a sea captain on a post-apocalyptic Earth completely covered in water and go on an adventure in a huge open world. Sail through storms, fight and trade, capture other people's boats or build your own, extract resources from the bottom of the ocean, reveal the secrets of the Age of Water world.<br/><br/><strong>Water post-apocalypse</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_1.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>The ocean destroyed a once great civilization, but people survived and adapted. They built settlements on the roofs of tall buildings and the tops of other man-made structures. People travel across the ocean in tiny boats and huge combat vessels. The ocean provides everything they need, including extractable resources on the seabed. And yet, the dream of real land is still alive.<br/><br/><strong>True open world</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_2.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Explore the world at your own pace, discover new settlements and meet their inhabitants. Complete tasks, search for and extract valuable resources from the bottom of the ocean, earn money on trade or simply sell the artifacts you have obtained, and when you get the idea of how this world works, build your own base.<br/><br/><strong>Hundreds of unique ships</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_3.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Build boats from scratch or modify existing ones. Players have access to dozens of hulls and hundreds of parts, from which they can assemble anything ranging from a small boat to a hefty vessel 30 meters long, and then install equipment, armor and weapons. It’s important not to forget to gather a team of good crewmembers so that there is someone to stand behind machine guns and cannons or do other work on board.<br/><br/><strong>Fierce naval battles</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_4.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Pirates are always waiting for you at sea, and in some cases more aggressive players even start to chase you, so do not forget to install enough guns on your deck.  You can destroy an enemy vessel, or you can capture it in battle and take it for yourself forever. Adventures might also get you into storming enemy fortresses and defending allied settlements!<br/><br/><strong>Personal naval base</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_5.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>This shelter is reliably protected from enemies, and it allows a player to organize the production of everything that the captain may need on it. Build factories for the production of equipment, weapons, hulls for boats of all sizes, as well as the necessary resources.<br/><br/><strong>Flexible balance between PvE and PvP</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_6.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>At first, you will only meet computer opponents, but later you can challenge other players if you are confident enough in your skills and gear. Always be on the lookout: if your task is to transport illegal goods, then other players may well take the quest to hunt smugglers. In Age of Water, everyone decides for themself who they are today - a peaceful traveler or a bloodthirsty pirate.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slice &amp; Dice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1775490/Slice__Dice/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1775490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Slice &amp; Dice is a tactical dice battle roguelike.<br/><br/>Take control of 5 heroes, each with their own unique dice. Fight your way through 20 levels of monsters and try to take on the final boss. If you lose a single fight you have to start over so be careful/lucky!<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/>- 3D dice physics, choose which dice to reroll<br/>- Simple turn-based combat<br/>- Level up a hero or gain an item after each fight<br/>- Randomly-generated encounters<br/>- Ridiculous combos<br/>- Undo actions as much as you like<br/>- Each turn is like a mini-puzzle<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/>- 128 hero classes (+99999?)<br/>- 73 monsters<br/>- 473 items<br/>- Too many modes<br/>- ∞ curses<br/>- Weird modding<br/>- Online leaderboards<br/><br/><strong>Credits</strong><br/>- Created by tann (it took ~7 years)<br/>- Pixel art by a3um<br/>- Music by Ziggurath, Aleksander Zabłocki, Louigi Verona, Cold Sanctum, Ro'sø, Andrew Goodwin<br/>- Trailer by Everdraed<br/><br/>I plan to not participate in any sales/deals/bundles. No AI was used to make this game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone in the Dark</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1310410/Alone_in_the_Dark/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Alone in the Dark weaves a chilling tapestry of psychological horror and Southern Gothic charm, reimagining the iconic game that set the benchmark for the genre. We invite you to join us on a journey into madness, where each encounter could be your last. With each step you take closer to unravelling Derceto's mystery, the eyes that watch from the darkness grow hungrier. Every bullet means the difference between survival and an unthinkable end. The next door you unlock could lead to a nightmarish realm offering nothing but slashing claws, grasping tentacles, and frayed sanity.  Journey to interbellum Louisiana, where an era of decadence hides a darker tale - of escape from past traumas and an intolerant society, into the waiting grasp of something darker, something that has patiently lurked for impossible eons. This is Alone in the Dark as you've never seen it - a skillfully-woven narrative of Southern Gothic elegance and eldritch madness that pays homage to its legendary origins while taking the next step forward in survival horror storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_VIPIntro_2.gif?t=1711546287"><h2 class="bb_tag">A Haunting Tale of Mystery and Madness</h2>Step inside Derceto Manor, an asylum shrouded in intrigue, guarding a terrible secret. Client Emily Hartwood and private investigator Edward Carnby embark on a harrowing quest for answers; Emily to the mystery of her missing uncle, Edward to the toughest case he will ever face, and both to questions they dare not ask themselves. This re-envisioned classic invites you to explore an unforgettable single player adventure rich with suspense, frights, and revelations that will test the limits of your imagination.<h2 class="bb_tag">Featuring Hollywood Talent</h2>Experience some of the greatest acting survival horror has ever seen through the performances of award-winning actors Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow) in their first videogame roles. Jodie and David’s immaculately captured likenesses breathe life into Emily Hartwood and Edward Carnby, lending a deeply personal aspect to Alone in the Dark’s story that demands it be played twice to get the full experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Tribute to Horror Pioneers</h2>Rediscover the essence of psychological horror in a game that respectfully nods to its 1992 origin, the game that established the survival horror genre. Alone in the Dark is your gateway to an experience steeped in the atmospheric dread of classic horror, with next-generation storytelling and gameplay. A must-play for fans of twisted tales, nerve-wracking exploration, and desperate combat.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Story That Challenges Reality</h2>Envisioned by Mikael Hedberg, acclaimed writer behind modern horror classics “SOMA” and “Amnesia”, Alone in the Dark’s intricate web of mystery delves into themes of trauma, faith, evil, and abandonment. Whether you choose to brave the nightmare as Emily or Edward, you will uncover secrets that defy everything you thought about videogame storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Atrmo_2.gif?t=1711546287"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore Derceto Manor in this reimagination of Alone in the Dark, a love letter to the 90’s cult classic horror game.<br/></li><li>Return to the roots of psychological horror and experience an atmospheric journey worthy of the game that started the genre.<br/></li><li>Dive into a world full of sounds that make your skin crawl with a haunting, yet mesmerizing doom jazz soundtrack.<br/></li><li>Enjoy the thrill of desperate survival in a world where reality starts to crumble, evil lurks in every shadow and ammunition is scarce.<br/></li><li>Experience this nightmare from either Emily Hartwood’s or Edward Carnby’s perspective and unearth the dark secrets of a gothic mansion.<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in a deep psychological story that goes beyond the realms of the imaginable, by Mikael Hedberg, cult horror writer of SOMA and Amnesia.<br/></li><li>See Emily and Edward brought to live by the Hollywood talent of Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow), who lend their voices, their appearance, and their formidable acting skills to the protagonists.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Riddles_2.gif?t=1711546287"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Park Baseball 25</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384620/Out_of_the_Park_Baseball_25/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_banner_1.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/>We are incredibly excited to announce <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong> - the special 25th Anniversary edition of our award-winning baseball strategy series. Can you believe it's been a quarter of a century? Out of the Park Baseball is not just a game - it's a legacy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_henry.png?t=1710574531"><br/><br/>If it happens in real baseball, it happens in Out of the Park Baseball! Discover new talent, draft the next superstar, negotiate with free agents, enter trade talks with other teams, build your dynasty and guide a franchise into an infinite future! As a manager, dive into the more hands-on management and set your team's lineups, pitching staffs, in-game strategy and call the shots from the dugout. You can oversee your league at a high level, or play out each game in the gorgeous 3D game mode, managing play by play or even pitch by pitch. OOTP has it all covered!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_badge.png?t=1710574531"><br/>Here are just a few of the new features coming to <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong>:<br/><br/><strong>A game-changing new Player Development Lab!</strong><br/><br/>Shape the future of your upcoming stars! You can channel your inner Player Development Director like never before. A modern new Player Development Lab is here for every team that allows you to give players individual programs to work on, developing them how you like. Do you want your hitter to work on improving their baserunning? Bunting? Contact? Would you prefer your pitcher to work on building up their stamina? Developing a new pitch? Velocity? It's all up to you - for each of your upcoming future stars!<br/><br/><strong>Massive Player Ratings and AI Upgrade!</strong><br/><br/>It’s the most comprehensive player ratings upgrade in the 25 year history of Out of the Park Baseball! Batting, Pitching, and Fielding ratings have been painstakingly modified to capture the essence of baseball, with modifications to Contact and Power for hitters, Movement and Stuff for pitchers, the addition of Catcher Framing and Stealing Aggressiveness, and much more. BABIP is now front and center for hitters and hurlers, while new internal ratings updates allow for even more flexibility for Commissioners around the world to adjust the game to their detailed delight. Plus, the AI throughout the game has been improved dramatically to deliver the most challenging OOTP experience ever! <br/><br/><strong>Even More Detailed Player Development Control!</strong><br/><br/>Delegate how each and every player on your team will spend their time day in, day out with coaches at practice. Want your power hitter to worry less about avoiding strikeouts and put that time and effort into working on his home run swing instead? Want your aging starter to spend more time practicing his control instead of spending that time worrying about his stuff? By allocating their time and focus to the areas you want, over time you can influence how players develop, maintain their skillset, and fight the aging curve.<br/><br/><strong>2024 Rosters and Rules!</strong><br/><br/>As always, Out of the Park Baseball features up-to-the-minute 2024 MLB rosters that get updated all season long, with every franchise represented from its big league club all the way down to the low minors, and everywhere in between! Plus, OOTP 25 features officially licensed leagues from South Korea (KBO) and Europe.<br/><br/><strong>Improved Historical MLB Modes!</strong><br/><br/>Set up historical MLB games in an all new streamlined way - and benefit from vastly improved historical player ratings! It’s never been faster or easier to experience the entire history of Major League Baseball, now producing even more realistic outcomes thanks to those comprehensive ratings and simulation engine upgrades.<br/><br/><strong>New Retro Visual Immersion!</strong><br/><br/>Watch games with a variety of experiences, including retro-style black and white, ‘50s-era, and ‘70s-era television presentations. Choose from all of these to play games, watch highlights, or just catch a ballgame from a bygone era!<br/><br/><strong>New Licensed Leagues!</strong><br/><br/>For the first time ever, Out of the Park Baseball features an officially licensed Honkbal Hoofdklasse league from The Netherlands and the British Baseball Federation from the United Kingdom! Look for their official clubs, players, competitions, and more!<br/><br/><strong>For the first time ever - an official partnership with the Baseball Hall of Fame!</strong><br/><br/>What happens when you combine the only game that has the entire history of baseball and the the greatest Hall of Fame in sports? An incredible, year-long journey! Join us as we partner with the Baseball Hall of Fame all season - and beyond. Explore Hall of Fame Plaques, with the official, accurate text for each Hall of Famer. Discover incredible Hall of Fame artifacts, curated and released in fun "exhibits" over the course of the season in concert with the Hall - and more surprises too. It's going to be amazing! <br/><br/><strong>Dozens of upgrades big and small!</strong><br/><br/>--&gt; Updated in-game engine base advancement and camera movements<br/>--&gt; A new manager decision history screen gives you a look back on your best and worst trades and transactions<br/>--&gt; Improved trade packages for prospect packages <br/>--&gt; Updated two-way functionality with injured players<br/>And much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/pt_store_text_banner2.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/><br/><strong>Perfect Team is back - bigger than ever!</strong><br/><br/>It’s an all-new Perfect Team! There’s nothing in the world like the incredible online competitions of Perfect Team. Featuring by far the largest player pool ever, and taking advantage of all the player rating and balance upgrades, this year’s Perfect Team is a whole new ballgame.<br/><br/><strong>Brand New Perfect Team Combinator Series Cards!</strong><br/><br/>Pulled non-live cards have a chance to be a special Combinator Series version of the card! Use other cards that share a link (for example being teammates) with the player to get a chance to boost the raw ratings of the Combinator Series card.<br/><br/><strong>A Perfect Team Tournament Roster Builder!</strong><br/><br/>Want to design rosters for the incredible array of Perfect Team Tournaments - all on your own? For the first time ever, Perfect Team will feature a Tournament Sandbox! You can tinker to your heart's content with varying rosters for every type of tournament, with no pressure. This long-requested feature makes its debut in Out of the Park Baseball 25!<br/><br/>In addition to the brand-new Tournament Roster Builder and Combinator Series, Perfect Team 25 also features:<br/><br/><strong>Team Chemistry</strong> - Players who played together in real life will get extra bonuses when on your roster together. Players gain bonuses for seasons they played together, as well as simply being part of the same team or from the same decades<br/><strong>Perfect Team competitions starting on the first day</strong>, including a huge Opening Weekend of Tournaments with big prizes and Perfect Team Championship Series qualifying from Day One! <br/><strong>New content all season long - and beyond!</strong> All new programs, missions, competitions, and excitement await you every day.<br/><br/>Out of the Park Baseball 25 runs on PC/Mac and features the American League and National League logos, the World Series trophy, official logos and jerseys for all 30 MLB teams and 15 KBO teams, over 150 Minor League Baseball league and team logos, and historical MLB logos.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Shire: Room One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517850/Toy_Shire_Room_One/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FkhSxB2MSgD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/Toy_Shire_-_Discord_Banner.png?t=1710352808"/></a><br/><br/><br/>Play through the <strong>three levels in Kevin's Room</strong> and defend your room against your old toys. Face Memphis-X in the final level and put a stop to his assault as he crushes your soldiers in an attempt to get to your base.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyVengeance.png?t=1710352808"><br/>You received new toys from your family. Isn't that lovely? Oh, it's for sure... <br/>Your old toys, though, aren't getting along as well. They are no longer cared for and have been forgotten. So what follows next? They're going to join together against you and assault your brand-new toys, so be prepared. But never worry! You're in luck since your brand-new toys are troops of green soldiers. They still require your aid though! Control, strengthen, and defeat the opposing forces! However, focus with care, the enemies you encounter might not be your old playthings!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/InteractiveTowerDefense.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Tower building alone won't be sufficient to repel incoming attackers. Build up your own troops in the best feasible positions, then unleash attacks into enemy territory. Never abandon your towers, and deploy your troops in accordance with the traits of the enemy. First, the attacking forces will attempt to get past your defenses. Build and improve towers to aid your army. By using unique abilities, you can support your troops and towers as well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/EpicBattles.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Safeguard your base against waves of attackers. You need to pick the right troops if you would like to prevail. Clean the paths and guard any open routes. Upgrade your troops and unlock new ones to take down the waves and claim victory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyRealm.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Enter a world and a narrative built around the toys that enriched your youth, including toy soldiers, dinosaur sets, robots, building blocks, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_3.gif?t=1710352808"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dune: Imperium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1689500/Dune_Imperium/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Header.png?t=1710955211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body0_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Experience the ultimate blend of strategy and intrigue as you navigate the treacherous landscapes of Arrakis in the award-winning board game <i>Dune: Imperium</i>!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle online, locally with AI, or against the formidable House Hagal.<br/></li><li>Earn Achievements that showcase your prowess as a leader.<br/></li><li>Embark on more than a dozen Challenges that will test your wit and cunning.<br/></li><li>Compete for badges in the rotating Skirmish Mode where no two games are the same!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body1_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Arrakis. Dune. Desert Planet. Raise your banner above the vast wasteland before you. As the Great Houses of the Landsraad marshal their forces and their spies, whom will you influence, and whom will you betray? A tyrannical Emperor. The secretive Bene Gesserit. The shrewd Spacing Guild. The ferocious Fremen of the Deep Desert. The power of the Imperium can be yours, but war is not the only way to claim it.<br/><br/><i>Dune: Imperium</i> blends deck-building and worker placement in a deeply thematic new strategy game where the fate of the Empire hangs on your decisions. Will you seek political allies or rely upon military might? Economic strength or subtle intrigues? A council seat… or a sharpened blade? The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body2_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>In <i>Dune: Imperium</i>, you'll step into the role of one of the leaders of the Great Houses of the Imperium in a struggle to control the planet Arrakis and the invaluable Spice it provides.<br/><br/>The game plays out in a series of ten rounds, each of which is defined by a new Conflict on the surface of the planet; some award critical resources, and some provide Victory Points that will propel you to dominance. But choose your battles wisely: spread your forces too thin, and you'll find your enemies growing too strong to oppose.<br/><br/>Each round, you'll draw a hand of five cards from your deck, which will get stronger over the course of the game as you acquire new cards. Each card can be played in one of two ways: To send an Agent out into the Imperium to gather resources, or to Reveal at the end of the round to purchase new powerful cards. You must maintain a careful balance to get the most of the resources available to you. How will you find your path?<br/><br/>As your game progresses, you'll vie for Influence with four factions of the Imperium: The Emperor, the economically powerful Spacing Guild, the mysterious Bene Gesserit, and the ferocious Fremen of the deep deserts. Earning Influence among the various groups helps you to earn the Victory Points you need...but will you compete with your rivals for their favor, or abandon alliances to pursue other opportunities?<br/><br/>Many strategies are at your disposal, and many paths to victory. The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Footer.png?t=1710955211"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals Zero Hour</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732960/Command__Conquer_Generals_Zero_Hour/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals Zero Hour brings you closer to the enemy than ever before. Engage opposing forces at hot spots around the globe as you match strategies and arsenals against the new masterminds of modern war.<br/><br/><strong>Arsenal.</strong> Unleash the next generation of 3D new units and 20 new upgrades including China's ECM Tank, GLA's BattleBus and the USA's Spectre Gunship.<br/><br/><strong>Missions.</strong> Take on 15 new missions and make tomorrow's headlines. Root out a splinter cell in Cairo, steal deadly toxins from a U.S. lab and more.<br/><br/><strong>Generals.</strong> Match strategies and arsenals against 9 enemy commanders with unpredictable personalities and tactics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Tiberian Sun™ and Firestorm™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229880/Command__Conquer_Tiberian_Sun_and_Firestorm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Second Tiberium War begins in this legendary sequel to the original Command &amp; Conquer. <br/><br/>With his forces stronger than ever, arch villain and leader of The Brotherhood of Nod - Kane - is pitched in an epic battle against the world's war machine - the Global Defense Initiative. Now you must orchestrate the fate of mankind.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on Dynamic Battlefields. Nature itself provides tactical opportunities - destroyable and deformable terrain, forest fires, treacherous ice fields and many more surprises that help or hinder your strategies.<br/></li><li>Exciting New Strategies and Units. Jump Jet Infantry, Hover Tanks, Tunneling APCs, Hunter Seekers, Laser Fences, Mechanized Battle Units and many more.<br/></li><li>The "Veterancy" Factor. Units can become faster and stronger as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>New Kinetic Battlefields. Flying shrapnel, shock waves and crashing debris are just a few of the exciting new technologies developed to enhance the in-game experience.<br/></li><li>The mood and attitude of the battlefield comes alive like never before - covert night missions, searchlights and new defenses intensify the thrill and excitement.</li></ul><br/>Then take the battle further in <strong>Firestorm, the official expansion pack for the game</strong>. Includes all-new campaign missions, cinematics, and units to decide the future of mankind.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Renegade™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229890/Command__Conquer_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer gets up close and personal in this classic First Person Shooter for one of the most iconic franchises.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wreak Havoc</strong> - Experience the Command &amp; Conquer universe on foot as Havoc, wise-cracking GDI Commando.<br/></li><li><strong>Make Your Own Rules</strong>  - Take on the evil Brotherhood of Nod using your own mix of brute force, stealth, and strategy.<br/></li><li><strong>Assault at Ground Level</strong>  - Dish out the damage in either first or third person.<br/></li><li><strong>Total Access</strong>  - Sneak inside and explore full-scale structures, like immense Tiberium Refineries and the ominous Hand of Nod.<br/></li><li><strong>Grind the Gears</strong>  - Beef up your arsenal by commandeering lethal vehicles, such as Nod Buggies, Flame Tanks, and Mammoth Tanks.<br/></li><li><strong>Weapons of Mass Destruction</strong>  - Choose from a multitude of weapons, including the Tiberium Auto Rifle, Chemical Sprayer, and the devasting Personal Ion Cannon.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™, Counterstrike™ and The Aftermath™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229840/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_Counterstrike_and_The_Aftermath/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert</strong> pushed the envelope for the RTS genre in the mid-1990s and became one of the most iconic strategy games of all time. <br/><br/><strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert</strong>  gives you the opportunity to be more devious, cunning, and ruthless than ever before. Red Alert puts the fate of the world in your hands!<br/><br/><strong>Counterstrike</strong>, the exciting expansion pack to Red Alert, is full of clandestine activity, experimental technologies, and disavowed tactics. Includes 16 all-new missions, where you decide the ultimate fate of the struggle between the Allies and Soviets.<br/><br/><strong>In The Aftermath expansion pack</strong>, prepare for guerilla tactics, insidious strategies, and forbidden weapons. Includes 18 all-new missions and multiple units in a showdown that will test your mettle.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ and The Covert Operations™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229830/Command__Conquer_and_The_Covert_Operations/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The legendary RTS game which started it all. Will you side with the humanistic GDI or bring the world to its knees with Kane and the Brotherhood of Nod. Your adversaries are without mercy. And so are you.  <br/><br/>Includes the <strong>The Covert Operations</strong> expansion pack with a range of challenging new missions.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Grindea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/269770/Secrets_of_Grindea/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/269770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Secrets of Grindea</i> is an old-school Action RPG with co-op support for up to 4 players. It is a tribute to and sometimes a parody of the old SNES games so many of us grew up with and loved! Journey through fantastical lands, and battle tons of different enemies and bosses in your quest for truth, friendship and, above all, finding the world's rarest treasures!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A rich world filled with 300+ unique, colorful characters and an engaging story to drive your journey forward.<br/></li><li>Co-op support for up to four players! Enjoy the entire storyline with your friends or call someone in to help with the more difficult challenges.<br/></li><li>Customization, customization, customization - design a character that represents you, then mix and match any of the 31 spells and skills across 9 different categories.<br/></li><li>30+ epic boss fights! Overgrown slimes, giant robots, mimics - we have it all!<br/></li><li>Side content - design your own home, fish, craft items, tame pets, partake in mini-games, grow plants - there’s plenty to keep you entertained when you want a break from the main story.</li></ul><br/>And last but not least:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Arcade Mode - Separate from Story Mode, the game includes a <strong>full roguelite</strong> version where you need to battle your way to the top on a single life, building a town of your own as you progress.  How far can you get?</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Night of the Assassins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2865920/Night_of_the_Assassins/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2865920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Night of the Assassins - you will find yourself in the role of a mysterious killer, able to manipulate the shadow and hide in it in order to approach your enemies unnoticed. Your character is a master of stealth and the art of assassination, who is legendary. Plunge into the dark world of assassins and killers, where every corner is teeming with danger. Your task is to fight enemies from the shadows using agility and killing skills. Make your way through intricate levels, solve puzzles and uncover secrets to reach your goal.<br>
<br>
The game is a 2D platformer with puzzle elements. Destroy enemies in the location to move further through the levels.<br>
<br>
Prepare for an exciting adventure in a world of shadows and intrigue, where your stealth and skill will become your strongest ally.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br/>
- Pixel graphics<br/>
- Interesting locations<br/>
- Various enemies						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2610810/Zoo_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610810/extras/click_follow3.gif?t=1711626929"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2129220/Zoo_Simulator/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2129220/Zoo_Simulator/</a><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2487060/Anonymous_Hacker_Simulator/" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2487060/Anonymous_Hacker_Simulator/</a><br/><br/><strong>The Prologue is only part of the full game and is completely free. Every player will be able to play it and see what awaits them in the full version of the game.</strong><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F3WSPK2GB5m" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610810/extras/przycisk_discord_Zoo.png?t=1711626929"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Renovate your Zoo!</strong></h2>In Zoo Simulator: Prologue, one of your first tasks will be to restore the zoo. You will have to put a lot of effort into cleaning neglected alleys and damaged places for your future animals. To do this, you will be using a lot of tools such as welders and water washers. Remember - hard work can result in a crowd of delighted visitors!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610810/extras/1.1.Renovate_your_ZooV2.gif?t=1711626929"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Various species of animals</strong></h2>There is no Zoo without the animals living in it, right? In our game, you decide which of them will live in your facility. Remember that the more interesting the specimens live in your zoo, the more people will want to see them, which means more income for your business. Sit down to the computer and choose from the most exotic and amazing animals from around the world!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610810/extras/02.Various_species_of_animals.gif?t=1711626929"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Arrange runs for animals</strong></h2>Animals from the farthest corners of the world will appear in your zoo, they will also require appropriate living conditions - so you must take care of lairs, hiding places, and plants that will make them happy. There will be a lot of different elements in the game, which you will be able to freely move, position and rotate, thus creating unique zones for animals.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610810/extras/03.Arrange_runs_for_animals.gif?t=1711626929"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Look after them</strong></h2>In Zoo Simulator: Prologue, you also need to take care of the well-being of your animals, which in return will repay you with peace, good health, and activity in their animal run. Feed them, look after them and pay special attention to their safety - animals love to nibble their nose wherever they have a chance to fit it! Thanks to this, animals will be more likely to show themselves to visitors and win their sympathy.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610810/extras/04.Look_after_them.gif?t=1711626929"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Develop your Zoo</strong></h2>As you run your business, you will need to develop it as well. There will be more visitors, which means more attractions that will be able to make their time more pleasant. Take care of the right number of public toilets and sanitary facilities, and eating places where they will be able to eat! Also, don't forget to buy interesting new animals. It is extremely important that guests do not want to leave your zoo and will invite their friends.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610810/extras/05.Develop_your_Zoo.gif?t=1711626929"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncle's Basement</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2863800/Uncles_Basement/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2863800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You found yourself in a small, dark room.<br>
You want to understand how you got here and what this place is, but you are overwhelmed by the desire to just get out.<br>
<br>
You don't know where the exit is, is it locked, or is there no exit at all?<br>
It's up to you to find out. But be careful, the person or creature you are here for hears everything and wants you dead, so you have only a few hours to leave this scary place. Or maybe just hide? The kidnapper is not so simple and deprived you of this opportunity, so you need to think carefully how not to meet him.<br>
<br>
Don't be sad, you may have a friend who will help you for a delicious piece of meat, don't miss this chance!<br>
<br/>
There are 5 levels of difficulty. Easy - we recommend it for those who have never been kidnapped. Medium is the middle ground. Hard is for those who like to suffer. "Impossible" or "Are you serious?" - we think the title speaks for itself. And the most beautiful level of difficulty is Practice. In practice you will not be disturbed and you can study everything around you in peace.<br/>
<br/>
What happens if I sit in fear and do nothing? Well you can find out for yourself :)						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Last Breath</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1835190/One_Last_Breath/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835190/extras/EARTHS_steam.png?t=1711622956"><br/><br/>One Last Breath tells a story about despair but also about hope. Even if the post-apocalyptic world of this 2.5D adventure is withered, Gaia’s powers might be enough to restore life. That won’t be easy, though. Lots of fearsome mutants will hunt her mercilessly<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835190/extras/gif_Steam_1_1.gif?t=1711622956"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835190/extras/POWER_steam.png?t=1711622956"><br/><br/>Born from mother nature’s very last breath, Gaia has the ability to control the environment. Create paths using trunks, summon vines to hang between gaps, and solve puzzles using your powers to save our planet.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835190/extras/gif_Steam_2_ready.gif?t=1711622956"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835190/extras/ECHOES_steam.png?t=1711622956"><br/><br/>Humanity doesn’t exist anymore. Decades of pollution and greed have driven it to absolute extinction. However, its echo still can be heard. Along her journey, Gaia will visit abandoned factories filled with hazardous, human-made obstacles. How are they still working?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835190/extras/gif_Steam_3_ready.gif?t=1711622956"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835190/extras/lifeanddeath_steam.png?t=1711622956"><br/><br/>Gaia’s adventure is all about balance. She will find both brutality and tenderness while trying to survive strange creatures and protect the defenceless ones. Only our world can be as ruthless as charming.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835190/extras/gif_Steam_4_ready.gif?t=1711622956"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835190/extras/features_steam.png?t=1711622956"><br/><br/>● Use your supernatural powers to solve all kinds of environmental-based puzzles.<br/>● Discover what happened to mankind while exploring a gorgeous but sorrowful world.<br/>● Escape from lethal mutants and save the helpless wildlife.<br/>● Enjoy an immersive experience thanks to a carefully crafted sound design.<br/>● Don’t forget to take care of our planet in real-life!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mountain Legends 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2882340/Mountain_Legends_3/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2882340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Race to the finish line before it’s too late. Defeat your opponents &amp; be the first to cross the finish line. This Game Works with Gamepad, Keyboard &amp; Touch Screen Devices as well.<br>
<br>
<br>
14 different vehicles.<br>
<br>
Good Quality of Graphics.<br>
<br/>
12 different mountain environments.<br/>
<br/>
All the levels are unlocked.<br/>
<br/>
Watch AI Play.<br/>
<br/>
All the cars are unlocked.<br/>
<br/>
No Ads &amp; In App Purchases.<br/>
<br/>
Totally offline game.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KanjiMemory</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2850520/KanjiMemory/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2850520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>KanjiMemory</i> (漢字Memory) is a game of Memory that lets you play rounds of Memory games with Japanese <i>kanji</i> characters and their associated readings. It is designed to be an entertaining way for students of the Japanese language to deepen their grasp of <i>kanji</i> while also training their short term memory.<br/><br/><strong>KanjiMemory offers the following:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full set of the current 2136<i> jouyou kanji</i> issued in 2010 by the Japanese Ministry of Education as potential memory card pairs<br/></li><li>Adjustable play deck size to tailor your own difficulty<br/></li><li>Adjustable display speed for memory cards to accomodate both speedy and slow play</li></ul><br/>Each round will set up a fresh play deck by choosing randomly selected <i>kanji </i>out of all available<i> jouyou kanji</i>.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Doors Escape - Let me In!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2812900/100_Doors_Escape__Let_me_In/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2812900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							100 doors game challenges and brain teasers are quite fun, but we invite you to try your luck in 100 Doors Escape: Let me In! Join our guy in this toilet rush game and help him overcome numerous obstacles by playing hidden object mini games and solving escape puzzles. 100 Doors Escape: Let me In! game is a fun find the key to open the doors experience. Unlock the door to enter the room in this quite amusing get in the toilet game.<br>
<br>
This is not a classic toilet and bathroom game that requires almost no effort to pass. This escape room game is indeed full of hundred doors game challenges that require logic effort and skills in order to solve hidden object riddles and puzzles. Nature calls! Help the guy make it to the toilet! Play 100 Doors Escape: Let me In! Game, a true jewel among find the key games!<br>
<br>
100 DOORS ESCAPE: LET ME IN! GAMEPLAY:<br>
<br>
Our little fella is a repairman with tons of work to finish throughout this escape room game, but whenever he finds himself at a certain location to do the job he has a peculiar tiny problem. This is where you come to the rescue by employing your brain at your best and solving all the mind-bending riddles and puzzles, and by seeking and finding all the hidden objects in this 100 doors unlock the room game. Namely, he needs to go to the bathroom, but somehow there always seems to be an obstacle for him to do so. You know how it is, pretty embarrassing, so man up and help the guy make it to the bathroom. He cannot solve all the escape room riddles as his urge really distracts him, so he needs all the bits and pieces of your knowledge to get to the toilet. Open 100 doors, escape rooms and eventually let the man finish his business. 100 Doors Escape: Let me In! game really gives you a chance to show some sympathy and be a good sport!<br>
<br/>
100 DOORS ESCAPE: LET ME IN! FEATURES:<br/>
<br/>
-  Exciting puzzles with hidden objects and conundrums to solve<br/>
-  Cool mechanics: move in time and space, combine objects, play brain games<br/>
-  Skip the level if you get stuck<br/>
-  148 levels, with more to come<br/>
<br/>
100 Doors Escape: Let me In!: no need to run for your life, but you do need to avoid getting completely embarrassed publicly! Join this bathroom rush and combine it with the best elements of escape the room 100 doors games. Download 100 Doors Escape: Let me In! Game, a revolutionary find the key to the toilet game you need to have! Help the poor man unlock the doors and get to the toilet in time!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperBody</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2884170/HyperBody/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2884170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to HyperBody dungeons, an experimental open-world VR game space with six intense gameplay levels: Pinkray, Seventeen/Sixty-One, Vampire Squid, Stratholme.GoStop, Typhoon Lionrock,  and Garden Portal.<br/><br/>Immerse yourself in an aesthetised trance world that showcases the anime, comics, games, and novels of European and Asian fandoms. The VR experience is "passive", requiring only basic movements such as walking, flying, rotating, and touching. It will help if you search for the portal with a shining eye shape that will take you to a new level. <br/><br/>The experiment encourages players to use their entire bodies to explore the VR space and provide feedback on its aesthetics, movement, and overall feelings!<br/><br/>Are you ready to embark on this psychedelic, rhythm-fueled adventure and imagine an alternative VR cosmos?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2884170/extras/gif1.gif?t=1711620618"><h2 class="bb_tag">LEVEL 1: PINKRAY</h2><br/>Pinkray is a result of a collaborative effort that celebrates queer "tuning" through vidding, shipping, interviews, and architectural mods. It showcases a new "game-fandom" that constantly emerges as "intra-actions". <br/><br/>It features non-collision NPCs, architectural ruins, visual novels with 3D animated texts, and affective NPC dialogues!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2884170/extras/gif2.gif?t=1711620618"><h2 class="bb_tag">LEVEL 2: SEVENTEEN/SIXTY-ONE</h2><br/>Seventeen/Sixty-One is co-created through research and interviews with Chinese science fiction writer Tang Fei. It offers an alternative vision of queer, feminine, and technology in the Chinese science fiction world. <br/><br/>It features 2D illustrations, animations and 3D texts as interactive paths, accompanied by various soundscapes and atmospheric objects.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2884170/extras/gif3.gif?t=1711620618"><h2 class="bb_tag">LEVEL 3: VAMPIRE SQUID</h2><br/>Vilem Flusser's book of the same name inspires the abstract cosmos of Vampire Squid. Explore multiple worlds created by remixing 3D scans of spaces, cartographies, and surfaces from London and Berlin. This complex spatial autoethnographic archive showcases Flusser's ideas on skin, space, and sexuality.<br/><br/>It features non-collision 3D-scanned architectural ruins on a cosmic scale and surreal NPCs.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2884170/extras/gif4.gif?t=1711620618"><h2 class="bb_tag">LEVEL 4: STRATHOLME.GOSTOP</h2><br/>Stratholme.GoStop presents a unique combination of physical and virtual elements based on my best childhood friend, Boxiao's short novel. It has modding and crossover elements between a Chinese post-industrial ordnance factory welfare zone and the Warcraft 3: The Frozen Throne universe. <br/><br/>It features visual novels based on dodecahedron objects and various Chinese urban space 3D-scanned ruins.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2884170/extras/gif5.gif?t=1711620618"><h2 class="bb_tag">LEVEL 5: TYPHOON LIONROCK</h2><br/>Typhoon Lionrock is highly speculative about a VR game space's movement, direction, scale, and soundscape. Very difficult and for hard-core players, this level is a tribute to my time killed at the Run Run Shaw Library, City University of Hong Kong.<br/><br/>Be careful not to get dizzy and nauseous from the multiple abstract scenes referenced in Hong Kong, Dunhuang, and Chongqing.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2884170/extras/gif6.gif?t=1711620618"><h2 class="bb_tag">LEVEL 6: GARDEN PORTAL</h2><br/>Garden Portal is based on Chinese immortality cultivation. Explore a non-linear audio-visual space through the primal VR experience with intentionally incomplete and imperfect sound and architectural design. <br/><br/>It features numerous NPCs to be found and touched with multiple hidden tokens and architectural ruins.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2884170/extras/gif7.gif?t=1711620618"><h2 class="bb_tag">PLAYER INSTRUCTIONS</h2><br/>For HyperBody's experimental nature, please check system requirements first, <i><strong><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/quickref/2884170" rel="" target="_blank">view the quick reference</a></strong></i> and start playing.<br/><br/>If you are interested, browse the manual and join our Discord community!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2884170/extras/gif8.gif?t=1711620618"><h2 class="bb_tag">SUPPORTED BY</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2884170/extras/wwiselogo.png?t=1711620618"><br/><i>Hyperbody utilises the Wwise sound engine (academic license) for an immersive soundscape.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2884170/extras/computing1.png?t=1711620618"><br/><i>The game's development benefited from valuable feedback received during various evaluation workshops at Goldsmiths Computing Department.</i> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost Lands: Stories of the First Brotherhood</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2826120/Lost_Lands_Stories_of_the_First_Brotherhood/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2826120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An unknown entity prowls the valleys and destroys everything in its path. Only a strong team of friends can cope with it.<br>
<br>
“Lost Lands: Stories of the First Brotherhood” is an adventure game in the genre of Hidden Objects, with plenty of mini-games and puzzles, unforgettable characters and complicated quests. <br>
<br>
Residents of the valleys are worried by the appearance of a mysterious villain. Information about incidents comes from different places. All witnesses talk about the same beast, which is so fast that it is impossible to see it. The most capable student of the Academy of magic will try to deal with this problem. A random partner and he follow the trail of the beast and help the affected inhabitants of the Lost Lands. However, friends are forced to look at the situation differently and change their plans after meeting the enemy. The adventure unites the partners and the “First Brotherhood” is born in the crucible of trials.<br>
<br>
- Find an unknown entity that is tormenting the entire area and unravel the mystery of its origin<br>
- See the story from two perspectives by playing as different characters<br/>
- Combine the powers of the main characters to solve many puzzles together and defeat the evil<br/>
- Discover new locations and indulge in nostalgia by returning to old ones<br/>
- Find out what the world of the Lost Lands looked like hundreds of years before Susan the Warrior appeared.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under The Yoke</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2592060/Under_The_Yoke/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step back in time and embark on a remarkable journey through the heart of Norman England, spanning over 250 years of fully realised Medieval English history.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/CraftYourCharacter.png?t=1711616432"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/Faces.gif?t=1711616432"><br/>Begin your humble life as a lowly serf playing your own custom character. Armed with just an acre of land, a ramshackle cottage, and enough provisions to survive winter, your quest for prosperity begins.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/FromGenerationToGeneration.png?t=1711616432"><br/>Guide your family through the Middle Ages, from one generation to the next. Each character boasts distinct personalities, needs, and skills, and it's your duty to oversee every facet of their lives, from their livelihoods to their social circles and even their daily sustenance.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/LivingBreathingCharacters.png?t=1711616432"><br/>Every character possesses three defining traits—Mind, Body, and Spirit—that dictate their compatibility with others, preferred activities, and unlock unique event options. Choose wisely, as each trait brings both advantages and disadvantages, impacting their daily toil and needs.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/Needs_Desires.png?t=1711616432"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/Moods.png?t=1711616432"><br/>Keep your characters content and productive by attending to their essential needs:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Satisfy their <strong>Taste</strong> with over 50 authentic medieval ingredients.<br/></li><li>Grant them <strong>Rest</strong>, allowing them precious respite from their laborious routines.<br/></li><li>Nurture their <strong>Faith</strong> through immersive Middle Ages church experiences.<br/></li><li>Foster their <strong>Social</strong> connections by participating in genuine medieval social gatherings and building lasting bonds with fellow villagers.</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/MasteringMedievalTrades.png?t=1711616432"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/Jobs.png?t=1711616432"><br/>Surviving in the Middle Ages demands a diverse skill set. Master the arts of <strong>Farming, Herbalism, Cooking, Husbandry, Carpentry,</strong> and <strong>Tailoring</strong> as you engage in the myriad tasks of a medieval peasant's life. From plowing fields to shearing sheep, there's always work to be done, though the season and the changing value of goods will keep you on your toes.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/AVillageAlive.png?t=1711616432"><br/>While you focus on your family, the village thrives around you. Forge friendships, pursue romance, and interact with your neighbours. But beware, as rival families vie for elections and jury seats. Consider forging alliances to collectively prosper.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/HomeSweetHome.png?t=1711616432"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/House.gif?t=1711616432"><br/>Life as a peasant extends beyond the fields. Enhance your cottage and garden with handcrafted furniture that can elevate the value of your goods, whether for personal use or lucrative market sales. If space becomes a constraint, negotiate with your Lord for a larger cottage or garden to accommodate more furniture.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/LiveableLivestock.png?t=1711616432"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/Animals.gif?t=1711616432"><br/>Farming entails more than just crops—farm animals provide vital resources. Purchase and breed cows, horses, goats, sheep, pigs, and chickens, each with their own unique needs and benefits. Opt for the strength of an ox or the speed of a horse, or reap the rewards of wool from sheep and the fertiliser from pigs.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/RekindleTheHallmote.png?t=1711616432"><br/>Revive the age-old Hallmote tradition—an annual gathering of villagers to address legal disputes and elect local officials. Dive into the realm of politics, with rewards for winning elections and voting for allies. Your male family members might also be summoned for jury duty during village disputes.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/DeathTaxes_FeudalAgreements.png?t=1711616432"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/Contract.png?t=1711616432"><br/>Negotiate your feudal dues and responsibilities with your Lord. From farmland to meadowland, your home to your garden, all aspects of your life are open to negotiation. As a serf, you'll toil on your Lord's demesne or face fees, but earning their respect could pave your path to freedom. Rise to a freeman status and expand your rights, from baking your own bread to hunting in the forests. Under The Yoke intricately replicates the medieval rights system.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/Liveatrulymedievalife.png?t=1711616432"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/Events.gif?t=1711616432"><br/>Immerse yourself in medieval England's vibrant tapestry through a dynamic event system, featuring hundreds of unique events that ensure every play-through remains fresh. From social intrigues to attending church, your choices shape your family's legacy throughout the ages.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592060/extras/RewriteHistoryYourWay.png?t=1711616432"><br/>Experience history like never before as your characters respond to the pivotal events of their time. With our dynamic event system, we weave 250 years of history from 1085 to 1335 into your personal narrative, enabling you to walk in the shoes of the common man as the world evolves around you.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CD 2: Trap Master</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2330870/CD_2_Trap_Master/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ever since 2019, when I first played <i>Slay the Spire</i>, I’ve dreamt of creating my own deckbuilding game. In <i>Trap Master</i>, as a youthful ninja, you will assemble a unique deck of traps and powers, discover treasure of surprising effects, and guard a different base each time until you are ready for the unforgiving boss.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330870/extras/title-1-eng-1008.png?t=1711625293"><br/><br/>Face off against 40+ types of enemies and defend over 100 bases. Shoot, scorch, slice. Punch, pierce, poison. Bounce monsters into water to drown them. Summon warriors to fight them. So many traps and tricks to exterminate waves of incoming enemies!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330870/extras/改尺寸EN_Gif-Perfect_Your_Card.gif?t=1711625293"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330870/extras/title-2-eng-1008.png?t=1711625293"><br/><br/>Collect cards to craft the deck of your choice. Start from a few basic trap cards, and expand to a versatile deck that could stop a variety of enemies in different terrains. Find powerful synergies with over 100 traps and skills, and test your strategy on the field!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330870/extras/改尺寸EN_Gif-_perfect_your_Card_with_Text.gif?t=1711625293"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330870/extras/title-3-eng-1008.png?t=1711625293"><br/><br/>Choose your path and encounter curious events that can change the course of your run. Unfold the dark secrets behind the relentless assaults, and study what it takes to become THE Trap Master.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330870/extras/gif-3-eng-event.gif?t=1711625293"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/>- <strong>100+ deadly traps and skills</strong> to craft your deck<br/>- Upgrades &amp; Inscriptions to beef up your cards<br/>- <strong>Over 100 cleverly-designed bases</strong> to defend<br/>- <strong>45 enemies</strong> with unique abilities to challenge and destroy<br/>- A treasure system to boost your power<br/>- Procedural generated system for extensive replayability<br/>- Events and encounters for an immersive adventure						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky Squadron</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1403400/Sky_Squadron/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1403400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1403400/extras/LogoDestroy600Width.gif?t=1711620099"><br/><br/><strong><i>Think you’ve got what it takes to keep Australia’s skies safe? </i></strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The tropical island paradise is being invaded, and only hot-shot Keith Koala can jump into the gunner’s seat and fend off some of the most menacing meanies that the Aussie Islands have ever seen!<br/></li><li>Grab the controls hands-on to blow fearsome foes out of the sky in thrilling aerial combat before they plunder everything your home has to offer.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1403400/extras/SS_Banner_Rounded2.png?t=1711620099"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1403400/extras/Gameplay_Final.png?t=1711620099"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Take control of a plucky koala and his native Aussie mates while they defend their home from evil invaders. Grasp the gun with both hands to precisely aim and blast foes in this classic arcade rail-shooter.<br/></li><li>Branching action-packed levels allow players to destroy enemy fighters, dismantle giant bosses and repair their plane on the fly. Invite a friend to join you in online co-op, or compete for the highest score on the global leaderboards.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1403400/extras/Features_Final.png?t=1711620099"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>An Australian take on the beloved “Star Fox” rail shooter formula, combined with thrilling WW2 gunner gameplay.<br/></li><li>Experience a <strong>koala-ty</strong> cast of Aussie animals fighting to survive against invasive enemies!<br/></li><li>Blast through every mission alongside your friends in seamless online co-op.<br/></li><li>Rich replayability - branching missions &amp; varied challenges.<br/></li><li>Tear apart foul foes piece by piece… literally! With dynamic and fully destructible bosses.<br/></li><li>Dominate the skies and claim your rightful position as an apex species with global leaderboards available for every single mission.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1403400/extras/Inspiration_Final.png?t=1711620099"><br/><i>Sky Squadron pays homage to the classics of the rail shooter genre, drawing inspiration from beloved series like <strong>Star Fox</strong> &amp; <strong>Panzer Dragoon</strong> while putting the player directly in the gunner’s seat through immersive VR.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1403400/extras/SS_Banner_Logo.png?t=1711620099"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1403400/extras/Break.png?t=1711620099"><br/>Keen to find out more? Chuck us on ya' <strong><u>wishlist</u></strong>, have a gander at out our <strong><u>Discord Server</u></strong> above, or give us a shout over on <strong><u>@SkySquadronGame</u></strong> over on Twitter to keep up with all <br/>the latest news. You'd be a drongo not to!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>飞跃星球（Eggy Space）</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2766790/Eggy_Space/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							《Eggy Space》is a light and casual tower defense game operated on the computer. The game is set in a fictional world, where due to the scarcity of resources, players play as interstellar travelers shuttling between various planets. While resisting the invaders, they also need to acquire resources. By placing props in the levels, defeating the invading races from other planets, and acquiring resources to upgrade the spaceship and recruit crew members, the players can continuously pass the levels. Eventually, they will obtain a habitable planet and rebuild their homes.<br/>
<br/>
  The game provides a variety of mechanisms. Players can place blocks such as ground or wall mechanisms to achieve efficient killing of monsters. Different mechanism blocks will also have bonds, producing linked effects and achieving new killing effects. More clever combinations await your attempts!<br/>
<br/>
  Outside the level, players can upgrade the props to increase the damage of the mechanisms and unlock more mechanism effects; and they can also recruit various heroes through the external Ark module. Heroes will automatically explore resources and help players build resource output more efficiently.<br/>
<br/>
  At the current stage of the game, we are still in a semi-complete state. Under the integrity of the battle, we will quickly complete the content for battle development. Please look forward to it!<br/>
<br/>
  Eggy Space Base QQ: 684340879						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>孤独之旅 Lonely journey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867190/_Lonely_journey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2867190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a 2d side-scrolling game similar to (Ori and the Blind Forest) and (Hollow Knight), embark on an adventure in this fantasy land, collect key items, buy powerful equipment, gather pets to fight together, 100+ elves will participate in the battle, and 30+ costumes to help in the battle						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I brought the noble girl home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2890100/I_brought_the_noble_girl_home/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2890100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The future war broke out, and many noble girls were taken away by unknown creatures. You were chosen by your superiors to go on a secret mission to bring these girls back.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2890100/extras/标题21.png?t=1711609368"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2890100/extras/GIF0.gif?t=1711609368"><br/>Step 1: Click on the girl's profile picture.<br/>Step 2: Select the Start button.<br/>Step 3: Enter the game, mouse operation, automatic attack.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2890100/extras/标题22.png?t=1711609368"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2890100/extras/GIF1.gif?t=1711609368"><br/>Control the mouse, kill the enemy. Unlock the girl slowly.<br/>Enemies can fire bullets or touch the player to damage the player.<br/>The game ends when the girl is finished or the player dies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2890100/extras/标题23.png?t=1711609368"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2890100/extras/GIF2.gif?t=1711609368"><br/>Click the Girls button and select the View button. You can enter appreciation mode.<br/>Click the Zoom in or zoom out button to zoom in and out.<br/>Click and drag the picture to control the position of the picture.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoodie Survivor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2883700/Hoodie_Survivor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2883700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Auto shooter score attack survival game where your character moves forward continuously and you control the direction of travel by rotating left and right<br>
<br>
There are six levels in total with 3 different themes: field, desert and space.<br>
<br>
Shoot enemies and avoid different types of indestructible hazards<br>
<br>
Score 61 points to unlock the next level<br>
<br/>
Each level can be played forever to try to beat your high score						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zen With A Pen</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2521470/Zen_With_A_Pen/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2521470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the intense world of <strong>Zen With A Pen</strong>, where serenity collides head-on with a mind-bending arcade challenge! Get ready to take command of your virtual pen and embark on an enthralling journey through a variety of levels filled with obstacles to overcome.<h2 class="bb_tag">What's in Store for You?</h2>In this offbeat indie game, your mission is crystal clear: guide the enso symbol, the Zen embodiment, to its serene destination. But beware! The path is riddled with ingeniously designed obstacles, engineered to test even the steeliest of nerves. It's a tightrope walk between tranquility and rage as you sketch guiding lines on parchment to navigate the enso through intricate terrains.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2521470/extras/zenWithAPenClips_01.gif?t=1711608866"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2>🖌️ Craft guiding lines to maneuver the enso symbol through intricate maps<br/>🎨 Immerse yourself in a visually pleasing minimalistic art style that soothes the soul<br/>😂 Confront obstacles that will push not only your steady hand but also your sanity<br/>🌟 Embark on a journey through multiple maps, each with varying levels of difficulty<br/>⚡️ Experience the perfect blend of casual arcade gameplay and hair-tearing frustration<br/><br/>Experience the enchantment of minimalistic art as you journey through a captivating array of maps. Each map unveils a unique set of challenges, handcrafted to both sharpen your skills and keep you on the edge of your seat. To succeed at the challenge you need to use your wit, patience and calm inner self. This together with some special powers and you have all the tools neccessary, even for the more challenging difficulties!<br/><br/>Moreover, <strong>Zen With A Pen</strong> immerses you in an auditory experience with its collection of calming and mesmerizing music tracks. Dive into a realm of tranquility, as each stroke of your pen is accompanied by soothing melodies that effortlessly meld with the game's serene atmosphere. Let these gentle tunes wash over you, elevating your gaming experience to new heights of relaxation (or perhaps a touch of frustration).<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2521470/extras/zenWithAPenClips_05.gif?t=1711608866"><br/><br/>So, are you ready to unleash your inner Zen artist and conquer the enso? <strong>Zen With A Pen</strong> eagerly awaits your artistic touch! Brace yourself for a challenge that leaves you feeling both serene and victorious, and most certainly frustrated. Grab your pen, take a deep breath, and let the Zen flow through your fingertips!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spellarium 4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2805410/Spellarium_4/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2805410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Eric, the wizard, has spent over 400 years in service to the Gods. A wizard's life is long yet not endless, so now Eric has to renew his life power. The Tree of Life will help him! Growing the Tree Of Life isn't an easy task. As usual, you'll help Eric build the Tree of Life by playing Match 3 levels as well as some additional bonus games: Spot the Difference, Hidden object scenes, Mahjong, and Solitaire!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Forgotten Villages of Gondomayit 2 - Kost Karangsari</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2760800/The_Forgotten_Villages_of_Gondomayit_2__Kost_Karangsari/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2760800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Forgotten Village of Gondomayit lets you experience the mystical atmosphere of Indonesia.<br>
Tells the story of a young man named Bagas, a vocational school student<br>
who lost the bet and received a challenge from his friends. He had to test his courage in one of the boarding houses in Gondomayit Village, which had long been abandoned by the residents after the eruption of Mount Merapi. However, many strange things happened when they first arrived at the village. Starting from a scary and lonely atmosphere,<br>
the appearance of strange creatures, full of puzzles and much more.<br>
And this game is also very interactive because there are missions that must be completed, starting from looking for clues as to why the boarding house is so haunted.<br>
Designed and developed from the ground up for fully immersive atmosphere and gameplay,<br>
The Forgotten Village of Gondomayit is our approach to a truly unsettling and terrifying experience.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War Tortoise</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2120250/War_Tortoise/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2120250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2120250/extras/PC_logo@4x_steam_bg.png?t=1711599100"><br/><br/>Take control of the mighty War Tortoise and experience a new kind of idle game!<br/><br/>Explore a vast world as nature's strongest battle tank: the War Tortoise. Summon a variety of units such as Mouse Rangers, Hamster Commandos, and giant Howitzer Beetles. Unlock dozens of pilots, heroes, and legendary tortoises to fight beside you. Upgrade your War Tortoise and support units from a huge list of talents and skills. Discover unique gameplay modes such as fishing and a free-roam adventure mode.<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Experience a unique spin on idle gameplay, mixing exploration, freedom and depth of choice, advanced graphics, and an interesting setting  <br/></li><li>Explore a huge world - choose where you want to go and how you want to progress   <br/></li><li>Unlock and upgrade countless active and passive abilities - customize your play style  <br/></li><li>Dozens of Pilots and Heroes to collect and master<br/></li><li>Unleash legendary Tortoises such as the Zombie Tortoise, Dragon Tortoise, and Mecha Tortoise <br/></li><li>Customize your War Tortoise with powerful armor and weapons <br/></li><li>Build up your fighting force with a variety of support units <br/></li><li>Relax at fishing spots and earn powerful permanent abilities<br/></li><li>Dismount and explore full free-roam adventure locations</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keys And Kastles</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2476190/Keys_And_Kastles/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2476190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are a brave guard of the kingdom and you have been entrusted with the most important job of all, protecting the king's treasures! But unfortunately, the entire fortune was stolen and the majesty blamed you for the bad work!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2476190/extras/Andando.gif?t=1711598944"><br/>No one knows who the Thief is and your sentence is to seek out all the wealth of the empire without your valuable magic sword!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2476190/extras/Design_sem_nome.gif?t=1711598944"><br/>Go through dozens of levels, between castles, pyramids and haunted houses, and look for hidden chests!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2476190/extras/Flecha.gif?t=1711598944"><br/>Beware of challenging traps and dangers! Take back your honor and be a hero again!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shade Hunters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2864340/Shade_Hunters/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2864340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Reclaim a silenced research laboratory under siege from a mysterious threat. This roguelite RPG offers:<br>
<br>
-Randomized skills (and everything else) for each playthrough<br>
-Hard-hitting active time-based (ATB) combat<br>
-An original soundtrack<br>
-Numerous unlockable characters and secrets<br>
-Variable difficulty levels and plenty of secrets to be uncovered<br/>
-Sci-fi humor through a "dad joke" lens<br/>
-Puzzles - including some not intended for you!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hole Void</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2876070/Black_Hole_Void/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2876070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Black Hole Void, the captivating game where you control the power of a black hole! Immerse yourself in a world full of excitement and challenges as you master the ultimate cosmic force.<br>
<br>
In Black Hole Void, you take control of the black hole, and your task is to devour the city or districts as quickly as possible to achieve the highest high score. But that's not all - you can give your black hole a unique look with a variety of skins by changing the eye ring to different colors.<br>
<br>
With a total of four different game modes, Black Hole Void offers a variety of challenges. In Time Mode, speed is key as you try to destroy the city or districts as quickly as possible to reach the top spot on the leaderboard. In Point Mode, the goal is to achieve as many points as possible without racing against the clock.<br>
<br>
However, in Defense Mode, you become the protector of the city or districts by collecting upgrades to make your black hole stronger and larger, defending it against enemy attacks. And if that's not enough, there's the Defense Turn-Based Mode, which works similarly to Defense Mode but with additional challenges and boss battles.<br>
<br/>
But that's not all! Black Hole Void also features a leaderboard where you can compare your high scores and compete with other players. Are you ready to conquer the infinite depths of the universe and become the master of the black hole? Then venture into the darkness of Black Hole Void now!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voice Love on Air</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2321120/Voice_Love_on_Air/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2321120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2321120/extras/无背景kv.png?t=1711591213"><br/><i>Voice Love on Air</i> is a BL Dating Sim Game centered on voice recording sessions for Radio Dramas.<br/>The protagonist Aki has the ability to hear a person's true feelings from their voice to uncover truths and lies.<br/>He started a recording studio of his own but ran into some business difficulties.<br/>To ease his financial situation, he agreed to help a friend in the sound recording for BL dramas.<h2 class="bb_tag">[Start Recording from Scratch]</h2>Take on different drama genre projects, study, and collect materials.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2321120/extras/（英）插图1.png?t=1711591213"><h2 class="bb_tag">[Do Your Best for Every Drama]</h2>Choose your favorite voice actor to work closely with in voice direction.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2321120/extras/（英）插图2.png?t=1711591213"><h2 class="bb_tag">[Get to know them… better]</h2>Meet up with your love interest on the weekends and hear his story.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2321120/extras/（英）插图3.png?t=1711591213"><h2 class="bb_tag">[Make Your Own Voice Love Story]</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2321120/extras/主角团2.png?t=1711591213"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cabbage Crop</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2882490/Cabbage_Crop/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2882490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Cabbage Crop, the pseudo tower defense game where you defend against animals with freshly cultivated crops! Play as the brother, or play as the sister, and protect your home from these wild invaders, while expanding your veggie arsenal with the help of the weird magic pet chicken!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Akatsuki: Lord of the Dawn</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2758030/Akatsuki_Lord_of_the_Dawn/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758030/extras/akatsuki_movie1_614x346.gif?t=1711585909"><br/><br/>Akatsuki: Lord of the Dawn is a real-time battle RPG where you make your own parties from a large variety of characters, use various military formations and techniques to take down your enemies.<br/><br/>The war between man and the demon king has ended, but the world is left ravaged. You take the role of a newly appointed lord, traveling across your lands to free your people from the remnants of the demon kings armies to bring back peace and stability once and for all.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758030/extras/Headline_En_1.png?t=1711585909"><br/>It's been a few years since the war ended and the demon king fell, but the world is still suffering in the aftermath.<br/>In the kingdom of Krenian, the king OdorianIV declares that the time has come to rid the kingdom of the demon kings forces, to rebuild and finally bring peace to his kingdom.<br/>He appoints those most worthy in each region of his kingdom into new lords, tasking them with this endeavor.<br/>One of those chosen is our protagonist, Ark Badona, in The Land of Dawn within the region of Celestia. Tasked with ridding his lands of the demon king's armies he sets out on his journey—<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758030/extras/Headline_En_2.png?t=1711585909"><br/>Become a lord and play as Ark Badona, carrying out your new duties. Take on quests and fight monsters as the story unfolds, and watch Ark grow through his journey.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758030/extras/Headline_En_3.png?t=1711585909"><br/>Choose between 48 different convoy characters to fill up your party, and utilize the 10 unique formations to lead your forces to victory!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758030/extras/Headline_En_4.png?t=1711585909"><br/>Build facilities for agriculture, fishing, forestry and more to rebuild the lands! Gather materials and research to create powerful weapons and armor to strengthen your troops!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2758030/extras/Headline_En_5.png?t=1711585909"><br/>Your convoy characters will fight automatically during battle. By raising their levels and giving them powerful equipment you can strengthen your forces, securing victory in battle. And by researching high-grade subclasses and performing class-ups you can power them up even further!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Are Not Alone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2249440/We_Are_Not_Alone/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2249440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2249440/extras/ezgif-5-f17430787b.gif?t=1711584672"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2><br/>Combining two beloved genres, first person horror with third person adventure, We Are Not Alone creates a new sense of suspense with its unique camera mechanic.<br/><br/>Looking through the camera allows safe exploration, as the creature can not meet your gaze.<br/><br/>Placing the camera down though, is essential to solving puzzles with both hands, yet it will leave you vulnerable.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2249440/extras/Hallway_Change.gif?t=1711584672"><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2>The world may be going to hell, but Riley's worries extend beyond that.<br/><br/><br/>3 months ago Riley's Sister applied for a job with the Osiris Initiative, the world leader in medical technology.  Despite initially having a way to contact her, daily communications have ceased. Something isn't right. <br/><br/>Attempting to locate her sister by using connections at her job, Riley is fired for gross misconduct with no answers. <br/><br/>Applying to be a test subject with the Osiris Initiative, Riley hopes to gain information on the illusive organisation and ultimately find her sister. <br/><br/>That is... if the experiment is as safe as they said.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore the vast complex, unlock the secrets of the experiment and ultimately attempt to escape with your life. <br/></li><li>Solve puzzles using items found throughout your isolation.<br/></li><li>Encounter a long lost piece of civilisation... that may not be so civil.<br/></li><li>Use the camera to explore in first person and place it down to solve puzzles in third person.<br/></li><li>Multiple endings based on player choices</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engine Room</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2818870/Engine_Room/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2818870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Fight your way through hostile space while managing a fragile ship from its heart - the <strong>Engine Room</strong>. Retreat to upgrade the ship or push your luck further into enemy territory for better rewards - or maybe get blown to pieces! Fight bosses, balance power, and manage supplies to stay alive!<br/><br/><strong>UPGRADE</strong><br/>Throughout your journey, you will acquire resources that can be used to unlock new powerful ship components to improve your chances of success! These come in several forms, such as weapons, shields, and engines!<br/><br/><strong>EXPLORE</strong><br/>Strategically choose your path forward through dangerous star systems. This can mean focusing on gathering resources, fighting powerful enemies, or slipping through with as little conflict as possible!<br/><br/><strong>MANAGE</strong><br/>Your ship has many functions that will need attention in order to keep running properly. You will need to manage which systems are powered on, what each crew member is doing, manage the inventory of a limited cargo bay, and more!<br/><br/><strong>FIGHT</strong><br/>Keep powerful enemies at bay by a variety of means! You can choose to put everything into highly upgrade weapons and burn through their hull, or focus on quick maneuverable engines to avoid incoming fire. Do whatever it takes to push further in to the heart of hostile space!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fission</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2884640/Fission/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2884640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The game is played by manipulating the paddle at the bottom of the screen to the left and right to hit back a ball that moves while reflecting on the screen. When the ball hits a fungus, the fungus disappears and the ball bounces back. The game is completed when all the fungi on the screen disappear by repeating this process. When the fungus disappears, a capsule that fission the ball may be dropped. There are 9 stages in total.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Life: Farm Vet</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2637870/My_Life_Farm_Vet/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2637870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">They need you on the farm - examine and treat lots of animals!</h2>Your job as a passionate vet is to examine sick farm animals, make the right diagnosis, treat them accordingly and nurse them back to health.<br/>Build up trust with the small and large two- and four-legged friends so that they soon feel better again. Your help is called for on the farm! <br/><br/><strong>What awaits you:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Design your own avatar<br/></li><li>You can get to your missions by car, on horseback or by foot<br/></li><li>Discover the large game world with 3 farms<br/></li><li>Treat over 90 diseases in your practice or on site in the stables</li></ul><strong><br/>Take care of these cute patients:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>pigs &amp; piglets<br/></li><li>cows &amp; calves<br/></li><li>sheep &amp; lambs<br/></li><li>horses<br/></li><li>goats<br/></li><li>dogs <br/></li><li>cats<br/></li><li>chickens, ducks and geese<br/></li><li>rabbits</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychometric Personality Profiler</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2833950/Psychometric_Personality_Profiler/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2833950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">ABOUT</h2>The Psychometric Personality Profiler was designed to adjust to the needs and personality of its participants.<br/>This Test includes five question groups that reach into the deepest parts of your brain to figure out who you really are.<h2 class="bb_tag">GAMEPLAY</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple Choice<br/></li><li>Sliders<br/></li><li>Textboxes</li></ul>The way you answer the questions does not matter. You just need to stay truthful.<h2 class="bb_tag">Rules</h2><strong>Keep your eyes on the Screen at ALL times!</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hulzuyot: Horror Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2865140/Hulzuyot_Horror_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2865140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Hulzuyot is a psychological horror game where you experience the perspective of a salary man who has a disease.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2865140/extras/descgif.gif?t=1711573157"><br/><br/><strong>Hulzuyot</strong><br/>In <strong>Hulzuyot,</strong> you arrive home after a visit to the doctor who informs you about your illness. You are a salary man who will have to perform household chores while your illness bothers you during the tasks. You will witness everything happening around you without being able to do anything but observe. You can read, play, and engage in household chores, but always <strong>be cautious.</strong><br/><strong><br/>Gameplay</strong><br/>Hulzuyot is a first-person simulator with mechanics involving various household tasks.<br/><br/><strong>You take between 35-45 minutes to complete.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Atmospheric environment and photorealistic graphics<br/></li><li>Retro VHS aesthetics<br/></li><li>Performing household chores</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Furious Flappers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2876970/Furious_Flappers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2876970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Your Flappers are furious and ready to kick some Hog butt. Help them destroy the evil Hogs by stretching your arms and flying in VR to bring peace to their world. Play through 36 unique levels, using 6 different Flappers, all with unique abilities, to destroy the Hogs! Shoot them using your slingshot, and then extend your arms and fly midair to direct your flight up, down, and sideways. Your Flappers can teleport, expand, explode, and much more! Destroy everything from small huts to enormous stone buildings with your flapping fury. Bonus points if you can finish levels with fewer birds, and finish them quickly too!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destroy Them !</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2874070/Destroy_Them/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2874070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to <i>Destroy Them</i> - the ultimate First Person Shooter arcade game where your mission is to obliterate all the robots across four different maps using advanced movements and tactics to earn points and beat your high score!<br/><br/>As you dive into each map, you'll find yourself surrounded by robotic enemies. But fear not, because you're armed with an assault rifle and you can move with advanced movements, you will be able to escape the ennemies with skill and ease.<br/><br/>And what sets 'Destroy Them' apart is its accessibility. Designed to run on practically any computer, whether it's a high-end gaming rig or a humble system, this game ensures that everyone can have fun, a bit like a flash game.<br/><br/>Play around on 4 different maps and maybe more that will come out later, all very different and fun in their own way. (some are KINDA unbalanced ngl)<br/><br/>So what are you waiting for? Play Destroy Them right now ! Whether you're a gamer looking for a challenge or a newbie wanting to dive into the action and have fun, this game is right for you !						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannot Contain</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2709510/Cannot_Contain/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to your new job here at <strong>Keep 'Em Contained</strong>, the private containment facility that caters to any and all of your containment needs.<br/><br/><i>"If we can't contain it, no one can!"</i><br/><br/>As our newest recruit, it is your sole responsibility to maintain the facility and keep the residents contained!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709510/extras/CannotContain_Map.gif?t=1711563334"><br/><br/>Whether it's fixing power faults, repairing the ventilation systems, or preventing the release of untold evils onto the world above, we know we can rely on you to fulfil your obligation to us, no matter the cost or sacrifice!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709510/extras/CannotContain_Faults.gif?t=1711563334"><br/><br/>We've spared no expense and provided you with a state-of-the-art CCTV system for monitoring the facility, as well as a cutting-edge new computer (with keyboard!) for analysing the facility's systems and locating any faults. Combine this with a torch and repair tools (generously loaned by us), and now you really have no excuse for failure!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709510/extras/CannotContain_Terminal.gif?t=1711563334"><br/><br/>We are excited to kickstart your (hopefully) long and productive career working for us! Good luck!<br/><br/>Disclaimer: <i>By accepting this job, you agree that in the event of one or more residents escaping containment, that you yourself will be contained immediately and indefinitely, assuming you survive that long.</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duplicate Dissolution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2825310/Duplicate_Dissolution/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Duplicate Dissolution is a short first-person puzzle game where you utilize your digital duplicates to solve a series of puzzles and conundrums.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825310/extras/Title1.png?t=1711574258"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825310/extras/Optimized_1.gif?t=1711574258"><br/><br/>Use the duplicates at your disposal in varied situations. In these floors covered by light, where your timing, planning and execution skills will be put to the test, your intelligence is your strongest asset.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825310/extras/Title2.png?t=1711574258"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825310/extras/Optimized_2.gif?t=1711574258"><br/><br/>Easily command your 3 digital duplicates to work alongside you. You can deploy a duplicate and activate them at any time, materializing what they hold and allowing them to interact with the environment. Overcome obstacles with duplicates that can complete simple tasks like pressing buttons on top of acting as extra weight or even elevation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825310/extras/Title3.png?t=1711574258"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825310/extras/Optimized_3.gif?t=1711574258"><br/><br/>Take on the role of NULL, the newest instance of the TESTER program. Created by the Operator; the experienced administrator of the Simulation, you’ll check whether the Simulation is operating smoothly. Run each process to its end and complete the diagnostic.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825310/extras/Title4.png?t=1711574258"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825310/extras/Optimized_4.gif?t=1711574258"><br/><br/>Delve into the depths of the Simulation as you pass through environments brought to life through futuristic designs and stunning lighting. Traverse the mechanical chambers of secrets of this program alongside your duplicates as a robotic data carrier.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825310/extras/Title5.png?t=1711574258"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tackle the challenges on your path, only with your duplicates and wits.<br/></li><li>Complete elaborate puzzle rooms, each comprised of clear and easy to use mechanics.<br/></li><li>Traverse the pristine, futuristic and darkly luminous chambers of the Simulation.<br/></li><li>Take in the original atmospheric soundtrack accompanying your adventure.<br/></li><li>Experience a minimalist narrative where the clues are hidden in the illusive Operator’s words.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
