<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1706225179"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1706225179"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1706225179"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1706225179"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1706225179"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1706225179"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1706225179"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1706225179"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1706225179"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1706225179"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1706225179"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1706225179"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNDERDOGS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2441700/UNDERDOGS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_Title.gif?t=1706205754"><br/><br/>Wrap yourself in 5 tons of metal and go smashing through a dark scene of UNDERGROUND MECH FIGHTS! Bash, crush, maul and rip apart enemy bots and mechs.<br/><br/><u><strong>IT’S FULL-ON METAL-ON-METAL VIOLENCE IN THIS PHYSICS-BASED MECH BRAWLER!</strong></u><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_Smooch.gif?t=1706205754"><br/><br/>But rampaging through the pits ain’t all - <u><strong>THIS IS A ROGUELIKE.</strong></u><br/>Gear up with 120+ items including power tools to customize your mech, meet 30+ characters, hire hackers and saboteurs, hustle and deal with the gangsters and psychos who run these streets as you claw your way up the food chain.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_DF_Pan.gif?t=1706205754"><br/><br/>This city is a dog-eat-dog shit show, but luckily you ain't alone.<br/>Your little bruv King is in your corner - hacking your enemies and giving you lip while you fight like a wild animal, smashing car sized pit bots that wanna kill you dead to the deafening roars of the blood thirsty crowds.<br/><br/><strong>This is New Brakka - The Mech Fighting Capital of the World.<br/>This is UNDERDOGS.<br/><br/>Welcome to the jungle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_Dem_Clean.gif?t=1706205754"/></strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIN: The Last Child</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1960070/RIN_The_Last_Child/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/extras/SAVE_kopia.png?t=1706205624"><br/><i>Play as RIN, the last child of the Creator, on a journey to restore order in a mystical world. Collect aspects and runes, craft spells, and confront powerful bosses - your transformed siblings. The fate of the world rests in your hands.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/extras/drive.png?t=1706205624"><br/>The story of RIN, her siblings, and their Creator, the Teller of Tales, was inspired by the well-known ancient myth about Cronus and his conflict with his children. It also touches upon the overall passing of gods who must be replaced by new gods. <strong>The creation myths</strong> seemed to match perfectly Metroidvania's dark fairy tale - no trace of man, but the importance of magic. An important motif and another layer of the script is the conflict between being obedient to authority - the father (the Creator) or freedom - the free will and responsibility for oneself and one's decisions. The story offers different possible endings based on your choices.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/extras/REKINDLE_kopia.png?t=1706205624"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/extras/gif1.gif?t=1706205624"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/extras/craft.png?t=1706205624"><br/>There are<strong> 18 elemental spells</strong> from three categories: attack (10), defense (5), and utility (3).<br/>The spells are created of Aspects of Magic (5) and Spell Patterns. Then, they can be enchanted with a currency by Lesser Runes (adding more damage) or upgraded by an upgrade scheme and Great Runes (changing the effect). The quick slot allows assigning 3 spells at a time but gives an option to quickly swap to another spell set. Mathematically, considering the combination of Lesser Runes, Great Runes, and Upgrades, there are as many as <strong>7776 spells variants</strong>. As you progress, the spells can be disassembled in order to use the aspects components for another assembly. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/extras/gif2.gif?t=1706205624"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/extras/fight.png?t=1706205624"><br/>On your exploration journey, you will <strong>fight many small creatures</strong> formed from their locations such as Slimes, Mosquitoes, but also bigger creepy beasts like Rats or Spitting Plants. The main fights though, will not only require a neat set of spells and skills but most importantly the decisions to take based on your will. As RIN, the sixth child of the Creator, you will<strong> confront five bosses</strong> - your unknown siblings.<br/><br/>The fate of the world rests in your hands. Can you save everyone?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phantom Abyss</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/989440/Phantom_Abyss/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/989440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Phantom Abyss is a massive asynchronous multiplayer game that casts players into procedurally-generated temples and tasks them with retrieving the sacred relics hidden within deadly chambers. Intrepid adventurers will dodge scores of hidden traps, leap treacherous chasms, and flee relentless guardians through branching paths until one of the relics are claimed or the devices of death overwhelm them. Be warned, you only get one attempt at each temple and failure or settling for a lesser relic means you will never see that temple again...<br/><br/>The cleverest players will use the phantom runs of failed attempts from other players to their advantage and avoid the missteps and mistakes that led to their doom. Once the legendary relic at the bottom of each temple is found, the temple goes away forever and becomes the priceless trophy of the skilled adventurer.<h2 class="bb_tag">Asynchronous Multiplayer</h2>Explore the perilous halls and colossal rooms of each temple alongside the phantoms of fallen players that came before you and use their successes and failures to your advantage to progress deeper than they ever could have hoped. Watch and learn from the mistakes of up to 20 phantoms including your Steam friends that have attempted the same temple and steal their whips as they fall.<h2 class="bb_tag">Unlock More Treacherous Floors</h2>Recover keys from chests to unlock deeper, deadlier sections of the temple that house more coveted relics. The more difficult a relic is to obtain, the greater the reward - the final Legendary Relic of a temple allows you to claim the whole temple so that it's gone forever.<h2 class="bb_tag">Blessings from the Gods</h2>As adventurers venture further into a temple, offerings of collected treasures can be made at altars to gain a new blessing for the rest of the run. Collect as much treasure as you can to please the gods and gain a double jump, glide jump, extended slide, damage protection, and more!<h2 class="bb_tag">Unlockable Whips</h2>Unlock new whips with success and choose from your collection before venturing into your next run. Each whips carries a minor blessing but also a curse that may complicate your attempt at riches and glory.<h2 class="bb_tag">Social Connections</h2>Players can share Temple Codes for their failed runs allowing friends to attempt the same temple or share their Adventure Code which yields a playlist of temples that a player has attempted in the past.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go Mecha Ball</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2008510/Go_Mecha_Ball/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2008510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Action-packed twin-stick shooter with arcade roguelite elements<br/></li><li>Experience the dual gameplay of walking and shooting as a mech, or rolling and bumping as a ball<br/></li><li>Navigate dynamic arena playgrounds with a mix of rolling, bouncing, leaping, and bounding<br/></li><li>Conquer four diverse worlds filled with unique enemies and obstacles<br/></li><li>Arm yourself with a versatile arsenal of over 25 destructive tools<br/></li><li>Unleash over 20 quirky and devastating abilities to dominate your foes<br/></li><li>Enhance your mechs with a vast array of more than 50 upgrades, creating a truly personalized combat experience.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2008510/extras/World1HecticKnockEnemyAbyss_short_crop_optimized.gif?t=1706198329"><br/><br/>Embark on an adrenaline-fueled journey through the neon-lit realms of Go Mecha Ball, where chaos meets strategy in a futuristic showdown! Engage in dynamic twin-stick shooter combat, execute acrobatic maneuvers across vibrant 3D platforms, all accompanied by a dynamically generated and interactive soundtrack.<br/><br/>Unleash the power of four distinct gun-wielding mechs, each with its own unique arsenal of weapons, abilities, and upgrades. Dive into the mayhem as you discover synergies, hone your playstyle, and navigate through an ever-evolving landscape of rampaging robots, colossal bosses, and arcade-like obstacles.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2008510/extras/World1LedgeSlamMissileLaserEnemy_crop_optimized.gif?t=1706198329"><br/><br/>Soar above the chaos by boosting up ramps, bounce off lively bumpers, or ride the updraft from giant fans, adding a layer of dynamic movement to your chosen strategy. Launch swarms of missiles, summon helpful allies, or create seismic disruptions by crashing into the ground like a meteor — the choice is yours.<br/><br/>With over 25 tools for mass destruction at your disposal and more than 20 quirky abilities to master, customize your mech to dominate the competition. Explore four visually stunning worlds teeming with enemies and challenges, each presenting an exhilarating playground for your ballistic escapades.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2008510/extras/World3WindTunnelGrenadeSniper_crop_optimized.gif?t=1706198329"><br/><br/>Every gunshot, impact, and interaction is a symphony of uniqueness, tailored to the situation, and driven by physics. It's not just a game; it's an audio-visual journey where every action you take is reflected in the immersive soundscape.<br/><br/>Are you a graceful butterfly, a relentless wrecking ball, or a precise master assassin? Choose your path and face off against a malfunctioning AI, determined to close the portals that connect your world to this thrilling, mechanized wonderland.<br/><br/>Get ready for an electrifying fusion of skill, strategy, and chaos in Go Mecha Ball — the ultimate adventure awaits!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2008510/extras/World2BumperDiscShotgun_crop_optimized.gif?t=1706198329"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2008510/Go_Mecha_Ball/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2008510/Go_Mecha_Ball/</a> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2072450/Like_a_Dragon_Infinite_Wealth/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>EPIC EMOTIONAL DRAMA</strong><br/>Two larger-than-life heroes brought together by the hand of fate, or perhaps something more sinister…<br/><br/>Ichiban Kasuga, an unstoppable underdog who’s no stranger to crawling up from rock bottom, and Kazuma Kiryu, a broken man facing down his last days.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/2_Epic_Emotional_Drama.gif?t=1706195448"><br/><br/><strong>BEST-IN-CLASS RPG ACTION</strong><br/>Experience one-of-a-kind combat with dynamic, fast-paced RPG battles where the battlefield becomes your weapon, and anything goes. Adapt your party’s skills to the situation with outlandish jobs and customizations to strategically subdue enemies with over-the-top moves. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/3_Best_In_Class_RPG_Action.gif?t=1706195448"><br/><br/><strong>INFINITE ADVENTURE</strong><br/>Live it up in Japan and explore all that Hawaii has to offer in an adventure so big it spans the Pacific. Unforgettable moments await at every step of the journey with a unique mix of quests and activities to enjoy at your leisure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/4_Infinite_Adventure.gif?t=1706195448"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Deluxe Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Ultimate Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/>- Assorted Outfit Bundle: Customize your party's look with outfits &amp; swimwear<br/>- Sujimon &amp; Resort Bundle: Get legendary Sujimon, resort guests and special boosters<br/>- Yakuza CD Collection Set: Increase your in-game playlist with classic karaoke tracks						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apollo Justice: Ace Attorney Trilogy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2187220/Apollo_Justice_Ace_Attorney_Trilogy/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2187220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2187220/extras/13_Apollo_CustomImages_600x338.png?t=1706177279"><br/><br/>Apollo Justice's Legal Journey Begins Anew!<br/><br/>Join rookie attorney Apollo Justice and his mentor, the legendary Phoenix Wright, in this collection of 3 games! This title features the 14 episodes of "Apollo Justice: Ace Attorney", "Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney - Dual Destinies", and "Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney - Spirit of Justice", and the 2 previously DLC-only Special Episodes for a total of 16 episodes!<br/><br/>Also included is a mountain of extra goodies that's sure to satisfy any Ace Attorney fan!<br/><br/>Orchestra Hall - Listen to the in-game background music and select orchestral arrangements!<br/><br/>Art Library - View illustrations, design specs, commissioned pieces, and even the special Spirit of Justice Prologue anime!<br/><br/>Animation Studio - Play around with character animations and recreate your favorite scenes!<br/><br/>This collection supports Japanese, English, French, German, Korean, and Traditional and Simplified Chinese. Mix and match to play in whichever languages you'd like!<br/><br/>Immerse yourself in this beautiful collection as you shout "Objection!" in these newly renovated halls of justice!<br/><br/>Some of the contents of the games in this collection are presented as initially released to preserve the games as originally created.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oblivion Override</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1952370/Oblivion_Override/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1952370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In a post-apocalyptic wasteland under AI’s iron grip, the remnants of humanity are imprinted in the digital shackles of the ‘Oblivion Code’. To unravel the intricate web of secrets within the dystopian AI civilization, Crimson, a rogue combat bot, embarks on a daring incursion into the neon-drenched corridors of Dulce Base…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1952370/extras/BOSS登场_裁剪_gif.gif?t=1706166161"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1952370/extras/湮灭线-Steam_feature小标题设计-5en.png?t=1706166161"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stage Four [Temple of Oblivion] leading to the final boss<br/></li><li>Complete main storyline and hidden endings<br/></li><li>New female character Mecha<br/></li><li>More compact maps with special challenge rooms<br/></li><li>Optimized character progression both inside and outside battles<br/></li><li>Weapon evolution attributes and the blocking function for initial weapons<br/></li><li>Game gallery, optimizations, and bug fixes</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1952370/extras/第四关_蓝蓝的场景_炫酷的三角攻击.gif?t=1706166161"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1952370/extras/湮灭线-Steam_feature小标题设计-1en.png?t=1706166161"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1952370/extras/康特_vs_里昂_gif.gif?t=1706166161"><br/><br/><i><strong>Master dodges, double jumps, and wall runs to traverse the sprawling underground network. Equip your robot with over 26+ specialized weapons, each featuring unique mechanics, combat choreography, and augmented skill effects.</strong></i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1952370/extras/湮灭线-Steam_feature小标题设计-2en.png?t=1706166161"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1952370/extras/机甲奥义展示_加框框.gif?t=1706166161"><br/><br/><strong><i>Unlock six state-of-the-art combat machines and charge into action: from ninja and thunder geek to viking warrior and feline assassin. Centered around their exclusive abilities, Atomic Evolution can be accessed at any point during your run. </i></strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1952370/extras/湮灭线-Steam_feature小标题设计-3en.png?t=1706166161"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1952370/extras/地形展示_1_.gif?t=1706166161"><br/><br/><i><strong>Explore the abandoned site of an arms factory, navigate through the maze of a bio-engineered greenhouse, and neutralize all impending threats lurking within the data center, leading you to the enigmatic temple of an ancient-tech civilization…</strong></i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1952370/extras/湮灭线-Steam_feature小标题设计-4en.png?t=1706166161"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1952370/extras/警戒.gif.gif?t=1706166161"><br/><br/><strong><i>Dare to crank up the Alert Level from Level I all the way to Level VIII? Brace yourself for far more grueling battles against enemies and bosses on increased hostility and retrofitted with advanced gear.</i></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III - Tech Luxe Pro Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2686650/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III__Tech_Luxe_Pro_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Get Call of Duty® Points* and in-game content for Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III and Call of Duty®: Warzone™.<br>
<br>
Pack includes:<br>
<br/>
- 2400 Call of Duty® Points<br/>
- Operator Skin for Abe Kaede<br/>
- 2x Weapon Blueprints<br/>
- Animated Calling Card<br/>
- Weapon Sticker<br/>
- Weapon Charm<br/>
- Animated Emblem<br/>
<br/>
Activision may update, replace, or remove this in-game content at any time.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2248950/TransSiberian_Railway_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take the helm of a classic Russian locomotive, discover the raw beauty and wildness of Siberia and try to survive on the longest railway line in the world. This is the Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator. A game for real adventurers!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/drinking1.gif?t=1706025563"><br/><br/>Complete the tutorial and the first kilometers of the route for free.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/explosion_gif.gif?t=1706025563"><br/><br/>The Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator offers amazing rail and survival challenges on real Russian dangerous routes. Feel what it is like to put your hands at the helm of a powerful freight locomotive and explore the untouched natural landscape that is sure to delight you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/shooting_gif.gif?t=1706025563"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Prologue features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Detailed simulation of driving a VL10 locomotive - the locomotive control is slightly simplified.<br/></li><li> Locomotive repair system - Manage and replace locomotive parts that are constantly wearing out.<br/></li><li> Train traffic simulation - Follow rail signs and signals to avoid derailment or damage to a part of the locomotive.<br/></li><li> Work system - Earn by completing transport orders. <br/></li><li> Game modes (Survival) and (Simulator). It is recommended to play in the (Survival) mode. This is the leading game mode that is constantly being developed. <br/>For players who are not interested in survival mechanics, a simple Simulator mode is available. <br/></li><li> Mafia system - Complete missions for the mafia to earn extra money.<br/></li><li> Survival system with statistics of hunger, thirst, alcohol, hangover, disease and hypothermia - Eat and drink to avoid death. <br/>Keep the right temperature so you don't freeze.<br/></li><li> Shooting system - Use your weapons for hunting and self-defense.<br/></li><li> Purchase and sales system - Buy various items, food, tools, weapons and ammunition.<br/></li><li> Locomotive inspection mode - Inspect the condition of locomotive parts and replace them in time to avoid damage.<br/></li><li> Dynamic weather system with day and night cycle - Survive extreme weather conditions.<br/></li><li> Route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Novosibirsk-Main) - scale 1:1. Buy the full version with the route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Krasnoyarsk).<br/></li><li> Police system - A corrupt militia watches over your movements.<br/></li><li> Much more to discover.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lil' Guardsman</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1924360/Lil_Guardsman/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this deduction adventure, you play as Lil - an unlikely 12-year-old hero - covering your dad's shift at the guard shed and are tasked with deciding the fate of over 100 unique characters.<br/><br/>You will question humans, elves, goblins, cyclopes, and other fantasy creatures using your powers of deduction to determine who to admit or deny based on how they respond to your questions and your trusty tools. Sending visitors to jail, inadvertently zapping them to smithereens, or letting them go on their merry way are all part of the job. But be careful: who you let through the castle gates will determine the kingdom's fate.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924360/extras/LilGuardsman_MainGame_Steam_HeaderBanner_01_FantasyComedyNarrative_English_ApprovedPublic.png?t=1706021019"><br/><br/>See the Sprawl and its fantastical &amp; quirky citizens through a royal wedding to one of two kingdoms vying for an alliance, and a subsequent siege by whoever you've angered in the process. Your decisions can determine the fate of the city and its people!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924360/extras/LilGuardsman_MainGame_Steam_GIF_01_FantasyComedyNarrative_ApprovedPublic.gif?t=1706021019"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924360/extras/LilGuardsman_MainGame_Steam_HeaderBanner_02_InterrogationPuzzles_English_ApprovedPublic.png?t=1706021019"><br/><br/>Interrogate 100+ fully voiced characters in just the right way to earn a perfect score.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924360/extras/LilGuardsman_MainGame_Steam_GIF_02_InterrogationPuzzles_ApprovedPublic.gif?t=1706021019"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924360/extras/LilGuardsman_MainGame_Steam_HeaderBanner_03_ToolsOfTheTrade_English_ApprovedPublic.png?t=1706021019"><br/><br/>Spend your hard earned gold wisely on powering up your guardsman toolkit, and strategically deploy these to admit or deny the right people or...goblins?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924360/extras/LilGuardsman_MainGame_Steam_GIF_03_ToolsOfTheTrade_ApprovedPublic.gif?t=1706021019"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924360/extras/LilGuardsman_MainGame_Steam_HeaderBanner_04_RewindTime_English_ApprovedPublic.png?t=1706021019"><br/><br/>Use your trusty Chronometer3000 to go back and get a higher score... but be careful not to break space and time in the process.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924360/extras/LilGuardsman_MainGame_Steam_GIF_04_RewindTime_ApprovedPublic.gif?t=1706021019"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Universim</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/352720/The_Universim/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>WHAT WOULD YOU DO WITH THE POWER?</strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Play God!</strong> </h2>Guide your fledgling sentient species (lovingly called “nuggets”) from Stone Age cave painters to star-faring explorers.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-1-2d869427c7.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Wield godly power</strong></h2>Command more than 15 godly powers to guide, protect — or discipline — your followers. Create devastating tornadoes, smite naughty followers with lightning bolts, or shake and sunder the very earth. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-1-998341a4ac.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Watch your Nuggets grow and thrive</strong></h2>Observe Nuggets' every move as they work and fight to survive. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-537928a55b.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Evolve and advance through the ages</strong></h2>Research more than 200 technological and societal advancements. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-daca04b5ec.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Expand your power and colonize the galaxy</strong></h2>Discover and colonize a galaxy of procedurally generated planets, each with  unique ecosystems and challenges to conquer.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-be2f66969b.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Manage delicate ecosystems</strong></h2>Manage the delicate balance of planetary ecosystems to help nuggets thrive. Your decisions and your followers’ ' actions influence global climates and have real environmental consequences. (Try not to kill them in an ecological disaster — well, unless you want to, of course.)<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-0095b39c11.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Delve into the deeper mystery of your existence</strong></h2>Unravel the layers of a deeper cosmic story that challenges your perception of who and what you are — and reveals unexpected twists!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-4830f44913.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>About This Game:</strong></h2><br/>The Universim is a strategy city builder game with “God” elements where you guide a civilization (Nuggets) from the Stone Age to the Space Age. Manage resources, dynamic challenges, and ensure your Nuggets can survive, thrive, and spread to the stars. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Animated_Planet_3.png?t=1705993770"><br/><br/>The Universim  features more than  200 research perks that will help you to shape your civilization. Be as benevolent or malevolent as you like to drive nuggets to evolve, advance, and expand. (Even the best civilizations need an occasional smiting).  <br/>Every planet in The Universim is procedurally generated and offers unique characteristics  and challenges, ensuring  that every world and every game is unique and engaging.  Ecological balance and resource management are critical to success. Nuggets have their own needs and behaviors you must attend to. Your guidance will shape how they deal with conflicts, natural disasters, alien creatures, and other civilizations. Their growth and evolution depends on you!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FSymAzCGWsk" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Crytivo_Discord.png?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FgUt5N68" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Discord_join.jpg?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://twitter.com/crytivo" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Twitter.png?t=1705993770"/></a> <br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Feepurl.com%2FbKnqM1" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/News.png?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><br/>This game published by <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/franchise/Crytivo" rel="" target="_blank">Crytivo</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Capitalist Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743080/100_Capitalist_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779640/100_Capitalist_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_6" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779640/100_Capitalist_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱💼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 CAPITALIST CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆💰💵</h2>🤑 Join the cutest adventure in the Wall Street, New York, heart of capitalism! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/600x200.png?t=1706062420"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level of Wall Street location<br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Capitalist Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779640/100_Capitalist_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100CapitalistCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Extra.png?t=1706062420"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779660/100_Capitalist_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100CapitalistCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1706062420"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779650/100_Capitalist_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=100CapitalistCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Artbook.png?t=1706062420"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/600x1.png?t=1706062420"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1706062420"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot" id="dynamiclink_7" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743080/100_Capitalist_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot" id="dynamiclink_8" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743080/100_Capitalist_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intravenous 2: Mercenarism</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2651330/Intravenous_2_Mercenarism/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Wishlist_Game.png?t=1705699394"><br/><br/>Step into the shoes of Gideon, a ruthless mercenary who cares about nothing but his wealth. Set two months before the events of Intravenous 2, you will take on seemingly simple jobs, the effects of which will ripple out and affect the main game's protagonist. But why should Gideon care? He's just in it for the money.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Stealth_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Stealth or Firepower:</strong> the choice is yours. Sneak through shadows, turn off the lights, pick doors, or unleash a hail of bullets. The game will adapt to your play style.<br/></li><li> <strong>Customize Your Skills:</strong> develop your skills the way you want to, whether it's mastering the art of stealth or becoming a gunslinging virtuoso.<br/></li><li> <strong>Bullet Time:</strong> Gideon is no stranger to stimulants that enhance his cognitive abilities - bending time to give him the edge in tense situations.<br/></li><li> <strong>Vast Arsenal:</strong> choose from firearms, gadgets, and a variety of ammo types to creatively tackle the challenge<br/></li><li> <strong>Weapon Modification:</strong> personalize each firearm with suppressors, laser sights, and more, tailoring your arsenal to the task at hand.<br/></li><li> <strong>Responsive AI:</strong> engage in intense combat with enemies that react to your actions, take cover, use tactics and call for backup.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Action_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Safety Hotline</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2357910/Home_Safety_Hotline/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/RuntimeLabel-HSH-Dark.png?t=1706120817"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/ShinyLogoOnlyGIF.gif?t=1706120817"><br/><br/><strong>Hearing noises? Seeing things? Call Home Safety Hotline! Our operators are standing by, waiting to give you the answers you need to protect your home from all manner of pests and household hazards.</strong><br/><br/>Home Safety Hotline is an analog horror inspired telephone operator simulator where you answer incoming callers' questions about what's inside their home. Read through a vast catalog of common pests and household hazards, and do your best to become an expert in home safety. You will be held responsible for what happens.<br/><br/>A new horror experiment from Nick Lives, the creator of <i>NiGHT SIGNAL</i> and <i>A Wonderful Day For Fishing</i>. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Navigate a vast catalog of safety information using the latest in 90's technology.<br/></li><li> Listen to original jazzy lo-fi music by David Johnsen while you place callers on hold.<br/></li><li> Correctly deduce what's in your callers' homes or else leave them to suffer the consequences.<br/></li><li> Learn about the various untold horrors that live inside your home.<br/></li><li> "Phobia Toggles" - An accessibility option that allows you to disable in-game images for common phobia triggers including arachnophobia and more.<br/></li><li> Unlockable Art Book detailing the game's development history.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2357910/extras/NumberOnlyGIF.gif?t=1706120817"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2744170/Artifact_SeekerPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/DS.png?t=1705638389"/></a><br/>The difference between the prologue version and the official version<br/>There is a special artifact in the prologue<br/>Characters: 2 in the prologue, at least 5 in the official version<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 3 in the final version.<br/>Systems: Tavern, Marketplace, and Endless Mode will be added to the game.<br/>Artifacts: More artifacts will be added to the game.<br/>Skills: More skills will be added in the official version.<br/>Words: More words will be added in the official version.<br/>Encounters: There will be more interesting encounters in the official version.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/11y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1z.gif?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/2y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/gif1.gif?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.gif?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong>[/b]<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.gif?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.gif?t=1705638389"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><strong><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.png?t=1705638389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.gif?t=1705638389"><br/>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </img></img></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frostrain</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735630/Frostrain/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/01_Thumnail.png?t=1705964349"><h2 class="bb_tag">Roam the frozen world</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Roam_the_frozen_world.gif?t=1705964349"><br/>Climate change has turned the world white and frozen, and the only thing moving on the planet is you, your passengers, and your train. It's a dead world, but ironically, it's all the more fascinating for it. A vivid landscape awaits you to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Keep your passengers happy</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Keep_your_passengers_happy.gif?t=1705964349"><br/>The passengers on your train will work diligently at your command, but be careful: if you don't manage their happiness properly, they might throw you off the train.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build your own train with card decks</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Build_your_own_train_with_card_decks.gif?t=1705964349"><br/>Each time you pass through a city, you'll be able to add new train cars by launching a heavy lift drone. Be careful with each choice you make. If you are lucky, you'll be able to build a better, more synergized, happily-ever-after train deck, but it won't always go as you planned.<h2 class="bb_tag">Reach the Promised Land</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Reach_the_Promised_Land.gif?t=1705964349"><br/>Lead your passengers in search of the Promised Land, somewhere on the eastern edge of the world. But the journey to the Promised Land isn't all smooth and pleasant. You'll have to pass through toxic areas, and a severe storm is brewing behind you. Pay attention to your passengers' happiness levels and lead them safely to the Promised Land. The journey is in your hands.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summoners War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2426960/Summoners_War/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2426960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>▶Features</strong><br/><strong>[Tactical RPG play]</strong><br/>Witness the dazzling display of each monster 's unique skills.<br/>23 different Rune sets to pick and choose additional abilities for your monsters!<br/>Come up with the best strategy to win battles in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[Endless Fun]</strong><br/>Decorate your Village, battle other summoners , explore dungeons , fight in PvP battles , expand your collection, train monsters , and more.<br/><br/><strong>[The Key of Colletion RPG : Massive Collection]</strong><br/>Fire, Water, Wind, Light and Dark!<br/>5 different attributes, and 1500 different monsters!<br/>Collect as many monsters as you can and win battles with your own decks .<br/><br/><strong>[Real-time Raid]</strong><br/>Battle as a team with your greatest monsters !<br/>A real-time battle with 3 users!<br/>Defeat the boss with your fellow Summoners using various tactics.<br/><br/><strong>[Homunculus]</strong><br/>The Forbidden Summoning Magic has finally been revealed!<br/>You can Evolve the skill of your choice with this special monster.<br/>Summon Homunculus and show off your strategy in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[All about Turn-Based RPG : World Arena]</strong><br/>Enjoy a real-time battle with Summoners worldwide!<br/>Experience a breathtaking battle that starts from Pick &amp; Ban.<br/>Reveal your unique strategy to the world and win battles .<br/><br/><strong>[Guild Content]</strong><br/>A sensational Guild PvP battle in the Isle of Conquest!<br/>Explore the Tartarus' Labyrinth and dungeons with Guild Members.<br/>Make your Guild the greatest of all.<br/><br/><strong>[Dimension Hole]</strong><br/>Fight against the ancient power emerged from a new dimension!<br/>Defeat the Ancient Guardians and meet the powerful monsters with new awakening power.<br/><br/><strong>[Artifact]</strong><br/>Artifacts are now dropped with MAX power-up levels!<br/>Summoners , fight against the powerful bosses and acquire Artifacts!<br/>Enhance your monsters with various sub properties of Artifacts.<br/><br/><strong>[Progression and Farming Structure Revamp]</strong><br/>Summoner progression structure renewed and content reward greatly improved!<br/>Dive into Summoners War and experience the enhanced progression system!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portal: Revolution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/601360/Portal_Revolution/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Portal: Revolution is a fan-made mod for Portal 2 which plays before the events of Portal 2 in the dead and decaying Aperture facility.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/ezgif-7-f507c3c464_1_.gif?t=1705968827"><br/><strong>Over 40 new puzzles</strong><br/>The campaign contains 40 brand new puzzles making use of new test elements and presents existing mechanics in a new way not seen in Portal 2.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resurrected "Pneumatic Diversity Vent" element<br/></li><li> New laser cube variant<br/></li><li> Over 15 puzzles using only the blue Portal-Gun<br/></li><li> Gel Cleansing Field</li></ul><br/><strong>Difficulty</strong><br/>Portal: Revolutions puzzle difficulty starts where Portal 2 stops, but fear not. All new mechanics and advanced portal tricks are taught to you. We have ensured through rigorous playtesting that every player can solve the puzzles. Although very few chambers require portals to be fired mid-air, no puzzles require advanced tricky movement.<br/><br/>Depending on your experience with Portal 2 mechanics, you can expect about 5 to 7 hours of playtime.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/banner_story_2.gif?t=1705968827"><br/>Set inbetween Portal and Portal 2, Portal: Revolution tells a brand new story using new characters. You play as a test subject who is awoken by a personality sphere called Stirling and join his mission to find a powerful device capable of restoring Aperture to its former glory.<h2 class="bb_tag">ENGINE</h2>Portal: Revolution uses a modified version of Portal 2: Community Edition's engine, which is a custom version of the Counter-Strike: Global Offensive Source Engine branch using licensed source code provided by Valve Software.<br/><br/>This allowed us to introduce many mechanics and improvements to the engine to create an experience which would be impossible in Portal 2.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Esports Godfather Origin</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2739460/Esports_Godfather_Origin/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/游戏简介英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/>"Esport Godfather" is a management simulation card game that revolves around the theme of MOBA esports. In this game, you will assume the role of a coach in an esports club and personally build your own team! Starting from scratch, what kind of playstyle will you devise for your team? In a constantly evolving meta, can you derive a unique understanding of what it takes to win? How will you unlock the potential of your handpicked athletes and mold them into superstars?<br/><br/>Ultimately, will you be able to become a legendary figure in the esports industry, crafting your own esports story and lifting the championship trophy?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/选手培养英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/>Each athlete is unique! They all have their own strengths and weaknesses.<br/>If an athlete's efficiency in earning money increases over time, they are undoubtedly a skilled late-game specialist.<br/>Successful ambushes can unlock hidden potential, propelling some athletes onto the path of godlike.<br/>As a coach, it's your responsibility to analyze each athlete's characteristics, devise training plans tailored to their needs, and guide them on their journey to becoming superstars!<br/><br/>· Every athlete possesses distinct abilities that will impact their performance on the battlefield!<br/>· An athlete's hero pool is crucial for Ban &amp; Pick strategies!<br/>· The tactic cards utilized by athletes in matches serve as the foundation of all strategies!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/版本变更英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/>The meta environment is ever-changing!<br/>Changes in the equipment pool, the structure of economic income, and the source of decisive advantages, even slight alterations to the rules can drastically shift the priorities of Ban &amp; Pick and alter the strategic approach!<br/><br/>· Equipment will be added or removed as the versions change!<br/>· The timing of crucial team fights will shift with each version update, making team composition crucial!<br/>· Does harassment grant more gold? Do kills damage towers? Each gameplay rule brings a fresh experience!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/指挥战斗英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/>You have the power to command the battlefield, with athletes attentively listening to your orders.<br/>Should you play it safe and focus on farming under the towers, or launch aggressive assaults and initiate attacks?<br/>Perfect team composition requires perfect leadership! The game is ever-changing, and you must face your opponents head-on!<br/><br/>· Each hero and athlete possesses their own tactic cards. It is through creative combinations and strategic application that they become unstoppable!<br/>· Offense or defense? Aggression or caution? The outcome rests in your hands. Formulate strategies and implement tactics!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/其他内容英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/>· Over 50 unique heroes in the starting lineup, each with their own special abilities!<br/>· 200+ tactic cards, granting you control over the battlefield!<br/>· Diverse athlete training options! As a mentor, it's important to tailor your teachings to each individual!<br/>· Unearth young talents and cultivate new forces in the youth training camp!<br/>· Choose sponsors, a top-tier club deserves the support of top-tier sponsors!<br/>· Trash-talking sessions, asserting dominance is a must before crucial matches!<br/>· Abundance of events, includes unexpected occurrences, athlete communication, team pep talks!<br/>· Training match plans, knowing your opponents inside out ensures victory after victory!<br/>· Regular season, playoffs, transfer periods—different decisions await you at different times!<br/>· When athletes reach their limits, you must help them break through and reach new heights!<br/>· Create a custom team logo for your club!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/工作室LOGO英文.png?t=1705633086"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones: NWO Wars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2487350/Alex_Jones_NWO_Wars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Play the OFFICIAL Alex Jones video game! Save the world from the evil globalists’ plot to turn everyone into bug-eating pod-dwelling libtards! STAY TUNED FOR FUTURE BONUS LEVELS AND CHARACTERS.<br/><br/><strong>Classic Run-and-Gun Gameplay</strong>: Enjoy fast-paced action, intricate animations, and detailed environments as you blast your way through waves of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>Unique Levels</strong>: Battle in various environments like secret underground bases, globalist conferences, and mind control facilities, all inspired by real events. Stay tuned for future levels.<br/><br/><strong>Challenging Boss Fights</strong>: Face off against the elite henchmen of the New World Order, including lizard overlords, secret society leaders, and genetically modified creatures.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Voice Lines</strong>: Featuring iconic and often humorous catchphrases from Alex Jones himself, adding flavor to every combat scenario. Special guest vocals by Ryan Katsu Rivera.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_06.png?t=1706220951"><h2 class="bb_tag">JOIN ALEX AND HIS ALLIES </h2><br/>Every day the deep state sues, lies, defames, and KILLS law-abiding patriots who threaten their power!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_05.png?t=1706220951"><h2 class="bb_tag">DEFEAT BIG TECH CUCKS and MORE</h2><br/>And other anti-American communist bosses throughout this adrenaline-inducing adventure!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_04.png?t=1706220951"><h2 class="bb_tag">PLAY AS ALEX!</h2><br/>For the first time in history, experience the world through Infowars leader Alex Jones’ eyes and see the WAR he fights!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/new_screenshot_03.jpg?t=1706220951"><h2 class="bb_tag">SAVE THE BABIES</h2><br/>It’s no secret the NWO REPTILES are after our children. Play NWO Wars now to help save these innocent victims from these MONSTERS!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_02.png?t=1706220951"><br/><br/>“They’re turning the friggin frogs gay!”<br/><br/>Only Alex Jones can stop this madness and restore balance in the Brain Force!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_01.png?t=1706220951"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowbreak: Containment Zone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668080/Snowbreak_Containment_Zone/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Snowbreak: Containment Zone is a 3D sci-fi RPG-shooter powered by the Unreal Engine 4 that offers a next-gen, cross-platform gaming experience, sharing your progress across all of your devices. <br/><br/>The Descent of the Titans turned a once-vibrant city into the devastated wasteland of Containment Zone Aleph. As the Adjutant of Heimdall Force, bravely undertake missions alongside Manifestations with the powers of gods and unique personalities, seeking to bring this bitter winter to an end...<br/><br/>[Enjoy Hybrid Combat]<br/>Snowbreak's weaponry injects realism into a sci-fi setting, with designs closely simulating future firearms technology. This combines with the otherworldly, RPG-like skill mechanic to create a refreshing combat experience.<br/><br/>[Take on Titans]<br/>The Descent of the Titans completely changed the world, and the battlefield. Feel the thrill of battling giants in this dystopian future!<br/><br/>[Befriend Operatives]<br/>Spend time with your Heimdall Force companions in the Base system. Decorate, chat, and give gifts to grow closer!<br/><br/>[Play Co-Op in Gigalink] <br/>Tired of exploring alone? Join up with friends and fight enemies together!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1705734315"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1705734315"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1705734315"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1705734315"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1705734315"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1705734315"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1705734315"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1704804364"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1705439381"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1705439381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1705439381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1705439381"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1705439381"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood West</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_steam_text_header.png?t=1704530905"><br/><br/>Weird West legends meet eldritch horror in <strong>BLOOD WEST</strong>, an immersive stealth FPS. Become the Undead Gunslinger, doomed to roam the barren lands until he finds the means to purge their curse and free his soul. No, this isn’t your typical Wild West desperado redemption arc. This is a damnation arc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_episodes_EN.gif?t=1704530905"><br/><br/>The Canyons, the Swamp, and the Mountains. Each swarming with abominable monsters and unholy demons, these are open-ended worlds for you to explore freely at your own pace. It will take the player over 20 hours on average to complete all three scenarios, and over 35 if they want to see everything the barren lands have to offer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_stealth_EN.gif?t=1704530905"><br/><br/><strong>Blood West</strong> is a stealth FPS inspired by the genre classics such as the Thief series (whose fans will be happy to hear the voice of Stephen Russell, the actor voicing the master-thief Garrett, returning here as the protagonist), S.T.A.L.K.E.R. games, or - from the contemporary catalog - Hunt: Showdown. The gameplay rewards the careful approach: scouting the area, stalking your enemies, and striking from the shadows. Can you figure out a way to clear a fort full of ghouls and monsters without raising an alarm?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_horror_EN.gif?t=1704530905"><br/><br/>The Barren Lands present the player with a nightmarish, twisted vision of the Wild West legends. The curse that has befallen the realm has corrupted every living thing, defiled the land itself, while summoning restless spirits and dark entities. In this mixture of gunslinger pulp and Lovecraftian horror, dark occult magick presents just as much of a threat as sudden lead poisoning.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_characters_EN.gif?t=1704530905"><br/><br/>In <strong>Blood West</strong> you will meet many colorful, yet strangely twisted, fully-voiced NPCs. Just as much prisoners of the Barren Lands as you are, they will sometimes share their unusual stories and send you on various missions. Play nice and they might reward you or become your allies. Cross them and risk their wrath.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_secrets_EN.gif?t=1704530905"><br/><br/>The game won’t hold your hand. You’ll have to explore the land for yourself (buying a map from a vendor might prove useful!), and figure out your own way to approach quests. As you poke around the three expansive maps, keep an eye out for hidden places and secret stashes. There’s gold in the mountains! Fair warning - it’s probably cursed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_brutal_EN.gif?t=1704530905"><br/><br/>If sneaking around isn’t exactly your thing, or you feel that you have a power advantage over your enemies, you can always take the head-on approach and meet your enemies guns blazing. <strong>Blood West</strong> comes from the creators of the fan-favorite boomer shooter <strong>POSTAL: Brain Damaged</strong>, so much gratuitous fantasy violence and pixelated blood splatter is to be expected!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_inventory_EN.gif?t=1704530905"><br/><br/>One man’s hell might be another hoarder’s paradise! From simple one-use items like bandages, through medical tinctures, explosives and incendiaries, straight to arcane artifacts that - once slotted - can change the way you play the game, the Barren Lands are just filled with STUFF. There are tons of useful items to discover, and there’s a special player’s stash crate for all those super-rare potions that you’ll hoard and never use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_weapons_EN.gif?t=1704530905"><br/><br/>A gunslinger without a gun would be just a regular slinger. Where’s the fun in that? <strong>Blood West</strong> makes sure you’ll have plenty of weapons to choose from. Revolvers, rifles, shotguns, carabines - a great variety of firearms, from standard army-issue to those infused with powerful magic, or straight-up possessed. And if you prefer not to cause a ruckus, there’s a wide selection of hand-to-hand combat weapons and archery weapons to pick your favorites from.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_skills_EN.gif?t=1704530905"><br/><br/>The RPG-like perk-based progression system in <strong>Blood West</strong> will allow you to highly customize the gameplay experience to your liking. Become a stealthy hunter, a revolver-fanning gunman or a relentless berserker. You will gain experience and progress through the skill tree, while discovering new artifacts in each of the scenarios that will bestow on you additional abilities. Combining skills and load-out creates more possible playstyles than you’d normally be able to explore in one playthrough.<h2 class="bb_tag">Are you ready to take back the frontier from the dark forces of demonic corruption and earn the right to move on to a better world? The Barren Lands call you, Gunslinger!</h2><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Njuma</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743320/Njuma/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>What is Njuma?</strong></h2><br/><strong>Njuma</strong> is a narrative driven pixel art game with an offbeat interpretation of the Game Jam’s theme: <strong>Take a Deep Breath.</strong><br/><br/>Draw your last breath and become the family's Spirit-Guide and <strong>Guardian of the Ancestral Tree</strong>. Help your descendents in their final moments by bringing them comfort and serenity as they transition to the afterlife.<br/><br/>The Ancestral Tree withers, generational trauma lurking in its shadow. You must piece together a tragedy and soothe a soul-scar which refuses to heal. The Fate of the family is in your hands.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>What you can expect</strong></h2><br/>A short walking simulator game, where you interact and get help from items and NPC's in the environment to interpret the story.<br/><br/>The NPC's interact with you as you walk close to objects, giving you clues of what they are seeking.<br/><br/>Pick up items, and place them to make a choice. Your choice matters!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>About development</strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743320/extras/credits_ella_01.png?t=1706256792"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743320/extras/credits_ben_01.png?t=1706256792"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743320/extras/credits_embla_01.png?t=1706256792"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743320/extras/credits_emmy_01.png?t=1706256792"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743320/extras/credits_joe_01.png?t=1706256792"><br/><br/>This game was developed as a submission for the Lv. 99 Game Jam in 2023. It was developed in the span of 10 days, and worked on further for 3 days for an update including bugfixes and a dialogue system unlocked by completing the game.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743320/extras/SCyEJS.gif?t=1706256792"><h2 class="bb_tag"></h2> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quallet</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2763930/Quallet/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2763930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Quallet is a game where you are a criminal in the land of Qualle, you steal things like planes to money from a bank, but watch out for the police!<br>
<br>
In Quallet, you are Nalim, a criminal that wants to get rid of the police in Qualle. But it won't be easy.<br>
<br>
In the game, you can enter free play mode after completing all missions. In free play mode, you can go to the club and help people on the street, like beggars, but before you do that, you need to complete missions by stealing planes, killing people and of course raiding the military base.<br>
<br>
In Quallet, there are 6 very difficult missions. Quallet also has multiplayer support, where the second player can use a USB controller. There are lots of things to do in the land of Qualle!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUFFLE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684930/TRUFFLE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">What is the Game?</h2>TRUFFLE is a minimalist puzzle maze game where touching the walls kills you instantly! The game will put your patience and dexterity to the test as you complete the large variety of levels. Collect the mushroom at the end of each level to win and don't touch any walls!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>20 Core levels to complete</li><li>6 Bonus levels to unlock</li><li>80 Watching Eyes to collect</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">About the Developer</h2>Hello! I am Ethan Robichaux and I solo developed this game over 4 months. At the time of TRUFFLE releasing I am a college student and I create games in my free time. This is my 4th full Steam game. TRUFFLE is also a complete remake of my first game with over double the content and made in an entirely new game engine. This game is completely free because I want as many people as possible to be able to play and enjoy the game I worked very hard on!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aftermath</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1916830/Aftermath/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1916830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>after·math [|æftərmæθ] 𝒏. A period or state of affairs following a significant event, esp. when that event is destructive or harmful.</i><br/><br/>The story of a soldier left alone in a bunker.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>虚构未来</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2729360/_/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729360/extras/bar1.png?t=1706256357"><br/><br/>A thorough crackdown on the underworld has been initiated by the City Hall of Serbia! Koushuk the former leader of the Black Shadow gang, loses everything in this catastrophic operation. However, through a fortunate turn of events,Koushuk becomes an unofficial member of the police force, working as an undercover cop.<br/><br/>However, due to recent reports of a serial killer on the loose, people in this small town, within the jurisdiction area, are highly vigilant. During an investigation, Kosatsuki encounters the enigmatic detective girl, Yana Mai.<br/><br/>Amidst the presence of cult followers, the peculiar town, the impending threat of the serial killer, and the conspiracy of the Crimson Lotus Society, the fate of these two girls intertwines. As they navigate through countless events, their ultimate destiny remains uncertain.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729360/extras/bar2.png?t=1706256357"><br/><br/>Experience an immersive gameplay of over 20 hours with a rich storyline, extensive side quests, and engaging missions.<br/><br/>Engage in thrilling battles using the intricate Dragonbone combat system, accompanied by stunning skill performances. Each character boasts unique and adorable models and animations!<br/><br/>Explore a variety of gameplay mechanics, including gathering, alchemy, cooking, item appraisal, and skill trees, ensuring a diverse range of activities to fulfill your gaming desires.<br/><br/>With the inclusion of a dynamic time system, the world undergoes different changes as day turns into night.<br/><br/>Prepare for multiple endings! The game offers both a regular ending route and a true ending route, adding depth and replayability to the overall experience.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729360/extras/bar3.png?t=1706256357"><br/><br/>20 hours and more<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729360/extras/bar4.png?t=1706256357"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729360/extras/f1.png?t=1706256357"><br/>[Gu shuoyue ]Combat cv：other<br/>Once a gang girl, Kosatsuki now serves as an unofficial police officer, ensuring law and order in Serbia.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729360/extras/f2.png?t=1706256357"><br/>[Banaime]Combat cv：other<br/>Self-proclaimed amateur journalist, alchemist, occultist, and archaeologist detective girl.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729360/extras/f4.png?t=1706256357"><br/>[Hecate]Combat cv：None<br/>A girl who comes to the aid of Kosatsuki in times of crisis, but her true identity remains unknown.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729360/extras/f5.png?t=1706256357"><br/>[Shiro]<br/>A mysterious girl whose true intentions remain elusive. What is her ultimate goal?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729360/extras/f10.png?t=1706256357"><br/>[Mysterious Girl]cv：青木阳菜<br/>……<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729360/extras/f3.png?t=1706256357"><br/>[Anna]Combat cv：梧桐<br/>A close friend of Kosatsuki, who inherits her father's cake shop.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729360/extras/f6.png?t=1706256357"><br/>[Lucy]Combat cv：梧桐<br/>A wealthy heiress from Arkham City, currently searching for her missing brother.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jump Out</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2729520/Jump_Out/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729520/extras/New_Project_3_5_40.png?t=1706255053"><br/><br/><strong>Precision Platformer - Jump Out</strong>: A minimalist game with a simple goal: get to the top! <br/>Jump Out is a platformer that challenges you to ascend through obstacles and hazards. You will need to hone your jumping skills and overcome your own limits. Inspired by other games that make climbing a struggle, Jump Out will test your perseverance and reward your achievement.<br/><br/><strong><u>Gameplay:</u></strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>WASD movement to climb and jump, simple but demanding controls.<br/></li><li>Saving mechanics? <i>Be gone!</i> - you have to reach the top in one go.<br/></li><li>Earn achievements and aim for the S+ rank (Masochist's delight!)<br/></li><li>Meet Pen, your mischievous jumping robot companion.<br/></li><li>Pixel art graphics and the retro-style animations.<br/></li><li>The equivalent to stepping on a plug when you fall.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729520/extras/New_Project_4_40.png?t=1706255053"><br/><br/>“What goes up must come down.” - <i>Isaac Newton</i> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Flight - Relic Hunter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2396160/Paper_Flight__Relic_Hunter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2396160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Paper Flight – Relic Hunter is an interactive game experience that is designed to ease your mind and have fun popping innocent balloons.<br/>You jump into the role of a little paper plane that is supposed to rescue the world from evil balloon demons by dashing through them.<br/><br/>Fast, relaxed, chaotic - You are free to enjoy the game any way you see fit as the only enemies of the game are balloons which generally are not well known for being too dangerous. The movement is fast but the world itself is somewhat peaceful. This enables you to lean back and enjoy the different levels and the sensation of flying. It is an excellent game for relaxing and blowing off some steam after an exhausting day of hassle.<h2 class="bb_tag">The game also features:</h2>• Juicy balloon destruction and exciting dashes<br/>• A dash meter that needs to be utilized to save the world<br/>• Beautiful visuals and soundtrack<br/>• The experience of flying as a paper plane<br/>• Intuitive and relaxing gameplay<br/>• A moment of inner peace and happiness popping balloons and little balloon demons<br/>• A game that is enjoyable but doesn’t take itself too series – lean back and have fun<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Description</h2>You start as a tiny paper plane in a giant world.<br/><br/>You move continuously forward and are free to fly wherever you want.<br/><br/>After you have played around a little and enjoyed the sensation of flying as well as explored the giant environments for the first time you start to discover nearby areas and hidden secrets. Very soon you will find many normal balloons and a whole bunch of huge demon balloons floating around in the environment.<br/><br/>The normal balloons are soft and you can easily pop them by simply flying through them. The huge demon balloons on the other hand are somewhat hard and you are unable to destroy them by simply hitting them with your paper plane.<br/><br/>Soon you will figure out that there is a solution to the problem. Whenever you pop a small balloon, you receive a little bit of dash power which enables your paper plane to become faster and perform a powerful dash.<br/><br/>Using the dash, you are able to pop even the strongest of all balloons and therefore defeat the evil demon balloons. Now everything is a matter of exploration as you need to find all of the demon balloons while keeping an eye on your dash meter.<br/><br/>Once you have destroyed all demon balloons in a level, a second wave of them will spawn and later a third wave. Every level is structured in 3 waves and once you have finished all of them you will be able to enter the next level and explore more of the giant world with your small paper plane.<br/><br/>While the fast movement and the dashing add a somewhat fast-pace game play to the mix, the overall game is still pretty relaxing as after all your enemies are balloons and do very little to defend themselves from your attacks. It’s a unique mix of exploration, relaxation and a minimalistic balloon combat system that brings fun without the need of too much thinking or strategizing.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Audio Converter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2778270/Free_Audio_Converter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							Free Audio Converter is an all-in-one audio converter and extractor, you can also convert files in batches. allowing you to both convert between different format audio files and extract audio from video files to mp3 aac formats. supports many video, high-definition (HD) video, and audio file types including AVI, MPEG, WMV, MP4, FLV, MKV, H.264/MPEG-4 AVC, AVCHD, MP3, WMA, WAV, AAC, FLAC, OGG, APE, among many others.<br>
Key Features<br>
Convert audio files to MP3 AAC format<br>
Extract audio from video files to MP3 AAC formats<br>
Support batch conversion<br>
Very easy to use						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Ride Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2467510/Dark_Ride_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2467510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Blue Squid Theme Parks presents the VR simulator of their most popular ride The Dark Zone. No need for long trips, now you can experience this iconic ride from the comfort of your own home. Point the torch at the animatronic monsters to earn points. Fun for the whole family! <br>
<br>
Ride length: 5 Minutes<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
- Immersive audio!<br>
- Realistic re-creation of the real Blue Squid Theme Park!<br/>
- Minigame to point the torch at the animatronic monsters!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>百煉登神  Immortal Tales of Rebirth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2103400/__Immortal_Tales_of_Rebirth/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About This Game</strong><br/><strong>DESTINY IS ALL! In this unique single-player fantasy martial arts game, you will play as a sect leader struggling to survive after the devastation of a sect war, working together with like-minded partners to rebuild your home and restore your sect.<br/><br/>On this vast, mysterious continent, you will experience diverse gameplay: tame powerful spirit beasts to become your loyal followers, cultivate gifted disciples, delve into the secrets of martial arts, and create your own unique martial arts style. The continent is full of hidden opportunities and challenges waiting for you to uncover: visit the elders who can pass on their skills, explore hidden caves, find lost martial arts, learn about reclusive sects, and even raise legendary divine beasts from a young age!<br/><br/>On this fateful journey, you will need to rely on your unique martial skills and wisdom, courageously face numerous enemies, and find a way to survive. Only by overcoming hardships and demonstrating wisdom and courage can you become a legendary grandmaster. Choose destiny and become immortal!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/分隔線2.png?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/Super_combo.png?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/白虎道妖.gif?t=1706250820"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/分隔線.png?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/Massive_skills.png?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/天道規則.gif?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/分隔線2.png?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/新玩法_英文.png?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/百鬼夜行.gif?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/分隔線2.png?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/Massive_events.png?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/Event104GIF_ENG.gif?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/分隔線2.png?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/Epic_Boss.png?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/劍魔.gif?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/分隔線2.png?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/征服你的敵人_英文.png?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/佔領.gif?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2103400/extras/分隔線2.png?t=1706250820"><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2FDC%3Ahttps%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FYxeaakU7" rel="noopener" target="_blank">DC:https://discord.gg/YxeaakU7</a><br/>QQ:756228101<br/>bilibili: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspace.bilibili.com%2F1085373768" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://space.bilibili.com/1085373768</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launch The Baby</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2353270/Launch_The_Baby/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2353270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Launch The Baby is a silly, arcade-like game, where you launch your baby out of a cannon to gain points. With these points you can customize your baby with many options to go full absurd. These points will also allow you to unlock new levels and other beneficial tools when launching.<br/><br/><strong>Customize your Baby to your heart's content with the points you earn from launching it as far as you can!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2353270/extras/Customization.gif?t=1706251825"><br/><br/><br/><strong>Experience multiple levels, each with their own themes and challenges</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2353270/extras/Volcano_Level.gif?t=1706251825"><br/><br/><br/><strong>Find hidden ways to keep moving forward!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2353270/extras/Hidden_Ways.gif?t=1706251825"><br/><br/><br/><strong>Enjoy the chaos of the ragdoll physics!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2353270/extras/Funny.gif?t=1706251825"><br/><br/><br/><strong>Oh and... Watch out for the Curse Cannon.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2353270/extras/Byebye.gif?t=1706251825"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TryAndLove</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2715590/TryAndLove/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"I Have a Date with a Beauty" is a fully dynamic and immersive real-person interactive work that simulates love. You will have a sweet love relationship with girls at different stages in your life. They have appeared at different stages of your life and given you different life experiences. But when they appear in front of you at the same time, what is your choice?<br/>You may not be able to choose too many times in life, but the ninth art gives you the possibility of multiple choices. In "I Have a Date with a Beauty", you will not only experience the sweetness of love, but also the helplessness of love. All the choices are yours.<br/><br/>A childhood sweetheart? Do men and women really have pure friendship?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715590/extras/1.jpg?t=1706245274"><br/><br/>Was it your favorite when you were a student? Will the dreams you once had really come to fruition?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715590/extras/2.jpg?t=1706245274"><br/><br/>Is it the inexplicable urge I had when I saw a beautiful teacher in cool clothes in the summer?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715590/extras/3.jpg?t=1706245274"><br/><br/>Is it the anchor who provides you with emotional value after a tiring work day? Is it possible for virtuality to enter reality?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715590/extras/5.jpg?t=1706245274"><br/><br/>Even that indescribable story? ? ? ? ? ? ? ? ? ? ?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715590/extras/4.jpg?t=1706245274"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game features</h2>1. Immersive first-person perspective, full real-life shooting, real-person interpretation (even most characters appear in their true colors)<br/><br/>2. Multiple branches, multiple endings, 25 completely different endings, and even hidden endings, which need to be explored one by one (falling in love takes time)<br/><br/>3. The results and processes of each new round of the game are likely to be different. As for why the mechanism is different, you can guess it after playing.<h2 class="bb_tag">Follow us</h2>This is a product produced by a small team of 4 people (not including the cast, crew, directors, screenwriters, etc.). We don’t have the extra energy to create various groups to maintain it, but we will collect every comment from everyone in the table. As the highest priority to continuously optimize our subsequent products.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Some things in heart</h2><br/>Making this product was inspired by another senior product; The other words above are too official, I want to say some inner words.<br/><br/>The products of my predecessors remind me of the imprint of love left deep in my heart throughout my life, so I want to leave them all in the form of game works, regardless of whether they will see them in the past.<br/><br/>Even if there are friends who can play our games, and even if they can instantly recall the former one, I think this work is also valuable.<br/><br/>Due to limited funding, the game presentation was not perfect and somewhat rough, but with a certain intention and desire, I thought about it and had the ability to do it. That's all.<br/><br/>Dedicated to all brothers who have had similar emotional experiences.<br/><br/>Finally, I dedicate myself to the girls who have appeared in my life before. (CY, YYY, ZQ, NHT), Wishing you always be loved.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mizeria</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2527360/Mizeria/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2527360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Find A Way Out</strong></h2><br/>A renowned archer Nuoli, embarks on a journey to escape from a mysterious castle. <br/><br/>Mizeria is a short game where you need to climb a giant tower with the help of your bow and a friendly spirit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Game Features</strong></h2><br/>-Simple game where you just have to climb out of a tower.<br/><br/>-Fun little bow, that can aid your climbing journey.<br/><br/>- Retro late 90's graphics. All the graphics from the early 5th gen era, with modern controls for smooth yet atmospheric gameplay.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>极简塔防 - Minimalist Tower Defense</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2617400/__Minimalist_Tower_Defense/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							They are... approching...<br/>Surging...<br/>...<br/>Today...<br/>...<h2 class="bb_tag"> Gameplay </h2>Collect resources and establish a defense line before dark<br/>And then Facing countless enemies<h2 class="bb_tag"> Game features </h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 40+distinctive Towers, almost every type has unique upgrades!<br/></li><li> 40+meticulously designed levels, 40+challenges that combine difficulty and fun!<br/></li><li> Countless enemies<br/></li><li> Minimalist design style, user-friendly gameplay, diverse difficulty levels</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"> Contact us </h2>Email: <a href="mailto:HappyFairy213@outlook.com">HappyFairy213@outlook.com</a><br/>Discord: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F35UaVRXQrB" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/35UaVRXQrB</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomorrow's Love Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2726890/Tomorrows_Love_Puzzle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							《Tomorrow's Love Puzzle》is an interactive live-action video game where you step into the shoes of a workplace employee named "Tomorrow". Harbored with life aspirations, you've been relentlessly trampled over in five years of working life. Yet, fortune smiles upon you as six beautiful women arrive in succession, immersing you in a first-person perspective love story.<br/><br/>The quiet and gentle school beauty, "Chu Chu".<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726890/extras/chuchu.gif?t=1706241010"><br/>The sexy and mature client, a female boss named "Jin Xiao".<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726890/extras/jinxiao.gif?t=1706241010"><br/>The mysterious girl, "Ni Keer".<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726890/extras/nikeer.gif?t=1706241010"><br/>The intellectual and stable baking teacher, "Yu Anran".<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726890/extras/yuanran.gif?t=1706241010"><br/>The straightforward and cheerful lifeguard, "Wang Yiman".<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726890/extras/wangyiman.gif?t=1706241010"><br/>The cute and kind childhood friend, "Tian Tiantian".<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726890/extras/tiantiantian.gif?t=1706241010"><br/><br/>Product Features:<br/>• A novel live-action interactive game, experience immersive love stories with six distinct women from the male protagonist's subjective perspective. Who you end up with is up to "you" in front of the screen.<br/>• Unlike other romance games, we offer not only excellent film materials but also delve deeper into gameplay. Based on the storyline, players can chat with the heroines, view their social circles, and engage in other gameplay to understand more about the plot's periphery, deeply interacting with the heroines.<br/>• As the friendship level increases, the real past of the heroines will be unlocked, with more background stories awaiting your exploration.<br/>• We'll automatically tag exciting videos and pictures for easy browsing.<br/>• Unlock six uniquely styled girls - a cold and noble witch, an elegant and contrasting senior, an energetic straight-shooter sports girl, a cute and adorable girl-next-door, and a mysterious and ever-changing young lady. There's a type of warmth that will strike directly at your heart, and your love stories with them begin tomorrow...<br/><br/>Game Production and Theme:<br/>This game is produced by Youyuan Media, in collaboration with Youku Video and San Zhi Xi Que Media. It is the first game jointly developed with a mainstream video platform. In this era of frequent interactive video products, we aim to create a "different" product, offering men a top-tier emotional value themed on freedom and pure love. After months of development, we assembled a team including well-known scriptwriters, directors, and game production experts.<br/>The male protagonist is a humble office worker, repeatedly oppressed in five years of working life, facing his boss's manipulations and colleagues' squeezes - a true reflection of what many of us experience daily. Fortunately, he meets six charming but different women, bringing endless color and joy to his otherwise dull life. We hope that if you're trapped in life and work, you will find some comfort and joy here.<br/><br/>A Few Words from the Heart:<br/>Our team worked hard to polish a good story. The producers, directors, and scriptwriters argued daily over the plot to select the perfect heroines that cater to different players' aesthetic preferences from over 500 acting resumes. It turns out everyone has different tastes! To find a more authentic feeling of love, the game developers racked their brains to develop gameplay. Everything we do is to find "that soft spot in your heart", regardless of whether the person beside you now is right or wrong, or whatever your circumstances may be. We want to tell you that no matter what choice you make, tomorrow will be better.<br/><br/>About Youyuan:<br/>We are a group of young people from all over the country, with various specialties and personalities, gathered in Shanghai, dreaming of games and art. We aim to capture beautiful moments through the lens and games, delivering sweet feelings of love and freedom to our users.<br/>This is our first game, and we hope you like it.<br/><br/>Official QQ Group: 913764459						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild Legion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2359760/Wild_Legion/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2359760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Wilderness Calls!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Embark on an epic adventure in the wilderness, where you'll brandish an arsenal of unique weapons, clash with hordes of formidable enemies, and amass precious materials and gold coins.</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2359760/extras/WL-Steam-Title-Craft.png?t=1706238848"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2359760/extras/WL_-_Crafting_-_Steam_-_ENG.gif?t=1706238848"><br/><strong>Gather</strong> wood to <strong>Build</strong> mighty <strong>Towers</strong> that will serve as your last line of defense. Use more wood to upgrade or repair towers. Or craft many bombs to BOOM enemies out of existence<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2359760/extras/WL-Steam-Title-Upgrades.png?t=1706238848"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2359760/extras/WL_-_Steam_-_Upgrades.gif?t=1706238848"><strong>Gold coins = EXP</strong>. <br/><strong>Kill enemies</strong> to <strong>get coins</strong> to <strong>level up</strong> and buy stats, weapons, or buffs. Wield <strong>multiple weapons</strong> — melee, ranged, and magic. Upgrade weapons and spells to MAX and buy related BUFF to unlock S-Rank synergies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2359760/extras/WL-Steam-Titles_4_ENG.png?t=1706238848"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2359760/extras/WL_Day-Night_Steam.gif?t=1706238848"><br/>Gather resources by <strong>DAY</strong>, when orcs target you. Protect the Moon Tower by <strong>NIGHT</strong> from the 4-side siege. During the day more resources appear, and orcs only target you. But during the night when the Moon Tower rises, orcs attack it and you need to <strong>build protective towers</strong> around it!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2359760/extras/WL-Steam-Title-Animals.png?t=1706238848"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2359760/extras/WL_Steam_Animal.gif?t=1706238848"><strong>Take the lost animal running in circles to the teleport</strong> to escape the orc invasion. In return, <strong>they will grant you special gifts</strong>!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2359760/extras/WL-Steam-Titles-Meta.png?t=1706238848"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2359760/extras/WL-Meta-Steam.gif?t=1706238848"><br/>Kill Bosses and elites to get a chance to receive gems. Then spend gems to increase your stats OR buy new towers.<br/><br/><i>We took big inspiration from Brotato, Noobs want to live, and Don't Starve. If you like the results of our efforts, please wishlist the game!</i><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FfQuNTcBrgV" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><strong>We are always available on Discord</strong> </a><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2359760/Wild_Legion/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2359760/Wild_Legion/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party Business Supreme</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2703940/Party_Business_Supreme/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are a cake working for Party Business Inc.<br>
<br>
Collect presents for the big client. Avoid forks that try to eat you, because you are a cake. Once you have collected the presents, you must deliver them to the big client.<br>
<br>
Your boss, Mr. Business, will evaluate your performance.<br>
<br>
Play on three distinct maps, each having three game modes: vanilla, survival, and a special mode for each map. Use keyboard or joystick to move around the map and collect presents while avoiding forks.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man in the Dark</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2694920/Man_in_the_Dark/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Man in the Dark</strong> is a dark-feeling third-person shooter, single-play game that realistically depicts the earth's apocalyptic feeling, set in a human race that has been turned into a place where zombies and monsters are rampant due to people's wrong choices, and doesn't require much learning and you have to kill and survive all the zombies and monsters that appear. <br/><br/>Once busy factories, quiet villages, beautiful lakes and remote deserts are in the dark of death, but please join me in the struggle of one person who cannot give up on life.<br/><br/><strong>Main function</strong><br/><br/>- <strong>Unique maps</strong> : 'Abandoned Warehouse, Creepy Town, Rainy Village, Mysterious Fog, Desert of Monster Creatures, and Abandoned Slums' Days and Nights' show a mankind covered with fear and dark.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694920/extras/slum.gif?t=1706258088"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694920/extras/creepy.gif?t=1706258088"><br/><br/>Each map has its own unique atmosphere, and there are many different elements to overcome in order to clear. The first map is open by default, and the next map is opened when you clear the previous map.<br/><br/>- <strong>Various weapons</strong> : Each map basically provides 3 kinds guns and grenades. The 3 kinds of guns are configured to match the characteristics of the map and can be used by changing them using a wheelboard.<br/><br/>- <strong>Equipment</strong> : Certain darkened maps are given Night Vision, Thermal Scope, Flashlight, Hands Flares, etc. to gain visibility.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694920/extras/darkness.gif?t=1706258088"><br/><br/>- <strong>Horrifying atmosphere</strong> : Humans who have turned from the darkness of the end to zombies, mysterious creatures and monsters whose is unknown, and infected dogs.. The realistic expression is even more frightening.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694920/extras/desert.gif?t=1706258088"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694920/extras/mist.gif?t=1706258088"><br/><br/>- <strong>Customizing character</strong> : Player can choose a variety of costumes or change the color of each part.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694920/extras/character.gif?t=1706258088"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kagura Genesis: Kuon's Story</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668840/Kagura_Genesis_Kuons_Story/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Turn-based combat. Roguelike adventure!<br/></li><li>Adjustable difficulty for the right challenge.<br/></li><li>Shop, upgrade, and top up your youkai's powers.<br/></li><li>Master and summon many kinds of youkai for combat.<br/></li><li>10+ hours of story and gameplay.</li></ul><br/>Kagura Genesis is a brand new series of replayable roguelike RPGs!<h2 class="bb_tag">CHARACTER</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668840/extras/chara01_eng.png?t=1706230933"><br/>Kuon Makami (Voice: Hanami Takanashi)<br/><br/>A girl who lives in a mountain shrine, secluded from the mortal world. Cheerful, straightforward, and pure of heart, she hasn’t encountered another human being since her mother died, which has left her remarkably naive.<br/><br/>Luckily, she’s also a demigod, sired by the deity Makami-no-Okami, and trained in swordsmanship and other arts by her mother, an exorcist miko. Although a newcomer to the realm of exorcism, her bloodline lends her impressive potential—if she can only learn to harness it.<h2 class="bb_tag">SUMMARY</h2>In a quiet forest, far from any settlement, there lives a girl named Kuon Makami.<br/>Having lost her mother not long ago, she spends her days alone with the wolf pup who is her best friend.<br/>But the peaceful times come to an end when a strange pall falls over the forest, bringing with it occasional incursions of dark spirits.<br/>Determined to find the source of the problem and stop it, Kuon begins training as an exorcist shrine maiden and sets out to brave whatever dangers lie within the depths of the woods...						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AuraRhythm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668470/AuraRhythm/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							🌟 <strong>Welcome to AuraRhythm - Immerse Yourself in Sonic Splendor</strong>! 🌟<br/><br/>Unleash the power of your music with AuraRhythm, the ultimate audio visualizer that transforms your listening experience into a mesmerizing symphony of sight and sound. Immerse yourself in a kaleidoscope of vibrant visuals that dance and pulse in perfect harmony with the beats, bringing your music to life like never before.<br/><br/>🎵 Synced Sensation: AuraRhythm ingeniously syncs with any audio playing through your device, effortlessly translating every beat, note, and melody into a breathtaking visual spectacle. Watch as pulsating waves, dynamic colors, and intricate patterns unfold in real-time, creating a unique and personalized light show tailored to your favorite tunes.<br/><br/>👁️ Visual Brilliance: Immerse yourself in a stunning array of visuals, ranging from hypnotic waveforms to intricate geometric patterns. AuraRhythm offers a spectrum of customization options, allowing you to tailor the visual experience to your preferences. Whether you prefer a subtle ambient glow or a vibrant explosion of colors, the power is in your hands.<br/><br/>🔗 Seamless Integration: With AuraRhythm, there's no need to configure complex settings or navigate through intricate menus. Simply launch the application, and let it seamlessly integrate with your audio output, effortlessly transforming your room into a dynamic audio-visual oasis.<br/><br/>🎨 Express Yourself: Customize your experience with a variety of themes and color schemes, ensuring that AuraRhythm reflects your unique style and mood. Whether you're hosting a chill session, an energetic party, or a focused work environment, AuraRhythm adapts to the rhythm of your life.<br/><br/>🌐 Universal Compatibility: AuraRhythm works with any audio source playing through your device, making it the perfect companion for music streaming, gaming, or any other audio-related activities. Immerse yourself in the visual symphony, no matter the content.<br/><br/>⚙️ Easy Setup: Getting started is a breeze with AuraRhythm. Simply download, install, and watch as your audio comes to life in a mesmerizing display of light and color. No technical expertise required – just plug and play!<br/><br/>Elevate your audio journey with AuraRhythm – where sound meets spectacle, and every note is a visual masterpiece. Dive into the rhythm, embrace the aura, and let the music take you on a visual voyage like never before. Experience AuraRhythm today!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1706225179"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1706225179"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1706225179"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1706225179"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1706225179"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1706225179"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1706225179"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1706225179"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1706225179"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1706225179"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1706225179"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1706225179"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shenanigans</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1936640/Shenanigans/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1936640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Let the Shenanigans Begin!</h2><br/>The Evil Dr. Wector has taken the Great Sunflower’s Sun Energy for his evil plan and now it is up to you to get it all back! Join the four hooligans, Simon, Sebrina, Rae, and Beast, in a wacky and goofy 2D adventure!<h2 class="bb_tag">A Wild 2D Adventure!</h2><br/>From the mind of The Escaped Mental Patient, John Coday, explore a world of goofy characters and zany places created by Mythos Makers and Co. Run, Jump, Wall Run, and Swing Your Hammer as you go through beautiful levels and take down enemies along the way. You can run through all the levels or take your time. Take advantage of the smooth and fast paced 2D platforming giving you ultimate control of the adventure! Explore the world or speed through to save it! The choice is yours!<h2 class="bb_tag">A wacky cast of Characters</h2><br/>Play as one of four nut cases. The bat wielding madman, Simon. His violent hamer swinging sister, Sebrina. A kind witch named Rae, and her empty headed magical creature, Beast.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caught On Camera</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2526500/Caught_On_Camera/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2526500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dive into <strong>Caught on Camera</strong>, a chilling simulation where you play as a security guard monitoring surveillance in a world where the paranormal becomes your reality. Your task is to observe and report strange occurrences, differentiating between mere glitches and true otherworldly events. As you flag anomalies for the system to fix, each shift becomes a test of nerve and attention, challenging you to maintain your sanity amidst the unexplainable. Are you ready to confront what lies beyond the screens?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking For Cats In a Badly Drawn City</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2772430/Looking_For_Cats_In_a_Badly_Drawn_City/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Welcome to the badly drawn town where the kittens hide!</strong></h2><br/>Explore the amazing corners of a city full of jagged lines and curved outlines. Your goal is to find <strong>100 cats</strong> hidden in the most unexpected places!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772430/extras/FlyGif.gif?t=1706216401"><br/><br/>Make your way through the streets and alleyways, looking for cat silhouettes on the roofs and windows of skyscrapers. Listen for magical purrs and follow tails flickering through the clouds!<br/><br/>Look for cats in parks with their mysterious trees, under bridges and in the most unexpected places, but be careful, some cats will turn their backs on you and you will only be able to spot them by their silhouette.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772430/extras/Cats.png?t=1706216401"><br/><br/>Use your imagination and keen eye to spot all the cats in the most unusual situations.<br/><br/><br/><a href="http://store.steampowered.com/developer/lostvolbytesgames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772430/extras/SubscribeToPublisher.png?t=1706216401"/></a> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bit's Escape</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2769260/The_Bits_Escape/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2769260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bit's is a small machine built in a underground factory, his dream is to escape and discover life beyond what is below the earth.<br>
<br>
A platform game with simple controls and dynamic gameplay.<br>
<br>
Throughout the adventure, Bit will run, jump over obstacles, utilize a double jump to overcome even larger obstacles, employ the ability to boost in the air to dodge traps, and much more in pursuit of freedom.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panda?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2768730/Panda/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2768730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a game where you select two panels and match the same pictures.<br/>Let's compete for the best time without getting confused by small differences.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2768730/extras/panda_616x353.png?t=1706214293"><br/>Select two panels.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2768730/extras/スクリーンショット_2024-01-10_235658.png?t=1706214293"><br/>Match the same panels to erase them.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2768730/extras/スクリーンショット_2024-01-10_235720.png?t=1706214293"><br/>Erase all panels as quickly as possible.<br/>Compete for your personal best.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2768730/extras/スクリーンショット_2024-01-10_235857.png?t=1706214293"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jett Rider</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2505250/Jett_Rider/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505250/extras/03-1.gif?t=1706208374"><br/><br/>Jett Rider, the most unlikely hero stars in the biggest 2D adventure of the year. Save the planet Gravos, free its people, face the toughest bosses... And don't forget to recycle!<br/><br/>A collision in the orbit of the planet Gravos is the starting point of an unforgettable adventure with tons of fun and love for the classics. Jett, the space sweeper, was only supposed to pick up the wreckage of the AC-137 cargo ship, but he soon discovered that something messy was brewing on the surface of Gravos.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505250/extras/06-1.gif?t=1706208374"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2></strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Shooter action, exploration, lots of humor and impressive bosses.<br/></li><li>Upgrade your jetpack and skills to reach unexplored areas of Gravos.<br/></li><li>Make money by recycling space debris.<br/></li><li>Expand your arsenal and choose your favorite weapon.<br/></li><li>Collect the Golden Idols and exchange them for unique items at the Peach Store.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505250/extras/wish_game.gif?t=1706208374"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505250/extras/maincol_gradient_rule.png?t=1706208374"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">MORE AMAZING VIDEOGAMES PUBLISHED BY JANDUSOFT</h2></strong><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2252680?utm_source=steam&amp;utm_campaign=descrip" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505250/extras/Farlands100.png?t=1706208374"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2103370?utm_source=steam&amp;utm_campaign=descrip" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505250/extras/finis100.png?t=1706208374"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2295610?utm_source=steam&amp;utm_campaign=descrip" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505250/extras/Abathor100.png?t=1706208374"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2387460?utm_source=steam&amp;utm_campaign=descrip" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505250/extras/Aureole100.png?t=1706208374"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1191660?utm_source=steam&amp;utm_campaign=descrip" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505250/extras/Rebel100.png?t=1706208374"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2095510?utm_source=steam&amp;utm_campaign=descrip" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505250/extras/Scholar100.png?t=1706208374"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505250/extras/maincol_gradient_rule.png?t=1706208374"><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fjandusoft" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505250/extras/discord.png?t=1706208374"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Grounds</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2402450/Zero_Grounds/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2402450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FDuvuj9JymU" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2402450/extras/Discord_purple.gif?t=1706208354"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2402450/extras/DOMINATE_IN_ZEROGRAVITY.gif?t=1706208354"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2402450/extras/MOVE_FASTER_WITH_A_JETPACK.gif?t=1706208354"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2402450/extras/BE_THE_QUICKEST_GUN_AROUND.gif?t=1706208354"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2402450/extras/COLLECT_HEADSHOTS.gif?t=1706208354"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2402450/extras/UNLOCK_BY_PLAYING,_NOT_PAYING-.gif?t=1706208354"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2402450/extras/Individualize_your_loadout.gif?t=1706208354"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2402450/extras/feel_the_low-poly_vibes.gif?t=1706208354"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2402450/extras/TEAM_UP,_MAKE_FRIENDS_AND_WIN.gif?t=1706208354"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaaaaAAaaaAAAaaAAAAaAAAAA!!! Remastered</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1372460/AaaaaAAaaaAAAaaAAAAaAAAAA_Remastered/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1372460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You're a skydiving, video-streaming guerilla artist in the floating city of Boston High. Your job is to leap from buildings, cause mischief, and not get caught by the police.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Grab Bag of Incredible Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Leap from mile-high skyscrapers.<br/></li><li> Kiss the sides of buildings with your mouth.<br/></li><li> There's, like, a parade with giant balloon floats on one level, and you can smack into them, ruining everything, just to be a jerk.<br/></li><li> Also, there's a level with a giant 4-story cake that you can topple over hapless spectators.<br/></li><li> We're experimenting with a thing where you're also able to break the city's wastewater storage systems, but you'd kinda have to be a double jerk to do it.<br/></li><li> Over 0 levels included in the full game!<br/></li><li> 0 weapons, unless you count the spray paint you use to tag windows.<br/></li><li> Unique, challenging, and other meaningless adjectives that every game uses to describe themselves.<br/></li><li> How many bullet points do you want, buddy?<br/></li><li> 'Cause here's another one.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Did You Know?</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> This is our follow-up to the original, award-winning series.<br/></li><li> The original is in the Guinness World Records for longest word in a video game title.<br/></li><li> It also broke Steam because the title was way long.<br/></li><li> And it won a bunch of awards. Some, for publications and conventions that don't exist anymore. Ten years is a long time.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNDERDOGS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2441700/UNDERDOGS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_Title.gif?t=1706205754"><br/><br/>Wrap yourself in 5 tons of metal and go smashing through a dark scene of UNDERGROUND MECH FIGHTS! Bash, crush, maul and rip apart enemy bots and mechs.<br/><br/><u><strong>IT’S FULL-ON METAL-ON-METAL VIOLENCE IN THIS PHYSICS-BASED MECH BRAWLER!</strong></u><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_Smooch.gif?t=1706205754"><br/><br/>But rampaging through the pits ain’t all - <u><strong>THIS IS A ROGUELIKE.</strong></u><br/>Gear up with 120+ items including power tools to customize your mech, meet 30+ characters, hire hackers and saboteurs, hustle and deal with the gangsters and psychos who run these streets as you claw your way up the food chain.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_DF_Pan.gif?t=1706205754"><br/><br/>This city is a dog-eat-dog shit show, but luckily you ain't alone.<br/>Your little bruv King is in your corner - hacking your enemies and giving you lip while you fight like a wild animal, smashing car sized pit bots that wanna kill you dead to the deafening roars of the blood thirsty crowds.<br/><br/><strong>This is New Brakka - The Mech Fighting Capital of the World.<br/>This is UNDERDOGS.<br/><br/>Welcome to the jungle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_Dem_Clean.gif?t=1706205754"/></strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Fine Tourney</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2523500/One_Fine_Tourney/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2523500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2523500/extras/OFT_LaunchTrailer_2023_GIFS_Normal_00_sm.gif?t=1706205717"><br/><br/><strong>Casual Archery Puzzles</strong><br/>Embark on archery escapades across a whimsical world following the adventures of five different protagonists.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2523500/extras/OFT_LaunchTrailer_2023_GIFS_Dragon_00_sm.gif?t=1706205717"><br/><br/><strong>Handcrafted Levels With Unique Challenges</strong><br/>Conquer strategies for over 40 handcrafted stages and unlock achievements, characters and levels on your way to win the big tournament.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2523500/extras/OFT_LaunchTrailer_2023_GIFS_Goofball_00_sm.gif?t=1706205717"><br/><br/><strong>Quirky Dialogue</strong><br/>Stroll through walkable levels and connect with the locals.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2523500/extras/OFT_LaunchTrailer_2023_GIFS_Platform_00_sm.gif?t=1706205717"><br/><br/><strong>Little Slices of Life</strong><br/>Unlock cozy dioramas and charming lore through achievements and story progression.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2523500/extras/OFT_LaunchTrailer_2023_GIFS_Campfire_00_sm.gif?t=1706205717"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Core Devourer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2199060/Core_Devourer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2199060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2199060/extras/AboutTheGame.gif?t=1706236255"><br/><i>Core Devourer</i> is a sci-fi action-packed roguelite where you hunt down huge hordes of droids and absorb their cores to become the strongest cybernetic being on the planet. In this game, you unlock weapons with unique effects, craft powerful gear and create endless combinations of upgrades for your character. Explore the procedural environment and discover the secrets of this apocalyptic world.<br/>Make your choice and break the game.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2199060/extras/CreateBuilds.gif?t=1706236255"><br/>Each weapon is unique and has special features. Choose from hundreds of unique upgrades and create game-breaking builds.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2199060/extras/FightBosses.gif?t=1706236255"><br/>Destroy huge hordes of droids that want to absorb your powerful core and fight bosses with unique patterns!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2199060/extras/Unlock.gif?t=1706236255"><br/>Complete achievements and farm resources by exploring the map, killing enemies and absorbing the cores of defeated bosses to unlock and craft new weapons, power-ups and gear for your character.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2199060/Core_Devourer/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2199060/Core_Devourer/</a><h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>UNIQUE WEAPONS.</strong> Choose from a huge selection of weapons with unique powers.<br/></li><li><strong>PROCEDURAL MAPS.</strong> Explore the diverse and procedural world of <i>Core Devourer</i>.<br/></li><li><strong>ENDLESS POWER-UPS.</strong> Try out every power-up and their infinite combinations. Find the best game-breaking builds.<br/></li><li><strong>SATISFYING PROGRESS.</strong> Upgrade your character with gear and augmentations.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIN: The Last Child</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1960070/RIN_The_Last_Child/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/extras/SAVE_kopia.png?t=1706205624"><br/><i>Play as RIN, the last child of the Creator, on a journey to restore order in a mystical world. Collect aspects and runes, craft spells, and confront powerful bosses - your transformed siblings. The fate of the world rests in your hands.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/extras/drive.png?t=1706205624"><br/>The story of RIN, her siblings, and their Creator, the Teller of Tales, was inspired by the well-known ancient myth about Cronus and his conflict with his children. It also touches upon the overall passing of gods who must be replaced by new gods. <strong>The creation myths</strong> seemed to match perfectly Metroidvania's dark fairy tale - no trace of man, but the importance of magic. An important motif and another layer of the script is the conflict between being obedient to authority - the father (the Creator) or freedom - the free will and responsibility for oneself and one's decisions. The story offers different possible endings based on your choices.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/extras/REKINDLE_kopia.png?t=1706205624"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/extras/gif1.gif?t=1706205624"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/extras/craft.png?t=1706205624"><br/>There are<strong> 18 elemental spells</strong> from three categories: attack (10), defense (5), and utility (3).<br/>The spells are created of Aspects of Magic (5) and Spell Patterns. Then, they can be enchanted with a currency by Lesser Runes (adding more damage) or upgraded by an upgrade scheme and Great Runes (changing the effect). The quick slot allows assigning 3 spells at a time but gives an option to quickly swap to another spell set. Mathematically, considering the combination of Lesser Runes, Great Runes, and Upgrades, there are as many as <strong>7776 spells variants</strong>. As you progress, the spells can be disassembled in order to use the aspects components for another assembly. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/extras/gif2.gif?t=1706205624"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1960070/extras/fight.png?t=1706205624"><br/>On your exploration journey, you will <strong>fight many small creatures</strong> formed from their locations such as Slimes, Mosquitoes, but also bigger creepy beasts like Rats or Spitting Plants. The main fights though, will not only require a neat set of spells and skills but most importantly the decisions to take based on your will. As RIN, the sixth child of the Creator, you will<strong> confront five bosses</strong> - your unknown siblings.<br/><br/>The fate of the world rests in your hands. Can you save everyone?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elements For Money</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2766500/Elements_For_Money/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cause reactions, discover new elements, and gain gold for your efforts in Elements For Money!<br/><br/>Every turn, you can move your elements around and get a new one from the shop. Adjacent elements can react to form new elements or provide gold bonuses for being next to other elements.<br/><br/>Get enough gold before payment to stay in the game, and obtain a high total gold count to get as high of a rank as you can.<br/><strong><br/>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>90+ elements to discover!<br/></li><li>~1000 reactions to cause!<br/></li><li>Playable with mouse and/or keyboard (support for both)!<br/></li><li>A randomized shop for roguelike gameplay!<br/></li><li>A variety of strategies to get high profit!<br/></li><li>Gold to gain!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766500/extras/Lava_Gif.gif?t=1706205612"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
