<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>American Truck Simulator - Kansas</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2298430/American_Truck_Simulator__Kansas/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2298430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Introducing Kansas! A U.S State that is home to a truly authentic cowboy culture and miles of land littered with wildflowers. Located in the Midwest of the USA, Kansas is known for its native grasslands, streams, abundant blue skies, and green grassland vistas. <br/><br/>Once considered to be the country’s agricultural heartland, "The Sunflower State" has managed to attract many large businesses and develop in other industrial areas due to its central location and convenient infrastructure for logistics operations. But, as the nickname suggests, nature is certainly doing very well to keep up with technological progress, as the state parks and vast prairies offer unique views with a marvelous atmosphere that will leave every trucker passing by with something to remember.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Deliver to 14 explorable cities including Kansas City, Wichita, or Topeka<br/></li><li>See several landmarks unique to Kansas such as the historic Dodge City, Monument Rocks, and Mount Sunflower<br/></li><li>Become a trucker transporting goods for Kansas' key industries - Salt Mine, Food Factory, Car Factory, Building Material Factory, and Battery Factory<br/></li><li>Deliver cargo to Aerosystem, playing a key role in Wichita's aerospace industry<br/></li><li>Visit Hutchinson and admire the world's largest silos<br/></li><li>Play a crucial role in one of America's largest agricultural states. Transport goods that sustain Kansas' farming legacy<br/></li><li>Enjoy trucking through several scenic towns (settlements)<br/></li><li>Drive through expansive prairies, providing unforgettable views</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Truck Simulator - Farm Machinery</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2638630/American_Truck_Simulator__Farm_Machinery/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Saddle up drivers, because the Farm Machinery DLC for American Truck Simulator has arrived! Transport everything from trusty tractors to forage harvesters across scenic virtual highways and roads. <br/><br/>Featuring 2 in-game brands, Owl &amp; Greenler, you'll be able to deliver a variety of unique cargoes on Lowboy, Dropdeck or Flatbed trailers to a number of agriculture-related industries large and small across the country.<br/><br/>This DLC includes:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Sprayer <br/></li><li>Crawler Tractor <br/></li><li>Forage Harvester <br/></li><li>Fertilizer Spreader <br/></li><li>Grain Trailer<br/></li><li>Autonomous Tractor <br/></li><li>Hay Baler <br/></li><li>Seeding Unit <br/></li><li>Disc Harrow</li></ul><br/>Naturally, we couldn't let you go driving without some themed cabin accessories for your cabin either! <br/><br/>Cabin Accessories<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Lunch Kit<br/></li><li>Scarecrow <br/></li><li>Straw Hat <br/></li><li>Stuffed Autonomous Tractor <br/></li><li>Harvester Toy </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turok 3: Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1996770/Turok_3_Shadow_of_Oblivion_Remastered/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/raptor_jumps.gif?t=1701367237"><br/><br/><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> is a faithful restoration of the classic first-person shooter originally released in 2000 for the Nintendo 64, upgraded through Nightdive Studios’ proprietary KEX Engine for play on modern gaming devices with up to a 4K resolution at 120FPS. <br/><br/>It joins Nightdive Studios and Universal Games popular Turok and Turok 2: Seeds of Evil remasters, capping off the trilogy. <i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> features upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<h2 class="bb_tag">FINISH THE HUNT</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/sniper_one_eye.gif?t=1701367237"><br/><br/><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> is the first title from Nightdive Studios to be remastered using the latest version KEX engine, which utilizes an improved renderer to achieve a higher tier of visual fidelity across 3D models, textures, and graphical effects.<h2 class="bb_tag"><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> Key Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A remastered version of the 2000 classic, available for the first time since its Nintendo 64 release<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS performance<br/></li><li>Advanced rendering features, including anti-aliasing, bloom, ambient occlusion, dynamic shadows, and motion blur	<br/></li><li>Remastered environment art, character models, and updated weapon models<br/></li><li>Brand new Achievements</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/robot.gif?t=1701367237"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinball M</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2337640/Pinball_M/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-1.png?t=1701360173"><br/><br/>The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-2.png?t=1701360173"><br/><br/>- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free<br/>- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage<br/>- Thrilling competition<br/>- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation<h2 class="bb_tag">Sink your teeth into these tables as purchasable DLC: </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">- Chucky's Killer Pinball:</h2> Step into a twisted realm where the innocent becomes sinister, and the playful turns menacing. Navigate through an eerie playfield where Chucky lurks in the shadows, ready to pounce.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Dead by Daylight™️ Pinball:</h2> Become the hunter or even the hunted in a thrilling fusion of classic pinball and the excitement of one of the most popular horror games ever created.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Duke Nukem's Big Shot Pinball:</h2> Enjoy the biggest, grooviest, most BADASS pinball table ever made packed with guns and babes. Push start and play with balls of steel!<h2 class="bb_tag">- The Thing Pinball: </h2>Use your pinball skills and battle against the shape-shifting alien through the arctic chill of U.S. Outpost #31. Can you trust anyone, even yourself?<br/>- Even more coming...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-4.png?t=1701360173"><br/><br/>Wishlist and find out more.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius - Drukhari</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668040/Warhammer_40000_Gladius__Drukhari/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<i>“What was it like, back then? Just sheer joy, I’m told. Entire civilizations, rendered down for stimulants. Stars drained dry of their power, for a decade-long soiree. Oh, to have been alive and powerful in the last days of Empire - before She-Who-Thirsts…” </i><br/>- Gyrthineus Roche, former Archon of The Last Blade.<br/><br/>The <strong>Drukhari </strong>are an ancient race that fell into degeneracy and depravity, with their remnants only surviving in immense Webway cities. Though they have suppressed the psychic power of their Aeldari kin, they have replaced it with preternatural agility and rapacious cruelty. Their lighting raids from the Webway carry off wealth and captives to dark Commorragh where they suffer intensely throughout their short lives…<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Mechanics </h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Power from Pain</strong>: As pain spreads across the battlefield, Drukhari are invigorated, thriving from the suffering. Their units gain additional bonuses depending on their experience level. <br/></li><li><strong>Corsair Outposts</strong>: The Drukhari rarely venture outside the webway, save to loot realspace resources. Their cities have a reduced growth rate, but it can be improved by controlling more outposts. <br/></li><li><strong>Raid from the Webway</strong>: The Drukhari strike swiftly from the webway, before vanishing with their plunder. Pay influence to create temporary portals and activate webway gates to move your raiding party across the map.<br/></li><li><strong>Raider Fortress</strong>: The Aeldari and Drukhari are forever battling over their access to the webway. Found cities on activated webway gates from which you can unleash your forces on Gladius Prime.<br/></li><li><strong>Soul Hunger</strong>: The souls harvested by the Drukhari are an invaluable resource used for their malevolent schemes. Destroying an enemy unit rewards you with influence that can be traded for economic boosts and combat effects. <br/></li><li><strong>Combat Drugs</strong>: The Drukhari’s foul Haemonculi render down some captives into powerful stimulants. Infantry units can pay with influence and hitpoints for temporary buffs that allow them to outperform their opponents. <br/></li><li><strong>Betrayal Culture</strong>: Drukhari are a vicious race, and only a huge display of riches will convince them to serve—as long as it also serves their interests. Drukhari cities have lower loyalty but gathering influence grants more loyalty. <br/></li><li><strong>Blade Artists</strong>: Blades have an omnipresent place in Drukhari culture, and each commorrite learns this from a young age. Drukhari units get bonus armour penetration in melee. <br/></li><li><strong>Raiders tactics</strong>: When attacking a new prey world, the Drukhari attack en masse from their specially designed vehicles to land troops as close as possible to the fighting. Drukhari transports are all assault transports and Drukhari infantry units can gain combat bonuses when disembarking.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Complete Units Roster </h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Archon <br/></li><li>Cronos<br/></li><li>Haemonculus<br/></li><li>Hellions<br/></li><li>Incubi <br/></li><li>Kabalite Trueborn<br/></li><li>Kabalite Warriors<br/></li><li>Raider<br/></li><li>Ravager<br/></li><li>Razorwing Jetfighter<br/></li><li>Reavers<br/></li><li>Scourges<br/></li><li>Succubus<br/></li><li>Tantalus<br/></li><li>Venom<br/></li><li>Voidraven Bomber<br/></li><li>Webway Portal<br/></li><li>Wracks<br/></li><li>Wyches</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truck &amp; Logistics Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/873840/Truck__Logistics_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Load, drive, and deliver through a huge open world with up to 24 players in cross-platform multiplayer. Join your friends in exciting heavy transport convoys. Jump into the driver's seat of more than 30 unique vehicles and carry out complex loading tasks to deliver a variety of cargo.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Load.gif?t=1701358833"><br/><br/><strong>Load pallets, containers, vehicles &amp; more!</strong><br/>Each mission is unique and comes with its own challenges. Start up your business by loading pallets into vans with a forklift. Then work your way up to loading heavy containers with telescopic handlers onto trailers. Maneuver vehicles such as cars, forklifts, skid-steers, wheel-loaders and more onto your trailers. Hundreds of unique and challenging missions and deliveries await you! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Drive.gif?t=1701358833"><br/><br/><strong>Drive cars, vans, trucks &amp; more!</strong><br/>Drive and customize over 30 unique vehicles. From minivans to heavy trucks, each vehicle has its own detailed interior and realistic driving physics. Vehicles can be damaged, causing axles to bend and making driving difficult. Refuel and repair at service stations to get back on the road in full swing. Make each vehicle your own by customizing it to your liking. Stick to the traffic rules or risk getting fined in random police traffic controls and radar speed cameras. Push your driving skills to the limit in many diverse and challenging missions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Deliver.gif?t=1701358833"><br/><br/><strong>Deliver in an open world with up to 24 friends!</strong><br/>Enjoy the ultimate delivery experience in co-op multiplayer. Join your friends, make convoys, earn money and expand your companies together. Escort other players safely to their destinations using specialized convoy equipment. Explore a vast 28 km² open world, from bustling cities to tranquil rural areas. Explore and uncover hidden secrets scattered across the map. Get ready for a journey into a dynamic and completely open world where the deliveries never end!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 30 unique vehicles with realistic interiors<br/></li><li>Huge 28km² open world (no hidden walls!)<br/></li><li>Cross-platform multiplayer with up to 24 players<br/></li><li>Escort convoys in co-op multiplayer missions<br/></li><li>Full day / night cycle<br/></li><li>Hundreds of different challenging missions<br/></li><li>Realistic driving physics and damage system<br/></li><li>Vehicle customization<br/></li><li>Random police traffic controls &amp; speed cameras</li></ul><br/>Start your company today! Join our community below, see you on the road!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FPCjxFjs" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Discord_2023.gif?t=1701358833"/></a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jurassic World Evolution 2: Cretaceous Predator Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2610980/Jurassic_World_Evolution_2_Cretaceous_Predator_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Introduce four ferocious new predators to your parks with Jurassic World Evolution 2: Cretaceous Predator Pack. Manage and control these striking dinosaurs as they fight for dominance in your parks and search for their next meal. Unveil the true power of the Cretaceous period to your park guests.<h2 class="bb_tag">Welcome the following extraordinary species:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Gigantoraptor, whose name means “Giant Thief”, is the largest known Oviraptorosaur from the Late Cretaceous era. Featuring an impressive coat of feathers and large elongated legs, the Gigantoraptor can maintain speed for an extended period of time as it chases down its prey.<br/></li><li>Concavenator has a distinctive narrow hump, formed by two extremely large vertebrae, making its profile instantly recognisable. This agile theropod from the Early Cretaceous period is a fierce hunter that will make an exciting addition to your parks.<br/></li><li>Utahraptor, one of the largest dromaeosaurs, is an intelligent and ruthless predator that is sure to impress your guests. With a stunning feather coat and large scythe-like claws, this predator, hailing from Utah, will stop any prey in its tracks.<br/></li><li>Tarbosaurus, is a gargantuan hunter inspired by the Universal Pictures, Amblin Entertainment and DreamWorks Animation Netflix Show, Jurassic World Camp Cretaceous: Hidden Adventure. This unique Tyrannosaurine theropod will need a secure enclosure to protect guests from its powerful jaws.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEVI</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2230650/TEVI/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FZ9KrdFvNRK" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/JoinUsOnDC.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Action-Packed_Combo_System.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/戰鬥動圖.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>The protagonist Tevi is nimble and agile, wielding both her trusty dagger and an oversized wrench for dishing out melee damage in style. Alongside her, companions Celia and Sable manifest as two floating orbitars, ready to unleash a variety of ranged offensive and supportive magic in battle. Adapt your combat style to suit any situation and bring down foes with flashy, dazzling combos!<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Thrilling_Boss_Battles.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Boss.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Every boss fight is a unique challenge requiring different strategies to tackle, all while you dodge their attacks and look for openings to counter-attack. <br/>As bosses change phases, their attack and bullet patterns become increasingly challenging, and they can even unleash devastating ultimates. Continual offense can submit bosses into a vulnerable BREAK state, during which you can deal massive bursts of damage.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Myriad_Abilities,_Equipment,_and_Exploration.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/badge.jpg?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Scattered across the the expansive world, there are over 300 different items and pieces of equipment waiting to be discovered. These items can enhance your abilities or introduce new ones, allowing you to find more methods of navigating the world and finding secrets. A cornucopia of equippable sigils can be freely configured to create builds tailored to your preferences and playstyle.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/A_Rich,_Expansive_Fantasy_World.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/場景6.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Dive into the vibrant world of Az, in which you will discover various towns, regions, peoples, histories, and civilizations, each with their own tale to tell. Along the way, you'll meet a large cast of strange and colorful characters. As their tales unfold and intertwine, you'll be drawn into a tale full of adventure, friendship, mysteries, and danger... <br/><br/>Get ready to embark on an unforgettable adventure, writing your own epic journey alongside Tevi!<br/><br/><a href="https://youtu.be/psxior_WswQ" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/角色介紹.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tevi（VA: Lynn）<br/></li><li>Celia（VA: Yoko Hikasa）<br/></li><li>Sable（VA: Natsumi Fujiwara）<br/></li><li>Zema（VA: Tomokazu Sugita）<br/></li><li>Vena（VA: Rie Kugimiya）</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Suika - Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2671970/My_Suika__Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A fun watermelon merge puzzle game!<br>
<br>
Think you can get 3000 points in this addictive watermelon puzzle game?<br>
<br>
Combine various matching fruits to help Kyo gather watermelons! Unlock new game modes and new fruit skins by obtaining high scores. Compete against other players on the global leaderboards!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call to Arms - Gates of Hell: Liberation</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2447590/Call_to_Arms__Gates_of_Hell_Liberation/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<strong>“Soldiers, Sailors, and Airmen of the Allied Expeditionary Force: you are about to embark upon the Great Crusade!”<br/>This DLC introduces the western front action in 1944, featuring the US faction, as well as German western front content.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/01Sherman.gif?t=1701279518"><br/><br/>Be among the first to scale the Atlantic wall and fight your way through the Bocage. <br/>Be the spearhead that breaks the stalemate in the battle of the Bulge. <br/>Re-live the rush to the Rhine bridge, on the road into the heart of Germany!<br/><br/>Or, fight for the Wehrmacht and be the one that leads the counterattacks, the one that stops the breakout. In other words; be the one that defends “Fortress Europe” facing all the classic dilemmas that come with it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/02Beach.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Single Player</h2>The single player campaigns focus on four legendary western front units: the “Liberation” campaign has the 2nd Rangers and the 3rd Armored Division on the US side. Beside 6 single player missions, this DLC also offers 4 skirmishes for the US faction, which are part of the campaign storyline.<br/>In all of the missions, you will find yourself in intense battles on iconic battlegrounds, recreated to the last detail; get a taste of the bitter fighting against fanatical opposition, liberating western Europe step by hellish step. The action will be intense and the immersion will be up there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/03Nebel.gif?t=1701279518"><br/><br/>The German campaign,  “Festung Europa”, has the 3rd Fallschirmjäger division and 116th Panzer division on the German side in 6 intense and compelling missions.<br/>Be the one that commands the Wehrmacht forces on the western front from Normandy to the last battles in the Ruhr pocket. In the German campaign you will enjoy a lot of new content as well! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/04Maps.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer</h2>“Liberation” adds the USA to multiplayer with 20 brand new western front MP maps, and all of the new weapons, vehicles and tanks; it also adds a new German late war doctrine.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/05Mist.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Conquest</h2>For conquest, 25 western front maps are included. These, like other maps, use the unique set of assets we have created to immerse you in the western front atmosphere. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/06wespe.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Visuals</h2>Liberation pushes the boundary of the visuals of the Gates of Hell universe to a new standard, with hundreds of highly detailed environment models, improved destruction for buildings and beautiful environments. To ensure the historical accuracy of our content, we have collaborated with WW2 Armor in Florida, who provided us with vast amounts of valuable documentation and knowledge.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/07Logo.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Content</h2>The Liberation DLC contains:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>10 US single player missions, including 4 US skirmishes<br/></li><li>6 German single player missions<br/></li><li>150+  new US and German vehicles, cannon, ships, aircraft and tanks<br/></li><li>50 new small arms<br/></li><li>500+ new humanskins<br/></li><li>20 new MP maps<br/></li><li>25 new DCG (Conquest) maps<br/></li><li>500+ new editor assets for the western European theater.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MULLER-POWELL PRINCIPLE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2155770/THE_MULLERPOWELL_PRINCIPLE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FeY9JWyTaAm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_discord.png?t=1701271403"/></a><br/><br/>It is a sci-fi story that takes place in the near future. You are Harry Herman, an employee of Delta Laboratories who researches interdimensional traveling. You had been participating in a project that was supposed to benefit all humanity, but something went wrong. Through the gameplay, you will solve various physics-based puzzles using an energy-manipulating weapon, travel across space and time to explore surrealistic universes and find out the dark truth about this project and your connection to it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_gameplay.png?t=1701271403"><br/>Solve various puzzles and trick enemies using physics interactions and your special tool - the Portable Energy Manipulator. <br/><br/><strong>PHYSICS PUZZLES &amp; INTERACTIVE ENVIRONMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/gameplay_physics.gif?t=1701271403"><br/><br/>Many objects in the game can be picked up, brought somewhere, or manipulated in other ways. Whether it's a computer terminal, a box you can carry, or a simple mug on a table. Explore various interactive environments to find clues and return to the riddle with a solution, which in some cases may be several. Nothing was made for you to solve, there's no cube dispenser or an obvious exit door at the end. It's all for you to figure out.<br/><br/><strong>PORTABLE ENERGY MANIPULATOR</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/gif_photongun.gif?t=1701271403"><br/><br/>The device you carry throughout the game can absorb different energy types from the environment and use them to perform various tasks.<br/><br/>Absorbing energy from a particular source will give the gun its’ properties. The heat energy from fire and radiators will melt glass, security cameras can be blinded by a beam of light, and for powering generators, you can take hazardous radiation from toxic puddles scattered across Delta Labs facilities. And of course, you will make an encounter with the quantum entanglement energy - the mysterious power capable of opening rifts between worlds. <br/><br/>Apart from solving environmental puzzles, your device can also be used against various creatures you'll meet in parallel dimensions. Most of the time you can't defeat your enemies; instead, you can use the Manipulator to outsmart or suspend them. Some enemies can be frozen in place using the force field energy, while others are sensitive to light and can be distracted by shooting a beam at it in the distance. You will require more advanced strategies and combining various energy types to pass them.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_story.png?t=1701271403"><br/>You find yourself in one of Delta Labs' off-world research facilities in an unknown dimension that looks more like a crashing-down laboratory. Your old friends Eugene and Alex try to connect with you shortly, and with their help, you start a journey through various dimensions. You will learn different physics interactions and meet unusual creatures on your way home. Along this, you have to unveil the mysteries of this project and your past. <br/><br/>Experience a non-linear story where your choice always matters. Can you get to the bottom of this, or just try to escape? Who to listen? Who to trust? Which side will you take? And will you finally “break the Principle”? That depends entirely on you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_setting.png?t=1701271403"><br/>Make your way back to Earth through mysterious parallel dimensions littered with puzzles and secrets, uncover mysterious connections between the worlds you visit, and reveal the dark truth about Delta Labs and your involvement with them. Dare to explore?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_features.png?t=1701271403"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Solve various physics-based puzzles<br/></li><li>Unique gameplay mechanics that involve an energy-manipulating weapon <br/></li><li>A mix of sci-fi with surreal and esoteric themes makes the game setting a unique design. Most of the time you'll spend in bizarre alien dimensions<br/></li><li>Deeply thought-out story and lore. Each location and each character in the game has its own story revealed through various notes, environmental narratives, and characters' conversations.<br/></li><li>The game features multiple endings that can be achieved through different choices </li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn around immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Other</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead by Daylight - Chucky Chapter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2656010/Dead_by_Daylight__Chucky_Chapter/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Main_Banner.png?t=1701272232"><br/> <br/>Meet your new best friend ‘til the end. Dead by Daylight: Chucky brings an iconic horror legend into The Fog with a new Killer: <strong>The Good Guy - Chucky</strong>. Purchasing this add-on unlocks an <strong>exclusive Charm: Good Guys Box.</strong> <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Killer_Power.gif?t=1701272232"><h2 class="bb_tag">CHUCKY</h2>Viciously cruel with a cutting sense of humor, Chucky is a brutally effective killing machine. Using his diminutive frame to his advantage, he’ll pop up when Survivors least expect it, chasing them down and introducing them to his trusty weapons.<br/> <br/><strong>Chucky’s Power: Playtime's Over </strong><br/><br/>The Good Guy is the first Killer in Dead by Daylight to feature a third-person camera.   <br/><br/><strong>Special Ability – Hidey-Ho Mode:</strong> When Chucky enters Hidey-Ho Mode, he becomes Undetectable and generates Map-wide footfalls, disorienting Survivors. Though Hidey-Ho mode can be entered at any time, it does have a cooldown.   <br/> <br/><strong>Special Ability – Scamper:</strong> While in Hidey-Ho Mode, Chucky can Scamper under a downed Pallet or through a Window, allowing him to quickly gain ground.   <br/><br/><strong>Special Ability – Slice &amp; Dice:</strong> While in Hidey-Ho Mode, Chucky can sprint and lunge forward to Slice &amp; Dice Survivors. This attack can be held, but Chucky will be unable to do anything else during this time. If a Survivor tries to Vault a Window or Pallet while you’re charging a Slice &amp; Dice attack, Chucky can quickly chain into a Scamper.   <br/> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Killer_Perks.png?t=1701272232"><br/><br/>Chucky comes with <strong>3 new perks.</strong><br/><br/> <h2 class="bb_tag">Hex: Two Can Play</h2>When a Survivor Stuns or Blinds you a number of times, a Dull Totem becomes a Hex Totem. When that Hex is active, Survivors who stun or blind you are Blinded for 4 seconds. The Hex effects persist as long as the related Hex Totem is standing.<h2 class="bb_tag">Friends ‘Til the End</h2>You become Obsessed with one Survivor. When you Hook a Survivor that is not the Obsession, the Obsession becomes Exposed and reveals their Aura for a brief duration. If you Hook the Obsession, a random Survivor will scream, reveal their position, and become the Obsession.<h2 class="bb_tag">Batteries Included</h2>When within the vicinity of a completed Generator, gain Haste. The movement speed boost lingers for a brief duration after you leave the Generator’s vicinity.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Exclusive_Item.png?t=1701272232"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXCLUSIVE CHAPTER ITEM: GOOD GUYS BOX</h2>The Chucky Chapter includes an exclusive item, the <strong>Good Guys Box Charm</strong>, only available as part of the DLC. Please note that this item cannot be purchased separately.<br/><br/><br/><i>His name is Charles Lee Ray. Chucky to his friends... You’ll be his friend ‘til the end, right?</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1701359196"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1701359196"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1701359196"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retro Commander</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/338820/Retro_Commander/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/338820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/338820/extras/icon_and_text_v05_-_600x195px.png?t=1700862195"><br/>Retro Commander is a <strong>post-apocalyptic</strong> real-time strategy wargame (RTS). Take command and fight it out in a world where a cataclysmic timeline has transpired on Mother Earth. Wage wars solo, against the AI, or take on your gaming comrades and friends in cross-platform multiplayer matches. Form teams and clans and fight co-op style with the AI and other players for ultimate victory.<br/><br/>As opposed to other real-time strategy game, Retro Commander tries to focus on both, a fun <strong>single player</strong> and a thrilling <strong>multiplayer</strong> experience. The game strives to be easy to learn with a modern user interface. Single player comes with skirmish matches against the AI as well as a comic-based <strong>story campaign</strong>. Multiplayer can be played cross-platform and includes a ranking and rating system.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u>Post-Apocalyptic</u>: Real-time strategy (RTS) played in a post-apocalyptic timeline on Mother Earth. The environment includes day-night cycles, rain, snow, wind and solar flare activity.<br/></li><li><u>Story Campaign</u>: Deep campaign and story line of humanity after a cataclysmic event. Factions come with their own specialized <strong>technologies</strong> such as stealth, robots, drones or shields.<br/></li><li><u>Single &amp; Multiplayer</u>: A challenging AI for both single and multiplayer matches with co-op play. Cross-platform multiplayer including <strong>LAN</strong>/internet. ONLINE play comes with an award and rating system.<br/></li><li><u>Play Modes</u>: In addition to regular skirmish matches, the game supports missions such as elimination, survival, <strong>capture the flag</strong>, defense and <strong>battle royale</strong>. Available in both single and multiplayer also are escort and rescue missions.<br/></li><li><u>Structures &amp; Troops</u>: Common troops for land, sea and air warfare is available to all factions. Specialized elements such as stealth, shields, <strong>EMP</strong> weapons, nukes, <strong>portals</strong>, orbital weapons, assimilator and other troops and structures provide for additional variety.<br/></li><li><u>Research</u>: A <strong>tech tree</strong> and research options enable to build specialized structures and troops. A <strong>Tech Snatcher</strong> can be used to steal enemy technology.<br/></li><li><u>Modding</u>: A map editor is included allowing for player-modded maps including player-modded campaigns. All elements including troops, structures, as well as graphics and sound effects, can be modded if desired.</li></ul><br/>Although some troops are shared, the game is trying not to be a generic RTS-games. There are <strong>faction-specific technologies</strong> each with their strengths and weaknesses.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u>GRA Technology</u>: gives access to <strong>stealth</strong> and cloaking. Included are cloaked agents and spies as well as bombers with EMP and nuclear weapons. Available also are snipers and heavy airlifts. Can build uranium fabricators.<br/></li><li><u>ELC Technology</u>: provides <strong>robots</strong>, <strong>airships</strong> and robo dogs. Available also are a mechanic and heavy airlift. Can build stationary EMP-field generators.<br/></li><li><u>IDB Technology</u>: provides <strong>hovertanks</strong>, <strong>drones</strong> including EMP-field drones and drones equipped with napalm weapons. Can build fusion generators for power.<br/></li><li><u>Mayan Technology</u>: consists of <strong>decoy</strong> capabilities. Included are hologram tanks, transformers, dogs and dolphins. Can build <strong>portals</strong>.<br/></li><li><u>Ancient Technology</u>: provides <strong>shields</strong>, EMP soldiers, assimilators and napalm tanks. Can build matter fabricators.</li></ul><br/><strong>Free vs Paid (DLC or in-game)</strong>: The free version includes unlimited access to over 12+ multiplayer scenarios and Chapter 01 of the single player campaign. Purchasing the DLC <strong>"All Maps &amp; Modding"</strong> grants full access to the game. It includes everything for single player including the story campaign, skirmishing against the AI, ONLINE multiplayer or LAN-play with friends and family.<br/><br/><strong>No DRM</strong>: There is no DRM in the game. You <strong>don't need to connected to the internet</strong> to play single player games or the campaign. You don't need to be logged in to play LAN games either. You don't need to login either for WAN games (locally hosted games over the internet), but you will have to work out your router settings and do the appropriate port-forwarding so your friends can connect from remote.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Stars And Time</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1677310/In_Stars_And_Time/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FZzFSRUBXEC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/discordbanner620.gif?t=1701180941"/></a><br/><br/><strong>What would you do if you were forced to relive your failures over and over again?</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam5_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> tells the story of Siffrin and their adventurer friends—a found family bound together by fate in order to end the tyrannical reign of an evil king. But as victory is just within the party’s grasp, a tragedy occurs, the clock resets, and <strong>they have to do it all again</strong>. <br/><br/>As Siffrin’s the only one who notices this loop, each new start wears away at his cheerful veneer, yet he keeps going in hopes he can end this temporal tragedy once and for all.<br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> is a <strong>time-looping RPG adventure</strong>. With each loop, Siffrin gains a new perspective on the world around them, opening up new solutions to puzzles and allowing them to make better choices in conversation. Equip memories as armor, pray to the Change God to improve your team’s capabilities each loop, and challenge deadly foes to Rock, Paper, Scissors as Siffrin seeks the truth.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam4_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Our Adventurers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Siffrin (he/they):</strong> Stressed, depressed, and under duress. (Don’t worry about it. They’re doing fine.) The punmaster protagonist of our neverending tale.<br/></li><li><strong>Mirabelle (she/her):</strong> A caring and nervous housemaiden mysteriously blessed by the god she so ardently follows.<br/></li><li><strong>Isabeau (he/him):</strong> Defender with a heart of gold. Cares dearly for his people and his friends.<br/></li><li><strong>Odile (she/her):</strong> The mature and nonsensical researcher studying…something. (No, she will not tell you what it is.)<br/></li><li><strong>Bonnie (they/them):</strong> Wait a minute, who brought this kid along???</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Save the world through the power of Rock, Paper, Scissors in <strong>strategic turn-based RPG</strong> combat encounters.<br/></li><li>Ignore the limits of time and space to <strong>fix your past mistakes</strong> by repeating the same two days over and over again.<br/></li><li>Equip the <strong>memories you have of your friends</strong> to make your party stronger in combat. <br/></li><li><strong>Watch the fate of this world unfold</strong> as you escape the twists and turns of this endless(???) loop.<br/></li><li>Eat <strong>samossas</strong> with your friends!<br/></li><li>Get heckled by a <strong>cheeky ethereal being of infinite starlight</strong>.<br/></li><li>Pray to a god for good luck in your travels. <strong>You’re gonna need it.</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam2_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/>If any of this interests you, you might also want to play the game’s initial prototype, <u><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1691420/START_AGAIN_a_prologue/" rel="" target="_blank">START AGAIN START AGAIN START AGAIN: A Prologue</a></u>. While you don’t need to play it to understand In Stars and Time, it’s fun to see the game’s roots.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 5 Tactica</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2254740/Persona_5_Tactica/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join the Phantom Thieves as they lead an uprising of the heart! Assemble a team of beloved heroes in a brand-new story in this thrilling combat adventure set in Persona’s iconic universe. The Persona 5 Tactica: Digital Deluxe Edition includes the following content:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Repaint Your Heart Challenge Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Weapon Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Picaro Summoning Pack + Raoul Persona</li></ul><br/><strong>Ignite your heart— An emotional uprising begins!</strong><br/><br/>After a strange incident, the Phantom Thieves wander into a bizarre realm where its citizens are living under tyrannical oppression. Surrounded by a military group named Legionnaires, they find themselves in grave danger until a mysterious revolutionary named Erina rescues them and offers an enticing deal in exchange for their help. What truth lies behind Erina and the deal she offers to the Phantom Thieves?<br/><br/>Persona 5 Tactica features an all-new story, the return of fan-favorite characters, and brand-new allies and foes. Join the group as they lead an emotional revolution in this thrilling combat adventure!<br/><br/><strong>An Emotional Revolution</strong><br/>Lead an uprising of the heart in a brand-new storyline that takes place in Persona’s iconic universe.<br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Squad</strong><br/>Assemble a team of beloved heroes to fight oppressive armies in thrilling turn-based combat.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Combat</strong><br/>Overthrow your enemies with powerful Personas, an assortment of weapons, and wipe them out with style!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Saga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1320140/Small_Saga/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Venture below the streets of London, and you will find the medieval kingdom of rats, mice, moles, squirrels, and shrews known as Rodentia.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G8.gif?t=1700830017"><br/><br/>If the rodents have a cardinal law, it is this: never attack a god. But Verm never had much respect for the rule of law. His tail was stolen by the Yellow God of Death, and now the mouse will have to fight all manner of beasts and titans on his quest to get it back.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G5.gif?t=1700830017"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G1.gif?t=1700830017"><br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Team up with a colorful cast of misfit rodents.<br/></li><li>Encounter awe-inspiring titans. Clash with a swashbuckling water vole, a pious lab rabbit, a poetry-spewing kraken, and many more.<br/></li><li>Meet the hideous vermin who run society, then overthrow them.<br/></li><li>Brandish your tiny weapons in strategic, turn-based combat. <br/></li><li>There is no grinding. Small Saga is a tightly-focused and boss-oriented adventure.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Faith</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1274600/The_Last_Faith/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The wicked and the blessed will be judged the same - let nothing stand in your way.<br/><br/>Often brutal, always empowering, The Last Faith is an unholy alliance of metroidvania and soulslike. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/extras/GIF_5.gif?t=1701261553"><br/><br/>The Last Faith thrives on merciless and precise combat, with a huge range of custom executions to perform.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/extras/GIF_4.gif?t=1701261553"><br/><br/>Discover a formidable arsenal of melee weapons, arcane spells, and long-range firearms, allowing you to carve a path your own way. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/extras/KUMISOULS_THELASTFAITH_GIF_02.gif?t=1701261553"><br/><br/>Nonlinear exploration is at the core of The Last Faith. Gorgeous pixel art depicts an imposing gothic landscape. Journey along snow-dusted mountains and castles bathed in moonlight. Discover and upgrade a formidable range of tools for destruction.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/extras/GIF_8.gif?t=1701261553"><br/><br/>Step into The Last Faith’s ravaged world as Eryk, who awakens with no recollection of his immediate past. Soon he will discover he is in a race against time as his mind and conscience begins to deteriorate. His desire for salvation from this affliction sets him on a cursed mission that crosses paths with ancient religions and divinities. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/extras/KUMISOULS_THELASTFAITH_GIF_01.gif?t=1701261553"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header_alt_assets_2.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astral Ascent</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1280930/Astral_Ascent/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Astral Ascent is a 2D platformer rogue-lite game set in a modern fantasy world. As one of 4 Heroes with very different personalities, you must escape from <i>the Garden</i>, an astral prison guarded by 12 powerful and vicious bosses, the Zodiacs.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CREATE YOUR OWN PLAYSTYLE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Gif_playstyle.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Unlock dozens of unique spells for your 4 distinct characters. Optimize your own build or try out new ones to take down 12 powerful bosses. Get stronger with time to match up with your foes. Each run will test your skills and your reactivity.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TWELVE ALMIGHTY BOSSES TO FACE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Zodiacs.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The Zodiacs are 12 experienced guardians dispatched over 4 gorgeous worlds. They’ll bring to the battlefield unique attacks, abilities, and patterns, backstories to uncover, and reasons to be fighting you. Get yourself warned!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>4 PLAYABLE CHARACTERS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/4_Character_banniere_steam7.png?t=1700851162"><br/><i>Unique characters. Unique weapons. Unique ways to play.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Ayla:</strong> The sole survivor of her guild of assassins, she uses her twin daggers to eliminate her enemies before they can react. Her speed and proficiency are unmatched.<br/></li><li><strong>Kiran:</strong> This orphan learned life the hard way. He uses his strength to deliver attacks powerful enough to create shockwaves. Brutal.<br/></li><li><strong>Calie:</strong> This talented sculptor wants her freedom back. She will use her magical gemstones to pierce enemy defenses and shred them to bits. She is unforgiving.<br/></li><li><strong>Octave:</strong> Trained by a powerful witch, this young fighter summons ethereal guns to attack his foes. When needed, he can conjure bigger weapons as well. Lethal in all cases.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A STORY THAT OPENS UP, ONE PIECE AT A TIME</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/ZimZim2.png?t=1700851162"><br/>Astral Ascent is a rogue-lite infused with narration. Replayability is part of our story which will be unraveled piece by piece. As you get stronger, you will discover more about the characters, their motivations, and the secrets of the world they’re trapped in.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>LOCAL CO-OP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Coop.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The weight of destiny is too heavy to carry by yourself? Don’t worry and bring a friend to play in our <strong>two-player co-op</strong> mode. Fight and crush your enemies together in local co-op or online using the <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/remoteplay?snr=1_614_615__1601" rel="" target="_blank"><strong>Steam's Remote Play Together</strong></a> feature.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A VAST, COLORFUL FANTASY WORLD WAITING TO BE EXPLORED</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Panning.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Dash across gigantic landscapes. Explore original and hand-crafted areas. Discover the world created by our artists, with a gorgeous art and frame-by-frame animation.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refind Self: The Personality Test Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2514960/Refind_Self_The_Personality_Test_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							All players approach games in varied ways, making different choices.<br/>No one ever plays in exactly the same way. Indeed, how a person plays can be an indicator of their personality...<br/>And Refind Self is a game where you can learn all about that personality.<br/><br/>One play is about one hour.<br/>Just enjoy this simple test during your busy time.<br/>And the third time test will show all your personalities, where the end of the story is also not far away.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/NormalScene.gif?t=1700145463"><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2>You are an android. The story begins with you standing at the grave of the Doctor who created you. The world is populated by robots in various forms, created for numerous purposes.<br/><br/><br/>Travel to places key to your memories of the Doctor, interact with the robots, and unravel the secrets behind the future the Doctor sought and what you were entrusted with.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/ConversationWithRobot.gif?t=1700145463"><h2 class="bb_tag">Important Characters</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/CR_Player_Normal.png?t=1700145463"> <strong>[Protagonist]</strong><br/>The player, a robot created by the Doctor as an EAI: an AI that can take action based on emotions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/CR_Daru.png?t=1700145463"> <strong>[Dull]</strong><br/>A robot clerk at the café. Always lazy due to misconfiguration by the Doctor.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/CR_GOGOscrap.png?t=1700145463"> <strong>[GoGo Scrap]</strong><br/>A robot that collects scraps. Sociable and boylike.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/CR_Inori.png?t=1700145463"> <strong>[Inori]</strong><br/>A shepherd robot created to carry out orders.<h2 class="bb_tag">How to Play</h2>Go wherever you feel like, converse, investigate, play minigames... Simply play as you please. There are no game overs, and there's no right or wrong way to progress.<br/><br/>With each action you take, your personality will be analyzed. Once analysis is 100% complete... Congratulations, you've beaten the game! Your personality results will then be revealed.<br/><br/>If you want to know more about your personality, you can go back to play again and again. Of course, this also goes for those who want to know the truth of the story.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/HowToPlay.gif?t=1700145463"><h2 class="bb_tag">Personality Comparison and Sharing</h2>Your test results are stored in an online database, and you'll be issued a unique results ID. You can share your results ID, and view others' results to compare them with your own.<br/><br/>Perhaps similar personalities mean good compatibility? That's another way of having fun with your results.<br/><br/>*Test result data does not include any personal identifiable information.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/PersonalityComparison.gif?t=1700145463"><h2 class="bb_tag">Examples of Possible Personalities</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/seikakuichirei_en.png?t=1700145463"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirate Fighting Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186400/Pirate_Fighting_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pirate Fighting Simulator is a free multiplayer PVP game developed in Unreal Engine 5 in which you fight other players using typical pirate weaponry. There are also cosmetics that you can unlock, these cosmetics can be either hats, weapon skins or in the form of a title that sits underneath your username. The game also includes emotes so you can absolutely boogie down silly style after destroying an enemy gamer. There are also two gamemodes one being TDM (Team Death Match)) and the second being FFA (Free For All).						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1699642767"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1700646226"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobalt Core</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2179850/Cobalt_Core/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_1.gif?t=1700087396"><br/><br/>Cobalt Core is a sci-fi roguelike deckbuilder with a unique single-axis combat system that will throw you for a loop. Many loops! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_2.gif?t=1700087396"><br/><br/>Give orders to your crew by playing cards: Will you <strong>raise shields</strong> to protect your ship, <strong>dodge</strong> incoming missiles and cannon fire to avoid damage outright, or <strong>strike</strong> preemptively to disable your enemy’s weapons? Outmaneuver your foes to stay just ahead of impending calamity, and reach the Cobalt Core!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/characters.png?t=1700087396"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fresh new spin on tactics –</strong>  dodge attacks and target weak points in this unique single-axis take on tactics combat. Outwit the enemy in a high stakes game of cat and mouse!<br/></li><li><strong>Customize your deck –</strong> hundreds of cards and split upgrade paths means no two runs will be the same. Find that perfect combo that brings your deck from powerful to overpowered.<br/></li><li><strong>Get to know your crew –</strong> each character comes with a completely unique playstyle and their own personal story. Bring 3 along, mix and match their decks, and see how these little goobers get along with each other.<br/></li><li><strong>Tons of replayability –</strong>  hundreds of different character+ship combinations before you even hit “start run”. Crank up the difficulty and really test your skills!<br/></li><li><strong>Forward momentum –</strong> untangle a narrative and unlock more playstyles as you go. Is there any escape from this time loop?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/grandma_cookies.gif?t=1700087396"><br/><br/>By the makers of <i>Sunshine Heavy Industries</i>, recipient of IGF's <strong>Honorable Mention for Excellence in Design 2022</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nickelodeon All-Star Brawl 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2017080/Nickelodeon_AllStar_Brawl_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/ReviewScores.jpg?t=1700669221"><br/><br/><strong>Nickelodeon All-Star Brawl 2</strong> lets you duke it out with the biggest and best fighting character roster yet, including all new characters like SpongeBob SquarePants, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, Squidward Tentacles, Jimmy Neutron, and more!<br/><br/>Choose your favorite brawlers, master their unique move sets, and use all-new powerful Supers to land the finishing blow with friends or across a unique, roguelike player campaign!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/General_GIF-Optimized.gif?t=1700669221"><br/><br/>Featuring:<br/>• <strong>New Single-Player Campaign:</strong> Put your skills to the test as you fight to stop Danny Phantom archvillain Vlad Plasmius from taking over the Nickelodeon universe!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/Campaign_GIF-Optimized.gif?t=1700669221"><br/><br/>• <strong>All-New Gameplay:</strong> New and revamped visuals meets new audio, animations, modes, stages, mechanics, taunts and move sets for all levels of play!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/GameplayRevamp_GIF-Optimized.gif?t=1700669221"><br/><br/>• <strong>Cinematic Supers:</strong> Power up your fighters with incredible new animated supers to deal devastating blows to your opponents!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/CinematicSupers_GIF-Optimized.gif?t=1700669221"><br/><br/>• <strong>New &amp; Improved Brawlers:</strong> Nickelodeon All-Star Brawl 2’s roster is better than ever, with even more variety in how each unique character plays. Battle with brand new Nickelodeon fighters as well as returning fan favorites!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2017080/extras/NewBrawlers_GIF-Optimized.gif?t=1700669221"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Succubus Sessions: Mami Mamiya's Sweet Slice of Hell</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2361690/Succubus_Sessions_Mami_Mamiyas_Sweet_Slice_of_Hell/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2361690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">GAMEPLAY &amp; FEATURES </h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Short-ish kinetic VN clocking in at 7+ hours till credits <br/></li><li>Lush backgrounds, event CGs, and 2D anime-style sprites <br/></li><li>Monster therapy, free room and board, and a supernatural twist! <br/></li><li>Veteran cast of professional Japanese voice actors </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">STORY </h2><br/>College dropout Koichi’s life has been nothing but Ls, so when his hard-won job evaporates overnight (again), he heads to Akihabara for some daytime distraction. <br/><br/><i>No savings, no career, no girlfriend. Where did it all go wrong? </i><br/><br/>He sighs into the crowd, then to no one in particular— <br/><br/><i>“...I sure could use a little kindness right about now.” </i><br/><br/>But in that moment, feet away, Mami Mamiya is searching, too. This shy she-demon is on the hunt for a human connection, and so Koichi’s story takes a supernatural turn... <br/><br/>Tempted by fate and an unsolicited invite from Mami, he hitches a car ride to her remote mountain abode. Little does he know he might never return. Or <i>will</i> he...? <br/><br/>Koichi is soon shocked to learn he’s in no ordinary village, but a succubine sanctuary, hidden from human eyes! <br/><br/>After years of self-exile and isolation, a son of Adam is just what this hamlet needs to reacquaint itself with the outside world. Demon contact, however, can prove lethal to the average joe... <br/><br/>Not our Koichi, though. This guy’s built different.<h2 class="bb_tag">MAIN HEROINE </h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2361690/extras/chara01.png?t=1701392972"><br/><strong>Mami Mamiya</strong><br/><i>Voice: Yuki Kitaohji </i><br/><br/>Mild and meek with a jealous streak. <br/><br/>For all her shyness, Mami’s powers are almost second to none. At first, she wasn’t too sold on the idea of befriending mortals, but for Koichi, she’s willing to make an exception. In truth, the two have met once before—at a summer festival years ago—and she’s been hoping to reunite ever since... <br/><br/><i>“Apparently, part of the plan was that I’d get to meet my father. If that was even possible... Guess I’ll never know.” </i> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>数学と親友とネタ帳 - Math, BFF, and Notes -</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2646260/__Math_BFF_and_Notes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2646260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"- Math, BFF, and Notes - 数学と親友とネタ帳" is a novel game in which the protagonist, Takuma Toomi, wrestles with his feelings for the older, married women in his life.<br>
A Bishojo Game released in 2017 under the "IncaRose" brand has been reworked for the "PandaShojo" platform for players around the world to enjoy.<br>
<br>
<br>
◆Introduction<br>
You'll be alright.<br>
She wraps me in her warm embrace, I feel the soft touch of her hair on my face.<br/>
<br/>
It was at that exact moment that I'd fallen in love.<br/>
Older women are what I needed.<br/>
There wasn't anything I could do to change how I felt.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
◆Synopsis<br/>
Takuma Toomi of the Manzai club is well known for his energetic greetings.<br/>
Good morning Mrs. Shiho, you're as pretty as ever!<br/>
Shiho Iizuka lives next door and was married to a recently popular TV personality.<br/>
Though she usually just laughs his approaches off, Takuma had made a point of greeting her whenever they met.<br/>
In fact, he'd only entered the Manzai club in an effort to emulate Shiho's husband.<br/>
<br/>
Though Takuma only has eyes for older women, Shiho wasn't the only target of his affections.<br/>
He'd already been turned down by his math teacher, Aki Tokie.<br/>
And then there was his Manzai partner's mother, Sanae Miyauchi.<br/>
<br/>
What can Takuma do to get closer to the women he admires?<br/>
No matter who he chooses, it's going to be an uphill battle......!<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
◆Characters<br/>
・Shiho Iizuka<br/>
You sure have grown up, Takuma. Is that a little muscle I'm starting to see on you now?<br/>
The housewife who lives next door. She's kind and pretty, but unfortunately she's already married.<br/>
She once protected Takuma from being bullied and he's spent every day since then trying to win her affections.<br/>
It seems that she's being abused by her husband, the recently famous TV personality, Gorongoro Dobazaki.<br/>
<br/>
・Sanae Miyauchi<br/>
I don't suppose he's here for me? Oh, who am I kidding?<br/>
The beautiful mother of Kouya, Takuma's best friend.<br/>
Of course, Takuma and Kouya got along well to begin with, but they probably wouldn't have become as close as they did if Takuma wasn't infatuated with Sanae.<br/>
She can play the Viola and also teaches a handicrafts class.<br/>
<br/>
・Aki Tokie<br/>
I need Takuma to come to school for supplementary math lessons......<br/>
A math teacher at Takuma's school. She was also his homeroom teacher during his freshman year.<br/>
Takuma confessed his feelings to her, but was rejected due to the age gap.<br/>
Unable to focus on his studies due to her beauty, Takuma is roped into taking remedial lessons.<br/>
<br/>
・Takuma Toomi<br/>
A student who can only have romantic feelings for women around the same age as his mother.<br/>
Unfortunately for him, he clams up and has trouble speaking around them.<br/>
He's formed a Manzai act together with his friend Kouya, uploading videos under the handle "Giesselbach's Area."						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Escape: Dead Complex</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2219840/Last_Escape_Dead_Complex/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2219840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dead Complex is a 2D Top Down, Survival Horror Game. <br/>Sneak, Loot and Fight your way out of an infested apartment complex and begin your final escape from the city.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Classic Survival Horror Gameplay<br/></li><li> Loot System<br/></li><li> Multiple Endings<br/></li><li> Real Time Lighting<br/></li><li> Full Controller Support</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvest Havoc</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2525490/Harvest_Havoc/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2525490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the heart-pounding world of 'Harvest Havoc' where multiplayer PvP meets a thrilling farming-themed extravaganza. Gather your friends and dive into this chaotic 2-6 player party game, where you'll become master farmers, sowing seeds, harvesting bountiful crops, and peddling your produce for victory.<br/><br/>But the true twist lies in the heart of the arenas, where chaos reigns supreme. Engage in ferocious battles with fists or grow formidable weaponry. 'Harvest Havoc' is a unique fusion of cultivation and chaotic combat, promising intense and unpredictable gameplay that will keep you on the edge of your seat. Who will emerge as the ultimate farmer-warrior in this wild and exhilarating experience?<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 5 wacky characters to choose from<br/></li><li> 5 unique levels with varied mechanics, crops, and weapons<br/></li><li> 3 alternate game modes <br/></li><li> Teams and Free-For-All modes<br/></li><li> Challenge your friends online or over LAN <br/></li><li> Fun chaotic gameplay </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incarnation</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2680810/Incarnation/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2680810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Incarnation is a mouse-only roguelike with reverse progression</h2>Experience a divine entity's descent from the heavens through a series of procedurally generated levels. After each level, you must lose one of your celestial powers until you are completely transformed into a human.<h2 class="bb_tag">Will you be able to reach mortality?</h2>The game was developed as a graduation project in the Visual Communication department at Bezalel Academy of Art and Design. This version features Steam achievements.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Lose powers to advance<br/></li><li>Unique mouse-only platforming<br/></li><li>Minimalistic pixelart<br/></li><li>Procedurally-generated levels</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer Virus Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2133050/Computer_Virus_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2133050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Safely experience the danger and excitement of digital chaos!</h2>In a world where cyber security breaches are on the rise, take this exciting opportunity to peek behind the curtains of the darkest aspects of the internet - computer viruses. Computer Virus Simulator will wreak havoc on you safely in-game.<br/>Computer Virus Simulator takes you on a thrilling journey through the world of computer virus all wrapped up in a completely harmless and immersive game.<br/>Navigate an astounding variety of computer virus simulations, from the commonplace to the uniquely obscure.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><strong>Realistic Simulation</strong><br/>Immerse yourself in the realistic simulation of computer viruses. There are many error dialogs, warning sounds, and beeps that mimic the behavior of a real PC.<br/><br/><strong>Variety of Viruses</strong><br/>Experiment with a large number of computer viruses, each unique and intricately designed. <br/><br/>Welcome. Have a nostalgic and exciting experience with DOOR OS.<br/><br/>Do you like system dialog? Then this game is for you!<br/><br/><strong>Please Note: This is not real computer virus, but a standard video game simulation for the purpose of learning and entertainment.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Safe Simulations</h2>Engage in these harrowing adventures without endangering your personal computer. Despite the striking realism, remember - this is a game. You can explore these threats in the most comprehensive, and non-destructive way possible.<h2 class="bb_tag">Realistic Experience</h2>Encounter simulated viruses which are strikingly close to the real ones. They exhibit the similar characteristics of creating error dialogues, marks, beeps, and system warnings that you would potentially face with actual computer virus.<h2 class="bb_tag">Are you ready to face the challenge?</h2>So, are you ready to dive center stage into this chaotic digital world? Navigate your way through the thrilling, yet absolutely safe, realm of computer viruses with Computer Virus Simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag">Remember, in this simulation game, it’s always safety first!</h2>Computer Virus Simulator is completely safe. It's thrilling to experience a virus-infected computer without any of the real-world dangers involved.<h2 class="bb_tag">Dive into the fun world of digital mischief.</h2>Whether you're a cyber-security enthusiast, or just curious about how computer viruses work, the Computer Virus Simulator is here to provide a risk-free, digital roller coaster ride into the world of simulated viral chaos. Remember, it's just a game.<br/><br/>Download now and immerse yourself in the adrenaline-fueled world of the Computer Virus Simulator! The cyber chaos is just a click away.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chronical</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2484810/Chronical/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The power of time is at your fingertips! Take control of a powerful Chronomancer in this mysterious puzzle-platformer. Explore the Chronical school to discover its secrets and learn new spells. Will you save all of the professors and reveal the mystery of the Time Loop?<br/><br/>Features:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Innovative puzzles and mechanics<br/></li><li>4 magic spells to master<br/></li><li>2-3 hours of gameplay<br/></li><li>Fascinating mysteries!</li></ul><br/>Chronical is a single-player puzzle-platforming game. This is a PC game with gamepad controls only. The game contains 2-3 hours of gameplay with fresh new mechanics and puzzles you haven’t seen before. The game was created by the class of 2022-2023 of Campus ADN, a school of videogame development in Montréal, Québec.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother's Embrace</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2633970/Mothers_Embrace/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You step into the shoes of a man returning to his hometown of Olaine, Latvia after 14 long years. Upon receiving a distressing message from his adoptive father, he braves the harsh winter to return home, only to find the eerie post-Soviet town empty and shrouded in a haunting silence.<br>
<br>
As you take on the role of the protagonist, armed with only a flashlight, you'll face unknown creatures and navigate the claustrophobic atmosphere of a small remote eastern European town. Your mission: to uncover the truth behind a long-buried tragedy. Follow a trail of cryptic notes and piece together the dark history that has left Olaine in this desolate state.<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br>
<br>
- Unique horror atmosphere and environments<br>
<br/>
- Heart-wrenching story about loss<br/>
<br/>
- Simple yet challenging gameplay<br/>
<br/>
- Old-school looking graphics<br/>
<br/>
- No Jumscares						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markus Ritter - Ghosts Of The Past</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2222680/Markus_Ritter__Ghosts_Of_The_Past/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2222680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">What can you expect?</h2><br/>We affectionately call it "queer cheesy trash". The 90s FMVs had their own charm and that included exaggerated acting, exaggerated characters and a penchant for hoarding items. We want to get back to that.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 100% FMV Point and Click Adventure Game<br/></li><li> 2 alternating playable main characters<br/></li><li> 15 different playable locations in Austria<br/></li><li> 13 interactive NPCs<br/></li><li> classic point and click puzzles!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2><br/>Markus was recently a pretty normal average guy. He has no particular ambitions in life and keeps his head above water as a photographer of photo books of questionable quality. But when he is plagued by nightmares, he starts to investigate. And a letter addressed to him, but with the wrong surname, changes his life completely.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2222680/extras/5_feuerzeug_recap_Marie.gif?t=1701374587"><br/><br/>The blood of a time-honored family of Shadowhunters beats in his heart. And with it comes a responsibility to his fellow man. For the Shadowhunters are destined to fight demonic beings, so-called 'shadows'. One such monster is currently killing in Vienna and has already claimed countless victims. Will Markus be up to the task?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2222680/extras/10a_buch_bekommen_Kopieren_01_1.gif?t=1701374587"><br/><br/>But not only the supernatural plagues our young Shadowhunter. His publisher has big plans for a book that Markus himself hasn't even written. Will his presence in the public eye be advantageous, or will it hinder his existence as a Shadowhunter?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2222680/extras/12c_schlafzimmer_Kopieren_01.gif?t=1701374587"><br/><br/>Then there's also his love life, which takes off at a most inconvenient time. There's Claudia, the secretary, but also Ludwig, the charismatic digital designer.<br/><br/>And then there's Ro. A young woman who suddenly appears everywhere the shadow is. What's the story behind her?						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons of Saturn</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2493140/Sons_of_Saturn/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2493140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2493140/extras/SonsOfSaturnLogo_w616.png?t=1701374587"><br/><br/>Sons of Saturn is a first person point and click adventure, brought to life using photos of abandoned locations all over the world.  You've returned to the collapsing underground city of Minerva to find out what happened to your mom, who you abandoned while fleeing the city.  If you want to find the answers you're looking for, you'll have to navigate a labyrinth of sewers and rooftops, piece together your history from whatever clues you can scrap together, and contend with the lingering spirits of those who weren't lucky enough to die during the city's collapse.<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore Minerva, the abandoned underground city halted by time.</h2> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2493140/extras/PanCity20fps8colorWidth616.gif?t=1701374587"><br/><br/>The character must navigate and discover their way through the city of Minerva, a technological metropolis where the dead dream and memories cling to life.  Sewers, rooftops, asylums, hospitals, and schools all remain, buried in place, untouched since the day of collapse.  With the help of your Ferryman guide, you must find what clues you can while surviving the lingering threats that the city still harbors.<h2 class="bb_tag">Unravel a rich narrative wrapped in pain, guilt, and loss.</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2493140/extras/JuliaLookingUpLong.gif?t=1701374587"><br/><br/>How can we live in an unjust world?  What cruel entity forced us to be conscious in a universe with such suffering?  Why is a hideous stuffed cat talking to me, and why can no one else hear them?<br/><br/>Sons of Saturn explores the depths of both the underground city Minerva and the protagonists' psyches.   Investigate both the cause of your pain and the warts that have grown up around it in your brain.<h2 class="bb_tag">Brought to life with photos of real abandoned locations.</h2><br/>Unedited photo of an abandoned location:<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2493140/extras/tann_office_unedited_w616.png?t=1701374587"><br/><br/>The asset used in the game:<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2493140/extras/tann_office_w616.png?t=1701374587"><br/><br/>Nearly all of the assets used in Sons of Saturn were derived from real photos, taken by the developers, of breathtaking abandoned locations found all over the world.  We hope exploring the world of Minerva recaptures the magical aura these spaces exude.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2493140/extras/MinervaOverRails_w616.jpg?t=1701374587"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hope of Bion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2526210/Hope_of_Bion/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2526210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Returning home after a work trip Bion finds that his family is gone and the city is flooded by bloodthirsty creatures that someday used to be people. The hero goes on a search of his family, visiting the most various places and at the same time trying to survive.<br/><br/>Hope of Bion is an adventure game with a lean towards story and atmosphere. Visit different locations, examine the objects of environment and fight enemies using weapons of melee and ranged combat.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2526210/extras/first_-_gif.gif?t=1701374237"><h2 class="bb_tag">The features of the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>interesting and atmospheric adventure with elements of horror;<br/></li><li>different levels, both in terms of location and tasks;<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2526210/extras/english-gif.gif?t=1701374237"><br/></img></li><li>ability to interact with the objects of environment and to communicate with the other survivors;<br/></li><li>defend yourself using a baseball bat or a firearm, but remember that ammunition is not endless;<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2526210/extras/shooting_-_gif.gif?t=1701374237"><br/></img></li><li>enemies need only one bite to kill the hero;<br/></li><li>the game is being developed fully by one person.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2526210/extras/picture_of_me-ENG_PNG.png?t=1701374237"><br/><br/>You can follow the development on the official discord server - <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FCgZWCkWh" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/CgZWCkWh</a> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDDOOR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2108840/REDDOOR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2108840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In REDDOOR, the player is immersed in a post-apocalyptic world overrun by zombies. The objective is to survive solo against endless rounds of the undead by strategically opening and clearing doors and using a variety of weapons, perks, utilities, and power-ups. The player earns points from killing zombies, which can then be used to purchase guns, perks, and unlock new areas, or turn on the power. The zombies enter the player's space through special "RED DOORS", and the game will end when the player dies.<br/><br/>To make the rounds a bit easier, the player can occasionally find power-ups such as resupply, nuke, max ammo, time skip, instakill, rapid fire, and shadow upon the death of zombies. These power-ups can give the player an edge in survival. The player can also upgrade their guns using the upgrade station and rarity station, making them stronger for high rounds.<br/><br/>Additionally, the player may stumble upon hidden Easter eggs scattered throughout the map, unveiling special abilities or secret weapons that can turn the tide of the undead onslaught. These hidden gems, when discovered and activated, add an element of surprise and excitement to the gameplay, rewarding players for their exploration and keen observation.<br/><br/>Randomly the undead will drop scrap, which the player can use for ammo or upgrading a weapon for a better rarity. As the increasingly challenging waves of undead become more formidable. Its important that you upgrade your weapons to the best rarity to not only enhances your survivability but also ensures that you are well-equipped to face the evolving zombies. In addition to upgrading weaponry, wisely allocating scrap for ammo becomes crucial, especially during intense rounds where ammunition conservation is key. <br/><br/>Players can also find the mystery box which is a random weapon generator. It contains 40 weapons at 5 different rarities. When bought a random weapon is rolled it also encourages players to take risks and adds strategic depth to their decision-making, as they must adapt their gameplay style based on the weapon they receive. Whether it's a powerful legendary firearm or a more common weapon, the mystery box introduces an element of chance that keeps the survival experience dynamic.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2108840/extras/guns.gif?t=1701373972"><br/><br/><strong>V5.14 Version</strong><br/><u>- 40 Weapons</u><br/><u>- 5 Maps ( ENIGMA, DEMO, REDFALL RETREAT, REDFALL, STALK )</u><br/><u>- 4 Gamemodes ( Survivor, Gungame, Timed, Speed+ )</u><br/><u>- 10 Perks ( Life, Health, Reload, Agility, Spread, Damage, Blast, Trigger, Magnet, Vision  )</u><br/><u>- Weapon upgrade/rarity system</u><br/><u>- 2 Different currencies Points &amp; Scrap</u><br/><u>- 10 Powerups ( Max ammo, Nuke, Shadow, Resupply, Time skip, Rapid fire, Instakill, Vampyrism, 2x Points, Sale )</u><br/><u>- 5 Grenades  ( Grenade, Impact grenade, Distract grenade, Frost grenade, Fire grenade )</u><br/><u>- Weapon skin customization ( 200 levels to earn )</u><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2108840/extras/JKFYREDDOOR.png?t=1701373972"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only Wish</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2542010/Only_Wish/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2542010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Only Wish</h2><br/>Welcome to "Only Wish", the next-generation advancement of the acclaimed "Only Up" genre. Embark on an unparalleled gaming journey enriched with breathtaking landscapes, groundbreaking gameplay, and an array of unique features that set it apart.<h2 class="bb_tag">Uncover Hidden Realms</h2>Delve into the heart of mystery. Every door you encounter conceals secrets and untold stories, beckoning you to discover what lies beyond.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2542010/extras/door.gif?t=1701370785"><h2 class="bb_tag">Revolutionary Vehicular Exploration</h2>Why limit your exploration to walking? Jump into a diverse selection of vehicles and traverse the vast expanses of our world. Feel the pulse of authentic driving dynamics and harness the full power of vehicle propulsion.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2542010/extras/car_driving.gif?t=1701370785"><h2 class="bb_tag">Engaging NPC Dialogues</h2><br/>Deepen your immersion with intricate interactions from our varied NPCs. Each conversation is designed to amplify your engagement and propel the storyline. Engage with characters, unravel hidden tales, and make pivotal decisions that could alter the trajectory of your adventure. Enter a realm where dialogue is an art, and every character weaves their own unique narrative.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2542010/extras/marcel.gif?t=1701370785"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potion Brew: Co-op</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2226750/Potion_Brew_Coop/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2226750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2226750/extras/Online_co-op.png?t=1701369356"><br/>Spend your in-game time with your friends!<br/>The game supports an online co-op mode (up to 5 players).<br/>There is also a proximity voice chat.<br/>Help each other, split into roles, brew potions together!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2226750/extras/Game_features.png?t=1701369356"><br/>The main goal of the game is to <strong>brew potions</strong> for your guests. There are two ways to sell your potions: active and passive.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Active selling</strong> - open a shop for a constant flow of guests for a given time and brew ordered potions. The success rate of completed orders will matter.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2226750/extras/Active.gif?t=1701369356"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Passive selling</strong> - no need to rush, brew any potions you want and put them on the sale shelf.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2226750/extras/Passive.gif?t=1701369356"><br/>Choose the one that you like the most.<br/><br/><strong>Rivals</strong> are waiting for you. They sell potions, just like you. Get ready to interfere with each other!<br/><br/>Wander through the magical forest and <strong>collect ingredients</strong>. Brew potions from them or sell them to a trader!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2226750/extras/Trading.gif?t=1701369356"><br/><br/><strong>The Build Mode</strong> lets you arrange in your house everything the way you want!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2226750/extras/Build.gif?t=1701369356"><br/><br/>Get new <strong>hairstyles and clothes</strong> with the earned gold and experiment with outfits.<br/><br/><strong>Happy brewing!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guardian: Planet Defense</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368540/Guardian_Planet_Defense/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take command of an orbiting defense satellite in this action-packed planetary defense shooter. Blast away at waves of incoming asteroids and crafty aliens before they break through your shields and damage your planet. Scavenge powerful weapons from vanquished alien ships and turn them against your foes. Endless levels provide an ever increasing challenge. How long can you survive?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAGMONTON</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2253110/RAGMONTON/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2253110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ragmonton is a Physics-Based Ragdoll Roguelike &gt; Fight enemies by collecting and combining your body parts for special powers, discover transformations, acquire unique relics and modify your power in a way that every run is unique.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2253110/extras/storehead1.png?t=1701367873"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Physics.<br/></li><li> Funny Ragdolls.<br/></li><li> Up to 4 players.<br/></li><li> Transformations.<br/></li><li> Random Levels.<br/></li><li> Roguelike Relics.<br/></li><li> An Intense Game.<br/></li><li> Retro Story Reimagining.<br/></li><li> Ragdoll Physics + Roguelike + Party Game.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2253110/extras/storehead2.png?t=1701367873"><br/>Discover Transformations !!!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2253110/extras/gif9.gif?t=1701367873"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOS OPS!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2475460/SOS_OPS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475460/extras/0000-0177_6.gif?t=1701367630"><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fam4VXzJKmp" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475460/extras/06_600x125.gif?t=1701367630"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Your beloved town is in danger!</strong></h2>Stay alert 24/7 to keep the situation in the town under control. No fires or lost cats allowed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475460/extras/SOS_10.gif?t=1701367630"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Ok, you've received the emergency call.</strong></h2> No worries. Just start your engines and HURRY UP, YOU LAZY #*$%#@*&amp;$#&amp;*!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475460/extras/SOS_02.gif?t=1701367630"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>You can try to fight the fire.</strong></h2> It's not that simple, and sometimes it can be a little dangerous, but people believe in you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475460/extras/ezgif.com-optimize__2_.gif?t=1701367630"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Or you can play football.</strong></h2>Yes, it's an emergency situation, but the ball seems so lonely here.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475460/extras/ezgif.com-optimize__1_.gif?t=1701367630"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>The cats are lonely too.</strong></h2>Grab them and find them a suitable place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2475460/extras/ezgif.com-optimize__4_.gif?t=1701367630"><br/><br/>Contact us: media@artdock.studio						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matchpoop</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2508090/Matchpoop/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2508090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Battle Against the Invasion of Sinister Poops!</h2>Following an ominous crimson moon, a portal to the depths of Hell's Septic Tank has been breached. The insidious legions of hellish poops have surged forth with an insatiable desire to conquer your bathroom! Will you rise to the challenge, thwart the invasion, and unravel the mystery behind this chaotic onslaught?<h2 class="bb_tag">Engaging Gameplay Mechanics</h2>Embark on an enthralling journey through 250 hand crafted levels, brimming with captivating mechanics and narrative elements woven into the gameplay.<h2 class="bb_tag">Confront Malevolent Overlords</h2>Put your skills to the test as you confront a diverse array of poop overlords and their relentless hordes. Each overlord presents a unique set of abilities and challenges, demanding strategic prowess and careful planning.<br/><br/>With destiny hanging in the balance, can you emerge as the triumphant champion, vanquishing the invasion and securing your rightful place as the ultimate poop-slaying hero?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turok 3: Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1996770/Turok_3_Shadow_of_Oblivion_Remastered/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/raptor_jumps.gif?t=1701367237"><br/><br/><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> is a faithful restoration of the classic first-person shooter originally released in 2000 for the Nintendo 64, upgraded through Nightdive Studios’ proprietary KEX Engine for play on modern gaming devices with up to a 4K resolution at 120FPS. <br/><br/>It joins Nightdive Studios and Universal Games popular Turok and Turok 2: Seeds of Evil remasters, capping off the trilogy. <i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> features upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<h2 class="bb_tag">FINISH THE HUNT</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/sniper_one_eye.gif?t=1701367237"><br/><br/><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> is the first title from Nightdive Studios to be remastered using the latest version KEX engine, which utilizes an improved renderer to achieve a higher tier of visual fidelity across 3D models, textures, and graphical effects.<h2 class="bb_tag"><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> Key Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A remastered version of the 2000 classic, available for the first time since its Nintendo 64 release<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS performance<br/></li><li>Advanced rendering features, including anti-aliasing, bloom, ambient occlusion, dynamic shadows, and motion blur	<br/></li><li>Remastered environment art, character models, and updated weapon models<br/></li><li>Brand new Achievements</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/robot.gif?t=1701367237"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1100320/Rest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1100320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Rest is a walking simulator with a dark and beautiful aesthetic where the environment tells the story. Travel to a monochrome world where you will experience an impactful narrative about guilt and loss. <br/><br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li></li></ul>Selective Color Scheme - Rest features a selective color scheme, where the entire world is monochrome, with objects of interest being colored.<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li></li></ul>Compelling Narrative - Uncover the tragic story of a grief stricken soul.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Series 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2655650/Hidden_Series_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2655650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In Hidden Series 2 Game all you need to do is focus on the items listed, tap on the hidden objects and complete the challenge in the best time. On completing a level it gives the gamer the chance to play the next level, Hidden Series 1 has 30+ stupendous levels that has enthralling game play and levels with various genre. Take  the brain teaser challenge and find the hidden objects as quickly as possible. Discover the unlimited fun of finding objects, highly replayable!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>30+ Levels of Unlimited fun to find Hidden Objects<br/></li><li>Best Timings and Best Clicks to keep this challenging with friends and family<br/></li><li>Multi language support<br/></li><li>Relaxing music to keep the players engaged in the object hunt</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goalgetter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1676860/Goalgetter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676860/extras/torschtzTest100_1_en.png?t=1701364690"><br/><br/>In the first-person football career simulator, you can make your dream of becoming a top striker in one of the major European leagues come true.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676860/extras/powerAilton_test3_180_1.png?t=1701364690"><br/><br/>You are a young, talented striker. Now, you have the opportunity to play professional football. Secure your spot through intense training or try to win the favor of fans and the coach in other ways. Give interviews, participate in TV shows, and read about your last game in the newspaper. Find the right agent to optimize your career.<br/><br/>But your personal life matters too. Do you want to get married, have children, and become a homeowner, or do you prefer a sports car? Will you risk it all at the casino, or slowly save your salary? Invest in stocks from various sectors and monitor their performance, or do you want to put your money into more speculative ventures? The decisions are yours alone to make. Sign endorsement deals and boost your popularity on social media through appropriate actions. Move to other teams and employ your personal fitness or mental coach.<br/><br/>Be careful not to fall in with the wrong crowd or get too distracted from football.<br/><br/>Win the favor of the national coach and participate in World and European Championships. Play with your favorite club in national and international cup and league matches. The game covers all major competitions.<br/><br/>In the game, do you want to dive, play for the team, or focus more on your personal success? Passing or shooting, time-wasting or counterattacking, playing on the offside line or provoking the opponent – it's all in your hands!<br/><br/>In addition to your career, with Goalgetter, you can also replay historic World Cup tournaments. Play as a striker in the 2022 World Cup, or do you want to experience the Miracle of Bern in 1954? It's up to you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676860/extras/featuresTest60_kl1.png?t=1701364690"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676860/extras/balken1.png?t=1701364690"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Extensive Content</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Simulate your player's entire career, from their first professional contract at the age of 17 to retirement.<br/></li><li> Replay historic World Cup tournaments.<br/></li><li> Take control of any national team in the world.<br/></li><li> Includes all major leagues and cup competitions such as the World Cup, European Championship, Club World Cup, Nations League, Champions League, Europa League, Conference League, Cup, League Cup, Super Cup, and more.<br/></li><li> Play with up to 4 players on one PC or through Steam Remote Play.<br/></li><li> You have full control over the game world. Customize players, leagues, countries, referees, and teams to your liking.<br/></li><li> Share your self-created editor and community content with other players through the Steam Workshop.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676860/extras/balken1.png?t=1701364690"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Impressive Presentation</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Beautiful 3D graphics in corresponding locations such as the stadium, locker room, office, casino, living room, etc.<br/></li><li> Former Goalgetter Ailton explains the intricacies of the professional football business to you in over 40 minutes of videos in the "Ask Ailton" feature.<br/></li><li> Detailed statistics.<br/></li><li> Engage in intense conversations with teammates, your girlfriend, agent, coach, etc. in 3D.<br/></li><li> Experience action-packed gameplay from a first-person perspective.<br/></li><li> Numerous realistic and occasionally humorous events add variety to the gameplay.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676860/extras/balken1.png?t=1701364690"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Infinite Possibilities</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Make the right decisions and apply the appropriate shooting techniques in live matches.<br/></li><li> Live-game options cover all aspects of modern football.<br/></li><li> Improve your 15 skills through training. Do you want to follow the coach's instructions or set your own priorities?<br/></li><li> Work on your 6 character traits, as this is the only way to exclusively benefit from the positive effects of the character trait.<br/></li><li> Choose 2 special abilities at the beginning of the game and acquire up to 11 more, such as Header Beast, Battle Pig, Monster Shot.<br/></li><li> Request favors from your teammates or help them secure their place in the team.<br/></li><li> Give interviews in newspapers and on television.<br/></li><li> Host fan parties and gatherings for your teammates.<br/></li><li> Enhance your popularity with teammates, fans, coaches, national coaches, the press, and others through various conversations and actions.<br/></li><li> Receive video tips from striker legend Ailton and thus improve your skills.<br/></li><li> Become a team council member and team captain, leading the national team as captain onto the field.<br/></li><li> Do you want to negotiate contracts yourself or hire an agent?<br/></li><li> Employ private fitness trainers, physiotherapists, or mental coaches.<br/></li><li> Enjoy your personal life, take vacations, host parties, start a family, and make friends, but be mindful not to jeopardize your fitness.<br/></li><li> Keep your girlfriend happy, negotiate sponsorship deals, and donate money to charitable causes.<br/></li><li> Become a social media star and increase your follower count with relevant posts.<br/></li><li> Purchase cars, houses, and other luxury items.<br/></li><li> Establish your own company and invest your football-related income in it.<br/></li><li> Visit the casino and play roulette or try your luck on a slot machine.<br/></li><li> Pay attention to your health to avoid long-term injuries and consider appropriate insurance.<br/></li><li> Invest in stocks and monitor their performance, or would you prefer to allocate your funds differently?</li></ul><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FDz2jg7nz3Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676860/extras/discord21.png?t=1701364690"/></a><br/><br/>Subsidized by the Federal Ministry for Economic Affairs and Climate Action.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676860/extras/BMWK_en.png?t=1701364690"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gangs of Sherwood</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1351000/Gangs_of_Sherwood/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1351000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1351000/extras/Sherwood_Description_EN_1.jpg?t=1701363873"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1351000/extras/Gif_1.gif?t=1701363873"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1351000/extras/Sherwood_Description_EN_2.jpg?t=1701363873"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1351000/extras/Gif_2.gif?t=1701363873"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1351000/extras/Sherwood_Description_EN_3.jpg?t=1701363873"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1351000/extras/Gif_3.gif?t=1701363873"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1351000/extras/Sherwood_Description_EN_4.jpg?t=1701363873"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1351000/extras/Gif_4.gif?t=1701363873"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakout Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2468060/Breakout_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2468060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Breakout Survivors brings classic <strong>Breakout gameplay</strong> together with <strong>Survivors-like mechanics</strong> in a single game. Destroy bricks with your balls before they reach you. Gain XP, Level Up and Pick Upgrades to help you in holding out against waves of falling bricks.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Easy to play with simple and fun controls<br/></li><li> Fight against procedurally generated waves of increasing difficulty<br/></li><li> Improve throughout your run through dozens of upgrades<br/></li><li> Select your weapons from a wide choice of powerful balls<br/></li><li> Unlock new kind of Balls and try new strategies<br/></li><li> Compete for the High Score in the Online Leaderboards</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assembly Line 2 Mobile Version</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2691010/Assembly_Line_2_Mobile_Version/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2691010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Assembly Line 2, the sequel to the factory-building and managing game.<br>
<br>
Assembly Line 2 combines elements from idle and tycoon games. Make the most money by using different types of machines to build an assembly line to craft resources and sell them. Unlock upgrades to make it more efficient and expand your factory.<br>
<br>
The goal is simple, build resources and sell them. Starting with a few machines and very basic resources, and using them with more advanced machines to craft and create more complex resources.<br>
<br>
Your factory will continue generating money even when you are offline. When you return to the game you will have piles of money waiting for you, but don't spend it all in one place!<br/>
<br/>
While Assembly Line 2 is an idle game, because you make the layout of your factory, it is up to you to optimize it to make the most money possible.<br/>
<br/>
Don't worry if you get lost with all those machines to build, the game offers an information menu so you can see what each machine does at any time. It also offers information on each resource price, so you can make decisions on what to craft. You can also see stats on the amount you are producing.<br/>
<br/>
Features:<br/>
- 20+ different machines to build and optimize the best factory.<br/>
- Tons of upgrades to increase productivity.<br/>
- More than 50 different unique resources to craft.<br/>
- Multi-language support.<br/>
- Back up your progress.<br/>
- No internet required.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Wonderland Solitaire</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2688790/Happy_Wonderland_Solitaire/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Enjoy the popular card game with 150 different solitaire variants and a beautiful winter ambiance!<br>
The game includes solitaire variants such as Freecell, Fan, Four Seasons, Klondike, Spider, Bakers Dozen, Canfield, Golf, Sir Tommy and many more.<br>
For each solitaire variant there is also a helpful tutorial during the game, so that even unknown game variants can be learned quickly. <br>
If you wish, you can view information about each card during the game. Happy Wonderland offers many different card decks, card backs and backgrounds.<br>
<br>
Suitable for beginners as well as avid solitaire players, this collection offers many hours of enjoyable solitaire fun and challenging gameplay.        <br>
<br/>
<br/>
The special features of "Happy Wonderland Solitaire":<br/>
    - 150 solitaire variants with winter and Christmas ambience<br/>
    - Various, hand-drawn card sets and matching cover sheets and backgrounds<br/>
    - Easy-to-understand help for quick start and easy handling						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake's Halloween Night</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2528580/Jakes_Halloween_Night/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2528580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>"It's October 31, follow Jake as he gets ready for a killer Halloween party."</strong><br/><br/>Jake's Halloween Night is a short horror game inspired by old slasher movies, that at the same time, makes a bit of fun of said genre.<br/>The project originally started, developed, and finished in October 2021 as a personal challenge, but now comes back remastered with new art, improved graphics, and lots of new secrets.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2></strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Pixel art visuals.<br/></li><li>Drawn cutscenes and objects.<br/></li><li>Story-driven with environmental storytelling.<br/></li><li>Three endings.<br/></li><li>A couple of classic (and cliche) horror references.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2><br/>The game has a duration of 15 to 25 minutes of gameplay, with simple puzzles. If you enjoy clicking everything to find bits of information in your surroundings, and piecing together the untold events going on, this game is for you.<br/><br/><strong>Controls:</strong><br/>Full screen: F4<br/>Move: WASD / Arrow keys<br/>Interact: Enter<br/>Menu: E<br/>Cancel: Esc / X<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2528580/extras/GameDivision.png?t=1701362472"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ace Racers SP</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2685150/Ace_Racers_SP/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685150/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ace Racers SP is designed to be an FPV drone racing simulator for space drones. The purpose of the project was to make a platform for players to create and share unlimited obstacles and maneuvering challenges for the practice of thrust physics vehicles, primarily a 6axis RCS spaceship. Also available in game is a "lunar lander" style vehicle, and a "forward only" style vehicle (which only moves forward), as well as a 6axis space vehicle purpose built for pushing freight around like a space barge. <br>
<br>
Although formatted with many similarities to a racing game, and titled as a racing game, the primary function of the game is to create courses and obstacle arrangements for the purpose of expanding the available unique maneuvers to practice for the vehicle type. It is possible to export and import saved courses/obstacle arrangements, and the end-goal of the project is to collect an ever increasing database of course material for players to sift through and expand their capabilities with the sticks. <br>
<br>
It IS possible to "race" yourself, although the course order and timing system are intended not for the purpose of player competition, but rather for the purpose of making it easier to share very specific arrangements/courses. By being able to create a course which highlights the next checkpoint it is possible to make a course, save the course order, and for another player to then "race" the course, without having to find a map or video instruction on the specific pattern of checkpoints. The course will simply tell you where to go next and when you are ready to fly without the racing system you can, or you can choose to continue to use the racing system in order to see your lap-times and compare them with your previous laps. <br>
<br>
This game was not designed with keyboard and mouse in mind, and instead was originally conceived as a way to make use of my own home-made 6axis controller. It is BEST played with some form of "space game rig" , for example a 6axis hotas, space mouse, or for some people a gamepad is adequate, if not a bit unintuitive for 6axis. The best "lunar lander" flight performance I personally have ever seen posted on the internet, was in the classic game "Lunar Flight" and was performed by a player claiming to have flown ONLY using keyboard (no mouse), and therefore the default control configuration for my game is also keyboard-only, as although I prefer my 4joystick gamepad , I am confident that keyboard-only is simply the superior choice over keyboard and mouse. This game uses Rewired so virtually any controller can be set up/configured by the player, although most/all should not be set up by default.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What games does your dad play - 你老豆玩乜GAME</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2690680/What_games_does_your_dad_play__GAME/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							What games does your dad play - It is a management game with the theme of running a game center, and players can replay a variety of stalls, electronic games, etc. from the 80s, 90s, and even 2000s.<br>
<br>
Operating a Game Center:<br>
Each game also requires a certain amount of funds and specific game tickets to build, and some also require employees to operate, so some need to increase manpower appropriately. In addition, all games also need maintenance and the center needs to be cleaned otherwise there will be fewer customers. You can also hire receptionists to increase the number of customers.<br>
<br>
Mini-games:<br>
In addition, every game in the game can also be played. Players only need to go to the game and press "E" to enter the mini-game.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Three more games were added to the first release:<br/>
1. Alien race - A shooting game where players avoid bullets while shooting alien creatures.<br/>
2. City ​​defense tower - A city defense game where players use two turrets to shoot down missiles all over the sky to defend the city.<br/>
3. Happy Block - An intellectual game where players need to put the scattered numbers in order.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lair of Anubis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2121000/Lair_of_Anubis/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2121000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Lair of Anubis is a short first-person horror adventure game. You became an archaeologist to uncover the truths of ancient civilisations. But your greatest desire has always been to discover a pyramid for yourself and have your name written in the history books. Just yesterday, a strange old man with unusual hieroglyphs tattooed on his face, the type you have never seen before, told you of a pyramid hidden deep in the sand, accessible only once every few centuries. You didn't put much stock in the story, but decided to investigate it anyway.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>Explore ancient pyramid full of mysteries. Collect items, solve puzzles, escape death traps and don't get caught!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2121000/extras/1.gif?t=1701362635"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>A story that builds intensity in a dynamic environment. The deeper you go, the more you will be drawn into a web of suspense, emotions and revelations that will keep you hooked until the very end. The end is inevitable. Lair of Anubis offers approximately 1.5 hours of gameplay and has 2 different endings.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2121000/extras/2.gif?t=1701362635"><h2 class="bb_tag">Examine system</h2>Explore interactive objects in a detailed 3D environment, carefully examining each element for a fully immersive experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2121000/extras/3.gif?t=1701362635"><h2 class="bb_tag">Puzzle solving</h2>Navigate your way through the environment by solving puzzles and avoiding deadly traps.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2121000/extras/4.gif?t=1701362635"><h2 class="bb_tag">You are not alone</h2>As you explore the pyramid, keep your eyes open and don't get caught!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2121000/extras/5.gif?t=1701362635"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A guard walks into a tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1536470/A_guard_walks_into_a_tavern/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1536470/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are a guard appointed by His Majesty, partnering with an imp to post bounties and send heroes to investigate strange occurrences and deal with monsters.<br/><br/>In addition to your hard work and side jobs to make ends meet, you have to maintain the reputation of factions to ensure your survival without being fired or assassinated. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1536470/extras/2023_main.png?t=1701389040"><h2 class="bb_tag">Introduction</h2>◆This is a narrative driven simulation game with management elements, where the storyline for each playthrough will be randomly generated from three main stories (each with 4 endings) and nearly a hundred sidestories.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1536470/extras/2023_story.png?t=1701389040"><br/><br/>◆Guard simulation: <br/>Deal with bounties; Make choices when poeple come to you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1536470/extras/2023_work_en.png?t=1701389040"><br/><br/>◆Enter the tavern:<br/>Hire heroes; Manipulate the equipment market; Maintain relationships with factions...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1536470/extras/2023_tarven_en.png?t=1701389040"><br/><br/>◆Fishing during work<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1536470/extras/2023_fishing_en.png?t=1701389040"><br/><br/>◆Raise your family and deal with family affairs<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1536470/extras/2023_family_en.png?t=1701389040"><br/><br/>◆Explore the city: <br/>The black market; Arena; Casino; Mystery locations in the sewers...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1536470/extras/2023heishi_EN.png?t=1701389040"><br/><br/>◆Get endings; Collect butterflies; Unlock decorations, special branches, and additional benefits for the next playthrough.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1536470/extras/shop_btf.gif?t=1701389040"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turf Wars: A Snail Escape</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2058360/Turf_Wars_A_Snail_Escape/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2058360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Get ready for a slimy adventure in 'Turf Wars: A Snail Escape'! As a colorful snail hero, you'll need to navigate through dangerous areas, battle difficult bosses, and expand your turf before your enemies do. This isn't just any garden - it's a roguelike adventure bursting with upgrades. So, are you ready to out-slime your foes and head out on this epic snail-paced adventure? (just kidding, it's fast!🐌)<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2058360/extras/SteamDescription_-_SurvivalGuide.png?t=1701360001"><br/>The garden is a dangerous place, so follow these tips:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Remain on your turf<br/></li><li>Plan your moves and make sure you got an escape route<br/></li><li>Pick weapons and upgrades strategically</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2058360/extras/Steam1.gif?t=1701360001"><br/>Using the right slime type will be the difference between easily sliding down the garden or drying out.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Grey - Unclaimed territory<br/></li><li>Yellow - Fast &amp; recharges weapons<br/></li><li>Green - Ultrafast!<br/></li><li>Red - Ultraslow!<br/></li><li>Black - Hurts... a lot</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2058360/extras/Steam3.gif?t=1701360001"><br/>A wild variety of powerful weapons and tools awaits. Equip up to 4 out of the 20 unique items available, try out different slime types, and unlock over 100 upgrades. Earn coins for in-run upgrades or gather gems to unlock permanent enhancements. Prepare for endless possibilities where you need to constantly adapt your strategy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2058360/extras/SteamDescription_-_AccessAbility.png?t=1701360001"><br/><br/>We strive to offer an inclusive gaming experience for all players, so you can always turn on the dedicated colorblind mode that utilizes shapes instead of colors. You can also navigate the garden with either controller or keyboard, both with remapping and autofire options, offering flexibility and freedom in how you play. More inexperienced snails can also turn down the heat a bit with extra difficulty settings.<br/><br/>So what are you waiting for? Gear up and jump into the Turf Wars - the battle awaits!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinball M</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2337640/Pinball_M/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-1.png?t=1701360173"><br/><br/>The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-2.png?t=1701360173"><br/><br/>- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free<br/>- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage<br/>- Thrilling competition<br/>- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation<h2 class="bb_tag">Sink your teeth into these tables as purchasable DLC: </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">- Chucky's Killer Pinball:</h2> Step into a twisted realm where the innocent becomes sinister, and the playful turns menacing. Navigate through an eerie playfield where Chucky lurks in the shadows, ready to pounce.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Dead by Daylight™️ Pinball:</h2> Become the hunter or even the hunted in a thrilling fusion of classic pinball and the excitement of one of the most popular horror games ever created.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Duke Nukem's Big Shot Pinball:</h2> Enjoy the biggest, grooviest, most BADASS pinball table ever made packed with guns and babes. Push start and play with balls of steel!<h2 class="bb_tag">- The Thing Pinball: </h2>Use your pinball skills and battle against the shape-shifting alien through the arctic chill of U.S. Outpost #31. Can you trust anyone, even yourself?<br/>- Even more coming...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-4.png?t=1701360173"><br/><br/>Wishlist and find out more.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crashy Laps</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2257410/Crashy_Laps/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Description</h2></strong><br/>Crashy Laps is a game to enjoy driving and overtaking aggressively where collisions and foul play are common, with a maximum of 4 Players. 20 little and funny tracks are waiting for you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/animation_race.gif?t=1701359029"><br/><br/>In Single Player mode, you can also compete to reach the Best Time in the Leaderboard of each track.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/animation_timetrial.gif?t=1701359029"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2></strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Use one or more <strong>Gamepads </strong>🎮, or <strong>Keyboard </strong>⌨️: you can use Keyboard for playing a maximum of 2 players at the same time.<br/></li><li>4 Settings for each part of day: Morning, Midday ☀, Evening 🌄 and Night 🌛.<br/></li><li>4 Competitions: Time Trial, Quick Race, Grand Prix and Championship.<br/></li><li>4 Areas with their own settings: road grip, environment, terrain types, etc.<br/></li><li>4 Tracks for each Area: <strong>16 Tracks + 4 Track variants.</strong><br/></li><li>3 AI 🤖 Difficulties: Novice, Professional and Expert.<br/></li><li>2 selectable Camera Views: <strong>Isometric or Top-down</strong>. Zoom in or out to adjust screen for aspects ratio from 4:3 until 21:9.<br/></li><li>2 selectable Engine Sounds: Combustion or Electric.<br/></li><li><strong>Customization</strong>: customize the number and the car colours.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/animation_customization_600px.gif?t=1701359029"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Competitions</h2></strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Time Trial 🏎️: play in Single Player mode and try to reach your Best Time and the World Record for each track.<br/></li><li>Quick Race, from 🏎️🏎️ to 🏎️🏎️🏎️🏎️: play a 4 laps race.<br/></li><li>Grand Prix 🏎️🏎️🏎️🏎️: play a Grand Prix with a qualifying lap for each player and 4 laps race.<br/></li><li>Championship 🏎️🏎️🏎️🏎️: play a Championship competing in the 4 Tracks of the selected Area and reach the Championship Cups by the selected difficulty.</li></ul><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Zones</h2></strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Candy Lands</strong>: drive in a sweet world where the mud is chocolate, on simple roads great for beginners.<br/></li><li><strong>Alpine Bridge</strong>: drive in an alpine area, always crossing bridges and tunnels.<br/></li><li><strong>Silver Dunes</strong>: drive in a desert area, on rough and uneven roads.<br/></li><li><strong>Frosty Way</strong>: drive in an icy area surrounded by snowy mountains, on slippery and twisty roads.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/animation_area_cl_150px.gif?t=1701359029"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/animation_area_ab_150px.gif?t=1701359029"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/animation_area_sd_150px.gif?t=1701359029"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/animation_area_fw_150px.gif?t=1701359029"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Around the World</strong>: drive in a tracks selection of the previous areas, with some changes.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/wish_game.gif?t=1701359029"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/maincol_gradient_rule.png?t=1701359029"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/letreros_descipcion.png?t=1701359029"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/maincol_gradient_rule.png?t=1701359029"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2252680?utm_source=steam&amp;utm_campaign=descrip" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/Farlands100.png?t=1701359029"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2103370?utm_source=steam&amp;utm_campaign=descrip" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/finis100.png?t=1701359029"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2295430?utm_source=steam&amp;utm_campaign=descrip" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/Dungeon100.png?t=1701359029"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2295610?utm_source=steam&amp;utm_campaign=descrip" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/Abathor100.png?t=1701359029"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1191660?utm_source=steam&amp;utm_campaign=descrip" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/Rebel100.png?t=1701359029"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2095510?utm_source=steam&amp;utm_campaign=descrip" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/Scholar100.png?t=1701359029"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/maincol_gradient_rule.png?t=1701359029"><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fjandusoft" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2257410/extras/discord.png?t=1701359029"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Axe Party VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2343290/Axe_Party_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2343290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Welcome to the Party! 🪓🪓🪓</h2><br/>Axe Party VR is a virtual reality axe-throwing experience. Compete against your friends or your own high score with 3 exciting and challenging game modes. <br/>Unlike other titles, our multiplayer is contained in a single VR headset allowing you to show off your axe-throwing skills and compete with your friends locally, without having to purchase multiple devices.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Modes</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>1. Classic Axe Throw: 5 throws per round. 3 rounds. Highest score wins. <br/></li><li>2. BreakRoom: A room of fun gadgets and breakables.<br/></li><li>3. Axe Hunt: Hunt virtual birds with axes.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eye of Nollyn</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2148780/Eye_of_Nollyn/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2148780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2148780/extras/A_the_Game.png?t=1701356140"><br/><br/>Not all detectives are geniuses.<br/><br/>Not all of them are nice.<br/><br/>Not all of them are legal.<br/><br/>In the city Nollyn, where money is what counts and what rules, is the private eye, Vin Virosa. He returns from years of hiatus as he's requested a case investigation from the president of Wilsons Corporation, the electric power corporation of the city. But as the investigation continues, something doesn't seem right...<br/><br/>Meet your clients, solve cases you're commissioned to, and receive the pay you deserve.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Game Features</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Intuitive Controls<br/>"Eye of Nollyn" features simple controls designed for players of varying expertise. whether you're an experienced veteran or new to the world of detective games, you'll find the controls intuitive and easy, ensuring an overall seamless and enjoyable gameplay experience.<br/></li><li> Intriguing Storyline<br/>The game "Eye of Nollyn" features an intricate and delicate storyline with plot twists after another. Become Nollyn's private investigator and solve crime cases emerging from the city's dark, mysterious alleys.<br/></li><li> Engaging Questions<br/>Test your reasoning with a unique combination of multiple-choice and short-answer questions in the game "Eye of Nollyn". Crafted to be challenging and yet fair, these questions will push your intellect without resorting to absurdity. <br/></li><li> Bribery System<br/>Still scared to try out the game? In "Eye of Nollyn," players have the option to bribe NPCs to extract additional information that might help them solve mysteries. With strategic bribery, players can gain valuable insights, making the game accessible and engaging for all.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
