<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>STAR WARS™: Battlefront Classic Collection</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2446550/STAR_WARS_Battlefront_Classic_Collection/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2446550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Fight in iconic battles from across the STAR WARS™ galaxy</h2>Play the classic STAR WARS Battlefront games, online and offline in this complete classic collection.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>This Classic Collection includes: </strong></h2><strong>STAR WARS Battlefront (Classic)</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Includes Bonus Map: Jabba's Palace</li></ul><strong>STAR WARS Battlefront II</strong><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Includes Bonus Maps: Bespin: Cloud City, Rhen Var: Harbor, Rhen Var: Citadel, and Yavin 4: Arena <br/></li><li> Includes Bonus Heroes: Asajj Ventress &amp; Kit Fisto</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features</strong></h2><i>Traverse the Galaxy in Campaign Mode &amp; Galactic Conquest</i> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Galactic Conquest: Devise your strategy, recruit your troops, and execute your tactical vision for conquering the galaxy. <br/></li><li>STAR WARS™  Battlefront Campaign: Experience iconic battles from STAR WARS Episodes I-VI<br/></li><li>STAR WARS™  Battlefront II Campaign: Join the rise of Darth Vader’s elite 501st Legion of Stormtroopers</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Massive Locations with up to 64-player Online Support</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on the ground: Wookiee Warriors, Jet Troopers, Droidekas and more in massive multiplayer action<br/></li><li>Drive iconic vehicles: Speeder Bikes, AT-STs, AT-RTs, and more in offensive and defensive battles<br/></li><li>Pilot legendary starships: TIE fighters, X-wings, and more in space and air dogfights</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Expanded Hero Assault</strong> </h2>Hero Assault is playable on all ground maps including: Death Star, Kashyyyk, Kamino, and Naboo for the first time ever<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight with heroes: Mace Windu, Yoda, Luke Skywalker, and many others!<br/></li><li>Battle with villains: Darth Maul, General Grievous, Darth Vader, and many others!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MechWarrior 5: Mercenaries - Solaris Showdown</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2782050/MechWarrior_5_Mercenaries__Solaris_Showdown/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							SOLARIS SHOWDOWN<br/>Fresh off a successful mission for the notorious Mercenary Star, Mason and crew journey to the Hardcore system where they collide with 'Mech pilot Duncan Fisher embarking on a quest to secure a spot in the FedCom Unification Tournament. Forming an unlikely alliance, Mason and Fisher traverse the shadows of Solaris, engage in harrowing 'Mech duels, and race against the clock to save the day - a true Solaris Showdown.<br/><br/>Join Duncan Fisher in a race against time to thwart the overthrow of the Solaris Council, discover the new Loader King 'Mech, collect 11 new Gladiator 'Mech variants, select new weapons and equipment tailored for close-quarter engagements, and help save the very future of Solaris<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Assist Duncan Fisher on his zany adventures, and witness his ascension as the official and iconic Voice of Solaris<br/></li><li>Seek fortune and Fame with new Arena Missions and reward system<br/></li><li>Solaris Showdown adds the new Loader King 'Mech chassis with 6 variants, including the mighty Hero LDK-IDM 'Indomitable'<br/></li><li>Collect 11 new 'Mech variants designed specifically for the intense Gladiator-style combat of the BattleMech arenas<br/></li><li>Select from an array of new Gladiator-style weaponry and equipment<br/></li><li>Enhancements to MechLab, AI Improvements, and various other free QoL updates</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Shire: Room One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517850/Toy_Shire_Room_One/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FkhSxB2MSgD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/Toy_Shire_-_Discord_Banner.png?t=1710352808"/></a><br/><br/><br/>Play through the <strong>three levels in Kevin's Room</strong> and defend your room against your old toys. Face Memphis-X in the final level and put a stop to his assault as he crushes your soldiers in an attempt to get to your base.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyVengeance.png?t=1710352808"><br/>You received new toys from your family. Isn't that lovely? Oh, it's for sure... <br/>Your old toys, though, aren't getting along as well. They are no longer cared for and have been forgotten. So what follows next? They're going to join together against you and assault your brand-new toys, so be prepared. But never worry! You're in luck since your brand-new toys are troops of green soldiers. They still require your aid though! Control, strengthen, and defeat the opposing forces! However, focus with care, the enemies you encounter might not be your old playthings!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/InteractiveTowerDefense.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Tower building alone won't be sufficient to repel incoming attackers. Build up your own troops in the best feasible positions, then unleash attacks into enemy territory. Never abandon your towers, and deploy your troops in accordance with the traits of the enemy. First, the attacking forces will attempt to get past your defenses. Build and improve towers to aid your army. By using unique abilities, you can support your troops and towers as well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/EpicBattles.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Safeguard your base against waves of attackers. You need to pick the right troops if you would like to prevail. Clean the paths and guard any open routes. Upgrade your troops and unlock new ones to take down the waves and claim victory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyRealm.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Enter a world and a narrative built around the toys that enriched your youth, including toy soldiers, dinosaur sets, robots, building blocks, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_3.gif?t=1710352808"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dune: Imperium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1689500/Dune_Imperium/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Header.png?t=1710364055"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body0_2.png?t=1710364055"><br/>Experience the ultimate blend of strategy and intrigue as you navigate the treacherous landscapes of Arrakis in the award-winning board game <i>Dune: Imperium</i>!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle online, locally with AI, or against the formidable House Hagal.<br/></li><li>Earn Achievements that showcase your prowess as a leader.<br/></li><li>Embark on more than a dozen Challenges that will test your wit and cunning.<br/></li><li>Compete for badges in the rotating Skirmish Mode where no two games are the same!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body1_2.png?t=1710364055"><br/>Arrakis. Dune. Desert Planet. Raise your banner above the vast wasteland before you. As the Great Houses of the Landsraad marshal their forces and their spies, whom will you influence, and whom will you betray? A tyrannical Emperor. The secretive Bene Gesserit. The shrewd Spacing Guild. The ferocious Fremen of the Deep Desert. The power of the Imperium can be yours, but war is not the only way to claim it.<br/><br/><i>Dune: Imperium</i> blends deck-building and worker placement in a deeply thematic new strategy game where the fate of the Empire hangs on your decisions. Will you seek political allies or rely upon military might? Economic strength or subtle intrigues? A council seat… or a sharpened blade? The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body2_2.png?t=1710364055"><br/>In <i>Dune: Imperium</i>, you'll step into the role of one of the leaders of the Great Houses of the Imperium in a struggle to control the planet Arrakis and the invaluable Spice it provides.<br/><br/>The game plays out in a series of ten rounds, each of which is defined by a new Conflict on the surface of the planet; some award critical resources, and some provide Victory Points that will propel you to dominance. But choose your battles wisely: spread your forces too thin, and you'll find your enemies growing too strong to oppose.<br/><br/>Each round, you'll draw a hand of five cards from your deck, which will get stronger over the course of the game as you acquire new cards. Each card can be played in one of two ways: To send an Agent out into the Imperium to gather resources, or to Reveal at the end of the round to purchase new powerful cards. You must maintain a careful balance to get the most of the resources available to you. How will you find your path?<br/><br/>As your game progresses, you'll vie for Influence with four factions of the Imperium: The Emperor, the economically powerful Spacing Guild, the mysterious Bene Gesserit, and the ferocious Fremen of the deep deserts. Earning Influence among the various groups helps you to earn the Victory Points you need...but will you compete with your rivals for their favor, or abandon alliances to pursue other opportunities?<br/><br/>Many strategies are at your disposal, and many paths to victory. The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Footer.png?t=1710364055"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead by Daylight - All Things Wicked Chapter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2661270/Dead_by_Daylight__All_Things_Wicked_Chapter/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Main_Banner.gif?t=1710259123"><br/><br/>Dead by Daylight’s All Things Wicked delves into the depths of analog horror with <strong>new Killer, The Unknown</strong>, and <strong>new Survivor, Sable Ward</strong>. A new Map, <strong>Greenville Square</strong>, is available for all players. Purchasing this add-on unlocks 2 exclusive Cosmetics: <strong>The Unknown’s Garden Casual</strong> and <strong>Sable Ward’s Designer Corset</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Killer_Power.jpg?t=1710259123"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE UNKNOWN</h2>If you hear a soft voice crying out for help in the woods, stay the hell away. The true nature of The Unknown remains a mystery, barring one fatal certainty: to cross its path is to risk an unknowable fate.<br/><br/><strong>The Unknown’s Power: UVX (Unknown Venom X)</strong><br/><br/>Charge and launch a burst of UVX, which bounces once and creates a Blast Area upon impact. If they touch the Blast Area, they will become Weakened against your Power.   <br/>If a Survivor is Weakened, they will lose a Health State whenever they touch a Blast Area. Survivors can lose the Weakened status by successfully looking at The Unknown for a brief duration.<br/><br/><strong>Special Ability: Hallucinations</strong><br/><br/>During a Trial, The Unknown will intermittently create Hallucinations and leave them in its wake. The Unknown can highlight and teleport to any Hallucination, leaving behind a temporary Decoy version of itself. Survivors can Dispel Hallucinations, but only by staring at one while standing completely still. Weakened Survivors will take longer to Dispel a Hallucination, and any incomplete attempt will reveal their location through Killer Instinct. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Killer_Perks.jpg?t=1710259123"><br/><br/>The Unknown comes with <strong>3 new perks.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Unbound</h2>Unbound activates for a duration when a Survivor becomes injured. During this time, you’ll gain a brief speed boost whenever you Vault a Window.<h2 class="bb_tag">Unforeseen</h2>When you kick a Generator, your Terror Radius transfers to it for a duration. During this time, your Terror Radius increases and you become Undetectable.<h2 class="bb_tag">Undone</h2>Gain Tokens whenever a Survivor misses a Skill Check. When you damage a Generator, all Tokens will be consumed. For each Token consumed, the Generator loses 1% total progress and becomes blocked for 1 second.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Survivor_Perks.jpg?t=1710259123"><h2 class="bb_tag">SABLE WARD</h2>While some fear the darkness, Sable Ward embraces it. Fascinated by horror and drawn to all things wicked, Sable was among the few Survivors to willingly step into The Fog in search of her best friend Mikaela.<br/>Sable Ward comes with <strong>3 new perks.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Invocation: Weaving Spiders</h2>This Invocation can only be performed in the Basement and takes a considerable duration of time to complete. Survivors can see your Aura during the process and can join you, increasing the Invocation’s speed.  <br/>Once complete, all Survivors will gain a boost of Repair progress. On the other hand, you’ll be Injured and Broken for the remainder of the Trial.<h2 class="bb_tag">Strength in Shadows</h2>When in the basement, you can quickly heal without a Med-Kit. Afterward, the Killer’s Aura is briefly revealed.<h2 class="bb_tag">Wicked</h2>Gain the ability to successfully unhook yourself from Basement Hooks. When you successfully do so, the Killer’s Aura is briefly revealed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_New_Map.jpg?t=1710259123"><h2 class="bb_tag">NEW MAP: GREENVILLE SQUARE*</h2><br/>A slice of small-town Americana, long abandoned, long forgotten. Now, something wanders freely along the overgrown streets: a writhing creature responsible for a string of disappearances across the country.<br/>*This map is free for all players.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Exclusive_Item_Killer.jpg?t=1710259123"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXCLUSIVE CHAPTER KILLER ITEM: GARDEN CASUAL</h2>Her prize-winning peonies wilted and died without someone to care for them. The All Things Wicked Chapter includes an exclusive item for The Unknown, the <strong>Garden Casual Outfit</strong>, only available as part of the DLC. Please note that this item cannot be purchased separately.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Exclusive_Item_Survivor.jpg?t=1710259123"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXCLUSIVE CHAPTER SURVIVOR ITEM: DESIGNER CORSET </h2>Once she saw it in the store window, she knew she had a reason to save her money. The All Things Wicked Chapter includes an exclusive item for Sable, the <strong>Designer Corset</strong>, only available as part of the DLC. Please note that this item cannot be purchased separately.<br/><br/><br/><i>If you’re seeing this, your fate has been sealed.</i> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contra: Operation Galuga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2235020/Contra_Operation_Galuga/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2235020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A new entry in the legendary Contra series is here! Contra: Operation Galuga is a thorough reimagining of the classic run-'n'-gun action game from the '80s, featuring modern graphics and sound, new stages, new enemies and bosses, new play mechanics, an updated weapons system, and explosive co-op combat for up to two players in Story Mode or four players in Arcade Mode!<br>
<br>
When the Red Falcon terrorist group takes over the Galuga Islands off the coast of New Zealand, elite Contra commandos Bill Rizer and Lance Bean springs into action, initiating an all-out war in which the fate of mankind hangs in the balance!<br>
<br>
Run, jump, and shoot your way through eight levels using a devastating arsenal - including the spread shot, laser, and homing missiles - now with stackable upgrades and awesome Overload abilities! The intense action is customizable with three difficulty settings plus a variety of additional challenge options. The true Contra legacy begins now!<br>
<br/>
Key Features:<br/>
•The original run-'n'-gun game is back, reimagined and more action-packed than ever!<br/>
•Attack aggressively across eight explosive stages! Infiltrate the jungle, ascend the waterfall, speed through an enemy base on a hovercycle, and more!<br/>
•Multiple playable characters with distinct abilities!<br/>
•Epic, screen-filling boss battles!<br/>
•New and fan-favorite weapons, now with stackable upgrades and incredible Overload abilities!<br/>
•Multiple difficulty options and a wealth of extra content						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebel Transmute</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1191660/Rebel_Transmute/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/Rebel_Transmute_Logo_Decorated_Steam.png?t=1710417586"><br/><br/>In this modern metroidvania you play as Moon Mikono, a space scrapper turned adventurer on a mission to uncover the true fate of her missing mother.<br/><br/>To accomplish this mission in your own, unique way you'll be swapping out game changing augments to suit your playstyle.  Aggressive and greedy?  Inquisitive and cautious?  Maybe you just want an army of friendly creatures!  With over 50 unique upgrades, Rebel Transmute allows you to play through a classic sci-fi adventure in YOUR style.<h2 class="bb_tag">CHALLENGING AND CUSTOMIZABLE COMBAT</h2>Use a variety of spells known as Bloodcasts, your trusty Foray-issued Blaster, and a variety of game changing Augments to take on a world of dangerous creatures and space travelers.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/16.gif?t=1710417586"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXPLORE AND MAP A VIBRANT SCI-FI WORLD</h2>The sprawling world of Rebel Transmute is full of stunning vistas: From vibrant greenery in the Overgrowth, to the fluorescent reefs of the Coral Fissure, to the sparkblood crystal-strewn Surface.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/09.gif?t=1710417586"><h2 class="bb_tag">Additional Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Encounter over <strong>80 unique enemies</strong> and over <strong>10 formidable bosses</strong>! From mutated worms and electrified beasts, to rogue AI's and gigantic bugs. All offering different and exciting challenges and interactions.<br/></li><li>Discover <strong>game-changing abilities</strong> hidden throughout the outpost.  Spin Bash, Wall Jump, and Void Dash your way across an interconnected network of tunnels, caverns, and research laboratories!<br/></li><li>Augment your playstyle with <strong>48 optional upgrades</strong> that can drastically change how you play the game.  Fight alongside a reprogrammed drone, twist your attacks into spiraling laser blasts, or even summon tentacles to block projectiles!<br/></li><li>Make use of a versatile mapping system to help track your progress.  Use custom markers, track your completion percentage, and find hidden terminals to uncover unexplored areas.<br/></li><li>Experience a <strong>personal and heartfelt story</strong>. As Moon searches for her mother she’ll also encounter various robot life, all with their own stories, personalities, and quests.<br/></li><li>A <strong>hand-painted pixel art</strong> aesthetic lends each and every character, enemy, and sector a personal touch.<br/></li><li>An immersive and atmospheric score, crafted to perfectly match every moment, from bombastic fights to solemn exploration.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMERHOUSE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2533960/SUMMERHOUSE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2533960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2533960/extras/summerhouse_new_store_page.gif?t=1709984408"><br/><br/>SUMMERHOUSE is a small-scale building game and a love letter to the feeling of long lost summer afternoons.<br/><br/>Craft a neighbourhood of tiny, beautiful lived-in homes in a variety of settings: the sea, the city, or the mountains. While there are some little secrets to uncover, there are no rules, and you can’t win or lose. Just chill out, build to your heart’s content and soak up the atmosphere.<br/><br/>If relaxation and creation are your thing, this is a game for you :)<br/><br/><i>Please keep in mind that this is a small game with no goals or challenges, created by a single person🙂</i> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORE BLASTERS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/BORE_BLASTERS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/BLAST.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_blast_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Blast your way through rocks and dirt with your machinegun drill. Carve through the ground to uncover precious ores and defeat menacing foes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/LOOT.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_loot_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Uncover ancient relics and artefacts hidden in the deep. Amass a fortune in rare gems &amp; ores.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/UPGRADE.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_mortar_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Invest in powerful upgrades and unlock new abilities, turning your humble gyrocopter into a fearsome force to be reckoned with.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/DISCOVER.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_discover_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Explore a diverse range of biomes, from treacherous volcanic caverns to lush overgrown underground forests, each with its own unique challenges and rewards.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/FEATURES.png?t=1709907021"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Intense mining action with fast-paced blasting<br/></li><li> Constant progress - even failed runs aren't punishing<br/></li><li> Diverse biomes to explore<br/></li><li> Purchase upgrades to overpower your gyrocopter<br/></li><li> Navigate the overworld to unlock new mine shafts<br/></li><li> Collect and loot rare gems, ores, and artefacts to upgrade your gear and abilities<br/></li><li> Endless replayability with procedurally generated levels</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_drones_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/><br/>Drawing inspiration from mining games like Motherload and Galactic Mining Corp, Bore Blasters takes the genre to the next level with high octane action and fast paced gameplay. Fans of digging and collecting will find plenty to love, while the addition of deadly enemies and mysterious artefacts will keep even the most seasoned miners on their toes.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/WL_arrow.gif?t=1709907021"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_missiles_frame.gif?t=1709907021"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Realm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1330000/Stolen_Realm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/GreenDragon.gif?t=1710364112"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TURN-BASED STRATEGY MEETS ACTION RPG IN THIS DUNGEON CRAWLING LOOTER</strong></h2><br/><br/>Stolen Realm is a <strong>simultaneous turn-based tactical dungeon crawling looter with action RPG elements</strong> where you control up to <strong>6 heroes, solo or through online co-op</strong>, venturing forth in adventures set in a high-fantasy, low-poly world. <br/><br/>Stolen Realm features an <strong>innovative turn-based combat system</strong> where <strong>simultaneous turns</strong> allow every team to take their actions at once, creating quick combat encounters that blend the tactical depth of titles like Divinity: Original Sin with the thrill of a fast-paced action RPG. Every battle scales based on the number of players involved, so you can easily jump in and out of the game even in the same playthrough!<br/> <br/>With a <strong>highly customisable class system</strong>, Stolen Realm allows you to create traditional RPG classes or break the mold to forge a unique champion of your own as you draw from a pool of hundreds of possible skills. Make a spell-slinging assassin, a priest born of frost, or a shadow-infused knight. Further customize your build by earning and reforging <strong>loot that truly changes the way you play</strong>: wield Abbadon the Soul Crusher, a mythic mace that raises slain enemies as skeletal warriors to fight for you, or unsheath the Bloodletter, a cursed sword that grants additional power at the cost of your lifeblood. D&amp;D-like events where attribute-based rolls will have permanent effects on your character add yet another layer to building a character that is truly your own. Anything is possible in this title that keeps compelling choices at the forefront of your experience.  <br/><br/>Keeping the core appeal of RPGs at its forefront, Stolen Realm ensures you spend all your time, fighting, building your characters and making compelling choices that determine your immediate path or effect your character, rather than getting bogged down in side quests and other RPG-bloat.   After each battle, pick your path between story events, resource gathering, shops and treasure rooms, until you get to the final boss of each <strong>procedurally generated adventure.</strong> If you’re up to a challenge, crank the difficulty up with <strong>6 different difficulty levels</strong> – or pick <strong>Hardcore Mode with permadeath</strong>, where every battle can be the last!<br/><br/>Also features <strong>Roguelike Mode</strong>, a fast paced version of the game where you can mix and match builds that are simply not possible in the traditional campaign!<br/><br/>Carve a place in history with your sword and magic. Rise to honor and glory in the battlefield. <strong>Recover the Stolen Realm.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/CycloneKick.gif?t=1710364112"><h2 class="bb_tag">PRAISE FOR STOLEN REALM</h2><br/>“The tactical depth of Divinity: Original Sin” - GamesRadar+<br/><br/>“we’re losing our evenings to… Stolen Realm” - TheXboxHub<br/><br/>“A gorgeous looking game” - PC Gamer<br/><br/>“You can be a fire warrior. You can be a healing necromancer. You can do all sorts of weird s**t.” - <strong>Sacriel</strong><br/><br/>“What I like about this game is it’s straight to the point. You just go in, you’re building your character, you’re getting items…and you just fight. There’s no bulls**t.” - <strong>Shroud</strong><br/><br/>“It’s rad” - <strong>Sequisha</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/Dwarven_Warmachine.gif?t=1710364112"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>KEY FEATURES</strong></h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play solo or with friends in up to 6 player online co-op, allowing you and your friends to wreak havoc amongst your foes<br/></li><li>Experience thrilling and fast-paced turn-based battles thanks to a simultaneous team turn system<br/></li><li>Full story campaign, roguelike mode and streamer mode<br/></li><li>Use over 300 skills in 10 distinct skill trees allowing for complete and flexible character customization<br/></li><li>Navigate hex-based battlefields where positioning is key due to battle shrines with special effects, exploding barrels and movable crates<br/></li><li>Find and loot over 700 unique items, fully customizable with modifiers, as you explore a wonderful world full of magic, secrets and unexpected dangers<br/></li><li>Co-op focused design keeps gameplay fast paced and strategic for up to 6 players <br/></li><li>Easy drop-in, drop-out design and automatic scaling that allows you to join or drop out mid-quest <br/></li><li>D&amp;D-like attribute-based rolls in special events that have permanent character effects<br/></li><li>Fight against over 200 types of enemies in battles that will be different every time: thanks to the Enemy Modifications feature, every creature you face on the battlefield will be unique<br/></li><li>A world that changes on each expedition, from frosty peaks guarded by the elusive Blue Dragon to overgrown jungles where the rock giants roam. <br/></li><li>Pick your path between battles, choosing where to go between story events, resource gathering, shops, fights, and treasure rooms until you get to the final boss of each adventure<br/></li><li>6 different difficulty levels<br/></li><li>Choose between Normal Mode and Hardcore Mode with permadeath if you want a real challenge!</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE 2K24</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2315690/WWE_2K24/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2315690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							FORTY YEARS OF WRESTLEMANIA<br>
<br>
WrestleMania is the biggest event in sports entertainment, where Superstars become WWE Legends. Experience a gripping retelling of WrestleMania’s greatest moments in 2K Showcase of the Immortals, where you can relive a collection of some of the most unforgettable, career-defining matches.<br>
<br>
AN ICONIC ROSTER<br>
<br>
WWE 2K24 boasts a star-studded roster featuring WWE Legends like “Stone Cold” Steve Austin, Undertaker, and Andre the Giant, alongside current WWE Superstars like “The American Nightmare” Cody Rhodes, John Cena, Rhea Ripley, and Roman Reigns, whose larger-than-life entrances and signature moves are heightened by ultra-realistic graphics.<br>
<br>
NEW MATCH TYPES<br>
<br>
From Guest Referee to Casket, Gauntlet, and Ambulance matches, there are a bevy of new match types to experience in WWE 2K24, including support for multiple Superstars in Backstage Brawl.<br>
<br>
PROVE YOURSELF IN MyRISE<br>
<br>
Unleash your raw talent and become the undisputed champ in MyRISE, featuring two thrilling career arcs and original storylines chronicling your ascent to WWE stardom from the men's and women’s divisions.<br>
<br>
BUILD YOUR FACTION<br>
<br>
Assemble your favorite WWE Superstars and Legends in MyFACTION. Acquire cards, build a dominant faction, compete in online multiplayer and the all-new ranked quickplay. Plus, earn exciting promotional and final rank rewards as you climb the new seasonal leaderboard!<br>
<br>
CONTROL THE WWE UNIVERSE<br>
<br>
Develop feuds, weekly shows, and more in Universe mode, WWE 2K24’s ultimate sandbox, with expanded rivalry actions, all-new cutscenes, and support for double-title matches!<br>
<br>
CALL THE SHOTS IN MyGM<br>
<br>
Oversee the biggest brands and Superstars in sports entertainment as you challenge rival general managers for the top spot in MyGM. Explore more match types, more brands, and new general managers. Trade Superstars between brands, make executive decisions on contracts, and amp up the drama.<br/>
<br/>
**Online play including MyFACTION requires an internet connection and 2K Account. Terms apply.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duelists of Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1664200/Duelists_of_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/DoE_EVO_Trailer_-_steam_gif_short_30fps.gif?t=1710102934"><br/>Duelists of Eden is a card-grid-fighting game set after the events of One Step From Eden. Build your custom deck and battle online in real-time action! There are over 14 unique characters with strengths and weaknesses to encourage creative spell combinations and synergies. Will you combo slashes, fire, or even use bombs to eliminate your competition?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/SaffronWitch_steam_header-features.gif?t=1710102934"><h2 class="bb_tag">Deckbuilding</h2>Fight in a mix of strategy and real-time action! Create your own unique combination of spells to take down the competition. <br/>Save and edit an unlimited amount of decks in the editor!<h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic cardtridge and combo system</h2>Create combos on the fly, adapting the scenario and what spells you and your opponent have.<h2 class="bb_tag">Tutorial and training mode</h2>Learn the ropes in the tutorial mode and deep dive into the mechanics via training mode. <br/>Training mode includes hitboxes, character states, quick deck edits, speed modifiers, and more!<h2 class="bb_tag">Custom rollback netcode</h2>The game was completely rebuilt to support custom rollback netcode, for the smoothest experience possible.<h2 class="bb_tag">Replay mode</h2>Review your matches in replay mode!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/Selicy_OSFE_gif_steam.gif?t=1710102934"><br/><br/>Local multiplayer may require a controller.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals Zero Hour</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732960/Command__Conquer_Generals_Zero_Hour/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals Zero Hour brings you closer to the enemy than ever before. Engage opposing forces at hot spots around the globe as you match strategies and arsenals against the new masterminds of modern war.<br/><br/><strong>Arsenal.</strong> Unleash the next generation of 3D new units and 20 new upgrades including China's ECM Tank, GLA's BattleBus and the USA's Spectre Gunship.<br/><br/><strong>Missions.</strong> Take on 15 new missions and make tomorrow's headlines. Root out a splinter cell in Cairo, steal deadly toxins from a U.S. lab and more.<br/><br/><strong>Generals.</strong> Match strategies and arsenals against 9 enemy commanders with unpredictable personalities and tactics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Tiberian Sun™ and Firestorm™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229880/Command__Conquer_Tiberian_Sun_and_Firestorm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Second Tiberium War begins in this legendary sequel to the original Command &amp; Conquer. <br/><br/>With his forces stronger than ever, arch villain and leader of The Brotherhood of Nod - Kane - is pitched in an epic battle against the world's war machine - the Global Defense Initiative. Now you must orchestrate the fate of mankind.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on Dynamic Battlefields. Nature itself provides tactical opportunities - destroyable and deformable terrain, forest fires, treacherous ice fields and many more surprises that help or hinder your strategies.<br/></li><li>Exciting New Strategies and Units. Jump Jet Infantry, Hover Tanks, Tunneling APCs, Hunter Seekers, Laser Fences, Mechanized Battle Units and many more.<br/></li><li>The "Veterancy" Factor. Units can become faster and stronger as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>New Kinetic Battlefields. Flying shrapnel, shock waves and crashing debris are just a few of the exciting new technologies developed to enhance the in-game experience.<br/></li><li>The mood and attitude of the battlefield comes alive like never before - covert night missions, searchlights and new defenses intensify the thrill and excitement.</li></ul><br/>Then take the battle further in <strong>Firestorm, the official expansion pack for the game</strong>. Includes all-new campaign missions, cinematics, and units to decide the future of mankind.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Renegade™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229890/Command__Conquer_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer gets up close and personal in this classic First Person Shooter for one of the most iconic franchises.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wreak Havoc</strong> - Experience the Command &amp; Conquer universe on foot as Havoc, wise-cracking GDI Commando.<br/></li><li><strong>Make Your Own Rules</strong>  - Take on the evil Brotherhood of Nod using your own mix of brute force, stealth, and strategy.<br/></li><li><strong>Assault at Ground Level</strong>  - Dish out the damage in either first or third person.<br/></li><li><strong>Total Access</strong>  - Sneak inside and explore full-scale structures, like immense Tiberium Refineries and the ominous Hand of Nod.<br/></li><li><strong>Grind the Gears</strong>  - Beef up your arsenal by commandeering lethal vehicles, such as Nod Buggies, Flame Tanks, and Mammoth Tanks.<br/></li><li><strong>Weapons of Mass Destruction</strong>  - Choose from a multitude of weapons, including the Tiberium Auto Rifle, Chemical Sprayer, and the devasting Personal Ion Cannon.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ and The Covert Operations™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229830/Command__Conquer_and_The_Covert_Operations/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The legendary RTS game which started it all. Will you side with the humanistic GDI or bring the world to its knees with Kane and the Brotherhood of Nod. Your adversaries are without mercy. And so are you.  <br/><br/>Includes the <strong>The Covert Operations</strong> expansion pack with a range of challenging new missions.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potions: A Curious Tale</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/378690/Potions_A_Curious_Tale/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Add Potions: A Curious Tale to your wishlist!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/Wishlist_616.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/LunaCombatGif.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Use your wits to strategize conflict resolution that goes beyond pure combat-- you’ll have to think on your feet and act quickly to sidestep danger and trick, charm, and scare your opponents into dropping valuable resources. <br/><br/>As powerful as your potions are, you’ll find yourself up against monsters that can shrug off your most powerful attacks. Manage your resources carefully and use the environment and even other monsters to defeat your enemies, or you may find yourself with an empty satchel when you need your elixirs the most.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/SteamCraftingVideoFullPotTitleNX.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>On her path to potions mastery, Luna must gather rare ingredients even before she brews her first potion. While her grandmother and friends teach her basic skills and recipes, Luna must fill her vials through experimentation and discovery. <br/><br/>Explore the deep crafting system as you discover new ingredients across 7 biomes to craft over 100 unique potions with different element combinations. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/PuzzleGifTitle.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Solve devious puzzles and mysteries with your wits and your arsenal of mystical potions. With a little help from your grandmother (a powerful witch in her own right) and Helios, your cat familiar, you’ll overcome the challenges of these enchanted lands.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/StoryTitle.png?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Growing up is hard, and it’s even harder when you’re a witch! Encounter fairy tale and folklore characters as you guide Luna on her quest to become a potions master. With her sharp-tongued familiar at her side, Luna learns important coming-of-age lessons: Respect is earned, advice can be deceiving, and adults aren't always right.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FQS2SN55CC4" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/SteamHeaderDiscord616.png?t=1709876407"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/PetCatHeart.gif?t=1709876407"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Saboteur™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/24880/The_Saboteur/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/24880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Not all wars are fought on the open battlefield. Download The Saboteur to visit 1940s Nazi-occupied Paris, as you play tough Irish racecar mechanic Sean Devlin. Working with the French Resistance, Sean is out for revenge against ruthless Nazi Colonel Kurt Dierker, who executed Sean’s best friend.<br/><br/>This open-world action thriller takes you through the seedy streets of Paris as you seek to undermine the German authority and lead a rebellion. Fight across rooftops and through dangerous alleys, and operate a wide variety of vehicles as you navigate your terrain. You can even climb the Eiffel Tower or Notre Dame Cathedral for a sniping mission.<br/><br/>Use stealth and disguise to strike at the heart of the Nazi war machine by disabling trains, destroying bridges, and blowing up enemy facilities. As you work to remove the oppressive forces from parts of the city, the drab black-and-white palette gives way to bright colors, signifying that you’ve inspired the townspeople. The more you incite the people, the more they’ll aid you by intervening in fights or providing a quick getaway from pursuing Germans. The Saboteur presents a fresh take on World War II and features dramatic cinematic elements. The action and intrigue is yours to experience via download on the PC now.<br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>First Ever Open-World Paris</strong> — Climb the Eiffel Tour, snipe from Notre Dame Cathedral, and brawl on the Champs d’Elysee as you sabotage your enemies. Fight, climb, and prowl through the dark alleys, rooftops, burlesque houses, and seedy streets of the City of Lights — the ultimate playground for the Saboteur.<br/></li><li><strong>The Art of Sabotage</strong> — Being the Saboteur is all about attacking while staying unnoticed. Get your mission intel at underground clubs and cabarets. Eliminate your adversaries with stealth attacks, disguise, distractions, and explosives. Master a variety of weapons, automobiles, and skills to sabotage enemy operations. <br/></li><li><strong>The Will to Fight</strong> — An action-packed experience and thrilling storyline are made even more engaging by an innovative visual style, characters, and the new “Will to Fight” technology. Experience how the city reacts and changes around you as you free it from Nazi oppression. Only you can restore hope and grandeur to Paris.<br/></li><li><strong>French Resistance Strikes</strong> — Call for support from The Underground in the form of getaway cars, weapon deliveries, distractions, and much more.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 March Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2845260/100_March_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🌸🌹 WELCOME TO 100 MARCH CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌷🐈</h2><br/>Join the cutest adventure in the Lovely world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of romantic 8 march themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x200.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 March Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁 DLC List for this game 🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Extra.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867620/100_March_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867640/100_March_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x1.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_15" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavy Storm Shadow:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802380/Heavy_Storm_ShadowPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FwmfaDVPKSa" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/dss.png?t=1710328042"/></a><br/><br/><strong>Differences between the prologue and the full version<br/>The prologue opens up a character<br/>The prologue opens up a map</strong><br/><br/><strong>Unlock the true potential of your mech and witness its constant growth and upgrades! In deserts, ice and even satellites, kill thousands of swarms to strengthen your mech!<br/>At the end of each battle you will gain valuable resources to upgrade your mech's weapons and armor, unlocking new skills and powerful equipment.<br/>Through battles, you'll gain the bonds of your mech's pilots, forming modules in different directions to shape your unique fighting style.<br/>Grow and upgrade your mech in real time to make it more and more invincible and become the ultimate weapon against the swarm!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/1y.png?t=1710328042"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/1z.gif?t=1710328042"><br/><strong>Monsters are coming at you like wave after wave, and as your mech's guns move, the monsters explode into a fog of blood and fall in pieces, painting the earth in scarlet. Operate your mech to dodge attacks, kill through the siege, and find a way to survive among hundreds of enemies!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/2y.png?t=1710328042"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/2z.gif?t=1710328042"><br/><strong>Explore your own powerful combat combo by unlocking more and more powerful weapons and skills! Become stronger by killing and choosing, picking up resources, choosing the most suitable enhancements, and finally killing the terrifying bosses head-on!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/3y.png?t=1710328042"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/3Z.gif?t=1710328042"><br/><strong> offers a rich arsenal of multiple primary and secondary weapons, as well as numerous skills with unique features. These weapons and skills will provide endless possibilities for your battles. In the future, there will be even more powerful mechs waiting to be harnessed by you! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/4y.png?t=1710328042"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/4z.gif?t=1710328042"><br/><strong>The game already offers 3 challenging maps, each with unique enemy combinations and powerful bosses waiting to be challenged for a completely different leveling experience. As the game continues to update, you will meet more new maps and new modes of play to make your Meat Pigeon adventure even more colorful. </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sixty Four</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2659900/Sixty_Four/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F7YXd3tScqS" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/discord.png?t=1710217001"/></a><br/><br/>Created by a solo developer, Sixty Four is a clicker game that gradually becomes more idle with every machine you unlock, up to the the ultimate goal of full automation. Upgrade a factory in an extraordinary world. Progress to unlock new resources and machines, leading to new ways to expand and grow.<br/><br/><strong>❒ From Foundation to Complexity</strong><br/><br/>Begin your journey with a simple machine generating distinct cubes. Use combinations of cubes to unlock advanced machinery and new gameplay elements.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_3a_smaller.gif?t=1710217001"><br/><br/><strong>❒ An Evolving Factory Adventure</strong><br/><br/>Your factory is not just a collection of simple machines; it's a dynamic environment of challenges and strategy. Face new situations and discover opportunities with every innovative and abstract machine you encounter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_4a_smaller.gif?t=1710217001"><br/><strong>❒ A Fresh Mix of Gaming Mechanics</strong><br/><br/>Sixty Four combines simple yet engaging elements from idle, incremental, and strategy games. Pursue constant improvement and unravel the secrets behind messages from an unknown entity.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_5a_smaller.gif?t=1710217001"><br/><br/>Music by Jake Chudnow						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Thaumaturge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1684350/The_Thaumaturge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Thaumaturge_accolade_616x320_steam.png?t=1709742147"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/TT_claim_EN_small.png?t=1709742147"><br/><strong>The Thaumaturge is an isometric, story-rich RPG with a unique take on turn-based combat, character development features, and investigation mechanics</strong>, facing you with morally ambiguous choices – set in a world teeming with mysterious powers and strange ethereal beings called <strong>salutors</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/City_3-01.gif?t=1709742147"><br/><br/>The year is 1905. Warsaw lives under the yoke of imperial Russian tsardom. Its inhabitants constitute a diverse group of different ancestries, views, and beliefs with often conflicting interests: Russian soldiers, Jewish merchants, Polish townspeople, and more. Despite the circumstances, the city is a buzzing metropolis, where one can attend a breathtaking party with the high society, and later get robbed in one of the dark alleys of the Praga district. A city of great hopes and dreams on one hand and dark desires on the other.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Buka_2.gif?t=1709742147"><br/><br/>A <strong>thaumaturge</strong> bears both a gift and a burden at the same time. This parallel holds true for <strong>Wiktor Szulski</strong>, the game’s titular protagonist, who is drawn back to the tumultuous streets of 20th-century Warsaw by family matters. The gift of thaumaturgy is intertwined with family legacy, passed down through one's ancestors. This mystical inheritance significantly shapes Wiktor’s life journey tied around a pursuit of unearthly entities and their hosts. As only a thaumaturge can tame these ethereal entities - known to a select few as <strong>salutors</strong> - utilizing their mystical abilities to discover secrets hidden within the human soul and speak to the Darkness, no one understands quite like Wiktor how everyone suffers their own demons.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Wiktor_3-01.gif?t=1709742147"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Shape your story</strong> – as a full-fledged RPG, it allows you to alternate your choices and make you deal with the aftermath. <br/></li><li><strong>Develop your character</strong> – creating your own version of the thaumaturge will allow you to approach situations in different ways. <br/></li><li><strong>Experience unique turn-based combat</strong> and defeat your foes using human attacks and skills as well as psychic strikes delivered by salutors.<br/></li><li><strong>Influence and manipulate</strong> the temperaments of other characters to bend their will to your liking. <br/></li><li><strong>Tame the power of salutors</strong> – use the unique set of their skills to gain an advantage while exploring the world and when bringing your adversaries to their knees. <br/></li><li><strong>See the world that’s inevitably gone</strong> – explore the uncommon, heavily researched historic period of the early XX century Warsaw, where crime and luxury are often two sides of the same coin. Meet historical figures and learn about their involvement in the story. <br/></li><li><strong>Created in Unreal Engine 5</strong> to deliver a detailed &amp; beautifully crafted world.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeeperRL</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/329970/KeeperRL/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/Peek-2018-11-28-09-43.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL is an ambitious dungeon simulator with roguelike and RPG elements. Take the role of an evil wizard and study the methods of black magic. Equip your minions and explore the world, murder innocent villagers and burn their homes. Build your dungeon, lay traps and prepare for an assault of angry heroes. <br/><br/>When you control your minions the game changes into a classic roguelike, with turn-based and very tactical combat. You can also play as an adventurer and assault dungeons made by you or other players.<h2 class="bb_tag">Dungeon management </h2>You will dig deep into the mountain and build dozens of rooms, corridors and traps. Your minions will train and produce weapons and armor. Prisoners will be tortured. You will research new technologies like alchemy, beast mutation and sorcery.<h2 class="bb_tag">Z-levels</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341">Develop your base across multiple floors by digging down into the earth or building up. Build fantastic dungeon designs or elaborate castles and towers.<h2 class="bb_tag">Roguelike mechanics </h2>The world is simulated on a very detailed level. Creatures use equipment and consumable items. There are dozens of special items, spells, attributes and special attacks. You can cut off heads and limbs and blind or poison your enemies. If you're not careful with fire, you can burn an entire forest or even your own dungeon.<h2 class="bb_tag">Large, procedurally generated maps </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-animated-gif-maker__2_.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL features a large, procedurally generated world. Explore dozens of locations, from small cottages and shops to major enemies dwelling in castles and dungeons. Uncover secrets, bring back great loot and prisoners back to your base in order to grow in power.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple playable factions</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/gif_keepers-ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>Play as a:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dark wizard researching black magic.<br/></li><li>White knight specialized in horses and angelic beings.<br/></li><li>Necromancer who crafts undead from the body parts of fallen enemies.<br/></li><li>Fragile colony of twelve dwarves.<br/></li><li>Goblin king searching for his lost wives.<br/></li><li>Collective of gnomes with a mechanized army.<br/></li><li>Lone adventurer focused on exploration.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Online map sharing </h2>KeeperRL offers the ability to download dungeons made by other players from Steam Workshop, and places them on your world map as enemies. See how others design their fortresses, fight with their minions, and steal their loot! After winning the game, you'll have the option to share your dungeon online as well.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Grindea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/269770/Secrets_of_Grindea/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/269770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Secrets of Grindea</i> is an old-school Action RPG with co-op support for up to 4 players. It is a tribute to and sometimes a parody of the old SNES games so many of us grew up with and loved! Journey through fantastical lands, and battle tons of different enemies and bosses in your quest for truth, friendship and, above all, finding the world's rarest treasures!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A rich world filled with 300+ unique, colorful characters and an engaging story to drive your journey forward.<br/></li><li>Co-op support for up to four players! Enjoy the entire storyline with your friends or call someone in to help with the more difficult challenges.<br/></li><li>Customization, customization, customization - design a character that represents you, then mix and match any of the 31 spells and skills across 9 different categories.<br/></li><li>30+ epic boss fights! Overgrown slimes, giant robots, mimics - we have it all!<br/></li><li>Side content - design your own home, fish, craft items, tame pets, partake in mini-games, grow plants - there’s plenty to keep you entertained when you want a break from the main story.</li></ul><br/>And last but not least:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Arcade Mode - Separate from Story Mode, the game includes a <strong>full roguelite</strong> version where you need to battle your way to the top on a single life, building a town of your own as you progress.  How far can you get?</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON BALL FighterZ</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/678950/DRAGON_BALL_FighterZ/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/extras/GIF_DBFZ_STEAM.png?t=1710262330"><br/><br/>DRAGON BALL FighterZ is born from what makes the DRAGON BALL series so loved and famous: endless spectacular fights with its all-powerful fighters.<br/><br/>Partnering with Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ maximizes high end Anime graphics and brings easy to learn but difficult to master fighting gameplay.<br/><br/>High-end Anime Graphics<br/>Using the power of the Unreal engine and the talented team at Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ is a visual tour-de-force.<br/><br/>3vs3 Tag/Support<br/>Build your dream team and sharpen your skills to master high-speed tag combinations.<br/><br/>Thrilling Online Features<br/>Ranked matches, interactive lobby, crazy 6-player Party Match... There is something for every taste!<br/><br/>Exclusive Story Mode<br/>Discover a never-seen-before scenario featuring Android 21, a brand new character whose creation was supervised by Akira Toriyama himself.<br/><br/>Spectacular Fights<br/>Experience aerial combos, destructible stages and famous scenes from the DRAGON BALL anime in 60FPS and 1080p resolution!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1710411298"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1710411298"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<br/><br/>※ <i>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</i> is the free-to-play version of <i>Meta-Ghost: The breaking show</i>, to showcase some of the gameplay content.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710411298"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1710411298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1710411298"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1710411298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1710411298"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1710411298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1710411298"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1710411298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1710411298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1710411298"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1710411298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1710411298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1710411298"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1710411298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1710411298"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710411298"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1710411298"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR WARS™: Dark Forces Remaster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2292260/STAR_WARS_Dark_Forces_Remaster/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_8.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/><i>Star Wars</i>™: Dark Forces Remaster has been brought to life by the team at <strong>Nightdive Studios</strong>, fully remastered through its proprietary KEX engine, allowing the game to run on modern gaming devices at up to 4K resolution at 120FPS. New and returning players will enjoy <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces Remaster’s upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<br/><br/>The original 1995 <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces raised the bar for FPS games, offering players a significant degree of movement and interactivity, a large selection of items and power-ups, and engaging environments. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_10.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/>In the first <i>Star Wars</i> FPS video game, players assume the role of Kyle Katarn, a defector of the Galactic Empire turned mercenary for hire. Katarn joins the Rebel Alliance’s covert operations division tasked with infiltrating the Galactic Empire, where he discovers the secret Dark Trooper Project. The development of this powerful new series of Imperial battle droids and power-armored stormtroopers stands to strengthen the Empire’s grip on the galaxy unless Katarn and the Rebel Alliance intervene.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>All fourteen original levels, featuring <i>Star Wars</i>™ worlds and capital ships<br/></li><li>Use your ability to jump, duck, and crawl to solve puzzles and defeat enemies<br/></li><li>Your Personal Digital Assistant provides you with in game information such including map, inventory, and mission briefing<br/></li><li>Engaging first-person ground combat featuring ten weapons and twenty types of enemies<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS visuals<br/></li><li>Advanced 3D rendering enables updated lighting and atmospheric effects<br/></li><li>Modern gamepad support adds a new weapon wheel, and rumble<br/></li><li>Controller Support - vibration and gyro controls <br/></li><li>A variety of power-ups are made available to the player, including health, shields, weapons and ammunition<br/></li><li>For combat, the player may use fists, explosive landmines and thermal detonators, as well as blasters and other ranged weapons<br/></li><li>Includes immersive environmental puzzles and mazes </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_1.gif?t=1709278523"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709870080"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garden Life: A Cozy Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1915380/Garden_Life_A_Cozy_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/MASTER_GIF.gif?t=1710146328"> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE1_EN.gif?t=1710146328"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF1.gif?t=1710146328"><br/> <br/>Plant and nurture your dream garden using gardening techniques based in real life and adapted for everyone to enjoy:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Plant seeds, leaving them enough space to thrive<br/></li><li> Water, fertilize, and clip your plants to enhance their natural beauty and nurture them to health<br/></li><li> Discover different colourful varieties and unlock the full potential of each plant<br/></li><li> Pull out all weeds or choose to leave some to protect plants from pests<br/></li><li> Admire your plants in full bloom even through the changing seasons : in Garden Life, all plants thrive no matter the time of year!<br/></li><li> Play the story mode or the creative mode</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE2_EN.gif?t=1710146328"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF2.gif?t=1710146328"><br/> <br/>You are in charge of an abandoned community garden and decide to roll up your sleeves to restore it to its former glory. Complete tasks given to you by your neighbours to earn rewards, unlock new tools, seeds, ornaments and areas of the garden, and learn more about what lies behind this secluded spot.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE3_EN.gif?t=1710146328"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF3.gif?t=1710146328"><br/> <br/>Instantly unlock every corner of your garden, including all the seeds and ornaments, and give free rein to your creativity: in this restriction-free mode, you can bring your dream designs to life!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE4_EN.gif?t=1710146328"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF4.gif?t=1710146328"><br/> <br/>Procedural growth simulation developed specifically for the game ensures each plant grows in its own way! Each and every plant grows procedurally, and some even adapt to their environment by climbing if planted close to certain objects.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE5_EN.gif?t=1710146328"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF5.gif?t=1710146328"><br/> <br/>In Garden Life, you are not restricted by a grid: place plants and objects freely to create your designs!  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE6_EN.gif?t=1710146328"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF6.gif?t=1710146328"><br/> <br/>Head to the village square to sell flowers and bouquets at your stall and use the earnings to buy new seeds, ornaments and tools in the shop. You can also donates flowers to help create huge floral sculptures in the pavilion and win adorable prizes! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE7_EN.gif?t=1710146328"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF7.gif?t=1710146328"><br/><br/>Add Garden Life to your wishlist, follow us, and join our discord community so you don't miss out on any news!<h2 class="bb_tag">Games from friends!</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1122340/Chef_Life_A_Restaurant_Simulator/?utm_source=FromChefLife" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1122340/Chef_Life_A_Restaurant_Simulator/?utm_source=FromChefLife</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skelethrone: The Prey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2139870/Skelethrone_The_Prey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/Wishlist_Follow_ENG.gif?t=1710431377"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/About_the_Game_628_x_182_bright.gif?t=1710431377"><br/>You're in for a great adventure inspired by games like Castlevania and Dark Souls.  Bloodthirsty monsters, divine creatures and epic boss battles. The game’s story is shaped by  choices that will define your journey.<br/><br/><strong>PROLOGUE KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Metroidvania</strong> - Unlock unique upgrades for movement and combat to expand the world. Maintaining the game's progression requires you to use different relics, items and abilities.<br/></li><li><strong>Challenging bosses</strong> - Test your skills against multiple bosses and other creatures from the Dark Ages. The game will constantly test your patience as you face challenging battles that require their own unique approach..<br/></li><li><strong>Exploration</strong> - The game features a huge world represented by a variety of hand-crafted levels. From fog-shrouded ruins, where undead corpses cling to any living being passing by, and shambling figures emerge. To the Sun-city that hides in the labyrinthine of an ancient tomb where an unspeakable evil lingers, long forgotten by mankind.</li></ul><br/><strong>AVAILABLE IN FULL GAME:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Weapons and Equipment</strong> – Your character can be armed with bows, scythes, longswords, whips, pistols, rifles, and many more traditional weapons. More exotic weapons will also be available to you, so use any means to achieve success.<br/></li><li><strong>Multiple Endings</strong> – Make key decisions along the way to determine Ericona's fate as you progress through the story.<br/></li><li><strong>Non-linear exploration</strong> – Play through levels and bosses, discover side areas with more secrets and enemies to defeat.<br/></li><li><strong>Combat galore</strong> - You must use an ever-expanding arsenal of weapons and equipment to repel  a wide variety of enemies. Put your courage, skills, and resolve on display for them.</li></ul><br/>"Skelethrone: The Prey" is a free prequel to the main game, setting the stage for the events that will unfold throughout Skelethrone's main campaign.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/Story_628_x_182_bright.gif?t=1710431377"><br/>The story takes place a few decades before the events of the game's main campaign. Assume the role of Derek Ericona, a lord who escaped the persecution is now trying to get to the borders of the neighboring kingdom to resist the tyranny of Queen Aurora, but he is being chased and faces an uphill battle. Prepare all your skills to overcome all the obstacles and difficulties prepared for our hero. And now the hunt is on!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F89UKE37PuC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/join_the_comunity_628_x_182_bright.gif?t=1710431377"/></a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Battle Online</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2767270/Lets_Battle_Online/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cross-playable, competitive online game<br>
<br>
3-player battle for the win!<br>
You win when your opponent is knocked off the field or reduced to 0 HP!<br>
<br>
Equip 2 specials, 2 weapons, and armor to fight.<br>
Collect unique items and find the strongest combination!<br/>
<br/>
1 vs 1 single mode<br/>
2 vs. 2 cooperative multiplayer mode<br/>
Fight together with a friend in the cooperative multiplayer mode!<br/>
<br/>
Controls<br/>
Q: Dash<br/>
W: Use Special 1<br/>
E: Use Special 2<br/>
R: Use Weapon 1<br/>
T:Use Weapon 2						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream Escape</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2848500/Dream_Escape/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2848500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Dream Escape" is a first-person horror chamber escape type of game, there are 6 different dreams, the player can choose one of the dreams to adventure, but also can save the current record, enter the next dream, if you are very strong, soon can complete all the dream adventure.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong> Operation instructions </strong></h2>The game control is mainly controlled by the keyboard and mouse, W is forward, S is backward, A is left, D is right, Space is jump, Shift is acceleration, and mouse movement controls the cursor. The white cursor object has no operation, and the red cursor object can be displayed. The specific operation matters are in the setting page and control menu. Note: Master the control operation to escape the dream.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong> Dream description </strong></h2>The current dream in the game is: "Secret Chamber", "Alien Academy", "Quiet Basement", "Dark Community", "Fright Morgue", "abandoned hospital tunnel".<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2848500/extras/shuim.png?t=1710428071"><br/><strong> Ancient bookshelves, a hidden door quietly opens, revealing a mysterious secret room full of mysteries. This is the arena of wisdom, where taboos and tricks are written. Frescoes on the walls, intricate organs and lost manuscripts are clues left by the wise men of the past.<br/><strong> College introduction </strong> : A former temple of knowledge, now a place where aliens lurk. Reflections dance in the dappled glass of the classroom, and strange devices are scattered everywhere, leaving behind the remnants of scientific research. A low echo came from the empty corridor, and the shadow of an unknown creature rustled in the corner.<br/><strong> Basement description </strong> : Deep inside a dark and mysterious old house. Here are hidden chambers and ancient secrets, echoing with indescribable whispers. The team must rely on glimmer exploration, brave the bloody clues, wisdom to break the millennium curse, and solve the forgotten mysteries of history.<br/><strong> Community description </strong> : An abandoned community that is calm on the surface but hides secrets inside. Behind every locked door here lies a mystery and a crime. Detectives, you need to go deep into this dark corner, uncover the fog, solve the complex mystery.<br/><strong> Morgue introduction </strong> : The darkness echoes with silence and secrecy. This is the beginning of a heart-pounding, terrifying exploration of the brink of life and death. In the dim light, the player must piece together the clues left by the dead to solve a complicated case. Hidden fears lurk in the atmosphere, and time is your worst enemy.<br/><strong> Hospital tunnel introduction </strong> : Under the abandoned hospital, the winding tunnels are eerie and narrow, with eternal darkness and the virulent air filling every corner. A place that once teemed with life is now filled with echoes of past events and horror. Deciphering forgotten cases and exposing buried experiments, each step can trigger fears of the past.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong> Escape Dream Instructions </strong></h2>Players need to find the last door to get out of the dream in the game, enter the room to escape the dream, and automatically return to the end of the main game - escape from the dream.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong> Update </strong></h2>The game will be updated at the end of each quarter, mainly to create new dreams and fix problems in the game.</strong> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>放置地下城-Idle Dungeon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2600040/Idle_Dungeon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The monsters in the dungeon are restless, attempting to occupy the mainland kingdom on earth! Warriors, pick up your weapons and go to the dungeon to eliminate monsters. Victory must belong to brave heroes!<br>
<br>
This is a Idle game,  a dungeon monster fighting game, and a game that takes your graphics card and computer to work all day. Of course, you don't have to go to work anymore. It's almost all automatic monster hunting. You just need to finish work, have a cup of coffee, and let the computer work automatically. When you go to work, you can turn off your computer and go offline. When you go online again, you will settle the profits from this period and put them in your backpack.<br>
<br>
Game core gameplay:<br>
<br>
Normal Dungeon<br>
<br/>
To unlock the next level, one must pass each level one by one and defeat the monsters on this level. The equipment dropped in each dungeon is different, and after collecting a set of equipment, you need to fight monsters in several dungeons. At the end of every 10 levels, there is a boss level. Winning the defending boss will unlock the next 10 levels of regular dungeons.<br/>
<br/>
BOSS Tower<br/>
<br/>
BOSS towers are all dangerous and powerful bosses, including some gatekeepers. Advanced book fragments, monster fragments, boss materials, and more have fallen inside. Defeating one boss will automatically challenge the next boss until you are defeated. Every day, you can challenge countless times and ultimately defeat your boss. If you fail, you can hang better equipment in regular dungeons, strengthen your equipment, and embed gemstones in your equipment.<br/>
<br/>
Infinite Tower<br/>
<br/>
There are both ordinary monsters and boss monsters in the Infinite Tower, which can gain a lot of experience and materials. They will challenge each monster until they defeat you.<br/>
<br/>
Suit<br/>
<br/>
The game provides sets made of BOSS materials, which can also be upgraded to higher-level sets. These sets have special effects and better attributes than ordinary equipment.<br/>
<br/>
Mining<br/>
<br/>
Sometimes, if you need to obtain more gems, you can go to the gemstone mining area for mining, which is also automatically completed. Just collect the following gemstones after a while.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
As for strengthening, forging, and refining, they are all old ways of playing with equipment and numerical values. It goes without saying that there are too many, and the main focus is on numerical cultivation.<br/>
<br/>
There are two types of currency in the game: gold coins and diamonds. Gold coins can be automatically dropped when fighting monsters in dungeons. Just do the task with diamonds and sell the purple equipment in your backpack.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's be a Tiger</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2852310/Lets_be_a_Tiger/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2852310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Let's Be a Tiger is an exciting and immersive game that puts you in the role of a powerful tiger in the wild. <br>
<br>
As the player, you will need to hunt for food to survive and thrive in your natural habitat. The game is all about exploring and discovering, with the player having to navigate through different environments, such as forests, jungles, and grasslands, in search of prey. <br>
<br>
You must use your sharp senses and powerful instincts to track down and catch your food.Let's Be a Tiger also features high-quality graphics and sound effects, providing an immersive and realistic experience. The game aims to help players understand the unique challenges and rewards of life as a tiger and to appreciate the natural world around us.<br>
<br>
Overall, Let's Be a Tiger is a fun and engaging game that provides a unique perspective on the world through the eyes of a powerful predator. It is an excellent choice for anyone looking for a fun and educational game that encourages exploration, discovery, and learning.<br/>
<br/>
Game features:<br/>
- 3 different tigers( Bengala,white,magic)<br/>
- Multiple levels<br/>
- Hunting						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghost Ninja</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2852270/Ghost_Ninja/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2852270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ghost Ninja is an action-packed game that puts players in the shoes of a skilled assassin. <br>
<br>
You'll play as a ninja whose mission is to infiltrate a tall building and take out your target for a sum of money. To succeed in your mission, you'll need to climb the building, using your ninja skills to navigate the various obstacles and avoid detection. <br>
<br>
Once you've reached your target's floor, you'll need to carefully observe their behavior to determine the best course of action. When the time is right, you'll strike with deadly precision, taking out your target before slipping away unnoticed. But be careful – if you're detected by the building's security, it's game over.<br>
With challenging gameplay and stylish graphics, Ghost Ninja is a game that will keep you on the edge of your seat from start to finish. <br>
<br/>
Do you have what it takes to become the ultimate assassin? Play the game and find out!<br/>
<br/>
Game Features :<br/>
- Espionage missions<br/>
- Murders on order<br/>
- Different attack targets						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Bicycle Stunts</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2852300/Ultimate_Bicycle_Stunts/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2852300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Get ready to experience the ultimate rush in Ultimate Bicycle Stunts! <br>
<br>
Embark on an electrifying journey into the heart of adrenaline-pumping action as you don the helmet, mount your bike, and prepare to unleash mind-bending stunts atop perilous tracks soaring above the vibrant cityscape. <br>
<br>
With jaw-dropping vistas and pulse-pounding obstacles at every turn, this game is your ticket to pushing boundaries and mastering the art of extreme bicycle stunts.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br/>
- Customize your experience <br/>
- Choose from 3 thrilling game modes: Free Mode for boundless exploration, Time Trial for race-against-the-clock challenges, and Stunt Mode for showcasing your most daring maneuvers.<br/>
- Conquer treacherous tracks designed to test even the most seasoned riders, with each level offering increasingly intense stunts and heart-stopping moments.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine School Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1986710/Marine_School_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1986710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>School life experience on island in the Minami tropical sea!</strong><br/>Marine School Simulator is a third-person action-adventure game.<br/>This is a small island in the South Sea. There are only girls<br/>Cook special dishes, farm in the fields, attract tourists, improve your island reputation, level up and boost with the points you earn.<br/>Spend your free days defeating dangerous creatures and relaxing with your cute girlfriends.<br/><br/>Customize your character's appearance with many costumes and hairstyles<br/>Over 20 classmates, various collectibles<br/><br/><strong>Controls</strong>.<br/>Mouse + keyboard and gamepad support; XBOX controllers are encouraged.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wartop</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2737310/Wartop/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2737310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Wartop is a virtual tabletop system created specifically for playing tabletop skirmish and war games. Built from the ground up to handle the specific needs of these kinds of games. Full freedom camera controls, interactive record sheets, a universal map editor, quick spawning of dice and tokens, the ability to use assets freely between systems and once you're ready to play it takes little time to go from starting a match to actually playing. <br>
<br>
The base game includes  an implementation of Many Ages from Hobby Dungeon Games as well as The Streets of Erekh by David Osborne. <br>
<br>
Wartop is not designed as a sandbox, all game systems feature a bespoke implementation for their system to support their specific needs.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acorn Cop</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2857940/Acorn_Cop/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2857940/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In Acorn Cop, you're taking a shooting test as a cop.<h2 class="bb_tag">The rules are so simple:</h2>- You must shoot and destroy all the acorns<br/>- You must NOT shoot any of the humans and other living things (use your best judgment)<br/>- Everything else you can shoot at will, some of them will be very useful when destroyed, and some are just collectibles<br/>- Do not miss more than 2 acorns for 20 minutes and you win the game (a.k.a passing the test)<h2 class="bb_tag">Controller guide:</h2>- Flick LS to change aim assist target<br/>- While you're slowing down by holding the LB button, ammo won't refill<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Permadeath<br/></li><li>Special items with unique effects like slowing time, clearing all the acorns on the screen, refilling ammos...<br/></li><li>Collectible items<br/></li><li>Classical music (makes violence classy)<br/></li><li>Boss fight<br/></li><li>Funny easter eggs<br/></li><li>Achievements</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slot Fever</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733430/Slot_Fever/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2733430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Do you love the thrill of spinning the reels and winning big? Then you'll love Slot Fever, the new game that brings the casino to your home. Slot Fever is more than just a slot machine game. It's a realistic and immersive experience that lets you enjoy the following features:<br/><br/><strong>Daily bonus</strong><br/>Every day, you can claim a free bonus that will boost your balance and let you play longer.<br/><br/><strong>Win the jackpot</strong><br/>The more you play, the more chances you have to hit the jackpot and win millions of credit.<br/><br/><strong>Realistic slot machine experience</strong><br/>Slot Fever simulates the look and feel of a real slot machine, with authentic sounds, graphics and animations.<br/><br/><strong>Steam community market support</strong><br/>You can sell and buy chips with other players on the Steam community market, <br/><br/>Slot Fever is the ultimate game for slot machine fans. Don't miss this opportunity to join the fun and win big. Download Slot Fever today and let the fever begin!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo School Girl</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2847580/Tokyo_School_Girl/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A unfortunate tragedy has happened in the city of Tokyo. Yuki who is destined to become the heir and ruler of Tokyo has been kidnapped by the powerful menace Lion Knight who wants nothing except to rule the city with a iron fist and become the city’s ruler. Lion Knight has placed experienced fighting ninjas across the city to stop anyone that gets in his way of destroying Yuki.<br>
Yuki has a sister named “Tokyo School Girl” the woman who wears a holographic dress so you can see her toned legs when she runs or is in combat, after all she wants you to know she has been preparing for this battle. Tokyo School Girl must defeat the ninjas of the city and rescue her sister who will become the ruler of Tokyo.<br>
Experience Tokyo School Girls journey in the epic open world of Tokyo and use souls-like combat with a sword and a gun.<br>
Lock on your enemy targets, dodge their attacks, pull levers that activate secret pathways, inflict damage on the ninjas, solve puzzles placed in the world, replenish your health, and make your way to defeat the Lion Knight and save your sister who is the only hope for the people of Tokyo! <br>
You must dodge fires and viscous attacks from the menace named the Lion Knight and ninjas across the city and use hand to hand combat and dodge mechanics to rescue your sister.<br>
It won’t be an easy task, this attack on Yuki was planned for a long time as Lion Knight holds a grudge against Yuki and Tokyo School Girls father and that is why he is causing chaos along with the desire of having complete control of the city. <br>
Lion Knight has heard many rumors of “Tokyo School Girl” and her fierce battles with criminals across the city in the underworld. <br/>
You must prove these rumors true to him, use your sword, gun, or hands and dodge enemy attacks, and find Lion Knight’s hiding spot in the city using clues across the map, and then come face to face with him and rescue your sister Yuki who is destined to rule Tokyo.<br/>
Lion Knight easily captured Yuki and would have gotten away with it if it weren’t for Tokyo School Girls popularity and her holographic dress that her legs peak through that caused talk around town along with her reputation as a jiu-jitsu fighter. Oh the urge of the people of Tokyo who quickly told Tokyo School Girl that her sister Yuki the future leader has been kidnapped by a big, mean, and metal giant of a knight.<br/>
Of course word got to Tokyo School Girl that Yuki was kidnapped. <br/>
Experience the third-person, open world journey of Tokyo School Girl in the beautiful city of Tokyo using souls-like combat with a gun, your hands, or sword, and dodge or jump from their attacks, or even jump over your enemies and then attack them to rescue your sister. <br/>
The final boss will take note of how you defeat your enemies and will use this against you in the final battle to save Tokyo.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soul Shifters: Online</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2858130/Soul_Shifters_Online/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2858130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							WELCOME TO THE EPIC WORLD OF SOUL SHIFTERS: ONLINE!<br>
<br>
Explore a vibrant universe where humans and Daemons collide in an epic battle for supremacy. Uncover the power of assimilation, transforming into powerful Daemons to face unimaginable challenges. Immerse yourself in this electrifying journey, where your courage will shape the destiny of the world.<br>
<br>
---<br>
<br>
INCREDIBLE FEATURES<br/>
<br/>
- ASSIMILATION: Become a hybrid warrior by absorbing Daemons, using them in combat, each with unique and deadly abilities.<br/>
<br/>
- TACTICAL DAEMON SWAPPING: Switch between Daemons to face diverse challenges. Swap during battle, choosing the best Daemon for each combat moment.<br/>
<br/>
- UNIQUE ABILITIES: Evolve your synergy with your Daemon to master up to 1 standard skill, 3 elite skills, and 1 supreme skill for each Daemon. Unleash elemental powers to crush your adversaries.<br/>
<br/>
---<br/>
<br/>
IMMERSIVE WORLD<br/>
<br/>
- EPIC CONFLICTS: Battle other hybrid warriors in epic duels and defeat powerful Daemons while exploring dangerous areas to become the mightiest Daemon Lord.<br/>
<br/>
- INTRIGUING NARRATIVE: Explore diverse micro-narratives with NPCs, featuring light and humorous storytelling.<br/>
<br/>
---<br/>
<br/>
CHALLENGES AND ACHIEVEMENTS<br/>
<br/>
- INTENSE BATTLES: Challenge yourself in intense battles as you grow stronger. Reach the final showdown with Legendary Daemons in epic battles that will determine the world's fate, with the possibility of absorbing them to become even more powerful.<br/>
<br/>
- MAP EXPLORATION: Freely explore the map, discover hidden chests, unravel mysteries, and uncover new areas.<br/>
<br/>
---<br/>
<br/>
TECHNICAL FEATURES<br/>
<br/>
- PLAY WITH FRIENDS: Soul Shifters is an online game, so invite your friends for epic adventures. Form strategic alliances to face even greater challenges.<br/>
<br/>
- MULTIPLATFORM: Enjoy the flexibility of playing on various platforms. Sync your progress and dive into the action wherever you are.<br/>
<br/>
---<br/>
<br/>
DOWNLOAD NOW AND EMBRACE YOUR DESTINY IN SOUL SHIFTERS: ONLINE<br/>
<br/>
Get ready for a unique experience where strategy, courage, and power converge. Download now and embark on this thrilling journey. Humanity relies on you to become the true Daemon Lord and save the world!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hive In Space</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2851340/Hive_In_Space/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2851340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Playtime:</strong> 30 to 60 minutes <br/><br/><strong>Gameplay:</strong> You will experience various anomalies such as hallucinations and auditory illusions in outer space.<br/>Utilize your auditory and visual senses to overcome these anomalies and successfully migrate to new planets.<br/>If you experience any hallucinations or abnormal conditions, proceed through the ‘West’ door. If you don’t, proceed to the ‘North’ door.<br/><br/><strong>Story:</strong> Fifteen years from now, as a black hole threatens to engulf the solar system, humanity has decided to migrate to the planet Trappist-1e. I was appointed as the chief engineer aboard the Hive spacecraft. However, during the astronaut test, I experienced severe anomalies such as hallucinations and auditory illusions after entering cryosleep. Yet, since these phenomena were unique to me, I pretended everything was normal and passed the test. As long as the antimatter engine remains stable until our arrival at Trappist. there should be no issues.<br/><br/><strong>Developer’s Note:</strong> Hive In Space began with the goal of “developing a game alone within 30 days.” As a non-specialist, I self-taught Unreal Engine. Consequently, there may be gameplay limitations, but I appreciate your understanding as you play.<br/><br/><strong>Distribution:</strong> If you could include the game’s title or a link to its Steam page in your livestream title or video description, it would greatly support a solo developer. We do not assume responsibility for any damages resulting from the distribution of videos related to this game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Kye</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2859540/Super_Kye/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2859540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the world of Super Kye, a thrilling puzzle adventure that challenges your strategic thinking and problem-solving skills. Each level presents a unique set of puzzles and obstacles, requiring careful planning to navigate through mazes and collect gems to progress.<br>
<br>
With its compelling gameplay enhanced by a level editor, Super Kye allows players to unleash their creativity by designing their own challenging puzzles. This game is a perfect blend of classic puzzle mechanics and modern design, offering endless entertainment for puzzle lovers everywhere.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Singing Saw Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2854670/The_Singing_Saw_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854670/extras/Untitled_design__4_.png?t=1710407488"><br/><br/>Prepare to embark on a musical odyssey like no other as you step into the spotlight as the lead soloist on the mesmerizing musical saw!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854670/extras/6.png?t=1710407488"><br/><br/>Ready for a new challange? The singing saw, with its ethereal tones akin to the theremin, presents a challenge unlike any other instrument. Its lack of traditional markers or keys demands precision and finesse from the performer, with every note subject to the subtle nuances of breath, posture, and movement. <br/><br/>Can you hold the note steady enough? Find out as you embark on the performance of a lifetime, playing your way through a single, 15 minute composition, orchestrated and directed by the greatest musical genius that ever lived; YOU!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854670/extras/score_explain.png?t=1710407488"><br/><br/>Controlled solely by the mouse, the Singing Saw Simulator responds dynamically to your every movement, refusing to "lock in" when the perfect note is struck. Prepare to be immersed in the exhilarating uncertainty of musical mastery as you constantly question: am I in tune?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854670/extras/10.png?t=1710407488"><br/><br/>Points are awarded for “correct” notes, but no extra rewards are given for high scores - i.e. The points don't matter! Yay! Instead, the game asks that you forget about points and envision the music as an experience; a performance in which you can relax and exercise your creativity in a safe space. To that end, the Singing Saw Simulator features several sections in which the player is encouraged to improvise across the 3+ octave range of the saw. If that sounds scary to non-musicians, then don’t worry; it just means you can mess around.<br/><br/>And remember - if you can create a melody that sounds more pleasing to you than the written one, then please do so. The Singing Saw Simulator acts as a real instrument, so get creative and carve out your own place in musical history!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854670/extras/9.png?t=1710407488"><br/><br/>The accompanying soundtrack, aptly named "The Masterpiece," is a genre-defying opus crafted exclusively for Singing Saw Simulator. From classical elegance to jazz-infused rhythms, from pulsating house beats to twangy country vibes – each section showcases the singing saw as the star of the show. Get ready to rock out with a dedicated metal segment! Keep up as the piece moves from classical string quartet to New York soft jazz; from upbeat contemporary house to country and western; from horror soundtrack to the psychedelia of the 1960’s.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854670/extras/8.png?t=1710407488"><br/><br/>But the excitement doesn't end there – with each playthrough, unlock a new spectrum of sounds for your saw, from haunting distortions to evocative vocal effects. Transform your performance on the fly with a simple scroll of the mouse wheel and watch as your music takes on a whole new dimension.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854670/extras/12.png?t=1710407488"><br/><br/>Prepare for unexpected challenges mid-song – from rating your performance to quirky mini-games like whack-a-mole and tic-tac-toe!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854670/extras/11.png?t=1710407488"><br/><br/>Why confine yourself to the one performance? Open up your media player, switch to windowed mode, and let your creativity soar in Freeplay mode. Jam along to your favorite tunes, experiment with new sounds, and make every performance uniquely yours.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854670/extras/13.png?t=1710407488"><br/><br/>Why'd I make this game? Well. I bought a musical saw. It was difficult to play. But fun. So I hope you have fun too!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find Cats With Friends</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2859450/Find_Cats_With_Friends/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2859450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Gather your friends and embark on an exhilarating adventure to a mysterious island</strong> where the law is set by the cozy purring creatures – <strong>cats</strong>! You are brave pirates who accidentally found yourselves on this enigmatic island, and now your team must collect a very unusual loot:<strong> a hundred mischievous kitties.</strong><br/><br/>In <strong>Find Cats With Friends</strong> your main goal is to collect each of the one hundred cats scattered throughout the island and bring them to the specially designated spot – the cat box. However, pirates must be prepared that these little rascals love to hide in the most unpredictable places: under bushes, in tree hollows, on top of hills, or even on the masts of abandoned pirate ships.<br/><br/>Along your journey, you will undoubtedly find various tools and items that will aid you in your quest for <strong>cats</strong>. Use them wisely to gather all the <strong>cats </strong>as quickly as possible!<br/><br/>Against the backdrop of beautiful tropical nature, interacting with local inhabitants, you and your friends will be immersed in a world filled with<strong> joy and fun.</strong><br/><br/>Gather your team (up to 6 players) and embark on an exciting pirate adventure in <strong>cooperative multiplayer mode</strong>, where the ultimate reward will be your ability to collectively find and bring all the cats on board your ship! <strong>Good luck, cat questers!</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astro Chef</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1812230/Astro_Chef/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812230/extras/SteamHeader.png?t=1710431266"><br/>Welcome to Astro Chef, the ultimate cosmic culinary voyage! Embark on a Culinary Adventure: Transform into a master chef of the cosmos, serving up a variety of dishes to diverse alien patrons with their own distinct preferences, all while navigating the challenges of an intergalactic kitchen.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812230/extras/SinglePlay-Coop.png?t=1710431266"><br/>Single Player &amp; Co-op Gameplay: Choose your path, whether to single-handedly restore your Uncle's restaurant to its former glory or team up with a friend in a dynamic co-op mode. In co-op, one player dons the VR headset while the other assists with the Intergalactic Kitchen Manual making teamwork and communication key to your success.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812230/extras/SteamStore_Explore_2.gif?t=1710431266"><br/>Explore, Experiment, and Excel: With an array of alien ingredients at your disposal, discover the perfect combinations to delight your customers. Utilize unique, otherworldly kitchen tools to craft dishes that are as delightful to look at as they are to serve.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1812230/extras/SteamStore_FunChallenging_1.gif?t=1710431266"><br/>Face Fun &amp; Challenging Progression: As you progress through themed chapters, the complexity of dishes increases, testing your culinary skills and adaptability. With each stellar rating, you're one step closer to becoming the ultimate Astro Chef.<br/><br/>Immerse Yourself in Stunning Visuals: Enjoy a game world brimming with vibrant art, detailed environments, and a cast of charming alien customers.<br/><br/>Are you ready to become the next Astro Chef?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spellarium 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2775580/Spellarium_3/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2775580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Spellarium 3 is one of our first games in the Match 3 Puzzle genre. The keyword is 'Puzzle,' which means that sometimes (not always!) you'll complete the level faster by removing objects in the correct order. If you feel a lack of challenge, you can also play Timed or Moves Limited modes. Additionally, there are Spot The Difference, Hidden Object scenes, Solitaires, a story, and a town to build!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glow Hockey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2846040/Glow_Hockey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Glow Hockey</strong> delivers a new style of hockey game. Easy to play, hard to master. Challenge yourself with your friend and the computer opponents!<br/><br/><strong>FEATURES:</strong><br/>+ Local Wifi multiplayer<br/>+ 2-player mode (on the same device).<br/>+ 3 game slots in Championship mode.<br/>+ 11 table themes.<br/>+ 4 selectable paddles and pucks.<br/>+ Landscape &amp; Portrait view.<br/>+ Multiple puck sizes (S, M, L).<br/>+ Multi-puck (up to 10 pucks at the same time).<br/>+ Rule settings for score and optionally with timeout.<br/>+ Colorful glow graphics.<br/>+ Smooth and responsive game play.<br/>+ Realistic physics.<br/>+ Quick play mode (single player), challenge yourself with 4 difficulty levels (Easy to Insane).						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyan's Snow House</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2856090/Cyans_Snow_House/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2856090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Cyan's Snow House" is a heartwarming short indie game that transcends language to provide a universally enjoyable experience. Without a single line of dialogue and requiring only simple mouse clicks to play, players step into the shoes of Cyan, a lone girl in a snow-covered village, who daily feeds and spends time with animals shivering from the cold. Despite its brief playtime of around 10 minutes, it leaves a lasting, wonderful impression on anyone, anywhere in the world. The gentle moments shared between Cyan and the animals convey a warm message: "Your place is here." Recommended for anyone seeking a moment of solace on a cold winter's day, this game promises to melt your heart with its soothing embrace.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Scarlet Chaos</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2799970/The_Scarlet_Chaos/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2799970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2>The Scarlet Chaos is a semi-open world turn based RPG with an immersive and ambient world, dynamic weather, and interactable environments.<br/>Build and customize your party members the way you want to play them, you can decide what they specialize in through specific gear, weapons or Ethermancy skills.<br/>Explore the world to grow your stats, gear and skills.<br/>Survive the nightmare realm. Run or fight your way though to see the next day.<br/><br/>Level up Haerrison's special Mind Stats through actions and consumables to unlock persuasion and intimidation checks in some dialogue.<br/>The core Mind Stats are: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Cognition - Can open special dialogue options</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Elder Sight - Can make the Nightmare more hostile or unlock new items/areas</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Perception - Can reveal items and things that normally you wouldn't see</li></ul><br/>More notable gameplay features are:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Lockpicking minigames</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Collectable costumes</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Unlockable Fast-travel stations</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Rich exploration</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Rich lore and environmental storytelling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>35+ Quests</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">The World and Story Setup</h2>In the New World of Kelaura, The Scarlet Order have forced their will upon the land by upholding the Order given to them by their God, Nyrataeus, any who oppose their Order are imprisoned or put to death, forbidding all use of Ethermancy and other manipulation of the Ether. <br/>The Order's arrival in Kelaura marked the start of a war with the native tribes across the continent, the Sidaquisi, the Udenvatoi, the Kawadinage and other smaller tribes all fought against the Order until one day, their infamous Lord, Yarlthon, disapeared, and the Order's power was weakened.<br/><br/>Decades later things are at a cold stand still between the Sidaquisi and the Scarlet Order, war is brewing back across the sea to the Order's homeland of Westervale, and corruption runs rampant amongst the Order's ranks.<br/>Detective Haerrison and his partner and wife, Detective Brock, investigate the murder of a local council member which leads to a derelict fortress swathed in cerebral nightmares of The Hat Man, and an encounter with a powerful woman with seemingly supernatural abilities.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2799970/The_Scarlet_Chaos/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2799970/The_Scarlet_Chaos/</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highwater</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2000960/Highwater/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2000960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Highwater is a whimsical, 3D adventure game with an isometric turn-based puzzle-combat system set in a flooded, post-apocalyptic world. Navigate by boat, discover islands, find new allies to help battle foes, and experience a humorous tale about friendship in this melancholic and atmospheric escape.<br/><br/>Amid the Great Climate Catastrophe, the flooded region of Hightower has become a kind of safe zone between the two dry regions: the nearly global ravaged land of the War Zone, and the fortified city of Alphaville, where the ultra-rich live behind giant walls.<br/><br/>With life on Earth becoming untenable for humans, and rumors of an escape to Mars floating around, Nikos begins a risky journey, picking up friends along the way. First to Hightower, then beyond to cross the impenetrable border of Alphaville, battling insurgents and stealing food along the way. Will Nikos and his friends manage to sneak onto the rocket in time?<h2 class="bb_tag">GAME FEATURES:</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2000960/extras/highwater_boating.gif?t=1710399674"><h2 class="bb_tag">Rich, Story-Driven Adventure</h2>Earth may be flooded, but it’s one heck of a view on the water. With a sense of humor, determination, and some great tunes, Nikos and friends will work together to explore the water-filled environment around them and embark on an adventure to evacuate to Mars and start a new life.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2000960/extras/highwater_story.gif?t=1710399674"><h2 class="bb_tag">3D Exploration &amp; Discovery</h2>Float along the vast waterways freely in your boat and explore the many different islands of a beautiful world where you’ll encounter danger, interact with fellow citizens, gather resources, and fight for a chance to escape to a new life.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2000960/extras/highwater_bear.gif?t=1710399674"><h2 class="bb_tag">Turn-Based Combat With A Twist</h2>Take on your enemies in a classic turn-based combat system where careful tactics and puzzle solving will help you come out alive. Interact with the environment and items around you: knock down a tree, push a shopping cart into an enemy, or duck behind a turned over car to gain the advantage.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2000960/extras/highwater_zap2.gif?t=1710399674"><h2 class="bb_tag">Original Radio Tunes</h2>The world may be ending, but there's still time to enjoy some good tunes. As you cruise along the water, Highwater Pirate Radio is the key source not only of unique and original music, but also for commentary on your ticket to survival.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fencing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1625810/Fencing/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1625810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Description:</h2>[Fencing] is a unique game. You can't control the characters to run and jump like other games. Here, you can only use the WASD keyboard or the left rocker of the handle to control the character's vertical upward, forward, left and right jump attack. <br/><br/>The injury mechanism is the same as the scoring mechanism in real fencing competition. If the sword hits different parts of the body, it will cause different degrees of damage! Head, legs, arms and upper body, the degree of injury decreased in turn.<br/>Based on the physical type of combat, therefore, according to your sword time, sword angle, sword length, to determine the hit character, whether it will fly in a certain direction!<br/>Contains the Ragdoll system, after each hit, it will open the corresponding Ragdoll simulation effect according to your hit to the character's body bone.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features:</h2><br/>-Unique character manipulation<br/>-Injury mechanism of fencing<br/>-Physical combat<br/>-Ragdoll simulation<br/>-Various game forms, free fight, local double, AI watch, follow-up will update the online mode!<br/>-At present, there are six available characters, and more will be launched in the future.<h2 class="bb_tag">About Me:</h2>This independent game, developed by me alone, has many shortcomings at present. I welcome the feedback from players who have purchased the game, and hope to make [fencing] more perfect in the future! In addition, I sincerely welcome the friends who love the game, as well as the old comrades in arms of the independent game camp, to actively communicate with me.<br/><br/>Wechat: IndieGameDream<br/>QQ: 2118431574<br/>QQGroup: 794795548						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slavania</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1349600/Slavania/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1349600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>KEY GEATURES</strong><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Magic Spear</h2></strong> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1349600/extras/spear.gif?t=1710399784"> Travel and fight your way through Slavania with the help of a powerful artifact: the magic spear. <br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Mobility-Based Combat</h2></strong> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1349600/extras/ability2.gif?t=1710399784"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1349600/extras/ability1.gif?t=1710399784"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1349600/extras/ability3.gif?t=1710399784"> Upgrade your spear to gain access to new mobility mechanics. Use the spear as a platform to jump on, cling to ceilings, and teleport to its location. Every upgrade unlocks new ways to explore the world.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Hit ‘em how you like</h2></strong> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1349600/extras/spearhead.png?t=1710399784"> Enchant your spear to make it slash, burn, freeze or pierce armor. Burn spider webs and carnivorous plants, freeze enemies in place, and destroy boulders blocking your way with a piercing spearhead. Use every ability the spear grants you. You’ve already paid for them, after all...<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Highly varied locations and captivating visuals</h2></strong> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1349600/extras/loc.gif?t=1710399784"> Journey through a mysterious land. Visit villages, cursed forests, and the underworld. A team of talented artists and animators have created a wide variety of unique places and environments for the game’s world.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple threats</h2></strong> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1349600/extras/enemy01.gif?t=1710399784"> Defend the citizens of Slavania from the dark and terrifying creatures of the underworld. Prepare to fight for your life against over 40 types of monsters. Strike first, before they overrun you.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Track down and hunt bosses</h2></strong> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1349600/extras/bosses.gif?t=1710399784"> Become an immortal hunter of mythical beings. Study monsters, collect notes with information about their habitats and weaknesses, then set out on a hunt.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Don’t forget to eat</h2></strong> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1349600/extras/items.gif?t=1710399784"> Munch on gingerbread, then wash it down with Water of Life and mead. Purchase new items and upgrades to increase your chances of survival in the beautiful but dangerous world of Slavania.<br/><br/><strong>FOLLOW US ON X</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1349600/extras/x.gif?t=1710399784"><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/SlavaniaGame" rel="" target="_blank">https://twitter.com/SlavaniaGame</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2846660/Strange/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846660/extras/gif1.gif?t=1710393419"><br/>Our character finds himself in the midst of mysterious events when his new friend Molly, whom he has just met at a night play, disappears.<br/><br/>To reach Molly, he must collect various clues and find the treasure in the forest that Will mentioned. But there is something else waiting for him in the forest.<br/><br/>In this exploration and puzzle game, you will collect various clues, research in the library and try to solve a mystery with the information you have gathered.<br/><br/>In this game set in a cute town, earn money by selling the apples you collect from the apple orchard to the market. go after a treasure for more money.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846660/extras/gif2.gif?t=1710393419"><br/><br/>Create a formula needed to open the portal and enter a fantastic universe.<br/><br/>Research and learn how the formula is made and collect the necessary elements to open the portal.<br/><br/>Scare your friends in a halloween event.<br/><br/>Strange is a game with realistic graphics in an atmospheric environment. It tells a mysterious story based on a mission system in which we do various mischief through the eyes of a child, and you can spend an enjoyable 5 hours.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR WARS™: Battlefront Classic Collection</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2446550/STAR_WARS_Battlefront_Classic_Collection/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2446550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Fight in iconic battles from across the STAR WARS™ galaxy</h2>Play the classic STAR WARS Battlefront games, online and offline in this complete classic collection.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>This Classic Collection includes: </strong></h2><strong>STAR WARS Battlefront (Classic)</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Includes Bonus Map: Jabba's Palace</li></ul><strong>STAR WARS Battlefront II</strong><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Includes Bonus Maps: Bespin: Cloud City, Rhen Var: Harbor, Rhen Var: Citadel, and Yavin 4: Arena <br/></li><li> Includes Bonus Heroes: Asajj Ventress &amp; Kit Fisto</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features</strong></h2><i>Traverse the Galaxy in Campaign Mode &amp; Galactic Conquest</i> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Galactic Conquest: Devise your strategy, recruit your troops, and execute your tactical vision for conquering the galaxy. <br/></li><li>STAR WARS™  Battlefront Campaign: Experience iconic battles from STAR WARS Episodes I-VI<br/></li><li>STAR WARS™  Battlefront II Campaign: Join the rise of Darth Vader’s elite 501st Legion of Stormtroopers</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Massive Locations with up to 64-player Online Support</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on the ground: Wookiee Warriors, Jet Troopers, Droidekas and more in massive multiplayer action<br/></li><li>Drive iconic vehicles: Speeder Bikes, AT-STs, AT-RTs, and more in offensive and defensive battles<br/></li><li>Pilot legendary starships: TIE fighters, X-wings, and more in space and air dogfights</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Expanded Hero Assault</strong> </h2>Hero Assault is playable on all ground maps including: Death Star, Kashyyyk, Kamino, and Naboo for the first time ever<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight with heroes: Mace Windu, Yoda, Luke Skywalker, and many others!<br/></li><li>Battle with villains: Darth Maul, General Grievous, Darth Vader, and many others!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Life of Logic</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2791740/A_Life_of_Logic/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a journey of intellect and emotion with "A Life of Logic", a narrative-driven game intricately woven around an elegant logic puzzle. In this captivating experience, your mission is to fill the board with the binary dance of 0s and 1s, all while mastering three deceptively simple rules:<br>
   + No Three Consecutive Same Numbers<br>
   + Balance in Rows and Columns:<br>
   + No identical rows or columns<br>
<br>
As you immerse yourself in solving these brain-teasing puzzles, a charming story unfolds, revealing a life adorned with memorable milestones and extraordinary moments. Each level you conquer peels back a layer of the narrative, enticing you to venture deeper into the tale of this extraordinary life.<br>
<br/>
Welcome to a new dimension of puzzle-solving, where the elegance of logic meets the richness of storytelling. A Life of Logic not only challenges your analytical prowess but also rewards you with hidden images, seamlessly blending the thrill of puzzle-solving with a captivating narrative.<br/>
<br/>
Key Features:<br/>
<br/>
Elegant Logic-Based Puzzle: ALOL introduces a binary puzzle that transcends the ordinary, providing an engaging challenge that surpasses the enjoyment found in traditional games like Sudoku.<br/>
<br/>
Story-Based Game: Immerse yourself in a narrative tapestry where each successfully solved puzzle unveils a hidden image, contributing to the enchanting story of an extraordinary life.<br/>
<br/>
Memorable Milestones: Revel in the joy of discovery as each puzzle brings you closer to unraveling the secrets of a life filled with remarkable milestones.<br/>
<br/>
Are you ready to embrace the harmony of logic and storytelling? Welcome to the immersive world of A Life of Logic!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corbid! A Colorful Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1034020/Corbid_A_Colorful_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/corbid_help_V2_ENG_V2.png?t=1710370857"><br/><br/>Dive into this exciting and colorful adventure! Help Corbid overcome the challenging mazes and secure his place as champion. Get ready to have fun as you embark on this colorful and exciting mission, where you'll have to use your dexterity and skills to solve the intricate puzzles in the huge gardens.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/CORBID_01_.gif?t=1710370857"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/corbid_obstacles_V2_ENG.png?t=1710370857"><br/>The gardens are full of fun riddles and puzzles in which you will have to do your best to advance. Use all your resources, feel the speed and the frenzy of the jumps to get as far as you can. Also, let yourself be advised by different allies and even help some of them to unlock new areas.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/Corbid_caja.gif?t=1710370857"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/corbid_friends_V2_ENG.png?t=1710370857"><br/>Find adventure companions on your journey to help you complete fun scenarios and become more effective against dangers. Combine skills to achieve unique moves and solve more complex puzzles. Above all, make friends!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/Corbid_boton.gif?t=1710370857"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/corbid_2_enemies.png?t=1710370857"><br/><br/>Get ready to fight in thrilling battles against terrifying final bosses. Use Corbid's skills to find the enemies' weaknesses and defeat them in a battle that will keep you on the edge of your seat - don't give up, stay focused and secure victory against these formidable opponents!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/CORBID_02_.gif?t=1710370857"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/corbid_3_ENG.png?t=1710370857"><br/><br/>Embark on an adventure through lush and vibrant worlds filled with creatures of every color imaginable. Dive into the mysteries hidden in the vast gardens and unravel the secrets they hold. Enjoy a wonderful journey where the magic of color will surprise you around every corner.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/CORBID_03_.gif?t=1710370857"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knife To Meet You</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1663650/Knife_To_Meet_You/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1663650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>CAN YOU HIT THE APPLE ON THE HEAD?</strong><br/>Be the knifemaster who makes the most stunning tricks! You can do whatever you want, and complete a level in different ways. All in bullet time slow mo! You can play only for fun or competitively online: in any 10 sec game you have a chance to break the World Record, visible for all players! You have 2 knives at start. Earn gold to buy other weapons by completing story levels, achievements, online battle levels, finding treasures, winning challenges.<br/><strong>And a mega bonus for inviting your friend. We reward every invite with 50X multiplier now!</strong><br/><br/><strong>TRICKS YOU CAN DO:</strong><br/>- Stuck, Slice, Pierce, Pin objects - all can be part of a multi combo!<br/>- Hat Trick: hit your friend's hat without hitting him!<br/>- Team Trick: pass a knife to your friend who finishes the job!<br/>- Underhand Trick: Throw with reverse spin and hit a target!<br/>- Spin Trick: Spin the knife at least 450 degrees before hitting the target!<br/>- Overtake Trick: Triple combo an object but in different order!<br/>- Sacrifice Trick: Quickly hit your partner after you have completed the level.<br/><br/><strong>FEATURES:</strong><br/>- 50 Story Levels<br/>- 3000+ online map levels<br/>- XP and gold system<br/>- 48 weapons (No-Spin Knife, Spin Knife, Axe, Fork, Cleaver, Nails, Card, Sickle, Scythe, Sword, Shuriken, Sawblade, Sabre, Dart, Spear, Tomahawk, Swiss Knife, Frisbee, Boomerang, Crossbow, Pistol, etc)<br/>- Leaderboard for each weapon, each level!<br/>- Survival levels: how far can you get?<br/>- Daily challange: one-chance circus: online challenge each day where you can try only once (new levels each day).<br/>- Level Editor and Community Levels<br/><br/><i>CAUTION Cut Hazard: Product has functional sharp edges. Contact may result in injury. Always keep blades away<br/>from fingers and body. Handle with care. Use with adult supervision.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Order of the Snake Scale</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2451470/The_Order_of_the_Snake_Scale/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> <u> !!! WARNING !!! </u></strong><br/><strong> <u> !!! Indie Retro Horror !!! </u></strong><br/>"Tank control" - player control system!<br/>Old school style puzzles!<br/>Self-created 3D models!<br/>For convenience, it is recommended to play on a xbox compatible controllers.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451470/extras/lov.gif?t=1710413854"><br/><br/><strong> <u> Discover a surreal world inspired by Lovecraft</u></strong><br/>Explore a dystopian world that accurately alludes to current world events.<br/>The universe describes one of the paths that humanity can follow. Every decision has its consequences. In this universe, power over humanity is exercised by Unions of States and Corporations.<br/>The prohibition of religion, mass sterilization, the appropriation of people's property, eugenics, the subjugation of humanity to the NML Corporation, this is the new world order.<br/>Are you ready to experience it?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451470/extras/story.gif?t=1710413854"><br/><br/><strong> <u> A suspenseful story</u></strong><br/>During the game, you will learn about the history of the Universe and the heroes who live in it.<br/>With each step in the game, you will discover the semi open world, its history and receive tips to help you solve the Happy Rock case.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451470/extras/niestandardowe_obrazy.gif?t=1710413854"><br/><br/><strong> <u> First, survive</u></strong><br/>A mysterious murder, monsters, rooms where you will definitely not be safe, corpses everywhere. <br/>It's easy to die in this world... Especially in the least expected moments.<br/>Stock up your inventory, collect clues, fight, make decisions and survive.<br/><br/><strong> <u> Explore and solve puzzles</u></strong><br/>Explore the atmospheric, unique, nooks and crannies of Happy Rock. Delve into the mystery of this place and the doomed world.<br/>Solve logic puzzles, combine facts to solve a murder case, demonstrate your skills during arcade missions.<br/>A dark world is waiting to draw you in. Perhaps forever.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the machine</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2775220/Inside_the_machine/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2775220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2775220/extras/feature_robot.gif?t=1710361702"><br/><br/><strong>Inside the machine</strong> is a simple yet challenging puzzle game with over 20 unique levels. You are playing a soul, jumping from machine to machine and controlling them to reach your goal until finally you get back to your original body.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2775220/extras/feature_switch.gif?t=1710361702"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echo of Ayllu</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1670240/Echo_of_Ayllu/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1670240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							After the last great galactic war, humanity plunges into darkness and the last survivors struggle for their lives, in a world where robots have seized power. Play as the resistance, opposing forces or friendly little aliens and... back the tide of history.<br/><br/><strong>ENTER THE BATTLEFIELD</strong><br/>Build a supercharged deck made up of 8 characters: 7 Allies and 1 Champion.<br/>Games are fully customizable, live against your opponent!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1670240/extras/steamplayscreen2.gif?t=1710372084"><br/><br/><strong>FULL CONTROL</strong><br/>In Echo of Ayllu, <strong> you decide your own way to win</strong> with <i>Artifacts</i>:<br/>- <i>Thunder </i>: Win the game by stealing all the opposing energies.<br/>- <i>Domination </i>: Smash the opposing characters!<br/>- <i>Tempus</i>: Control the battlefield across space and time!<br/><br/>The traditional mana system is over too.<br/>Each character placed on the board bring an amount of <i>Power Particles</i> in play that the player can use as they wish. The <i>Powers Particles</i> boost your characters by multiplying their attack and can unlock powerful abilities. Use them wisely, these resources are precious.<br/><br/><strong>THREE FACTIONS</strong><br/><i>- Terra (Earth)<br/>- Proxima<br/>- Elysia. </i><br/><br/><strong>MULTI-MODES</strong><br/>Many modes have been implemented: Standard, Reversal, Mirror, Draft, Unlimited ... have fun everytime, everywhere!<br/><br/><strong>INTERPLAYER MARKET</strong>.<br/>Fed up with paying boosters all the time when new cards are released? Echo of Ayllu offers you an in-game market where all players can meet to buy, trade or sell their cards. Do business, collect, or have fun speculating if you want, everything is possible. Echo of Ayllu is a real trading card game!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1670240/extras/steamcollec.gif?t=1710372084"><br/><br/><strong>LEADERBOARD</strong><br/>Climb the seasonal leaderboard, earn rewards in tournaments, control the galaxy!<br/><br/><strong>ADVENTURE</strong>.<br/>Dive into a spectacular vision of the future of our humanity. And make history.<br/>The magnificent adventure mode will introduce you to the basic mechanics of the game, but also to the liabilities of the main characters . Sit back, get ready to take off.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1670240/extras/steamadventure.gif?t=1710372084"><br/><br/><strong>Social</strong><br/>Join colonies, form your crew, build alliances.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F6XuK7GS" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1670240/extras/whited.png?t=1710372084"/></a><br/>Let's talk! Discover the news around the game, and get your beta access!<br/><br/><i><br/>"My friend and I have been walking in the vast Siberian desert for several weeks. The burning days passed by - the freezing nights too. And yet, we were still there. Nothing could have overcome our determination. It guided our steps. The atrocities of the new wars, all these repeated invasions have brought up in us old visceral forces that we should never have known. And despite all that, there was nothing we could do to prevent it ... this genocide ... The whole earth is nothing more than a vast ruin, a shadow of a civilization that it has housed ... at the mercy of a planet that owes it everything.<br/>We didn't know it yet, but my companions and I weren't alone. We thought we were the last bastion of invisible resistance. In reality, we were the very first link.<br/>Billions of billions of kilometers away; allies, friends ... whole armies were preparing. A science from another time came to us and we were not only going to change the course of our destiny, but also that of all of humanity. All... of... Humanity. But that we didn't know yet."</i>  - Rover Hamilton, October 2417						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Shire: Room One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517850/Toy_Shire_Room_One/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FkhSxB2MSgD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/Toy_Shire_-_Discord_Banner.png?t=1710352808"/></a><br/><br/><br/>Play through the <strong>three levels in Kevin's Room</strong> and defend your room against your old toys. Face Memphis-X in the final level and put a stop to his assault as he crushes your soldiers in an attempt to get to your base.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyVengeance.png?t=1710352808"><br/>You received new toys from your family. Isn't that lovely? Oh, it's for sure... <br/>Your old toys, though, aren't getting along as well. They are no longer cared for and have been forgotten. So what follows next? They're going to join together against you and assault your brand-new toys, so be prepared. But never worry! You're in luck since your brand-new toys are troops of green soldiers. They still require your aid though! Control, strengthen, and defeat the opposing forces! However, focus with care, the enemies you encounter might not be your old playthings!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/InteractiveTowerDefense.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Tower building alone won't be sufficient to repel incoming attackers. Build up your own troops in the best feasible positions, then unleash attacks into enemy territory. Never abandon your towers, and deploy your troops in accordance with the traits of the enemy. First, the attacking forces will attempt to get past your defenses. Build and improve towers to aid your army. By using unique abilities, you can support your troops and towers as well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/EpicBattles.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Safeguard your base against waves of attackers. You need to pick the right troops if you would like to prevail. Clean the paths and guard any open routes. Upgrade your troops and unlock new ones to take down the waves and claim victory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyRealm.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Enter a world and a narrative built around the toys that enriched your youth, including toy soldiers, dinosaur sets, robots, building blocks, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_3.gif?t=1710352808"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uootoy 3671</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1947440/Uootoy_3671/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1947440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The legendary comical action puzzle game 'Uootoy' -- which was first published in the August 1984 issue of I/O Magazine (published by Kougaku-sha), gained popularity on the FM-7, PC-88, and Sharp X1. Now the ultimate evolution has arrived in the form of 'Uootoy 3671'.<br>
<br>
The objective of the game is simply to arrive at the goal. However, a plethora of obstacles stand in your way. Simplistic yet amazingly varied, every stage is bound to keep you entertained.<br>
<br>
TENTEN-kun, the star of the original 'Uootoy', will be joined by TELTEL-chan. As either the hero or heroine, players can take on all 100 of the original Uootoy's stages. An even greater challenge awaits in the story mode, which contains 100 new stages. A map editor is also included, ensuring many sleepless nights for dedicated players.<br>
<br>
Uootoy 3671 features a team of massively talented musicians. WING, whose credits include the 'Mega Drive Mini 2' and previous Mindware titles, has produced the sound system. Junko Ozawa, the legendary Namco composer.<br>
<br/>
*  WING, whose credits include the 'Mega Drive Mini 2' and previous Mindware titles, is the producer of the game's sound system."<br/>
* Junko Ozawa, the legendary NAMCO composer who has worked on Nintendo classics such as 'Rhythm Heaven' &amp; 'Tomodachi Collection'."<br/>
*  Daisuke Shiiba, another fantastic artist responsible for works on 'Rhythm Heaven', 'Tomodachi Collection', and the 'Final Fantasy Pixel Remastered' series."						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StepByStep</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2642870/StepByStep/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2642870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a multi-person co-created online painting game, by the members of the word relay painting, to complete a number of complete paintings together, quickly call on friends to draw your story!<h2 class="bb_tag"> Painting in 3d scene: </h2><br/>Paint in 3d scenes, intertwine fantasy with reality with a paintbrush, and more scenes await you to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Special brush: </h2><br/>With a special brush, you can paint a wider variety of pictures, perhaps with more variety.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Work with others: </h2><br/>Multiple people work together, you can continue to create on other people's paintings, and complete a story together.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Create your own brush: </h2><br/>You can easily customize your brush, and your own brush may be more convenient to use.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Collect flowers: </h2><br/>You can give flowers to others in multiplayer, or receive flowers from others as proof of recognition.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Create your own artwork: </h2><br/>Create your own portfolio and paint to your heart's content.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
