<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>The Texas Chain Saw Massacre - Nancy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2665290/The_Texas_Chain_Saw_Massacre__Nancy/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2665290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Bring home Nancy, possibly the most heinous and disturbed Family member of them all! She's an expert at using her friendly looks to lure unsuspecting Victims into deadly situations they can't escape. Her barbed wire traps and unnatural Spy ability make for a unique and deadly combination.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destiny 2: Season of the Wish Silver Bundle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2218002/Destiny_2_Season_of_the_Wish_Silver_Bundle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2218002/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Purchase the Season of the Wish Silver Bundle and receive the 'Brave Explorer' Legendary Emote along with 1700 Silver (1,000 + 700 bonus Silver) which you can use to purchase Season of the Wish, cosmetics, and more! <br>
<br>
Visit the Seasons tab in-game to use your Silver and buy Season of the Wish.<br>
<br>
To unlock your new Emote, visit the Special Deliveries Terminal in the Tower.<br/>
<br/>
One-time purchase only available during Season of the Wish. Silver is an in-game currency used at the Eververse store.<br/>
<br/>
Season of the Wish not included with purchase.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead by Daylight - Chucky Chapter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2656010/Dead_by_Daylight__Chucky_Chapter/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Main_Banner.png?t=1701190880"><br/> <br/>Meet your new best friend ‘til the end. Dead by Daylight: Chucky brings an iconic horror legend into The Fog with a new Killer: <strong>The Good Guy - Chucky</strong>. Purchasing this add-on unlocks an <strong>exclusive Charm: Good Guys Box.</strong> <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Killer_Power.gif?t=1701190880"><h2 class="bb_tag">CHUCKY</h2>Viciously cruel with a cutting sense of humor, Chucky is a brutally effective killing machine. Using his diminutive frame to his advantage, he’ll pop up when Survivors least expect it, chasing them down and introducing them to his trusty weapons.<br/> <br/><strong>Chucky’s Power: Playtime's Over </strong><br/><br/>The Good Guy is the first Killer in Dead by Daylight to feature a third-person camera.   <br/><br/><strong>Special Ability – Hidey-Ho Mode:</strong> When Chucky enters Hidey-Ho Mode, he becomes Undetectable and generates Map-wide footfalls, disorienting Survivors. Though Hidey-Ho mode can be entered at any time, it does have a cooldown.   <br/> <br/><strong>Special Ability – Scamper:</strong> While in Hidey-Ho Mode, Chucky can Scamper under a downed Pallet or through a Window, allowing him to quickly gain ground.   <br/><br/><strong>Special Ability – Slice &amp; Dice:</strong> While in Hidey-Ho Mode, Chucky can sprint and lunge forward to Slice &amp; Dice Survivors. This attack can be held, but Chucky will be unable to do anything else during this time. If a Survivor tries to Vault a Window or Pallet while you’re charging a Slice &amp; Dice attack, Chucky can quickly chain into a Scamper.   <br/> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Killer_Perks.png?t=1701190880"><br/><br/>Chucky comes with <strong>3 new perks.</strong><br/><br/> <h2 class="bb_tag">Hex: Two Can Play</h2>When a Survivor Stuns or Blinds you a number of times, a Dull Totem becomes a Hex Totem. When that Hex is active, Survivors who stun or blind you are Blinded for 4 seconds. The Hex effects persist as long as the related Hex Totem is standing.<h2 class="bb_tag">Friends ‘Til the End</h2>You become Obsessed with one Survivor. When you Hook a Survivor that is not the Obsession, the Obsession becomes Exposed and reveals their Aura for a brief duration. If you Hook the Obsession, a random Survivor will scream, reveal their position, and become the Obsession.<h2 class="bb_tag">Batteries Included</h2>When within the vicinity of a completed Generator, gain Haste. The movement speed boost lingers for a brief duration after you leave the Generator’s vicinity.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656010/extras/DBD_CH30_Exclusive_Item.png?t=1701190880"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXCLUSIVE CHAPTER ITEM: GOOD GUYS BOX</h2>The Chucky Chapter includes an exclusive item, the <strong>Good Guys Box Charm</strong>, only available as part of the DLC. Please note that this item cannot be purchased separately.<br/><br/><br/><i>His name is Charles Lee Ray. Chucky to his friends... You’ll be his friend ‘til the end, right?</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1701185282"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1701185282"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1701185282"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retro Commander</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/338820/Retro_Commander/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/338820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/338820/extras/icon_and_text_v05_-_600x195px.png?t=1700862195"><br/>Retro Commander is a <strong>post-apocalyptic</strong> real-time strategy wargame (RTS). Take command and fight it out in a world where a cataclysmic timeline has transpired on Mother Earth. Wage wars solo, against the AI, or take on your gaming comrades and friends in cross-platform multiplayer matches. Form teams and clans and fight co-op style with the AI and other players for ultimate victory.<br/><br/>As opposed to other real-time strategy game, Retro Commander tries to focus on both, a fun <strong>single player</strong> and a thrilling <strong>multiplayer</strong> experience. The game strives to be easy to learn with a modern user interface. Single player comes with skirmish matches against the AI as well as a comic-based <strong>story campaign</strong>. Multiplayer can be played cross-platform and includes a ranking and rating system.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u>Post-Apocalyptic</u>: Real-time strategy (RTS) played in a post-apocalyptic timeline on Mother Earth. The environment includes day-night cycles, rain, snow, wind and solar flare activity.<br/></li><li><u>Story Campaign</u>: Deep campaign and story line of humanity after a cataclysmic event. Factions come with their own specialized <strong>technologies</strong> such as stealth, robots, drones or shields.<br/></li><li><u>Single &amp; Multiplayer</u>: A challenging AI for both single and multiplayer matches with co-op play. Cross-platform multiplayer including <strong>LAN</strong>/internet. ONLINE play comes with an award and rating system.<br/></li><li><u>Play Modes</u>: In addition to regular skirmish matches, the game supports missions such as elimination, survival, <strong>capture the flag</strong>, defense and <strong>battle royale</strong>. Available in both single and multiplayer also are escort and rescue missions.<br/></li><li><u>Structures &amp; Troops</u>: Common troops for land, sea and air warfare is available to all factions. Specialized elements such as stealth, shields, <strong>EMP</strong> weapons, nukes, <strong>portals</strong>, orbital weapons, assimilator and other troops and structures provide for additional variety.<br/></li><li><u>Research</u>: A <strong>tech tree</strong> and research options enable to build specialized structures and troops. A <strong>Tech Snatcher</strong> can be used to steal enemy technology.<br/></li><li><u>Modding</u>: A map editor is included allowing for player-modded maps including player-modded campaigns. All elements including troops, structures, as well as graphics and sound effects, can be modded if desired.</li></ul><br/>Although some troops are shared, the game is trying not to be a generic RTS-games. There are <strong>faction-specific technologies</strong> each with their strengths and weaknesses.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u>GRA Technology</u>: gives access to <strong>stealth</strong> and cloaking. Included are cloaked agents and spies as well as bombers with EMP and nuclear weapons. Available also are snipers and heavy airlifts. Can build uranium fabricators.<br/></li><li><u>ELC Technology</u>: provides <strong>robots</strong>, <strong>airships</strong> and robo dogs. Available also are a mechanic and heavy airlift. Can build stationary EMP-field generators.<br/></li><li><u>IDB Technology</u>: provides <strong>hovertanks</strong>, <strong>drones</strong> including EMP-field drones and drones equipped with napalm weapons. Can build fusion generators for power.<br/></li><li><u>Mayan Technology</u>: consists of <strong>decoy</strong> capabilities. Included are hologram tanks, transformers, dogs and dolphins. Can build <strong>portals</strong>.<br/></li><li><u>Ancient Technology</u>: provides <strong>shields</strong>, EMP soldiers, assimilators and napalm tanks. Can build matter fabricators.</li></ul><br/><strong>Free vs Paid (DLC or in-game)</strong>: The free version includes unlimited access to over 12+ multiplayer scenarios and Chapter 01 of the single player campaign. Purchasing the DLC <strong>"All Maps &amp; Modding"</strong> grants full access to the game. It includes everything for single player including the story campaign, skirmishing against the AI, ONLINE multiplayer or LAN-play with friends and family.<br/><br/><strong>No DRM</strong>: There is no DRM in the game. You <strong>don't need to connected to the internet</strong> to play single player games or the campaign. You don't need to be logged in to play LAN games either. You don't need to login either for WAN games (locally hosted games over the internet), but you will have to work out your router settings and do the appropriate port-forwarding so your friends can connect from remote.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header_alt_assets_2.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirate Fighting Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186400/Pirate_Fighting_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pirate Fighting Simulator is a free multiplayer PVP game developed in Unreal Engine 5 in which you fight other players using typical pirate weaponry. There are also cosmetics that you can unlock, these cosmetics can be either hats, weapon skins or in the form of a title that sits underneath your username. The game also includes emotes so you can absolutely boogie down silly style after destroying an enemy gamer. There are also two gamemodes one being TDM (Team Death Match)) and the second being FFA (Free For All).						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1699642767"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1700646226"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658820/Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							10 possible fruits and one goal, reach the Watermelon.<br/>Your job is to combine matching fruits to evolve them to the next one and eventually reach the coveted Watermelon.<br/>To help you, you have 3 different abilities at your disposal. But watch out, using these will cost you some of your points. Be smart about when you use them to get the highest score!<h2 class="bb_tag">GET THE WATERMELON</h2>How many Watermelons can you combine before your basket overflows?<h2 class="bb_tag">USE YOUR ABILITIES</h2>Power, level up and destroy — These abilities will help you reach the Watermelon, using any of those will also allow you to angle your aim.<h2 class="bb_tag">GOLDEN FRUIT</h2>If luck is on your side, you might even see the mysterious Golden Fruit. Find it and witness its effect firsthand.<h2 class="bb_tag">STATISTICS</h2>Track your progress with in-depth statistics. Visit the menu to see the number of fruits you've combined, your ability usage, and much more.<h2 class="bb_tag"></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.codecks.io%2Fwatermelon-game" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/extras/Roadmap_Banner.png?t=1700532981"/></a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football Manager 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2252570/Football_Manager_2024/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2252570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a real boss and write your own football story in Football Manager 2024, the most complete edition in the series yet. <br/><br/>Whether you’re a manager who likes to build from the bottom or prefers to chase immediate glory, the perfect challenge awaits. The arrival of the new Meiji Yasuda Insurance Ltd J. League licence unlocks J1 League, J2 League, J3 League for the first time ever, giving you the opportunity to explore new horizons in Japan.<br/><br/>Wherever you manage, it's up to you to build a team capable of competing with the world's elite.<br/><br/><strong>Game Description </strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Continue your relentless journey to the top of the footballing world by using the new ability to import your existing career from Football Manager 2023.<br/></li><li>Craft a winning tactical approach, incorporating modern football’s most popular systems and cutting-edge positional innovations to deliver victories on the pitch. <br/></li><li>Master the transfer market, using new ways to shape your side to cultivate a squad capable of achieving your goals. <br/></li><li>Level up your players on the training field, developing the mentality and teamwork needed to transform contenders into champions. <br/></li><li>See your tactical vision come to life on Matchdays, with every game elevated by improvements to ball and player movements.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">NEW FOR THIS SEASON</h2><br/><br/><strong>TRUER FOOTBALL MOTION</strong><br/><br/>Enhancements to player animations, ball physics and lighting deliver the most immersive Match Engine in Football Manager history. Move to the cutting edge of football by using the new Inverted Full-Back player role, while more intelligent player rotational movements add more fluidity to every highlight. <br/><br/><strong>DOMINATE FROM SET PIECES</strong><br/><br/>Make an impact at both ends of the pitch with an overhauled Set Piece Creator. Lean on the expertise of brand-new Set Piece Coaches to develop winning routines in every scenario that will help you to outsmart your rivals. <br/><br/><strong>BRACE FOR TRANSFER BATTLES</strong><br/><br/>Showcase your squad-building skills in our most refined transfer market yet. You’ll face a trickier battle for talent as your rival opposition managers are now more strategic than ever in their recruitment decision-making. <br/><br/><strong>NEW AGENTS TO BUILD A DREAM SQUAD</strong><br/><br/>Better shape your perfect squad with the introduction of new Intermediaries that will help you offload surplus players for a cut of the final transfer fee. Additional functionality for existing Agents and the debut of TransferRoom, a football marketplace for transfers in real life, gives you more real-world powered tools than ever to build an elite team and dominate the competition.<br/><br/><strong>ELEVATE PERFORMANCES WITH TARGETS</strong><br/><br/>Motivate your team to achieve more on and off the field by setting them individual Targets. Whether you’re focusing on goals scored in a season or average training performances, challenge your star players and top prospects to maximise their ability. <br/><br/><strong>A HOST MORE ADDITIONS</strong><br/><br/>Enjoy greater variety in every career with the arrival of two new game modes. Real World mirrors when players actually joined your club. Your World sets club squads and budgets at the day your career starts, meaning that only players who joined before that date will be in your squad, giving you the opportunity to rewrite your team’s transfer window.<br/><br/>Elsewhere, you can look to dominate international management and plan for your country's future with a revamped National Pool that gives you a better overview of the talent at your disposal. Match preparation and briefing meetings deliver you winning insights before each fixture. <br/><br/>That’s not all though, with many more changes waiting for you to discover in every career.<br/><br/><i>This version contains information that is still under approval process by rights holders and may contain data that does not, at this time, accurately reflect real world data. For context, some club and player assets may be absent during this version.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cards and Castles 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1719390/Cards_and_Castles_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1719390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Both incredibly deep and easy for new players to pick up, this fun and wacky CCG features a tactical board for a touch of strategy. Cards played spring to life on the battlefield as animated characters who can move and block enemies, adding depth to the traditional CCG formula. Build unique decks from 7 different iconic factions: Vikings, Crusaders, Warlocks, Pirates, Ninjas, Druids, and the NEWLY ADDED undead!<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Worldwide Online Cross-Platform Multiplayer<br/></li><li> Cross-Platform Accounts<br/></li><li> Multiplayer Lobbies, Friends Lists, and Chat<br/></li><li> Draft Mode<br/></li><li> Single Player Modes<br/></li><li> Collectible Cosmetics<br/></li><li> Lots of Free Cards<br/></li><li> Penguins</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For The King II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1676840/For_The_King_II/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_AboutThisGame_Steam_StoreBanner_2_EN.png?t=1699521848"><br/><br/>Once beloved by her people, Queen Rosomon has turned against her subjects, casting them into servitude in the darkness of Fahrul’s mines whilst building alliances with sinister and malevolent forces.<br/><br/>Gather your party in four player co-op or adventure alone through Fahrul as you risk everything to fight the tyrannical queen and bring an end to her oppressive reign.<br/><br/>From the creators of For The King, the much-loved RPG that blends roguelite and tabletop gameplay comes a new chapter in Fahrul’s history, designed on an updated engine bringing innovation and gameplay refinement for returning heroes and new adventurers alike.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading01_Inspired_ENGLISH.png?t=1699521848"><br/><br/>For The King II is easy for anyone to pick up and play, but takes skill, patience, and strategic excellence to master whilst remaining infinitely replayable with a procedurally generated map that ensures no two playthroughs will ever be the same. Unique yet familiar dice roll inspired movement, encounter and combat mechanics add even more spontaneity and variety as your fortunes rise and fall on the roll of the dice.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF01_InspiredByTabletop.gif?t=1699521848"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading02_Digestible2_ENGLISH.png?t=1699521848"><br/><br/>For The King II provides a complete campaign with over 30 hours of gameplay, split into 5 separate adventures, each narratively linked. The journey is long and the path is treacherous but fear not, if your party fails you will start stronger and wiser on your next playthrough with better starting items to draft into your loadout.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF02_RogueliteCampaign.gif?t=1699521848"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading03_Muster_ENGLISH.png?t=1699521848"><br/><br/>Create your party from 12 unique character classes, each with their own unique perks, strengths and playstyles. From the heavy-handed hitter of The Blacksmith, to the wily potion-wielding Alchemist, you choose which characters will take on the fearsome Queensguard and the combat strategies that will ensure success. Introduce new characters to your party with mercenaries and companions that enable you to pluck wild beasts from the forest floor and recruit ruthless mercenaries from local taverns (for a price of course) to bolster your ranks in times of trouble.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF03_MusterYouMight_.gif?t=1699521848"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading04_Party_ENGLISH.png?t=1699521848"><br/><br/>Traverse Fahrul solo or with up-to three friends in four-player co-op. As a solo player you can control all characters in your party, giving you complete ownership of the campaign map and combat strategy whilst in four-player co-op you must coordinate and negotiate with your party members. Play online multiplayer with your friends controlling your own character(s) or play offline co-op on the same PC. Offline co-op supports multiple controllers; each controller will have input control on everyone’s turn.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF04_PartyofFour.gif?t=1699521848"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading05_Evolved_ENGLISH.png?t=1699521848"><br/><br/>Inspired by turn-based classics, For The King II adds strategic depth to much-loved combat mechanics with the new Battle Grid, where movement and position provide you and your enemies with strategic buffs and penalties. Defend the back row by equipping a mighty Tower Shield, push enemies into lethal pools of burning fire, or entangle melee troops with dark magic cast with weapons looted from vanquished foes. The choice is yours!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF05_EvolveTurnBased.gif?t=1699521848"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading06_Explore_ENGLISH.png?t=1699521848"><br/><br/>Fahrul is both beautiful and deadly in equal measure. On your journey you will encounter a wealth of diverse biome environments brought to life in a breathtaking art style. From lush forests, toxic swamps and lava-filled wastelands to pirate (no scratch that!) Merling-infested tropical seas, For The King II transports you deep into the wonders of Fahrul, leading you further than ever before into this stunningly-imagined land of adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF06_ExploreFantastical.gif?t=1699521848"><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Ffortheking" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTK_Discord_Banner_EN.gif?t=1699521848"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoboCop: Rogue City</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1681430/RoboCop_Rogue_City/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FGzNdTVQAs6" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/ROBOCOP_ROGUE_CITY_BANNER_DISCORD_615x195px_EN.jpg?t=1701074570"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif01_EN.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif02_EN.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Description_Banner01_EN.png?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif03_EN.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Description_Banner02_EN.png?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif04_EN_V1.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Description_Banner03_EN.png?t=1701074570"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR OCEAN THE SECOND STORY R</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2238900/STAR_OCEAN_THE_SECOND_STORY_R/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2238900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The highly acclaimed second instalment in the STAR OCEAN series, returns as STAR OCEAN THE SECOND STORY R. <br/><br/>Brought to life with a unique 2.5D aesthetic, which fuses 2D pixel characters and 3D environments, this remake includes everything that made the original release so great while adding new elements too!<br/>Experience new battle mechanics, full Japanese and English voice overs, original and re-arranged music, fast-travel and so much more! Discover the definitive version of a classic but modernized JRPG that’s perfect for newcomers and long-time fans alike.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2238900/extras/RED_STEAM_Gif_Story_EN.gif?t=1700154197"><br/><br/>Space Date 366 - A Federation officer finds himself transported to a mystical planet. While searching for a way home, an encounter with a young girl draws him into a quest to save her people, just as an ancient prophecy foretold... <br/>Choose your path and witness an awakened destiny. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2238900/extras/RED_STEAM_Gif_Features_EN.gif?t=1700154197"><br/><br/><strong>- Fantasy and Science Fiction collide in a unique visual style</strong><br/>From dangerous dungeons to bustling towns, the world of STAR OCEAN THE SECOND STORY R is depicted in a stunning 2.5D style that combines beautiful 3D graphics with nostalgic 2D pixel characters. <br/><br/><strong>- Experience a story with dual protagonists</strong><br/>Start your journey with either Claude or Rena. Depending on your choice, the perspectives and the allies you can recruit will change. <br/>Get to know party members via the unique Private Actions system, grow relationships and unlock various endings.<br/>New character illustrations have also been created by long-term series artist Yukihiro Kajimoto. <br/><br/><strong>- Thrilling, visually explosive battles!</strong><br/>Enjoy fast-paced combat and use new mechanics to strategically defeat foes. <br/> “Break” by continuously dealing damage and order your allies to follow-up with an Assault Action to deal massive damage.<br/> <br/><strong>- Pair powerful gear with a plethora of skills</strong><br/>Customize party progression with a large selection of skills, including Cooking, Art, Metalcraft, and many more. Build up to Specialty levels and master the enhanced Item Creation system to craft ultimate equipment with different effects. <br/><br/><strong>- Japanese and English voiceover</strong><br/>All event scenes are now fully voiced using the same voice cast from the original game. In addition, the dialogue from STAR OCEAN SECOND EVOLUTION (2008) is also included and can be selected. <br/><br/><strong>- An iconic soundtrack rearranged by Motoi Sakuraba</strong><br/>All tracks have been re-composed, including full-band performance and strings sound. Exploration and movie scenes themes also have new recordings that take them to even greater heights.<br/> <br/><strong>- 3 difficulty modes</strong><br/>Pick EARTH for a relaxing journey, GALAXY for a satisfying challenge or UNIVERSE… if you’re brave enough to really put your skills to the test.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Talos Principle 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/835960/The_Talos_Principle_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/835960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/835960/extras/Talos2_reviews.jpg?t=1700476673"><br/><br/>Born into a new world where biological humanity is extinct but human culture lives on in a city of robots, you find yourself swept up in a mind-bending adventure involving a mysterious megastructure hiding enormous powers.<br/><br/>The more you discover, the more you will be confronted with questions about the nature of the cosmos and the purpose of civilization. The broken promise of a better tomorrow, the fear of repeating humankind’s mistakes, faith in reason or renouncing humanity altogether - the choices you make and the sides you take will determine the course of events.<h2 class="bb_tag">A New Generation of Puzzles</h2>Solve a wide array of puzzles with varying difficulty levels, including clever metapuzzles and highly challenging Gold puzzles. Finish the game without solving every puzzle, or pursue the rewards of complete mastery. A variety of new abilities, such as gravity manipulation and mind transference, join the established mechanics of the original Talos Principle, creating a fresh but familiar experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Philosophical Odyssey</h2>Take the next step forward in the story of The Talos Principle in a thought-provoking, character-driven interactive story with multiple endings penned by returning writers Jonas Kyratzes (The Eternal Cylinder, Clash: Artifacts of Chaos) and Tom Jubert (The Swapper, Subnautica), joined by Verena Kyratzes (The Hand of Merlin, Serious Sam 4).<h2 class="bb_tag">Brave New World</h2>Explore more than a dozen all-new environments, from a city on the brink of a paradigm shift to the varied landscapes of a mysterious island that holds the keys to the future. Take a break from puzzle-solving to discover long-buried secrets and strands of forgotten history.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Melodies of Creation</h2>Immerse yourself in the rich, bittersweet world of The Talos Principle with a stunning soundtrack by master composer Damjan Mravunac (Serious Sam, The Talos Principle), with a guest appearance by Chris Christodoulou (Risk of Rain 1 and 2).						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Time at Sandrock</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1084600/My_Time_at_Sandrock/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>My Time at Sandrock</strong>-Just like My Time at Portia, My Time at Sandrock takes place in a wholesome post-apocalyptic world 330 years after the Day of Calamity destroyed most modern technologies.<br/><br/>After accepting a job offer to become Sandrock’s newest Builder, you’ll arrive in the wild and rugged city-state, where it’s up to you and your trusty tools to restore the community to its former glory. Gather resources to build machines, befriend locals, and defend Sandrock from monsters — all while saving the town from economic ruin!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/Build_your_workshop.png?t=1700732786"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/build_workshop-min.gif?t=1700732786"><br/><br/>Transform a run-down workshop into a well-oiled production facility! Use an intricate set of machines to process materials and produce parts of huge structures before assembling them piece by piece to help Sandrock flourish.<br/><br/>Create hundreds of unique items at the worktable to decorate your homestead, give gifts to Sandrock’s residents, or assist with community requests.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/Explore_the_open_world.png?t=1700732786"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/explore-min.gif?t=1700732786"><br/><br/>Explore vast deserts surrounding the city-state of Sandrock. Dive into ruins to dig for Old World relics, seek our materials in hard-to-reach locations, or spend time relaxing in Sandrock with your neighbors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/Extensive_story___NPCs.png?t=1700732786"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/npc-min.gif?t=1700732786"><br/><br/>Experience a detailed story complete with hundreds of sidequests and over 30 all-new characters. Spend time getting to know Sandrock’s residents, uncovering backstories, and making meaningful connections along the way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/New_combat.png?t=1700732786"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/combat-min.gif?t=1700732786"><br/>Quickly shift between melee combat and third-person shooting mechanics in dynamic action battles.Use the new weapons and defense break mechanic to your tactical advantage, or boost your stats to simply smash through battles! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/MINI_GAMES.png?t=1700732786"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/mini_games-min.gif?t=1700732786"><br/>A diversity of mini-games allow you and local Sandrock residents to stay entertained in the desert town.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/Multiplayer_EN.png?t=1700732786"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/multiplayer-min.gif?t=1700732786"><br/>Explore, build, and battle with up to 4 players. Together, shape the dynamic town, construct towering structures, engage in battles, share romantic moments, and dive into mini-games. Every move counts, earning points and unlocking new dimensions for your evolving character. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/And_more.png?t=1700732786"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Use your workshop’s profits to turn the empty prairie into farmable land;<br/></li><li>Grow crops for extra cash or transform them into delicious dishes;<br/></li><li>Attend festivals with Sandrock’s residents;<br/></li><li>Find secrets and much more!</li></ul><br/>Both <strong>Portians </strong>and <strong>brand-new Builders </strong> who have never set foot in Portia will find a fun new world with lots to explore at their own pace, along with divergent NPC stories to enhance replayability. Experienced Builders will find everything you enjoyed about <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/666140/My_Time_At_Portia/" rel="" target="_blank"> My Time at Portia </a> and more, and you will feel right at home in the delightful life-sim RPG that is My Time at Sandrock.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FdZAQjFp" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1084600/extras/Steam_DiscordJoin_banner_Sandrock_003_1_.jpg?t=1700732786"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet S</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1948430/Planet_S/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Planet S is a real-time strategy game where your goal is to colonize multiple planets in a solar system to advance your civilization, build a city and supply it to grow your faction.<h2 class="bb_tag">Procedural planets</h2>The world consists of up to 14 procedurally generated planets which you can colonize. A planets type affects things like the appearance, the farm productivity and the kind of resources you can find on it. Every player starts the game with a spaceship and enough materials to colonize their first planet. Uncolonized planets can be claimed by building a spaceport on it. Once you claimed a planet, you can integrate it into your economy! <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948430/extras/PP.gif?t=1700519036"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build your civilization</h2>To advance your faction and unlock new buildings you need to attract residents and provide them the goods they require. By gaining more and more residents, you will unlock new production chains which will increase in complexity. At some point, your first planet won't be able to supply you with the resources you need, so you need to expand to other planets. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948430/extras/Build_Your_Civ.gif?t=1700519036"><h2 class="bb_tag">Choose your path</h2>While you start your population with workers, you need to make a decision when you advance to the second tier. You can upgrade your residents to the science or military civilization type. You can adjust the direction in an adjacent city center. Your decision will determine your path for the game and set a focus on either a more peacefully or a violent way of playing and winning the game. It may be rational to carefully consider your decision and adapt to the situation you are in. <br/><br/>Residents of a civilization type generate either science or military research points, which you can invest into research. The two research trees unlock bonuses and unique buildings for the corresponding civilization type. Through that, the game experience will rely heavily on the path you select. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948430/extras/Choose_your_path.png?t=1700519036"><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer</h2><br/>You can play alone or with up to three friends. You can either practice diplomacy and negotiate agreements, or act militarily against each other. Coupled with the fact that each player can build his civilization differently, every game remains exciting. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948430/extras/War.png?t=1700519036"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slay the Princess</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1989270/Slay_the_Princess/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1989270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You're on a path in the woods, and at the end of that path is a cabin. And in the basement of that cabin is a Princess. <br/><br/>You're here to slay her. If you don't, it will be the end of the world.<br/><br/>She will do everything in her power to stop you. She'll charm, and she'll lie, and she'll promise you the world, and if you let her, she'll kill you a dozen times over. You can't let that happen. Don't forget, the fate of the world rests on your shoulders.<br/><br/><i>You're not going to listen to him, are you? We're supposed to save princesses, not slay them...</i><br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Fully voice-acted</strong> by the impeccable Jonathan Sims and Nichole Goodnight.<br/></li><li> <strong>Hand-penciled art</strong> - every background and sprite is drawn traditionally with pencil and paper by Ignatz-winning graphic novelist Abby Howard.<br/></li><li> <strong>A princess.</strong> She's very bad and you have to get rid of her for all our sakes.<br/></li><li> <strong>No, the Princess isn't a cosmic horror.</strong> She's just an ordinary human Princess, and you can definitely slay her as long as you put your mind to it.<br/></li><li> <strong>Don't even think about trying to romance her.</strong> It won't end well for you.<br/></li><li> <strong>Hopefully you won't die.</strong> But if you do, you'll die a lot. Be careful and stay focused on the task at hand!<br/></li><li> <span class="bb_strike">Time loops</span> <strong>No time loops.</strong> Don't be ridiculous. Time is a strictly linear concept and it certainly doesn't "loop," whatever that's supposed to mean.<br/></li><li> <strong>A branching narrative</strong> where what you say and what you believe determines both who you are and how the story unfolds.<br/></li><li> <strong>A new roleplaying experience from the creators of <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1609230/Scarlet_Hollow/" rel="" target="_blank">Scarlet Hollow</a>.</strong><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FxCnAeqkkEY" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1989270/extras/discord_3.png?t=1700249330"/></a><br/><br/><i>Slay the Princess is a choice-driven psychological horror visual novel/dating sim with dramatic branching, light RPG elements, and hand-penciled art.</i></li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TELEFORUM</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186570/TELEFORUM/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FUdjMNaKkQe" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186570/extras/CR-Channel-Join-Discord.png?t=1701076571"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186570/extras/TELTETEXT-2.png?t=1701076571"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186570/extras/TELEFORUM-vhs_GS.gif?t=1701076571"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186570/extras/TELTETEXT-1.png?t=1701076571"><br/><br/>Journalist Walter Martins ended his life during the broadcast of “TELEFORUM”, a now-canceled TV program.<br/><br/>You’re visiting the apartment of his widow - to console the grieving woman and shine some light on this awful story…<br/><br/>But that’s not the main reason why you’re here.<br/><br/>It’s all about the <strong><i>tape</i></strong>, isn’t it?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186570/extras/TELEFORUM-what_GS.gif?t=1701076571"><br/><br/>Try to find out the truth and, <strong><i>PLEASE</i></strong>, ■■ NOT ■■■■■ ■■■■ ■■■■. This is important.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>FEATURES</strong></h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Analog VHS visual style, inspired by found-footage horror;<br/></li><li>As the reporter, conduct an interview with a grieving wife - balance between finding answers and pushing her over the edge;<br/></li><li>As the cameraman, explore the surroundings to uncover the truth;<br/></li><li>Multiple endings - can you solve the mystery of the tape?</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infection Free Zone – Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2485640/Infection_Free_Zone__Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1465460/Infection_Free_Zone/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485640/extras/go_ifz_112_steam_city__1_.jpg?t=1698678399"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1465460/Infection_Free_Zone/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1465460/Infection_Free_Zone/</a><br/><br/>Face the first few days after the survivors come to the surface. Gather resources, scavenge the buildings and create a Zone that will be able to stop horde attacks at night. Conquer Prologue to prove you're ready for the upcoming full version of Infection Free Zone.<h2 class="bb_tag"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485640/extras/go_ifz_SOCIETY_HAS_COLLAPSED_V2.gif?t=1698678399"/></h2>“The Mad Virus” has spread throughout the world with the speed of jet planes. The infected are highly aggressive, fast and strong.   <br/>In a couple of weeks, society collapsed. Cities are empty. There is no electricity, no water, and no food.  Yet, there are a few survivors...<h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485640/extras/go_ifz_REBUILD_ENG.gif?t=1698678399"/></h2>Establish a new “Infection Free Zone” wherever you choose. Set up shelters and production facilities. Adapt existing buildings to new needs. Build new farms and cookhouses. Establish defenses with walls, gates, and towers.<h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485640/extras/go_ifz_SCAVENGE_ENG.gif?t=1698678399"/></h2>Utilize your knowledge of the city. What is the best place to defend? Where were the grocery stores, where were the pharmacies? Where would you look for weapons? <br/>Remember that it’s dangerous to search the old buildings, there might be some infected lurking in the dark!<h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485640/extras/go_ifz_FIGHT_THE_INFECTED_ENG.gif?t=1698678399"/></h2>Each night your settlement might be attacked by large hordes of the infected. Fight them off with every tool available - melee and ranged weapons, vehicles, walls and towers. Strengthen your Zone and create an impregnable fortress, or simply enjoy rebuilding entire cities!<h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485640/extras/go_ifz_FIGHT_THE_LIVING_ENG.gif?t=1698678399"/></h2>Your Zone is not the only one that exists. Your survivors will surely find other surviving groups. Some will be friendly and willing to trade, but others will be extremely hostile. There might be some fighting involved!<h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2485640/extras/go_ifz_DEFEND_THE_ZONE_ENG.gif?t=1698678399"/></h2> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diablo® IV</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2344520/Diablo_IV/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2344520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join the fight for Sanctuary in Diablo IV, the ultimate action RPG adventure. Experience the campaign and new seasonal content.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2344520/extras/D4-Steam_Game-Standard_Edition_Image-616x347-en.png?t=1701194709"><br/>Diablo® IV Standard Edition includes:<br/>- Inarius Wings &amp; Inarius Murloc Pet in Diablo® III**<br/>- Amalgam of Rage Mount in World of Warcraft®**<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2344520/extras/D4-Steam_Game-Product_Copy_Image_01-616x347-en.png?t=1701194709"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2344520/extras/D4-Steam_Game-Product_Copy_Image_02-616x347-en.png?t=1701194709"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2344520/extras/D4-Steam_Game-Product_Copy_Image_03-616x347-en.png?t=1701194709"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2344520/extras/D4-Steam_Game-Product_Copy_Image_04-616x347-en.png?t=1701194709"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2344520/extras/D4-Steam_Game-Product_Copy_Image_05-616x347-en.png?t=1701194709"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wizard with a Gun</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1150530/Wizard_with_a_Gun/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1150530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Wizard with a Gun is an online cooperative sandbox survival game set in a magical wilderness wrought with dangerous creatures and arcane mysteries. Embark on a journey alone or with a friend to collect, craft, and outfit your wizard however you see fit as you explore the unknown. Carefully design weapons, bullets, and furnishings for your tower home but try not to burn it all down as the magic you wield escalates beyond your control...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1150530/extras/G9.gif?t=1697605388"><h2 class="bb_tag">Magical Weapon Customization</h2>Collect resources from the world and craft unique enchanted ammunition for your arsenal of guns. Combine elements for intended or suprising effects that alter the shot, blast radius, bullet trail, and even the status of the creature in your crosshairs<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1150530/extras/G5.gif?t=1697605388"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customized Whimsical Wizards</h2>Create a dazzling wardrobe for your magic wielder from robes and hats to armor and accessories - functional and fashionable in a way that's sure to impress.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1150530/extras/G7.gif?t=1697605388"><h2 class="bb_tag">Randomly Generated Biomes</h2>Explore and uncover new sections of the world filled with deserts, swamps, tundra, and prairies - all loosely floating together through space and time after the world was fractured. Unleash cosmic power from the safety of your tower to reset the world and emerge once again to find a new layout to once familiar lands.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1150530/extras/G8.gif?t=1697605388"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cooperative Adventuring</h2>Survive alone or with a wizard friend in online cooperative play to combine resources, magic, and creativity in your tower building. Or just watch it all burn down together - the choice is yours.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1150530/extras/G6.gif?t=1697605388"><h2 class="bb_tag">Systemic Gameplay</h2>Experiment with new spell combinations and find out how they affect enemies and the world around you the hard way. Creative arrangements can lead to powerful creations that overwhelm your foes while untethered amalgamations can be a recipe for disaster!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lords of the Fallen</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1501750/Lords_of_the_Fallen/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1501750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1501750/extras/lotf_accolades_16x9_HD_Mainbody.png?t=1701192165"><br/><br/>"the first true next-gen soulslike"<br/><strong>- IGN</strong><br/><br/>"best looking action-rpg to date"<br/><strong>- Fextralife</strong><br/><br/>"the first game I've seen that genuinely looks like one of the tech demos Epic's been showing off"<br/><strong>- PC Gamer</strong><br/><br/>"jaw-droppingly impressive"<br/><strong>- GamesRadar</strong><br/><br/>"fighting through two worlds at once is an action RPG gamechanger"<br/><strong>- PLAY</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1501750/extras/1_mainHeader.gif?t=1701192165"><br/><br/><strong>Lords of the Fallen</strong> introduces an all-new, epic RPG adventure in a vast, interconnected world more than five times larger than the original game. <br/><br/>After an age of the cruellest tyranny, the demon God, Adyr, was finally defeated. But Gods… do not fall forever. Now, aeons later, Adyr’s resurrection draws nigh. As one of the fabled Dark Crusaders, journey through both the realms of the living and the dead in this expansive RPG experience, featuring colossal boss battles, fast challenging combat, thrilling character encounters, and deep, immersive storytelling. Will your legend be one of light… or one of darkness?<br/><br/>Dare to Hope.<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore A Vast, Interconnected World</h2>Journey across two expansive, parallel worlds in your epic quest to overthrow Adyr. While the living realm presents its own brutal challenges, untold terrors lurk in the nightmarish realm of the dead. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1501750/extras/2_vastWorld.gif?t=1701192165"><h2 class="bb_tag">Define Your Own Legend</h2>Fully customise your character’s appearance from a wide array of visual options, before selecting one of nine character classes. Whichever starting path you take, develop your character to your own playstyle by upgrading stats, weapons, armour and spells. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1501750/extras/3_defineLegend.gif?t=1701192165"><h2 class="bb_tag">Master Fast, Challenging Fluid Tactical Combat</h2>Only those that master the deep, tactical combat can hope to survive. Choose from 100s of uniquely brutal weapons, or forgo metal for magic with devastating attacks of the arcane.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1501750/extras/4_fluidCombat.gif?t=1701192165"><h2 class="bb_tag">Unite or Fight in Online Multiplayer</h2>Experience the expansive, single player campaign alone, or unite with other lampbearers in online co-op. You are free to journey together for as long as you or they desire, collecting vigor (xp) and any weapons or gear enemies drop, ready to bring them back to your own world. Key items and quest progression won't be transferred, to retain the integrity of your own tale. For those playing online, be warned, as heroes from other realms can, and will invade.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1501750/extras/5_onlineMultiplayer.gif?t=1701192165"><h2 class="bb_tag">Wield a Device of Ungodly Power</h2>Your lantern possesses the ungodly power to cross between worlds. Use this dark art to reach forgotten places, unearth fabled treasures, and even manipulate the very soul of your foe.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1501750/extras/6_ungodlyPower.gif?t=1701192165"><h2 class="bb_tag">Rise from Death</h2>Fall in the world of the living, and rise again… in the world of the dead. You now have one final chance to return to your living state, as all manner of hellish creature descends upon you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1501750/extras/7_riseFromDeath.gif?t=1701192165"><br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Embark upon two vast, parallel worlds - that of the living… and the dead<br/></li><li>Master a fast, fluid and challenging combat system <br/></li><li>Overcome epic and colossal boss battles <br/></li><li>Wield devastating magic attacks and character buffs<br/></li><li>Invite a second player to join your campaign in uninterrupted, online multiplayer (only host saves world progress)<br/></li><li>Encounter a wide array of characters, eager to offer a dubious hand… <br/></li><li>Fully customise your own unique character <br/></li><li>Choose from 9 starting character classes, including Knight, Rogue and Fire Apprentice</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Hawk's™ Pro Skater™ 1 + 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2395210/Tony_Hawks_Pro_Skater_1__2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2395210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Play the fully-remastered Tony Hawk’s™ Pro Skater™ &amp; Tony Hawk’s™ Pro Skater™ 2 games in one epic collection, rebuilt from the ground up in incredible HD.<br>
<br>
Skate as the legendary Tony Hawk and the original pro roster, plus new pros. Listen to songs from the era-defining soundtrack along with new music. Hit insane trick combos with the iconic handling of the Tony Hawk’s™ Pro Skater™ series.<br>
<br>
Play all the original modes and go head-to-head with local 2-Player modes. Show off your style and creativity with upgraded Create-A-Park and Create-A-Skater features. Compete against players from around the world in Multiplayer modes and leaderboards.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COCOON</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1497440/COCOON/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1497440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Jeppe Carlsen, the lead gameplay designer of LIMBO and INSIDE — COCOON takes you on an adventure across worlds within worlds. Master world-leaping mechanics to unravel a cosmic mystery.<br/><br/><strong>Worlds within Worlds</strong><br/>COCOON is a unique take on the puzzle adventure genre, where each world exists within an orb that you can carry on your back. Wrap your head around the core mechanic of leaping between worlds—and combine, manipulate, and rearrange them to solve intricate puzzles.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1497440/extras/GIF_C9_15.gif?t=1699984773"><br/><br/><strong>Alien Machinery</strong><br/>Interact with alien environments and biomechanical devices left behind by an ancient civilization. Journey through unique and diverse biomes, from industrial structures to massive organic caverns, and discover how they are connected to one another.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1497440/extras/GIF_A_15.gif?t=1699984773"><br/><br/><strong>Orb Abilities</strong><br/>Each orb has an ability that can be unlocked, thereby turning the orb into a unique tool for you to utilize within other worlds. Use these abilities to uncover hidden pathways and objects, fire projectiles to trigger switches, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1497440/extras/GIF_B2_15.gif?t=1699984773"><br/><br/><strong>Monstrous Guardians</strong><br/>Mighty guardians protect every world, and you must face them in fierce battles. Each fight is unique and requires you to master new and satisfying mechanics.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1497440/extras/GIF_D_15.gif?t=1699984773"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonring</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2373630/Moonring/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2373630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>A <i>free</i> game by the co-creator of the XBox's Fable series.</strong><br/><br/>Five hundred years ago, the land of Caldera was plunged into endless darkness. Decades later, five moons rose in the sky, bringing light to the world and strange Gods with it. With them came the Dreams: calls to Devotion promising supernatural Gifts.<br/><br/>Thus, the new Calderan civilisation was born; a world of Devotion and Dreamers, Gods and Gifts, with a Dreamless Archon acting as the Gods' mortal representative. But Archons are not eternal, and a successor must be found.<br/><br/>You are Dreamless: free to choose your own destiny, to ask questions others dare not, or even become Archon yourself.<br/><br/>What will you do, Dreamless one?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2373630/extras/SteamSeparator.png?t=1697860475"><br/>Moonring is a retro-inspired open-world, turn-based, tile RPG in the style of the classic Ultima games, but created from the ground up with modern design sensibilities.<br/><br/>The world's geography is hand-designed, but the deadly dungeons beneath the surface reconfigure each time you leave... or die.<br/><br/>Travel, trade, sneak, fight and sail the world of Caldera. Speak with the townsfolk, learn Caldera's secrets, and challenge the Archon for his throne... or even overthrow the Gods themselves!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2373630/extras/SteamSeparator.png?t=1697860475"><br/>Features:<br/>- Large, hand-designed open world<br/>- An infinite supply of dungeons generated using your character name<br/>- Over 100 varied enemy types, from fodder to bosses<br/>- 35 unique Gifts from the Gods, their usage changing with the moon phases<br/>- Sailing, ship-to-ship combat and boarding<br/>- A Dungeon Synth OST with over 50 tracks, all made using retro Mod Trackers!<br/>- A hidden magic system and many other mysteries<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2373630/extras/SteamSeparator.png?t=1697860475"><br/>A note from the creator:<br/><br/>Hi folks. I've loved RPGs since the early 1980s, and grew up playing games like Lord British's 'Ultima' series and early Roguelikes. This is my love-letter to a style of gaming that has largely fallen out of fashion: with its vivid, bright sprites overlaid on stark black backgrounds, true open-world gameplay, and lack of handholding. The days I spent playing these games were spent in joyful exploration and discovery, venturing into the dark unknown, a co-author of the experience, filling in the gaps left by the primitive art with my imagination. For those of you who did the same, I hope Moonring recaptures some of the spirit of those days for you. For those who did not, I hope that the more modern conveniences you find in this game allow you to catch a glimpse of what we did 40 years ago.<br/><br/>My heartfelt thanks to all who spared even a moment to play this. Please be kind to my mistakes. I will fix them. :-)<br/><br/>- Dene						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Train Sim World® 4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2362300/Train_Sim_World_4/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2362300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							YOUR HOBBY – YOUR ADVENTURE – YOUR WAY<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2362300/extras/Gif_1.gif?t=1701194771"><br/><br/>Feel the power of simulation in your hands. Experience immense velocity and express unrivalled creativity with Train Sim World 4! Expand your rail hobby and discover the raw emotion of driving a diverse array of iconic routes and trains. From training center to mountain pass, this is your journey.<br/><br/>RAIL SIMULATION FOR ALL<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2362300/extras/Gif_2_1.gif?t=1701194771"><br/><br/>Learn the basics of operating a range of traction in the Training Center, which now features the Class 323 and 8F as well as the Class 66, meaning you can get to grips with diesel, steam and electric power, before taking to the rails of the real world. Play with trains that work for you, new difficulty ratings offer early insight into the complexity of content, and new settings eliminate trip-up areas, build your confidence, then master every machine.<br/><br/>FREEDOM TO CREATE<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2362300//extras/Gif_3.gif?t=1701194771"><br/><br/>FREE ROAM! Pick any train you want and drive it wherever you want – you now have complete control over how to run routes in your way. Take a photo and make the memories last with PHOTO MODE and GALLERY – pause in the middle of the action and craft the perfect shot; the power is in your hands. Get creative with the upgraded SCENARIO PLANNER and LIVERY DESIGNER, which now feature additional tools and options to fine tune your personalised train experience. Share your hard work with other players through CREATORS CLUB. <br/><br/>CHOOSE YOUR PATH<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2362300//extras/Gif_4.gif?t=1701194771"><br/><br/>Whether you are brand new to Train Sim World or a long-standing veteran, enter Train Sim World 4 in your own way – various paths and upgrade options are available to get you started. If you upgrade from a previous Train Sim World, your collection and profile progress come with you!<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2362300/extras/TSW4_SKU_Infographic_Steam_Standard_616x347.png?t=1701194771"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2362300/extras/TSW4_SKU_Infographic_Steam_Deluxe_616x347.png?t=1701194771"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2362300/extras/TSW4_SKU_Infographic_Steam_Special_616x347.png?t=1701194771"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2> <br/><ul class="bb_ul">  <li>Learn to drive realistic trains on detailed routes <br/></li><li>Expand your knowledge on the Training Center <br/></li><li>Put your skills to the test across engaging scenarios and varied timetables  <br/></li><li>Express your creativity with Livery Designer, Scenario Planner and Photo Mode <br/></li><li>Choose your journey with Free Roam <br/></li><li>Experience all Train Sim World 4 has to offer with new available content <br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>East Coast Main Line: Peterborough - Doncaster with the LNER BR Class 801 <br/></li><li>Antelope Valley Line: Los Angeles - Lancaster with the Metrolink F125 <br/></li><li>S-Bahn Vorarlberg: Lindau - Bludenz with the ÖBB 4024 <br/></li><li>DELUXE EDITION: LNER Class A3 60103 Flying Scotsman <br/></li><li>DELUXE EDITION: Railpool BR 193 Vectron (and Nahverkehr Dresden - Riesa) </li></ul> </li><li>Expand your collection with new upcoming and TSW Compatible content <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>SPECIAL EDITION:<br/></li><li>Southeastern Highspeed: London St Pancras – Ashford Intl &amp; Faversham<br/></li><li>Linke Rheinstrecke: Mainz - Koblenz<br/></li><li>LGV Méditerranée: Marseille - Avignon<br/></li><li>Northeast Corridor: Boston - Providence</li></ul></li><li>Your existing collection comes with you <br/></li><li>Powered by Dovetail Games’ proprietary SimuGraph® vehicle dynamics engine and Unreal Engine 4® technology  <br/></li><li>Download size will vary depending on purchased content </li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Paso, Elsewhere</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1546310/El_Paso_Elsewhere/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1546310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>El Paso, Elsewhere</strong> is a supernatural neo-noir third-person shooter. Hunt werewolves, fallen angels, and other damned creatures in a vivid slow motion love letter to action classics. Fight your way through a reality-shifting motel, floor by bloody floor. Save the victims of Draculae, lord of the vampires. Destroy the villain you loved--even if it means dying yourself.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1546310/extras/topbar.gif?t=1698158343"><br/><br/>Somewhere in El Paso, Texas, a three-story motel gained another 46 stories... all below ground.<br/>So, yeah.<br/>This is going to get loud.<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURING</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Original hip-hop soundtrack.<br/></li><li> Molotov cocktails filled with holy blue flame.<br/></li><li> A fully-voiced neo-noir story campaign set in a reality-shifting motel full of monsters.<br/></li><li> Hordes of destructible physics objects; for shooting.<br/></li><li> More slow-motion dives than you would think it is humanly possible to fit into a single video game.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1546310/extras/endbar.gif?t=1698158343"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WitchSpring R</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1958220/WitchSpring_R/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1958220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1958220/extras/en-intro.gif?t=1698161918"><br/>WitchSpring R is a story-driven RPG combining elements of simulation, collecting &amp; crafting, and battling. Play as Pieberry, a white-haired, bunny-eared witch growing up in a forest filled with monsters. To relive her childhood memories (eating delicious food!), she longs to venture among humans, but she can't find a way to the outside world... until your story begins! A world of new experiences is waiting for YOU to explore with her.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Features </h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1958220/extras/en-魔女养成.gif?t=1698161918"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Train Pieberry in all kinds of skills to make her more powerful! Your choices decide her future growth<br/></li><li>Collect and fuse various magic ingredients. Cook magical meals for Pieberry to increase her magic abilities<br/></li><li>"Feed" unneeded nutrients to Pieberry's staff to upgrade it in the direction you choose.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1958220/extras/动画-俯卧撑.gif?t=1698161918"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1958220/extras/en-丰富的剧情.gif?t=1698161918"><br/>Follow Pieberry through an all-new story, encountering all sorts of witches, humans, and never-before-seen monsters. Are they friends? Foes? Or...? All kinds of hidden stories are waiting for you to set out and uncover!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1958220/extras/动画-丢士兵.gif?t=1698161918"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1958220/extras/en-多重收集.gif?t=1698161918"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Magic tomes, recipes, and special items are hiding all over the world for you to discover;<br/></li><li>Train different types of pets for different types of help on your adventure;<br/></li><li>Choose your favorite magic attributes to train, designing your own battle strategy.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1958220/extras/动画-骑猪.gif?t=1698161918"><br/><br/>Finally (and most importantly!), our star Pieberry is brought to life with adorable, lively animation and voice acting. She can even dress as a human to sneak into the village!<br/><br/>Please Follow and Wishlist the game, and join our community to get all the latest updates!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astro Planes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2645970/Astro_Planes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Astro Planes is set in the year 2074. Where you play as a lone pilot with advanced weaponry at your disposal. You are humanity's last hope, earth's finest. Defend earth from the unknown alien threat. As you travel across space, jumping through portals and engaging in fast paced battles with advanced aliens from many light years away. Your mission, Defend earth, locate the alien home world and bring this war to an end<br>
<br>
Astro Planes is a (single player) 3D side scroller space shooter with some 2.5D elements and many levels to play through. With a sci- fi themed fantasy atmosphere set in space and classic space shooter mechanics. Astro Planes is the modern day side scroller and space shooter of today.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2331710/Sky_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Sky Survivors</strong> is an arena shooter roguelite. Choose from a variety of skills, unlock unique characters and weapons. Build «stairway to heaven» — a sky tower, each floor of which gives your character a unique bonus. Create your own overpowered build to survive against hordes of monsters!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/1-st_eng.png?t=1701195497"><br/>Over 100 different skills will help you create a unique build every run. You can become an elemental mage, a weapon master, or summon magic books to destroy your enemies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/action.gif?t=1701195497"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/3-st_eng.png?t=1701195497"><br/>Each weapon has its own unique playstyle.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/chakram.gif?t=1701195497"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/4-st_eng.png?t=1701195497"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Bullet Hell — classic «roguelike». Increased speed of monsters and their projectiles. You and the monsters take more damage.<br/></li><li>Deckbuilder — the number of monsters and the amount of experience gained are increased.<br/></li><li>Standard Mode — perfect for the first time.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/5-st_eng.png?t=1701195497"><br/>Build a «stairway to heaven» — floors that grants your character a unique permanent bonus or a powerful temporary buff.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/obelisk.gif?t=1701195497"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2331710/extras/6-st_eng.png?t=1701195497"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><h2 class="bb_tag">Auto-aim mode for gamepads and PC.</h2></li><li><h2 class="bb_tag">Over 100 different skills to choose from.</h2></li><li><h2 class="bb_tag">«Stairway to Heaven» — each floor has its own unique bonuses.</h2></li><li><h2 class="bb_tag">Unique weapons that completely change your playstyle.</h2></li><li><h2 class="bb_tag">Diverse characters with unique abilities.</h2></li><li><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple game modes allow you to choose the playstyle to your liking.</h2></li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARPZONE DRIFTER 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693070/WARPZONE_DRIFTER_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							With full throttle and no breaks, WARPZONE DRIFTER 2 is a minimalistic, retro-hardcore, physics-based drifter minigame.<br>
<br>
You control a car that has to pass through three checkpoints before teleporting to the next warpzone. How many times you can teleport in 2 minutes is your score. There is a creature hunting you.<br>
<br>
Players can expect old-school gameplay with a simple objective and a difficult challenge.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOS Zombie Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2689600/SOS_Zombie_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2689600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							SOS Zombie follows the harrowing journey of a group of diverse survivors trapped in a city overrun by a zombie apocalypse. The group fights waves of increasingly aggressive zombies while preparing for a rescue helicopter scheduled for evacuation a rescue point.<br>
<br>
Gameplay:<br>
<br>
Setting: The game unfolds in an expansive, decaying cityscape with abandoned buildings, narrow alleys, and desolate streets. The environment is dimly lit, and eerie soundtracks intensify the sense of impending danger.<br>
<br>
Objective: Players must survive successive waves of increasingly aggressive zombies while locating essential supplies, fortifying their position, and signaling the incoming rescue helicopter.<br/>
<br/>
Survival Elements: To endure the relentless assault, players scavenge for resources such as ammunition, medical supplies, food, and building materials to fortify their position. They must strategize and manage these resources efficiently, balancing offensive and defensive strategies.<br/>
<br/>
Combat System: The game offers an arsenal of weapons, including pistols, shotguns, assault rifles, explosives, and makeshift traps. Each weapon has distinct advantages and limitations, encouraging players to adapt their tactics based on the situation. Headshots are critical for conserving ammunition and taking down zombies swiftly.<br/>
<br/>
Base Building: As the game progresses, players have the opportunity to fortify their position by constructing barriers, setting up turrets, and reinforcing their safe zone.<br/>
<br/>
Helicopter Rescue: Throughout the gameplay, players must maintain a distress signal to guide the rescue helicopter. This involves activating an SOS signal that attracts the zombie waves<br/>
<br/>
Multiplayer Mode: Players can team up in a cooperative mode, strategizing together to fend off the undead and increase their chances of survival.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long Gone Days Soundtrack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/511220/Long_Gone_Days_Soundtrack/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/511220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Immerse yourself in the captivating post-rock soundscape of the Long Gone Days OST! <br>
Inspired by Mariusz Duda, Sebastián Marín uses a balance of electronic and acoustic instruments to highlight the game's themes of conflict and human connection.<br>
<br>
Soundtrack includes both mp3 and FLAC files.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vampire Dynasty: Diaries</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2708990/Vampire_Dynasty_Diaries/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							We will show you a bloody good time. From established historical facts about the origins of vampire myths to lesser known information about the blood sucking creatures of nightmares this digital magazine will give you something to sink your teeth in if you are a fan of Count Dracula, Vlad the Impaler, Nosferatu or other sharp-fanged beasts.<br>
<br>
Add to that an exiciting look behind the scenes of the development of the anticipated new entry to the Dynasty franchise and get to know the lore of the fictitious Balkan area of Sangavia as well as the mysterious characters you are going to meet.<br>
<br>
Enjoy the first issue free-of-charge! Further issues will be arriving in irregular intervals and subject to a charge.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oh Darling! I Hate To Tell You This...</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2686360/Oh_Darling_I_Hate_To_Tell_You_This/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686360/extras/title0.png?t=1701185920"><br/>Little Darling makes a wish at the place where all the wishes come true. Then her journey begins. She has to fight against the monsters with the power of light.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686360/extras/title1.png?t=1701185920"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Enter the gates of the hell to reveal the truth.<br/></li><li>Find upgrades &amp; different bullet types!<br/></li><li>Fight against bosses of hell.<br/></li><li>Survive the enemy waves.<br/></li><li>Find your mama.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1701185282"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1701185282"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1701185282"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IN TRUCK DRIVING</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2660320/IN_TRUCK_DRIVING/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2660320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Get set to enjoy the truck simulator and experience real truck driving on the highway<br/><br/>This truck simulator is set in an open-world realistic 3D environment in which you have to cruise through city traffic and as well as on endless stretches of comfortless highways. The addition of different types of trucks improves the experience. Unlock these trucks by advancing to the next modes.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Four different modes</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Many levels to play</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interstellar Impact</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2540160/Interstellar_Impact/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Interstellar Impact in a stylized single player adventure game. Explore the vastness of space by traveling and evolving throughout different stages.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540160/extras/Asteroid_GIF_600x200.gif?t=1701173048"><br/><br/>Starting as an innocent asteroid your goal is to evolve and progress to larger stages. Collide with smaller asteroids and evolve to the planet stage.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540160/extras/Planet_GIF_600x250.gif?t=1701173048"><br/><br/>As you grow and become the source of all light in the universe your journey is not over. Do not hit any larger objects until you explode and become a black hole.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540160/extras/Sun_GIF_600x250.gif?t=1701173048"><br/><br/>Defy gravity, increase your speed and set up the best time possible.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noctuary</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2143680/Noctuary/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/英文_大标题.png?t=1701172317"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/1奇光异彩_英文.png?t=1701172317"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/英文_主角介绍.png?t=1701172317"><br/><br/>Noctuary is a dual-protagonist Visual Novel. Players can play the role of the duo, Fancia Dream and Alina Nightsong who have dreams of "becoming Arborangers who protect and serve everyone." Travel through the fairy-tale-like world as the duo, experience their lively daily adventures, and gradually encounter the life story of a mysterious girl who came down from the sky.<br/><br/>Meanwhile, don't forget to fight against the everpresent monsters—"Darkritters!" These dangerous enemies threaten the life of Illuminators constantly. Sharpen your fighting skills, defeat ferocious monsters and ensure peace in your community!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/2华丽战斗_英文.png?t=1701172317"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/ARPG01_英文.gif?t=1701172317"><br/>During your adventure, you will fight against various enemies. You can defeat them with a cascade of powerful combo attacks!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/ARPG02_英文.gif?t=1701172317"><br/>The two main characters master different skills and present various fighting styles, which allows you to win a battle in whichever method you choose. Switch between the two girls in battles to cope with enemies' attacks and finish them off with the powerful On-field Switch skill and the Synergy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/3任务选择_英文.png?t=1701172317"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/Quest01_英文.gif?t=1701172317"><br/>Embark on various missions within Inlixaland and become a unique "Arboranger."! In addition to the main storyline that spans several tens of hours, there are also over 20 side routes and quests featuring different stories and characters to explore. Join forces with diverse Illuminators as companions, cultivate relationships, and earn adventure rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/4祝福标题_英文.png?t=1701172317"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/Blessing01_英文.gif?t=1701172317"><br/>The friendships and blessings you harvest along the journey will strengthen you in battle. Feel free to combine the "Blessing Petals" that are embedded with features of different characters to customize your battle style. In addition, there are many other well-designed cultivation systems that are ready for you to explore!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2143680/extras/感谢尾图_英文.png?t=1701172317"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panda Magix : Golden Trains Edition - Slots</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693830/Panda_Magix__Golden_Trains_Edition__Slots/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Panda Magix : Golden Trains  Edition is a 5 reel, 25 payline slot machine (pokie) with a Oriental theme oriented from left to right. - WITH THE SIMILAR LIGHTNING STRIKE FEATURE.<br>
This new version is our second release with our new Golden Trains Feature.  <br>
Grab yourself a drink, sit back, play and enjoy. Now also with authentic background ambience recorded from a live venue to create a real atmosphere, just like you are actually at a casino.<br>
<br>
Free game feature is awarded when 3 or more scatters appear on any line and is awarded 8 free games.<br>
During free games any (6) six cash values on screen  trigger the Golden Trains Feature.<br>
During play any (6) six or more Golden Trains ( Symbols ) scattered anywhere on screen start the Golden Trains Feature..<br/>
During the Golden Trains Feature there will be 3 free spins, when an additional dollar value lands on screen it will re-trigger free spins back to 3 until no more coins land on screen, win Mini, Minor and Major jackpots when symbols land on screen.<br/>
<br/>
To Win Grand Jackpot screen needs to have all 15 reels lite up with a winning value.<br/>
Scattered during Free spins paid or free cannot be retriggered during play.<br/>
<br/>
This is the closest slot machine simulation you can get to the real thing, with features like, Reserve Button and Paytable. <br/>
Play Pokies4fun Slot Simulations at work or at home without losing a cent, Great Games Great Fun........<br/>
No real money can be won.<br/>
For Amusement Only. If you are looking for the best Australian slot machine games, then look no further than Pokies4fun. Pokies4fun is a leading provider of online and offline pokies for fun that are designed to entertain and thrill you. Pokies4fun offers a wide range of slot machine games with different themes, features, and jackpots.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Splash: Animals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693480/Color_Splash_Animals/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Color Splash: Animals is a charming and relaxing puzzle game that will lift your spirits and take You into the world of adorable animals and art. Venture into the gallery, where you will find many extraordinary and colorful animal paintings.<br/><br/>You need to skillfully move puzzle pieces, find their corresponding places, and harmoniously connect the colored details. Paying great attention to detail and applying a creative approach will help you become a true master at assembling animal pictures.<br/><br/>Start gathering your collection of animal pictures right now!<br/><br/>In Color Splash: Animals:<br/><br/>•50 levels<br/>•Colorful art<br/>•Simple controls (mouse)<br/>•Achievements<br/>•Relaxing music<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693480/extras/640х360.png?t=1701158425"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StarL2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2669330/StarL2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							StarL 2 brings you an electrifying Match 3 game designed to push your puzzle-solving abilities to their limits! Engage in a captivating adventure as you align dazzling gems and shatter through an impressive array of tiles across more than 130 levels, each presenting its own unique challenge. Immerse yourself in breathtaking visuals and indulge in endless entertainment with the remarkable StarL 2!<br>
<br>
Enjoy countless hours of Match 3 fun with over 130 levels!<br>
Uncover a treasure trove of exclusive power-ups.<br>
Utilize convenient tools to maintain your competitive edge.<br>
Beat the clock to become the master of gem-matching!						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekend solitaire: Summer village</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2672790/Weekend_solitaire_Summer_village/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Weekend Solitaire Summer Village dives into a bright world filled with vibrant gameplay, colorful animations, and hours of addictive card-solving fun! Enjoy an exciting journey through 130 levels of various complexities, each presenting a unique challenge that will put your solitaire skills to the test. Get ready to unwind and bask in the joys of summer with Weekend Solitaire Summer Village!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClearIt 16</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2677910/ClearIt_16/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							ClearIt16 immerses you in a vivid puzzle adventure filled with precision and skill. The game's vibrant colors and intricate levels offer a unique experience as you navigate its challenges. Your task is simple: shoot balls from the game's edges to hit the center, aiming to align similarly colored balls. Once these like-colored balls touch, they vanish, edging you closer to the ultimate goal – a clear field.<br>
	In ClearIt16, the core field showcases a captivating pattern crafted from balls, ensuring every move you make is strategic. With options to shoot from the top, bottom, left, and right edges, every choice holds significance. Though you're granted unlimited time, the game's complexity elevates as you advance, pushing your strategic thinking and foresight. With 200 levels and five unique game modes, the challenge awaits. Are you ready to clear the field?						</br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redrum Hotel</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667000/Redrum_Hotel/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Redrum Hotel is the very first title by MetalMana Games. It's a short, first-person horror adventure game where you collect scattered notes and try to avoid the evil presence that seeks to rid you of your sanity. You play as a hotel attendant who seems to be slowly losing his mind. There are mysterious forces lurking within Redrum Hotel, accompanied by a dark history that seems to keep on growing with every new visitor. Can you keep your sanity? Will you escape?<br/><br/><strong>Experience The Horror Of Redrum Hotel</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Avoid the sinister girl who watches you every move.<br/></li><li> Wander through Redrum Hotel's creepy hallways, dining hall, foyer and storage room.<br/></li><li> Collect the 7 mysterious notes scattered around the hotel.<br/></li><li> Manage your flashlight's battery level as you search through the darkness.<br/></li><li> Get out alive.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nitrojet</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1563210/Nitrojet/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1563210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Nitrojet is a chaotic metroidvania where <u><i>everything</i></u> is destructible. Run and rip your way through ancient ruins, cities, and caves, all while surviving dangerous airborne beasts. Use your tools and abilities to navigate the twisted lands, use your jetpack to soar through the skies, and burn your way through the ash. <br/><br/>It's a chaotic world. One wrong step and you'll be torn apart. Combat is high speed and frenzied, with threats ripping through all parts of the sky. Struggle against all the odds and claim your throne as the flame-borne god of destruction. Will you bring the world back from the brink, or will you rip it to shreds once and for all?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1563210/extras/Untitled_video_-_Made_with_Clipchamp__1_.gif?t=1701129674"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Everything, from the ground, to the people, to the world itself, is destructible.<br/></li><li>Use your tools to exploit and conquer every part of the environment.<br/></li><li>Sleuth out many different solutions to each and every encounter.<br/></li><li>Seize control of the bodies of enemies, using them to further your combat and exploation. <br/></li><li>Map out and explore the vast ruins covering the isolated world's peak, discovering Nitrojet's 12 full areas.<br/></li><li>Unlock and discover new abilities to help you burn your way through the world.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1563210/extras/Untitled_video_-_Made_with_Clipchamp__3_.gif?t=1701129674"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1563210/extras/Untitled_video_-_Made_with_Clipchamp__2_.gif?t=1701129674"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1563210/extras/Untitled_video_-_Made_with_Clipchamp__4_.gif?t=1701129674"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats and Seek</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2672090/Cats_and_Seek/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							😻 100 Cats!<br/>🔍 Hint system<br/>🎨 Choose your favorite color<br/><br/>Let's play hide and seek with 100 cats!<br/>Can you find them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/extras/game_play.gif?t=1701124095"><br/><br/>And if bored with black and white doddles you can choose <strong>your own favorite color</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/extras/change_color.PNG?t=1701124095"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Requiem</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2382640/Death_Requiem/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2382640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Death Requiem is a survival fantasy game. You'll dive into the dungeon and explore the gothic environment to experience the grandeur of architecture. At the same time, danger is approaching... The rift in the universe has opened and countless enemies are coming. Use your strategy and skill combination to fight against the enemies. Are you ready to deal with constant stream of enemies and ready to start a wonderful adventure?<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Intense Combat:</strong> Play as the third person character and fight against constantly spawning demons from the outside world. Different combat styles and abilities allow the player to create your own attack preference and bring different game experiences.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wave System:</strong> Enemies will be refreshed in each wave and more and more. There will be more powerful enemies spawning in later waves. Get ready to face each wave of enemies' onslaught and try to survive as long as you can in this tense and exciting battle</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Collection system and hidden rewards: </strong> Player needs to collect items and gold scattered in the world that can be used to buy weapons and upgrade character's abilities. There is a hidden boss that can boost character's attributes after being killed. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Skill trees and upgrade system: </strong> When killing enemies, player can get blood currency that can be used to upgrade character's attributes. The skill trees contain various expertise that can be used expand character's attack style. These skills include basic attacks, healing abilities and weapon upgrade and can be unlocked through current expertise level</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Element upgrade: </strong> There are four kinds of magic cloaks in the game that can give players corresponding attributes that include: Fire, Poison, Lightning, Dark. Each magic cloaks contains magic skills that assist the player in killing enemies. These skills can be upgraded from skill trees once the player finds the cloak.  </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echoes of Fear</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2650750/Echoes_of_Fear/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2650750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Echoes of Fear invites you to unravel ancient mysteries beneath the tranquil facade of a valley frozen in time. Engage with a series of cryptic riddles, guiding your steps through a series of haunting houses, each hiding secrets that echo through the ages. Can you decipher the enigmatic clues and escape the eerie enigma that shrouds the valley?<br>
<br>
Gameplay:<br>
<br>
Explore the breathtaking Valley, take in the beautiful scenery while at the same time gathering clues to help determine the final location of the Artifact. Each house you enter contains paranormal encounters in one way or another.  <br>
<br>
* Hostile Wildlife - Wolves roam the map and they are very sneaky, you will need to keep your head on a swivel when you are out roaming around.<br/>
* The Guardian - The Artifact is guarded by a creature that will chase you upon seeing you. You can outrun it, but beware, you have limited Stamina.<br/>
* Torch Drain - You have your trusty torch at your disposal to help you once the sun sets. Be careful though, the battery drains in 2 minutes and takes 3 times as long to fully recharge.<br/>
* Stamina - Sprinting in this game sometimes is a must, especially when being chased. Obstacles are your best friend.<br/>
<br/>
How long will you last in Echoe's of Fear? For if you die, its game over. With no weapons to defend yourself, you must use your wits to survive!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond fantasy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2560740/Beyond_fantasy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2560740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2560740/extras/615_190_english.png?t=1701109195"><br/><br/>+ Beyond Fantasy's content can be played in single player or multiplayer.<br/><br/><a href="https://youtu.be/yBXuvMErMJY" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://youtu.be/yBXuvMErMJY</a><br/><br/>+ Beyond Fantasy is a shooting action bullet hell game that combines action, roguelike, and other elements.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2560740/extras/Anim.gif?t=1701109195"><br/><br/>+ Use dash(space bar) in battle and block enemies for 15 minutes to unlock the next area you can go to.<br/><br/>+ Each character class has a skill tree, and you can unlock the skill tree by collecting gold in the game.<br/><br/>+ A platformer-style (Devil's valley) game is also provided, so you can acquire a puppy when you achieve it within a given time. Depending on your records, you can acquire many different types of puppies.<br/><br/>+ Play a basketball game, a mini-game within the game. Leaderboards are provided, and you can get a colleague based on your score and ranking.<br/><br/>+ If you unlock a pet, you can summon it in Beyond Fantasy's roguelike.<br/><br/>+ Unlocking a colleague allows you to summon it in Beyond Fantasy's roguelike.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falling for Beans</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2615120/Falling_for_Beans/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the tale of Jack and the Beanstalk like never before! Control Jack as you attempt to climb down the Beanstalk while being chased by the mighty Giant. Strategically fall between the vines of the stalk and a variety of leaves, all of which have special attributes that both hinder and assist in your decent. Don't fret if you don't make it on your first go, collecting beans while descending both tops off your health and allows you to buy upgrades for future attempts!<br>
<br>
Do you think you can survive falling down the mighty Beanstalk?						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suika Shapes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2686690/Suika_Shapes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F9PdMuVHbRE" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686690/extras/discordbanner.png?t=1701191952"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686690/extras/suika.gif?t=1701191952"><br/><br/>🍉 In Suika Shapes, match two shapes of the same color to create a larger shape and increase your score. Careful though, the more you play, the less space you have<br/><br/>🔄️Rotate and strategically match shapes<br/><br/>🌐Features leaderboards for all gamemodes! Compete against the world, specialize and become a master of your favorite mode, and challenge your friends to beat your scores.<br/><br/>⚡Infinitely smooth interpolated graphics and highly responsive mouse control scheme<br/><br/><br/>🟢15 Unique Shapes all with leaderboards!:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Circles<br/></li><li>Triangles<br/></li><li>Squares<br/></li><li>Rectangles<br/></li><li>Pentagons<br/></li><li>Hexagons<br/></li><li>Pluses<br/></li><li>"T" Shapes<br/></li><li>"W" Shapes<br/></li><li>Various Tetriminoes<br/></li><li>... Or any combination of the above!</li></ul><br/>🛠️5 Modifiers to change up gameplay<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Swap - allows you to swap shapes with the "Next" shape<br/></li><li>Slippery - all shapes become slippery<br/></li><li>Charge - Charge up and shoot out the shape with extra force<br/></li><li>Low gravity - reduce gravity<br/></li><li>Bouncy - All shapes become bouncy</li></ul><br/>🎮3 Gamemodes<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Normal - The classic suika mode, aim to create and merge watermelon shapes. All shapes are carefully balanced so merging two watermelons is possible but very difficult<br/></li><li>Speed mode - The floor is rising faster every minute, match shapes quickly to lower it - or run out of space!<br/></li><li>Evolution - Start off with smaller shapes, then every double watermelon clear the shapes grow in size a little! Best for long play sessions</li></ul><br/>⏱️All this puzzling too slow for you? Try the rising floor mode and test your speed! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686690/extras/speed_suika.gif?t=1701191952"><br/><br/>The floor is rising faster every minute, match shapes quickly to lower it back down! Hold to charge and shoot out the shape with extra force!<br/><br/>Mix and match any shape, gamemode, and modifier and challenge your friends to beat your score!<br/><br/>Multiplayer will not be in the game at release but may be added in a future update.<br/><br/>Based on the game スイカゲーム (watermelon game)<br/><br/>Contact: <a href="mailto:suika-support@zan-kai.com">suika-support@zan-kai.com</a> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plunder Ball</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2679500/Plunder_Ball/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2679500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Plunder Ball is developed and published by an employee-owned independent game studio.  Support independent and employee owned game studios!<br>
<br>
Pirates.  Zombies.  Pinball.  Plunder Ball is a casual pinball-inspired game.  Survive wave after wave of zombie pirates as you fire, bounce, and tilt your way to victory. Gather gold and collect powerups to help you achieve a new high score. There is one board to play on, and the rounds do not stop- the only limit is how long you can survive against the onslaught of the undead. The more gold you collect between rounds, the greater your chances of survival.<br>
<br>
Powerups include:<br>
- A mega-sized cannonball to do massive damage<br>
- A fiery cannonball for rapid-fire attacks<br/>
- A bomb-equipped ball for explosive carnage						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grappling Gunners: Arena FPS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2652750/Grappling_Gunners_Arena_FPS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2652750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							It is an PvP FPS game where you can engage in high-speed gunfights with full freedom of movement, utilizing two grappling hooks on both sides. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2652750/extras/Demo_Grapple.gif?t=1701143973"><br/><br/>In addition to grappling, skills can be used to perform a variety of moves.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2652750/extras/Demo_FireAndSkill.gif?t=1701143973"><br/><br/>Master seven skills, including instant teleportation and bullet time, to battle your foes.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2652750/extras/Demo_SkillMenu.gif?t=1701143973"><br/><br/>When you and your friends feel like playing something different, like an FPS, we'd be delighted if you could enjoy a quick game.<br/>Since this is a solo project, updates may take some time, but we would appreciate your thoughts and feedback.<br/><br/>左右の2本のグラップリングショットを駆使して、縦横無尽でハイスピードな銃撃戦ができるFPSゲームです。<br/>瞬間移動やバレットタイムなど7つのスキルを駆使し戦おう。<br/>フレンドと何か他のゲームとかFPSやりたい！ってなった時にサクッと遊んでもらえると嬉しいです。<br/><br/>個人制作のため、アップデートには時間がかかるかもしれませんが、感想やフィードバックを頂ければ幸いです。						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War Maze</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2585570/War_Maze/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							War Maze is turn-based strategy game based on chess!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585570/extras/UnlockLayoutAll.png?t=1701093600"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585570/extras/WishlistGIF.gif?t=1701093600"><br/>War Maze matches are played on a map of tiles, similar to chess. Each piece has different tile-based movement and attack patterns. Each piece also has a certain amount of attack and health points.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585570/extras/UnlockOneLevelTwo.png?t=1701093600"><br/><br/>Beat your way through the campaign to get a sense of each piece's mechanics and unlock skins!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585570/extras/UnlockOne.png?t=1701093600"><br/><br/>Buy and select skins to form your own army to fight with in multiplayer mode!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585570/extras/UnlockOneLevelMult.png?t=1701093600"><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FZqKrbYTQAc" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585570/extras/discordCommunityImage.png?t=1701093600"> </img></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585570/extras/374448.png?t=1701093600"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shot Supreme</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2313600/Shot_Supreme/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2313600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Shot Supreme is an arcade basketball game inspired by incremental games. Like a clicker, but you have to score baskets.<h2 class="bb_tag">Score Points</h2>Sink baskets to score points<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2313600/extras/ShotSupreme_ScorePoints.gif?t=1701141283"><h2 class="bb_tag">Complete Missions</h2>Earn upgrade points by completing goals<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2313600/extras/ShotSupreme_CompleteMissions.gif?t=1701141283"><h2 class="bb_tag">Buy Upgrades</h2>Use your points to upgrade your abilities<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2313600/extras/ShotSupreme_BuyUpgrades.gif?t=1701141283"><h2 class="bb_tag">Unlock Special Balls</h2>Unlock special balls to earn even more points<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2313600/extras/ShotSupreme_UnlockBalls.gif?t=1701141283"><h2 class="bb_tag">Rinse and Repeat</h2>Complete every goal and max out all your abilities to earn a huge score!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My GF Doesn't Know What I'm Into</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2449820/My_GF_Doesnt_Know_What_Im_Into/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2449820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">About the game:</h2><br/>xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx<br/>"I've always been looking at you from afar.<br/><br/>I began to like you from the moment we first met,<br/><br/>and I can't keep my feelings hidden anymore.<br/><br/>Please come to the big cherry tree after class.<br/><br/>I want to tell you how I feel."<br/><br/>xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx<br/><br/><strong>🤍My new girlfriend is so cute and sweet. I can't believe such a nice girl likes me so much. But... would she still want to be with me if she knew what I'm into? 🤍</strong> <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>    A heart-pounding horror visual novel telling the story of you and your new girlfriend.<br/></li><li>    Pick the name of your friend and girlfriend, as well your own name.<br/></li><li>    Your choices determine what kind of story you'll get to see in each playthrough.<br/></li><li>    Featuring six different endings. Aim to see them all...?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2449820/extras/xcZ1h0.png?t=1701120688"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2449820/extras/duuaWP.png?t=1701120688"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2449820/extras/hY5jGY.png?t=1701120688"><br/><br/><br/>---------------------------------------------<h2 class="bb_tag">About Meiri Games:</h2><br/>I'm a solo Brazilian game developer who enjoys making cute horror games. MyGF is my first Steam release! I hope you enjoy this short adventure.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typing Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2683510/Typing_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2683510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Typing Battle" is a game based on typing speed and accuracy. In this game, players need to use the keyboard to input designated characters in order to defeat their opponents or achieve their goals.<br/>The game is highly competitive and requires players to have fast reaction skills, accurate judgment, and superb typing skills. Players can compete against other players in the game to challenge their limits, or enter as many words as possible within a limited time to earn higher scores.<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2683510/extras/ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1701085669"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacecraft Tactics</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2642080/Spacecraft_Tactics/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2642080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Progress through 5 chapters of the campaign, collect loot, craft items and upgrade your ship to overcome increasingly difficult challenges on 3 difficulty levels or in the integrated speedrun mode<br/></li><li> Micromanage your crew and your ship while staying on top of tactical battles<br/></li><li> Create and share your own ships and scenes in the built-in editors<br/></li><li> Play single player or online co-op, PvE or PvP in the 5 included game modes<br/></li><li> Designed to be modular from the ground up, Spacecraft Tactics supports community-created mods</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Play the campaign</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The last rebel outpost got spotted by imperial scouts. Relocate the outpost before the main fleet attacks!<br/></li><li> Throughout the campaign you must collect loot, craft items and upgrade your ship to overcome increasingly difficult challenges<br/></li><li> Adapt your strategy and loadout to different situations as you progress through the campaign<br/></li><li> Play single player or online with a friend<br/></li><li> Designed with multiple playthroughs in mind<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Every playthrough is different<br/></li><li> 3 difficulty levels<br/></li><li> Speedrun mode with predictable rng, special game design and integrated display of splits</li></ul></li><li> Global highscores</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Micromanage your ship</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Distribute energy between systems<br/></li><li> Manage your crew<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Control ship systems<br/></li><li> Damage control<br/></li><li> Heal and revive crew members<br/></li><li> Manage inventories<br/></li><li> Provide emergency power to systems<br/></li><li> Automations</li></ul></li><li> Systems are connected to and powered by grids: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Energy<br/></li><li> Shield<br/></li><li> O2<br/></li><li> Network</li></ul></li><li> Maintain fields<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Shield (Shield emitters)<br/></li><li> O2 (Air vents)<br/></li><li> Healing (First aid stations)</li></ul></li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Tactical battles</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Manage your capacitor, shield buffer and EM emissions<br/></li><li> Use the right loadout to suit your tactical situation<br/></li><li> Position your ship and keep an eye on your opponents<br/></li><li> Develop a strategy and execute it</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Editors</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Create your own ships in the ship editor<br/></li><li> Design new scenarios in the integrated scene editor<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Play them in single player or online in custom game mode<br/></li><li> Most game modes also allow to use custom ships and scenes</li></ul></li><li> Share your ships and scenes with the integrated sharing functionality and in Steam Workshop (bundled as mods)</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Game modes and match making</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The following game modes are available for single-player and multiplayer games:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>The Last Outpost</strong>: Save the last rebel outpost from the empire!<br/></li><li> <strong>Battles</strong>: Multiplayer PvE mode with progression<br/></li><li> <strong>Arena</strong>: Multiplayer PvP arena<br/></li><li> <strong>Race</strong>: Test your skills maneuvering your ship and hunt for highscores<br/></li><li> <strong>Custom Game</strong>: Sandbox mode, play your own scenes or test your ship in a procedural generated environment</li></ul></li><li> Play on our server (for official highscores) or host your own game server:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Game server is embedded in the game (best for LAN sessions or custom games if you are able to forward a port in your router)<br/></li><li> There is also a dedicated game server included</li></ul></li><li> Use Steam game invites, find online games in the game browser or receive a quick-join code</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Modding</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Spacecraft Tactics has been designed from the ground up to be modular and support mods created by the community:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Change the balancing of the game or introduce new gameplay elements with the integrated entity editor<br/></li><li> Bundle your own ships and scenes and distribute it as a mod<br/></li><li> Customize the presentation by creating your own tilesets, sounds / music or even texts / translations<br/></li><li> Develop your own mods in Groovy programming language, ranging from simple scripts for your scenes up to full conversions</li></ul></li><li> Mods can be shared in Steam Workshop</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scroll Survival</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626690/Scroll_Survival/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Monsters will appear from all directions, and you need to survive by acquiring and enhancing magics.<br>
<br>
There is 22 magic, and there is 6 scroll to enhance magic, and there is 11 scroll to enhance character.<br>
<br>
You can learn 6 magic, and enhance damage, speed, duration, range, cooldown, number of each magic by using scroll.<br>
<br>
If you wanna make a many ice crystal, you need to choose magic number increase scroll.<br/>
<br/>
If you wanna make a fast magic arrow, you need to choose magic speed increase scroll.<br/>
<br/>
If you wanna make a giant tornado, you need to choose magic range increase scroll.<br/>
<br/>
So magic build you can choose is infinite.<br/>
<br/>
Boss monsters appear at the 4th, 8th, and 12th minutes of every stage.<br/>
<br/>
There is 12 stage total, and each stage has different terrain and different monsters.<br/>
<br/>
Find useful scroll, enhance your magic, and survive for 12 minutes!<br/>
<br/>
Good luck!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God secret</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678590/God_secret/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							It is a deep-sea themed survival game. In this vast and colorful ocean, there are numerous obstacles ahead that hinder your progress. However, you must control your position to constantly cross obstacles to reach the finish line, earning one point for each obstacle you cross. The incredible beauty of the abyss hides countless secrets and mysteries that can be explored, but danger always hides beyond your faint light. It is wise to use your skills to explore the dark seabed and illuminate your path. This game is a great test of players' eye and hand abilities. Come and see if you can find the secret hidden in the deepest depths of the sea!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24H Stories: The Blackout</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2690290/24H_Stories_The_Blackout/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">introduction</h2><br/>Experience various terrifying encounters on a night of power outage from a first-person perspective. As the story progresses, the line between reality and imagination will become blurred. Before the truth is revealed, one question needs to be answered: Who am I?<h2 class="bb_tag">features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>First-person Perspective: Experience a night of horror from a first-person perspective.<br/></li><li>Multiple Scenes: Explore maps based on the style of modern apartment buildings (5 in total).<br/></li><li>Psychological Horror: Immerse yourself in terrifying encounters within an eerie story.<br/></li><li>Puzzle-solving: Solve puzzles in complex environments using document clues.<br/></li><li>Choice Inclination: Alter the course of the plot through dialogues.<br/></li><li>Horror Scene Warning Feature: Don't like sudden horror scenes? No problem, with this feature enabled, you'll receive warnings in advance!<br/></li><li>Save Feature: Automatic chapter-based saving feature.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">about</h2><br/>This work is part of the 24H Stories series. Please refer to the information on the right for other works in the series.<h2 class="bb_tag">For youtuber and livestreamer</h2><br/>You are welcome to share any videos or pictures on your video platform. Feel free to express your opinions, whether positive or negative. I would greatly appreciate it if you could feature my game in your creations. If you would like me to include your related content (name, avatar, link) on the creator recommendation page of the next game, please submit your request in the discussion forum. Thank you :)						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange world</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2669160/Strange_world/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a game of drawing lines and receiving water. <br>
The small water cup in the game feels particularly sad because there is no water in the cup. Let's help it successfully receive water together. In the game, we need to draw lines to guide water into the water cup to pass the level. Drawing lines requires ink, and the less used, the higher the star rating. <br>
Note that you can use fixed objects around you to maintain the position of the line segment.<br>
 The entire game has almost only two shades of blue and white, and the characters and scenes are also outlined with extremely simple lines.<br>
 Simplicity exudes a sense of mystery and looks unique. With beautiful graphics, elegant music design, and simple yet compact operation, the game can bring players a very relaxed gaming experience. Now let's challenge together!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ink: Tournament Paintball</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1997630/Ink_Tournament_Paintball/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1997630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>START YOUR PAINTBALL TOURNAMENT</strong><br/>Set up your tournament rules, invite your friends and dominate the field. Ink: Tournament Paintball® is a FPS/PVP online that provides you the opportunity to play against the world  or in a private environment versus bots. You can join and find rivals on our constantly growing community on <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F6PH26dVnxf" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Discord.</a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1997630/extras/paintball_tournament.gif?t=1701130242"><br/><br/><strong>COMPETITIVE EVENTS</strong><br/>Are you ready to lead your team to victory? <br/>You can play on the <strong>Competitive League</strong> a <strong>5v5 Elimination Mode</strong> and work hard to rank up.<br/>This intense paintball experience is perfect for players who love a challenge and thrive under pressure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1997630/extras/competitive.gif?t=1701130242"><br/><br/><strong>FULLY CUSTOMIZABLE GUNS</strong><br/>Get the best paintball guns, more than <strong>+50 variations</strong> and <strong>a lot of attachments</strong> are ready on the in-game store to have a new owner. <br/>You can attach every accesory on the <strong>Workbench Menu</strong>, each one will modify the visual aspect and of course <strong>the performance of the marker</strong>. And not only your guns, you can also <strong>change the entire outfit</strong> of your character.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1997630/extras/customization.gif?t=1701130242"><br/><i>You can read specs of each item on store description.</i><br/><br/><strong>TAKE ADVANTAGE OF EVERY MOMENT</strong><br/>You can use the waiting room to work on the last details of the strategies to follow with your team, reviewing the layout together.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1997630/extras/layout.gif?t=1701130242"><br/><br/><strong>REALISTIC AS F*</strong><br/>Play now on Windy City Major, IL. Atlantic City, NJ. or the final step on Kissimmee, FL. Start your trip around the World Cup of Paintball 2022-2023 today on Ink: Tournament Paintball®!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
