<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>The Sims™ 4 For Rent Expansion Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2140610/The_Sims_4_For_Rent_Expansion_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2140610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Build Residential Rental lots in any livable World with up to 6 units per lot and households of up to 8 Sims per unit. Choose to live as a tenant or property owner in The Sims™ 4 For Rent Expansion Pack. Your Sim can now own and manage multiple Residential Rental lots or move into a home where they’re closer to their neighbors than ever (perfect for snooping!). From potlucks to evictions, there’s a lot to do and a bustling new world to do it in. Purchase through January 18 to get bonus items** to bring the Night Market home for your Sims.<br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Street Eats Digital Content</strong> — Bring night market flavor home with a grill cart, street umbrella, and fruit basket, available when you order from November 2 through January 18**.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>New Lot Type</strong> — New Residential Rental lots give you the chance to get creative with multi-family dwellings. Give your Sims a basement suite to rent out, a duplex to keep 2 families close, townhomes for multiple families, or even build apartments of up to 6 units (or more if you know the cheat). Each Residential Rental can be customized to your specifications.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Property Management</strong> — Property owner Sims can be present property managers, living among their tenants, or they can live in a separate residence while generating income from several property investments. If your Sim doesn’t want to manage the whole property, then perhaps the new Handyperson Career might be better suited to them. Property owners should keep their Unit Ratings high because, if they don’t, they could face consequences like a Tenant Revolt.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Closer Than Ever</strong> — Sims in Residential Rentals will inevitably get tangled up in each other’s lives. They’ll meet with other tenants at Social Events like a community potluck, in the garden, or other common areas at their Residential Rental, and have ample opportunity to discover their neighbor’s secrets by eavesdropping, snooping, or even breaking and entering. If you discover something juicy, you can blackmail other Sims for a bribe, too!<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Bustling and Beautiful</strong> — One of the most iconic scenes Tomarang has to offer is the Night Market where your Sims will savor new foods and add unique objects such as the pressure cooker and electric kettle to their homes. As you explore the world, you might even see children playing new games of marbles and hopscotch or discover the 4 new traits and 4 new aspirations unique to For Rent.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1701985511"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1701985511"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1701985511"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1701985511"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader - Season Pass</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687230/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Season_Pass/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Gain access to the two upcoming major expansions for Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader and save with the bundle price!<br>
<br>
1. Void Shadows<br>
(coming June 2024)<br>
<br>
The first major story expansion is all about the Rogue Trader's voidship, the life of its crew, and the threats lurking in its holds. Dive into a new epic story integrated into the main narrative, battle new enemies, and recruit a new companion — a death cult assassin. Explore new decks of your voidship, unlock new upgrade options, and master the mechanics of void combat. Meet new members of your crew on the bridge, such as the Astropath, the chirurgeon, and others.<br>
The events of this story will be reflected in the game's epilogue.<br/>
<br/>
This expansion offers 15 hours of gameplay.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
2. Lex Imperialis<br/>
(coming December 2024)<br/>
<br/>
The second major story expansion sees the Lord Captain join forces with a new companion — a member of the Adeptus Arbites. As the past of House von Valancius begins to present itself in a new light, the Rogue Trader faces difficult decisions that may affect the future of the entire Koronus Expanse.<br/>
Over the course of this story, you will get a chance to learn more about the collection of the Imperial Tithe, otherwise known as the Grand Harvesting. Interfere with this fundamental process of the Imperium at your own peril. Discover new areas, game mechanics, and archetypes — and of course, encounter new horrors of the Immaterium.<br/>
<br/>
This expansion likewise offers 15 hours of gameplay.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader - Deluxe Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682660/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Deluxe_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2682660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Gear up for Koronus Expanse with additional in-game items and digital goodies!<br/><br/>This pack includes:<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Digital Artbook<br/>Explore the beauty of the Koronus Expanse in this artbook made by our talented artists and designers!<br/></li><li>Digital OST<br/>Relive every moment through Rogue Trader’s breathtaking soundtrack, crafted by a team of talented composers. Listen at any time in the best format available, including tracks in FLAC and MP3 quality.<br/></li><li>Wallpaper Pack<br/>Get access to amazing game art in formats ideal for use as wallpapers on your PC/Mac or phone.<br/></li><li>In-Game Item - Firestorm-Class Frigate<br/>An alternative voidship to suit your needs, with alternative starting gear and a unique appearance!<br/></li><li>In-Game Item - Blast Wave Shotgun<br/>Blast your enemies away with this unique shotgun! It allows you to push your adversaries back even if you miss the shot.<br/></li><li>In-Game Item - Wrath of Saint Drusus Chainsword<br/>Show those heretics how it’s done. While this Chainsword removes the ability to make area attacks, it offers some amazing single target damage through truly devastating combos with your party. <br/></li><li>In-Game Item - Heirloom Autopistol<br/>The von Valancius Dynasty is venerable and proud, having access to some truly ancient weaponry – this Autopistiol, for example. The mastery required for creating this pistol has been lost to time, but the sheer craftsmanship enables the user to take their gunning skills to the next level.</li></ul><br/>Digital Goodies: Steam\steamapps\common\Warhammer 40,000 Rogue Trader\DigitalOSTArtbookWallpapers						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1702000678"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1702000678"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Born of Bread</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1555140/Born_of_Bread/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Beings from another age are causing havoc across the land! And with their mischief comes a great threat to everyone. The unlikeliest hero, a golem born of bread, will find himself and his newfound buddies in the middle of a drama that's thousands of years in the making. Together, they will visit incredible locals and meet fascinating characters. Although he may not look like much, Loaf might be the hero this land kneads.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Sentient Bread on a Quest</h2><br/>Play as a flour golem who possesses a never-ending childlike wonder and a set of odd abilities in this 2.5D adventure game!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Cinematic_opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/>Explore the different regions of a wonderful world ripe with mysteries and team up with a colorful cast of fleshed-out characters. With the help of your buddies, face off against menacing and weird baddies and engage in a fun and quirky turn-based combat system.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Enviro_opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/><strong>A home-cooked battle system</strong><br/>Born of Bread puts a twist on turn-based combat tropes with a fun interaction system that will test your reflexes.<br/>This interactive system also features a weaknesss and resistance system that makes battles more strategic.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Combat_Opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/><strong>Team up with your buddies</strong><br/>Loaf can't do it alone. Meet new characters during your adventure, each with their own abilities and personnality. Use their unique skills to overcome threats and obstacles whether in fights or when exploring.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Buddies_opti.gif?t=1701871457"><br/><br/><strong>Stream your fights to a fake audience!</strong><br/>Your dragon buddy Dub will let you save your progression but also stream your fights to a fake audience with his little laptop! Gather more viewers and answer their demand to get rewards!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>While the Iron's Hot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1906830/While_the_Irons_Hot/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/WTIH_Steam_Banner_Game_Header__1_.png?t=1701795624"><br/><br/>In the faraway land of Ellian, legendary artisans have gathered for ages to perfect their craft. Now it’s your turn to join them.<br/><br/>Step into the boots of a journeyman blacksmith on a quest to become a master in While the Iron’s Hot, a crafty adventure assembled with mystery, wit, and charm. Forge, smelt, and combine works of metal to grow your smithing skills and discover exquisite new items to create. Explore an island filled with resources, treasures, puzzles, and fellow artisans with their own motives and designs. Rebuild the ruins of Ellian’s long-abandoned blacksmiths’ village to restore its former glory and grow your own crafting capabilities—and ultimately become a true master smith.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/Village_Upgrade_Gif_-_640x360.gif?t=1701795624"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/WTIH_Steam_Banner_Features__1_.png?t=1701795624"><br/><br/><strong>Forge, smelt, assemble</strong><br/>Master every step of the smithing process. Smelt ore and metal into ingots, and shape them into useful parts. Grind each piece to perfection, then use your creativity, knowledge, and finely honed observation skills to assemble alloyed works of art.<br/><br/><strong>Smith a solution</strong><br/>In a land of artisans, you can forge your own key to almost any challenge. Repair machinery to open up pathways. Overcome puzzling environmental conundrums. Win over the isle’s most hardened personalities with your crafty smithing wiles.<br/><br/><strong>Unearth a whimsical adventure</strong><br/>The land of Ellian is a bright, even a little mystical, world populated by charismatic and quirky characters. Explore tunnels with puzzles and resources, and embark on a combat-free journey to reforge the links of a world where crafting connects everything.<br/><br/><strong>Discover the island’s secrets</strong><br/>Ellian is a land of creativity cloaked in mystery. Craft the equipment you need to venture out to new regions. Meet villages full of adept alchemists or skilled shipwrights, but take care—not everyone trusts that you have the best interests of Ellian at heart.<br/><br/><strong>Rebuild a legendary smiths’ village</strong><br/>Forge a new home in Stal, a former haven for blacksmiths, now in ruin following a mysterious disaster. Revitalize the village to upgrade your own capabilities, and prove to the artisans of Ellian you’re worthy of becoming a master blacksmith.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/Environment_Gif_-_634x356.gif?t=1701795624"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood West</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_steam_text_header.png?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>Weird West legends meet eldritch horror in <strong>BLOOD WEST</strong>, an immersive stealth FPS. Become the Undead Gunslinger, doomed to roam the barren lands until he finds the means to purge their curse and free his soul. No, this isn’t your typical Wild West desperado redemption arc. This is a damnation arc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_episodes_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The Canyons, the Swamp, and the Mountains. Each swarming with abominable monsters and unholy demons, these are open-ended worlds for you to explore freely at your own pace. It will take the player over 20 hours on average to complete all three scenarios, and over 35 if they want to see everything the barren lands have to offer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_stealth_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/><strong>Blood West</strong> is a stealth FPS inspired by the genre classics such as the Thief series (whose fans will be happy to hear the voice of Stephen Russell, the actor voicing the master-thief Garrett, returning here as the protagonist), S.T.A.L.K.E.R. games, or - from the contemporary catalog - Hunt: Showdown. The gameplay rewards the careful approach: scouting the area, stalking your enemies, and striking from the shadows. Can you figure out a way to clear a fort full of ghouls and monsters without raising an alarm?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_horror_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The Barren Lands present the player with a nightmarish, twisted vision of the Wild West legends. The curse that has befallen the realm has corrupted every living thing, defiled the land itself, while summoning restless spirits and dark entities. In this mixture of gunslinger pulp and Lovecraftian horror, dark occult magick presents just as much of a threat as sudden lead poisoning.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_characters_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>In <strong>Blood West</strong> you will meet many colorful, yet strangely twisted, fully-voiced NPCs. Just as much prisoners of the Barren Lands as you are, they will sometimes share their unusual stories and send you on various missions. Play nice and they might reward you or become your allies. Cross them and risk their wrath.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_secrets_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The game won’t hold your hand. You’ll have to explore the land for yourself (buying a map from a vendor might prove useful!), and figure out your own way to approach quests. As you poke around the three expansive maps, keep an eye out for hidden places and secret stashes. There’s gold in the mountains! Fair warning - it’s probably cursed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_brutal_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>If sneaking around isn’t exactly your thing, or you feel that you have a power advantage over your enemies, you can always take the head-on approach and meet your enemies guns blazing. <strong>Blood West</strong> comes from the creators of the fan-favorite boomer shooter <strong>POSTAL: Brain Damaged</strong>, so much gratuitous fantasy violence and pixelated blood splatter is to be expected!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_inventory_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>One man’s hell might be another hoarder’s paradise! From simple one-use items like bandages, through medical tinctures, explosives and incendiaries, straight to arcane artifacts that - once slotted - can change the way you play the game, the Barren Lands are just filled with STUFF. There are tons of useful items to discover, and there’s a special player’s stash crate for all those super-rare potions that you’ll hoard and never use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_weapons_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>A gunslinger without a gun would be just a regular slinger. Where’s the fun in that? <strong>Blood West</strong> makes sure you’ll have plenty of weapons to choose from. Revolvers, rifles, shotguns, carabines - a great variety of firearms, from standard army-issue to those infused with powerful magic, or straight-up possessed. And if you prefer not to cause a ruckus, there’s a wide selection of hand-to-hand combat weapons and archery weapons to pick your favorites from.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_skills_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The RPG-like perk-based progression system in <strong>Blood West</strong> will allow you to highly customize the gameplay experience to your liking. Become a stealthy hunter, a revolver-fanning gunman or a relentless berserker. You will gain experience and progress through the skill tree, while discovering new artifacts in each of the scenarios that will bestow on you additional abilities. Combining skills and load-out creates more possible playstyles than you’d normally be able to explore in one playthrough.<h2 class="bb_tag">Are you ready to take back the frontier from the dark forces of demonic corruption and earn the right to move on to a better world? The Barren Lands call you, Gunslinger!</h2><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley: A Rift in Time</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2632050/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley_A_Rift_in_Time/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Once an ancient kingdom full of treasures and magical artifacts, Eternity Isle has become lost in time as a result of Jafar’s meddling in magic. Journey to this faraway land and utilize a mysterious new Royal Tool—the Hourglass—as you discover new secrets and uncover lost treasures. Stop Jafar’s scheme to steal the Spark of Imagination, an ancient relic that holds the fabric of Dreamlight Valley together. With the help of the Hourglass, you are the key to fixing rifts in time and putting an end to Jafar’s evil plan!<br/><br/><strong>Unravel a Whole New Story on Eternity Isle</strong><br/>Help foil the plans of the nefarious Jafar as you meet new friends and find treasures lost in time in a new story unfolding in three acts. Secrets from Dreamlight Valley’s past can be uncovered using a new Royal Tool, the Hourglass, as you reveal what happened long before the Forgetting…<br/><br/><strong>Discover a New Island </strong><br/>Delve into three new Biomes, each with new areas to explore and make your own. From Ancient’s Landing to the Glittering Dunes and the Wild Tangle, each has a fully customizable layout to decorate with lost treasures and exclusive Disney- and Pixar-inspired furniture.<br/><br/><strong>Spend Time with Four New Villagers</strong><br/>Reunite EVE with WALL·E, help Rapunzel start an art class, take lessons in heroics from Gaston, and decide if you can really trust Jafar. Explore Eternity Isle with your new friends… or move them back to live in Dreamlight Valley!<br/><br/>Play Scramblecoin, a new board game that your Villagers are waiting to play with you.<br/><br/><strong>Wield the Royal Hourglass</strong><br/>Find a new Royal Tool, the Hourglass, and use its magic to find Relics lost in time. Build Ancient Machines to help automate Activities such as gardening and cooking, which makes it easier than ever to run your island. Take your new Hourglass back to Dreamlight Valley and explore the Realms to see what other treasures you can find!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1701702754"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1701702754"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1701702754"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1701865363"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1701865363"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SteamWorld Build</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2134770/SteamWorld_Build/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-Homestead.png?t=1701599791"><br/>One final landrush! The planet is dyin', Astrid, and it's dig or die trying! <br/><br/>That mine under our town is sitting empty, and wouldn't you know there's rumours of ancient tech down there that might help us out of this predicament. Round up the posse, circle the wagons, and let's get to buildin' a new home! Collect resources above ground and ores down below so we can get those wealthy bots in here to help us build bigger, and we can get the heck out of here!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_1.gif?t=1701599791"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_manage.png?t=1701599791"><br/>As your borders expand, new steamfolk will find their way to you! Every bot is crotchety in their own way, and it's up to you to keep them steaming along. Barter to boost efficiency, keep goods flowing to and from the mines and keep everyone happy to make them work their darndest and hardest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_2.gif?t=1701599791"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-DIG-DEEP.png?t=1701599791"><br/><br/>Stare into the abyss long enough and it might just stare back... we're going looking for riches and something down there doesn't want to share! Have gun, dig gravel, and make sure the mines don't collapse upon you as you defend yourselves from the creepy crawlies that lurk within...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_3.gif?t=1701599791"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_features.png?t=1701599791"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break ground on a bustling SteamWorld town, inspired by the Old West.<br/></li><li>Keep your steambots from getting cranky by ensuring their complex needs get met<br/></li><li>Dig deep and spread wide to produce resources to aid your search for ancient technologies<br/></li><li>Defend your mine from the creepy varmints that lurk deep below your town<br/></li><li>Trade resources at the local train stop and welcome special visitors who'll lend a hand<br/></li><li>Five distinct maps littered with secrets for the discerning SteamWorld explorer to find<br/></li><li>Developed from the ground up for both mouse and controller, whichever takes yer fancy.<br/></li><li>Four difficulty levels, including a sandbox difficulty for when you just want to Build!</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalypse Party</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2351560/Apocalypse_Party/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">The moment of "Apocalypse" approaches, this time... ...you fight for yourself!</h2><br/><strong>「Apocalypse Party」</strong> is distinct from the former 「Project Zero」<br/>In this installment, you will delve deeper into this long-standing battle, with the story gradually becoming incredible! Time travel? Apocalypse? Saving the world? You will face many more unknown challenges... ...<br/>But it still retains our beloved RogueLike + mowing-down-enemies combo, and you will face this catastrophe online with your friends (of course, you can also face it alone)!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Engaging and Deep Mechanics ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT01_Skills_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/><strong>Talent pool expanded to 450! And most of them are mechanics that can change the course of battle</strong><br/>Additionally, there are:<br/>- Hundreds of distinct ranged and melee weapons!<br/>- A plethora of divine ultimate skills!<br/>- 35 varied hero characters, hundreds of unique hero skills<br/>The richness has increased by <strong>more than 10 times compared to the former installment</strong>! Can you build the strongest combo?<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Supports Multiplayer, shall we join the hunting party tonight? ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT02_MutiplePlayerMode_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>Support <strong>up to 3</strong> multiplayer online! <br/>Massive hordes of zombies, exhilarating mowing-down action, why enjoy it alone?<br/>Imagine the joy of roaming through a sea of zombies with your friends!<br/>Call them, support each other, move forward or retreat together, survive here!<br/><strong>Of course, we kindly remind you, a "friendship-ends" scenario is not excluded :)</strong><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ You crave some real challenge, don't you? ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT04_Boss_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>In this game, you will face the ultimate challenge.<br/><strong>9 highly challenging Bosses!</strong><br/>Only rapid growth can help you withstand the fierce attacks from the Bosses, accept the challenge, defeat them, and show them who’s boss now!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Perhaps we can do some time traveling! ■</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT05_Medivel_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>A brand new storyline takes you into this familiar yet strange world, continuing a tale of redemption amidst time traveling:<br/>The tragic death of loved ones<br/>The desperate nuclear explosion<br/>The eerie rebirth<br/>The deathly quiet town<br/>The dark dungeons<br/>... ...<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ We are continuously focusing on your gameplay experience! ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT03_Combat_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>We have keenly listened to the feedback from the players of our former installment, reworked the combat system of the game, continuously bringing more fluid gaming experiences to players.<br/>-<i>Mix and use combat methods like melee weapons, firearms, spells, summoning, witchcraft... ...</i>! They will bring you a fun experience.<br/>-<i>Drive vehicles, summon planes, dragon flying, use otherworldly ninjutsu, even use the mysterious Dual-vector Foi</i>, and more easter eggs await your exploration.<br/>-This game encourages an online experience, but undoubtedly, the single-player part can still experience all the systems and joy of this game.<br/><br/>Smooth operation (handling) is also an important part we continuously focus on！<br/>We have made the game’s operation &amp; flow experience more user-friendly.<br/><strong>Easy to get started, yet "easy to learn, hard to master"!</strong><br/><br/><strong>"Since the apocalypse is here, join us for the last revelry."</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/Library_Hero_EN.jpg?t=1701678706"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-4 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">4-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with three other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1701703276"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinball M</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2337640/Pinball_M/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-1.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-2.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free<br/>- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage<br/>- Thrilling competition<br/>- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation<h2 class="bb_tag">Sink your teeth into these tables as purchasable DLC: </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">- Chucky's Killer Pinball:</h2> Step into a twisted realm where the innocent becomes sinister, and the playful turns menacing. Navigate through an eerie playfield where Chucky lurks in the shadows, ready to pounce.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Dead by Daylight™️ Pinball:</h2> Become the hunter or even the hunted in a thrilling fusion of classic pinball and the excitement of one of the most popular horror games ever created.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Duke Nukem's Big Shot Pinball:</h2> Enjoy the biggest, grooviest, most BADASS pinball table ever made packed with guns and babes. Push start and play with balls of steel!<h2 class="bb_tag">- The Thing Pinball: </h2>Use your pinball skills and battle against the shape-shifting alien through the arctic chill of U.S. Outpost #31. Can you trust anyone, even yourself?<br/>- Even more coming...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-4.png?t=1701703297"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn back immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Option</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.<br/>If you are easily intoxicated, changing the following settings may help.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera shake】</strong><br/>The camera shakes when you walk or run, but if you set the value to 0.0, the camera will not shake.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Acceleration】</strong><br/>If you set the maximum value to 30.0, the camera will move without delay.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Sensitivity】</strong><br/>If the sensitivity is high, the camera will move significantly when the mouse is moved. <br/>Adjust the value if you find it difficult to operate the camera with the default value of 1.<br/><br/><strong>【Motion Blur】</strong><br/>Afterimages will appear when the camera is moved. Recommended to disable at 30FPS<br/><br/><strong>【Preset】</strong><br/>Set the overall graphic settings.<br/>If you do not have sufficient specs, it is better to set it to "Low" to avoid sickness.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1701853441"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1701853441"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1701853441"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats and Seek</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2672090/Cats_and_Seek/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							😻 100 Cats!<br/>🔍 Hint system<br/>🎨 Choose your favorite color<br/><br/>Let's play hide and seek with 100 cats!<br/>Can you find them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/extras/game_play.gif?t=1701587609"><br/><br/>And if bored with black and white doddles you can choose <strong>your own favorite color</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/extras/change_color.PNG?t=1701587609"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header_alt_assets_2.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1701808865"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1701948634"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1701948634"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1701948634"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658820/Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							10 possible fruits and one goal, reach the Watermelon.<br/>Your job is to combine matching fruits to evolve them to the next one and eventually reach the coveted Watermelon.<br/>To help you, you have 3 different abilities at your disposal. But watch out, using these will cost you some of your points. Be smart about when you use them to get the highest score!<h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLAYER</h2>Measure your fruit skills against another player.<h2 class="bb_tag">GET THE WATERMELON</h2>How many Watermelons can you combine before your basket overflows?<h2 class="bb_tag">USE YOUR ABILITIES</h2>Power, level up and destroy — These abilities will help you reach the Watermelon, using any of those will also allow you to angle your aim.<h2 class="bb_tag">GOLDEN FRUIT</h2>If luck is on your side, you might even see the mysterious Golden Fruit. Find it and witness its effect firsthand.<h2 class="bb_tag">STATISTICS</h2>Track your progress with in-depth statistics. Visit the menu to see the number of fruits you've combined, your ability usage, and much more.<h2 class="bb_tag"></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.codecks.io%2Fwatermelon-game" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/extras/Roadmap_Banner.png?t=1701768047"/></a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football Manager 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2252570/Football_Manager_2024/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2252570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a real boss and write your own football story in Football Manager 2024, the most complete edition in the series yet. <br/><br/>Whether you’re a manager who likes to build from the bottom or prefers to chase immediate glory, the perfect challenge awaits. The arrival of the new Meiji Yasuda Insurance Ltd J. League licence unlocks J1 League, J2 League, J3 League for the first time ever, giving you the opportunity to explore new horizons in Japan.<br/><br/>Wherever you manage, it's up to you to build a team capable of competing with the world's elite.<br/><br/><strong>Game Description </strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Continue your relentless journey to the top of the footballing world by using the new ability to import your existing career from Football Manager 2023.<br/></li><li>Craft a winning tactical approach, incorporating modern football’s most popular systems and cutting-edge positional innovations to deliver victories on the pitch. <br/></li><li>Master the transfer market, using new ways to shape your side to cultivate a squad capable of achieving your goals. <br/></li><li>Level up your players on the training field, developing the mentality and teamwork needed to transform contenders into champions. <br/></li><li>See your tactical vision come to life on Matchdays, with every game elevated by improvements to ball and player movements.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">NEW FOR THIS SEASON</h2><br/><br/><strong>TRUER FOOTBALL MOTION</strong><br/><br/>Enhancements to player animations, ball physics and lighting deliver the most immersive Match Engine in Football Manager history. Move to the cutting edge of football by using the new Inverted Full-Back player role, while more intelligent player rotational movements add more fluidity to every highlight. <br/><br/><strong>DOMINATE FROM SET PIECES</strong><br/><br/>Make an impact at both ends of the pitch with an overhauled Set Piece Creator. Lean on the expertise of brand-new Set Piece Coaches to develop winning routines in every scenario that will help you to outsmart your rivals. <br/><br/><strong>BRACE FOR TRANSFER BATTLES</strong><br/><br/>Showcase your squad-building skills in our most refined transfer market yet. You’ll face a trickier battle for talent as your rival opposition managers are now more strategic than ever in their recruitment decision-making. <br/><br/><strong>NEW AGENTS TO BUILD A DREAM SQUAD</strong><br/><br/>Better shape your perfect squad with the introduction of new Intermediaries that will help you offload surplus players for a cut of the final transfer fee. Additional functionality for existing Agents and the debut of TransferRoom, a football marketplace for transfers in real life, gives you more real-world powered tools than ever to build an elite team and dominate the competition.<br/><br/><strong>ELEVATE PERFORMANCES WITH TARGETS</strong><br/><br/>Motivate your team to achieve more on and off the field by setting them individual Targets. Whether you’re focusing on goals scored in a season or average training performances, challenge your star players and top prospects to maximise their ability. <br/><br/><strong>A HOST MORE ADDITIONS</strong><br/><br/>Enjoy greater variety in every career with the arrival of two new game modes. Real World mirrors when players actually joined your club. Your World sets club squads and budgets at the day your career starts, meaning that only players who joined before that date will be in your squad, giving you the opportunity to rewrite your team’s transfer window.<br/><br/>Elsewhere, you can look to dominate international management and plan for your country's future with a revamped National Pool that gives you a better overview of the talent at your disposal. Match preparation and briefing meetings deliver you winning insights before each fixture. <br/><br/>That’s not all though, with many more changes waiting for you to discover in every career.<br/><br/><i>This version contains information that is still under approval process by rights holders and may contain data that does not, at this time, accurately reflect real world data. For context, some club and player assets may be absent during this version.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nessy The ... Robot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2250530/Nessy_The__Robot/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2250530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2250530/extras/xLLf+L.gif?t=1701998406"><br/><br/><strong>Nessy The Robot</strong> is a platformer game designed for the 8bit generation. Where you play as Nessy, a little controller-themed robot, on a quest to stop his home, Pixel Park, from total destruction.<br/><br/>Fight your way through zombified robots, slime creatures, and a multitude of other enemies &amp; bosses, as well as a plethora of levels, secrets &amp; easter eggs to discover, collectible gems to... well... collect, as well as characters &amp; dogs to talk to.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>6+ worlds/courses to explore<br/></li><li>Multiple secrets to discover<br/></li><li>Unique &amp; interesting enemies<br/></li><li>Collectibles<br/></li><li>Cutscenes<br/></li><li>Memorable characters</li></ul><br/>=======================================						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runemancer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2603590/Runemancer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2603590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In Runemancer you play the vital role of a healer, the cornerstone of any adventurer group. Your mission is to support your allies by skillfully combining runes to amplify their abilities.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2603590/extras/gameplay-1.gif?t=1701994654"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><br/><i>Empower Your Allies</i>: As the healer, your expertise lies in combining runes to enhance your comrades' capabilities. Turn the tide of battle by strategically boosting their strength and ensuring their survival.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2603590/extras/gameplay-3.gif?t=1701994654"><br/><br/><i>Choose Your Path</i>: You have the opportunity to select new abilities as you progress through the game. Your choices are crucial, shaping your character's development and determining your party's destiny. Pick your abilities wisely based on the unique build you envision for your team.<br/><br/><i>Wave-Based Challenges</i>: Runemancer offers an exciting wave-based gameplay experience, with each stage presenting distinct challenges. Face off against hordes of formidable enemies and adapt your strategies as you progress through the game's dynamic stages.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2603590/extras/gameplay-2.gif?t=1701994654"><br/><br/>Prepare to embark on an epic adventure as the healer in Runemancer. Your decisions will be the key to success as you empower your allies and guide them to victory in this thrilling wave-based RPG.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stacks:Jungle!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2522060/StacksJungle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2522060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Stacks:Jungle is an adventure card game set in the lush heart of the jungle. Get ready to embark on an unforgettable journey filled with crafting, quests, and exploration! Unlock new cards with booster packs, combine them to uncover craft recipes, build amazing structures, gather loyal companions, try delicious exotic food, venture into uncharted territories, make new friends, discover hidden treasures, and so much more.<br/><br/>DISCLAIMER: This game is inspired by Stacklands, but it is not Stacklands, and it is not a sequel to Stacklands. It is a completely independent project that feels and plays differently in many ways. Please use the Steam discussion forums if you notice any issues with the game or the included localizations.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>    Immerse yourself in a beautiful and magical jungle environment, where adventure and exciting quests await, all through the power of cards!<br/></li><li>    Powered by the Stacks: Engine, a card game framework heavily inspired by the renowned Stacklands game.<br/></li><li>    Collect, create, and use over 150 unique cards.<br/></li><li>    Learn and master 70+ craft recipes creating game-changing strategies.<br/></li><li>    Explore 22 breathtaking locations filled with mysteries and secrets waiting to be uncovered.<br/></li><li>    Take on over 200 tasks and quests, testing your skills and unraveling the jungle's mysterious lore.<br/></li><li>    Experience a lightweight survival aspect with the hunger mechanic, adding an extra layer of challenge to your adventure.<br/></li><li>    Choose from three captivating scenarios: go on a treasure hunt, master the art of fishing, or indulge in the beauty of butterfly collecting.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idle Cave Miner</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2289450/Idle_Cave_Miner/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2289450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Idle Cave Miner is an idle game about crafting items, mining gems, and building your team of miners. Tap to mine gold, diamonds, and other resources in a completely destructible, interactive mine. Assemble your team of miners to try to reach as deep as possible, find the best combination using each miner's strengths and abilities as a starting point for your strategy. Prestige, craft, and travel to other mines to increase your strength to dig deeper, and find what lurks below.<br/><br/><strong>IDLE CAVE MINER FEATURES:</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Smelt, Craft, and Refine Ores:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Craft cool new Items to mine deeper than ever and find new rare ores and gems!<br/></li><li> Upgrade your forges to increase their speed and efficiency when smelting rare ores or refining beautiful gems!<br/></li><li> Use the items you crafted to permanently boost the stats of your team of miners!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Build your own team of Miners:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Unlock cool and unique new miners to mine for you and help you progress deep within the mines!<br/></li><li> Upgrade your miners with items you crafted to take them to the next level of mining efficiency!<br/></li><li> Idle away as your miners work for you, giving you profits you've never seen before!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple Mines:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The mine upgrades with you, the further down you go, the more the mine shifts to accommodate new unique and fun environments!<br/></li><li> Unique mines to explore, each with their own resources for you to obtain, whether those are rare ores to be smelted or unique gems to be refined!<br/></li><li> Farm these mines to get resources to become stronger than ever and progress in the main mine, giving you access to new and interesting new ores and gems!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Endless upgrades:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Upgrade everything about your favorite miners, building an increasingly strong team to progress further than you've gone before!<br/></li><li> Prestige to receive powerful rewards that allow you to go deeper than ever into the unknown depths of the mines!<br/></li><li> Gather permanent upgrades that remain with you when you prestige, allowing you to breeze through what was previously impossible!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Lots of missions and achievements:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Complete fun achievements to unlock cool rewards!<br/></li><li> Participate in daily, weekly and monthly missions that give you increased rewards based on their difficulty level!<br/></li><li> Check your game's stats at any moment to view your overall progress and other fun statistics!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Other cool features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Cloud Saves!<br/></li><li> Online Leaderboards!<br/></li><li> Play Offline!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Touhou Meijinka ~ Song of Divine Tempest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2630380/Touhou_Meijinka__Song_of_Divine_Tempest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2630380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							It is raining and pouring. It's not your average thunderstorm, but a primordial one. This storm doesn't seem to stop. At the same time, the storm is also producing gospel chanting, leading to people being attracted to the concert. The Land of Illusions ends up becoming empty, giving the local bands no opportunity to perform for their people.<br/><br/>Based on an original screenplay by Emiko Hosokawa, you take control of one of four humanoids to set out and find the source of the concert. Originally based on a fangame album featuring an original score by <i>Chuhou Joutai</i> creator Susumu Takajima, you must traverse six stages of varying terrain to find the concert's mastermind. Whether you're alone or with a friend*, your own danmaku is imperative. This will not be an easy journey - you must dodge your enemies' danmaku and overcome their spell cards.<br/><br/>*Additional accessories may be required for local multiplayer modes.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Four playable characters spanning different backgrounds<br/></li><li>Four difficulty modes with different spell cards<br/></li><li>A six-stage main game plus a post-game extra stage<br/></li><li>A series of original characters created by Susumu Takajima and Emiko Hosokawa to fight against<br/></li><li>1990s-style musical score by Susumu Takajima<br/></li><li>Controller support<br/></li><li>Co-op mode</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sona-Nyl of the Violet Shadows Refrain</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2656690/SonaNyl_of_the_Violet_Shadows_Refrain/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The 5th entry in Liarsoft's Steampunk Series is a mysterious fairytale in which fantasy and reality intertwine.<br/><i>*This is the PC port of the Xbox360/PSP Refrain release upscaled to 1280 x 720.</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2><br/>The year is 1907. The 20th century is still young.<br/><br/>This is a world that experienced a 19th century very different from our own. A world of innumerable steam-powered Engines. The unnaturally rapid development of this steam civilization filled the air with smog, robbing humanity of the blue skies they'd once known.<br/><br/>There is one place in particular where the sky is darker than anywhere else: the ruins of the Engine city New York, perpetually shrouded in grey clouds and polluted rain. Five years ago, a mysterious disaster known as the "Great Disappearance" reduced this entire metropolis to a deserted, crumbling wasteland. Sealed off from the world by the United States government, it stands in utter silence. Not a single soul now walks its streets.<br/><br/>But today, a woman named Elysia quietly sets foot inside it - guided by a singular purpose. Her destination: old Manhattan, said to be the epicenter of the catastrophe.<br/><br/>Unbeknownst to her...<br/><br/>There is a place said to be the city's "Underground." This is an enormous subterranean realm, permeated with a dim purple light. No one on the surface world knows of its existence. In this place, the Skyscrapers that crumbled five years ago still stand tall; but their forms are warped and twisted.<br/><br/>"Underground New York" is a place of black and violet shadows. A prison with no exit. And beneath its unnatural "sky," the men and women who vanished five years ago still exist...<br/>	Cowering in fear of the seven monsters known as the "Messengers."<br/>	Suffering terror, agony, and death at the hands of the "Messengers."<br/>They linger on in this twisted underground city, as if waiting for something.<br/><br/>A girl named Lily sets foot in this place, her mind devoid of memories. There is only one thing she's certain of.She doesn't have a reason. She doesn't know who or what awaits her. She doesn't even know why she feels this way. But even so, she's absolutely certain.<br/><br/>	"Manhattan. The ends of the violet sky."<br/>	"I have to go there. I'm the only one who can."<br/><br/>─The girl sets off for the tower of violet shadow looming far in the distance.<br/>─With every step, she finds the shades of those yet to fade away.<br/>─And sheds tears without knowing why.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>- Visual Novel with a mix of fantasy and the historical real world.<br/><br/>- Vividely drawn CGs to explore!<br/>- 25 hours of average reading time.<br/>- Developed by Liar-soft, acclaimed for their Steampunk series!<br/>- Written and directed by Hikaru Sakurai						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bugs N' Guns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2648130/Bugs_N_Guns/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2648130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bugs N' Guns is a cooperative third person shooter.  Players take the role of Bugs and Guns two employees working as trash disposal for the crappiest company in the world.  Tasked with finding and escorting a "cargo" train named MARC - OS that was lost in an alien environment players will need to work together to survive the hostile flora and fauna that will impede their path.<br>
<br>
COOPERATIVE<br>
<br>
The most important feature in Bugs N´ Guns is that this game requires two people to play.  Not only is it impossible to play without another player but within the game all the challenges players will face require cooperation otherwise, defeat is assured.<br>
<br>
ONLINE- LAN<br/>
<br/>
In order to play this game players require an internet connection.  Once inside the game player may choose to play either on LAN or by choosing to play with random people on a public match or playing with friends through private matchmaking.<br/>
<br/>
SHOOT AND COMBINE<br/>
<br/>
The main way players interact with the world of Bugs N´ Guns is through shooting.  Shoot to protect, kill, and cooperate.  That is correct in this game players can generate elemental effects with their weapons and these elemental effects can combine with the weapons of the other player providing players with more fire power when they choose to work together.<br/>
<br/>
PROTECT THE TRAIN<br/>
<br/>
The main goal in this game is to escort the train M.A.R.C - OS.  Through out the game the train will guide players through a series of crazy scenarios forcing the players to adapt or die.  The most important thing to understand is that players can die all the times they want, but if the train dies, the game is over.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silence Channel 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2145220/Silence_Channel_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2145220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>We always search for truth while awake, but truth can be found in our nightmares…</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2145220/extras/SL2_Details_Img2.jpg?t=1701980320"><br/>Woke up to a strange sound and opened my eyes. Sitting in my bed, confused and shocked, I looked at the partly open door. Someone with strange eyes was staring at me through the door, suddenly the door closed! I came to and realized that someone had sneaked into my house. All I could think of at that moment was to call the police, that is, if everything is in its place. Am I to try this maze on my own or will someone help me out?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2145220/extras/SL2_Gif04.gif?t=1701980320"><br/>Silence Channel is a series of <strong>Psychological Horror</strong> video games based on true stories, each episode of which tells its own unique story and character development. In Silence Channel 2, players need to solve puzzles, hide from enemies, find hidden items, and even fight with strange creatures in order to unravel the story and escape from the environments they are trapped in.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2145220/extras/SL2_Gif03.gif?t=1701980320"><br/>The story of this episode is also based on a true story. At the beginning of the game, we are introduced to an unknown character who witnesses strange and supernatural events in her house and does everything she can to escape from it. Then we hear a phone call report from a woman to the police stating that someone has entered her house and she needs help. At this time, an officer named John Martin, who is the closest patrol officer to the house, is dispatched to investigate the scene, and a new story begins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2145220/extras/SL2_Gif02.gif?t=1701980320"><br/>The Silence Channel 2 will be available on 7th December 2023​. You can follow us on Instagram and X for more details (@LexipGames​)<br/><br/>Features :<br/>• Try to find the way out<br/>• Pass through strange and dark places<br/>• Discover story of the game<br/>• Generated Events <br/>• Randomly Elements<br/>• Realistic Graphics<br/>• Different Puzzles<br/>• Hide and Sneak						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Momon: Relic Seekers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2409540/Momon_Relic_Seekers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2409540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Tsuki's world is falling apart due to an event caused by Amaterasuna's corruption and only the relics are capable of recovering it. Help Tsuki recover the relics that were scattered across different worlds populated by monsters and evil creatures.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Build your deck:</strong> Combine cards with different elements and characteristics to create your combos and get the best result.<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with cards:</strong> Fight against monsters from different worlds using magic cards with different abilities.<br/></li><li><strong>Collect the Relics: </strong> Explore six diverse worlds with procedural generation elements to collect the relics that have been scattered.<br/></li><li><strong>Momons:</strong> Discover and collect new momons, cute magical creatures that help Tsuki on her journey with their magical abilities.<br/></li><li><strong>Discover:</strong> Decide your route with each journey, discover new momons, cards and events that can bring benefits, collectibles or harm your journey.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slam Dunk Basketball</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693680/Slam_Dunk_Basketball/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Elevate your virtual basketball experience to new heights with Slam Dunk Basketball, the game that takes control to the next level! Strap on your virtual sneakers and immerse yourself in the action like never before, enhanced by the groundbreaking Perspectacles head tracking glasses.<br>
<br>
🏀 Precision Player Control Take charge of every steal, dodge, and dunk with unparalleled precision. Slam Dunk Basketball puts you in the driver's seat, allowing you to navigate the court with skill and finesse, making split-second decisions that can turn the tide of the game.<br>
<br>
🕶️ Perspectacles Integration Step into a new dimension of gaming with Perspectacles. These cutting-edge glasses synchronize seamlessly with your movements, enhancing your PC screen with dynamic 3D stereo views based on your real-time viewpoint. The court comes alive as you move, providing an immersive experience that blurs the line between reality and virtual hoops.<br>
<br>
👀 Dynamic Views Immerse yourself in the heart of the action with Perspectacles. As you track the ball, dodge opponents, and execute jaw-dropping dunks, the game adapts to your perspective, creating an engaging and lifelike visual experience that mirrors your every move.<br>
<br>
🔒 Strategic Gameplay Outsmart your opponents with strategic moves, steal the ball with precision, and master the art of dunking in style. Slam Dunk Basketball challenges you to be not just a player but a strategic tactician on the court.<br>
<br/>
🏆 Customization and Progression Personalize your player, choose your team colors, and unlock a variety of skills and dunks as you progress through the game. Rise through the ranks and showcase your unique style on the virtual court.<br/>
<br/>
Experience the future of virtual sports with Slam Dunk Basketball and Perspectacles. It's not just a game; it's a groundbreaking fusion of cutting-edge technology and basketball excitement that puts you at the center of the action. Lace up, put on your Perspectacles, and redefine the way you play virtual hoops!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape Tunnel</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2663310/Shape_Tunnel/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2663310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Welcome to Shape Tunnel: A Dimensional Challenge!</strong><br/>Prepare yourself for a mind-bending journey through twisting tunnels and geometric puzzles. In Shape Tunnel, you control a shape hurtling down an endless, ever-changing tunnel. Your mission? Match your shape to the constantly evolving tunnel geometry by deftly rotating the shapes in your path. Precision and quick thinking are your best allies - mismatch and it’s game over!<br/><br/>Features:<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">🌀 Shape-Matching Madness:</h2></strong> Rotate and maneuver your shape to perfectly align with the tunnel. Every twist and turn demands split-second decisions. Can you keep up with the ever-shifting geometry?<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">💎 Collect Diamonds:</h2></strong> Amidst the challenge, collect dazzling diamonds strewn throughout the tunnel.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">🔮 Infinite Levels:</h2></strong> With procedurally generated tunnels, your journey is never the same twice. Each level presents a new challenge, ensuring that your skills are continuously put to the test. How far can you go?<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">🕶️ Perspectacles Compatibility:</h2></strong> Shape Tunnel is designed for an immersive experience with Perspectacles, the cutting-edge head tracking 3D glasses. Feel the thrill of the tunnel's twists and turns in stunning three-dimensional reality. The shapes come to life, and so does the challenge!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">🎉 Endless Adventure:</h2></strong> There's no limit to your adventure! Shape Tunnel offers infinite gameplay, ensuring that your pursuit of the perfect match never ends. How long can you keep the streak alive?<br/><br/>Dive into the depths of Shape Tunnel, where reflexes meet geometry, and every move counts. Can you conquer the ever-changing shapes, collect the diamonds, and navigate the tunnel's twists and turns? It’s time to find out!<br/><br/>Shape Tunnel: Match, Rotate, Conquer.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infinity Sky</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2671790/Infinity_Sky/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for an adrenaline-pumping aerial adventure in "Infinity Sky," the ultimate test of your reflexes and precision! Take control of a high-speed jet soaring through the breathtaking skyline, where towering buildings hurtle towards the screen, challenging your ability to dodge, weave, and survive.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><strong>🔹 Intense Aerial Action: </strong>Strap into your jet and brace yourself for heart-pounding action as skyscrapers approach at breakneck speed. Swiftly maneuver your way through the maze of buildings to stay alive.<br/><br/><strong>🔹 Collect Rings of Fire: </strong>Amidst the chaos, keep your eyes peeled for rings of fire scattered throughout the cityscape. Collect them to score points and prove your mastery of the skies. Every ring brings you one step closer to victory!<br/><br/><strong>🔹 Dynamic Challenges:</strong> As you progress, the game intensifies. Buildings rise and fall, creating ever-changing obstacles that demand lightning-fast reactions. Adapt to the evolving challenges or be left in the dust.<br/><br/><strong>🔹 Infinite Levels: </strong>The sky's the limit! Experience an endless journey where every moment presents a new challenge. How long can you survive in the infinite expanse of the "Infinity Sky"?<br/><br/><strong>🔹 Perspectacles Enhanced:</strong> Immerse yourself fully in the world of "Infinity Sky" with Perspectacles, the groundbreaking 3D webcam tracked glasses. Feel the rush of wind as you dodge buildings, and experience the thrill of collecting rings of fire in a way that blurs the lines between reality and gaming.<br/><br/><strong>🔹 Compete for Glory:</strong> Challenge your friends and players from around the globe in a race for the highest score. Show off your agility and claim your place at the top of the leaderboards.<br/><br/>In "Infinity Sky," the sky is not just the limit; it's your playground. Are you ready to push the boundaries of your piloting skills? Dodge, dive, and collect your way to victory in this high-flying, endlessly challenging adventure! Strap in and take off into the "Infinity Sky" today, enhanced by the immersive power of Perspectacles!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diamond Dash: Plaid Peril</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2671780/Diamond_Dash_Plaid_Peril/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a dizzying adventure high above the city skyline in "Diamond Dash: Plaid Peril," a cutting-edge rolling ball game designed exclusively for use with Perspectacles 3D webcam tracked glasses. Strap in for an exhilarating journey along a twisting path suspended in the air, weaving its way between towering buildings adorned in vibrant yellow and plaid patterns. This unique gameplay experience transcends reality, allowing you to immerse yourself in a visually stunning world where your reflexes and precision will be put to the ultimate test.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><strong>🔸 Plaid Paradise:</strong> Immerse yourself in a world where plaid tracks and buildings create a mesmerizing and challenging environment. The vibrant yellow hues accentuate the perilous path that lies ahead.<br/><br/><strong>🔸 Diamond Hunt:</strong> Collect sparkling diamonds strewn along the path to earn valuable points. Master the art of balance and speed to snatch up as many diamonds as possible while navigating the treacherous twists and turns.<br/><br/><strong>🔸 Leap of Faith:</strong> Take daring leaps from ramp to ramp, defying gravity as you jump between tracks. Execute flawless jumps to avoid slipping off the path – one wrong move, and it's game over!<br/><br/><strong>🔸 Intuitive Controls:</strong> Enjoy smooth and intuitive controls that let you guide your rolling ball with precision. Master the nuances of movement to conquer the intricate plaid tracks.<br/><br/><strong>🔸 Challenging Levels:</strong> Progress through increasingly difficult levels, each designed to push your skills to the limit. Maneuver through complex obstacles, sharp turns, and unexpected traps that will keep you on the edge of your seat.<br/><br/>"Diamond Dash: Plaid Peril" is not just a game; it's a groundbreaking experience enhanced by Perspectacles 3D webcam tracked glasses. Step into the future of gaming, where reality and imagination blend seamlessly. Strap on your Perspectacles, collect those diamonds, and prove that you have what it takes to conquer the perilous plaid path high above the city!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow Strike: Street Combat</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693200/Shadow_Strike_Street_Combat/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the adrenaline-charged world of "Shadow Strike: Street Combat" on the Steam platform! Immerse yourself in the heart-pounding action of this 3D side-scrolling fighting game, where every move counts and every street corner holds a new challenge. Set against the gritty backdrop of an urban landscape, your journey through the mean streets will push your combat skills to the limit.<br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">1. Intense 3D Side-Scrolling Combat:</h2></strong><br/>Engage in dynamic, visually stunning battles that bring the streets to life. Experience the thrill of 3D side-scrolling combat like never before as you face off against formidable opponents in a quest for supremacy.<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">2. Urban Warfare:</h2></strong><br/>Navigate through realistic urban environments. Meticulously designed to provide a unique and challenging combat experience, ensuring that each showdown is different from the last.<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">3. Perspectacles Head Tracking Integration:</h2></strong><br/>Immerse yourself even deeper in the gritty urban combat with seamless integration for Perspectacles head tracking glasses. While the game features side-scrolling action, Perspectacles enhances the visual experience by providing a heightened sense of depth and perspective. Feel the pulse of the city streets as you move your head, allowing for a more immersive and engaging environment. While the traditional side-scrolling format remains, Perspectacles enriches the visual experience, bringing the urban chaos to life in a way that goes beyond conventional gaming visuals.<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">4. Dynamic Combat System:</h2></strong><br/>Master a diverse range of combat techniques, from hand-to-hand brawling to adrenaline-pumping special moves. String together combos and perfect your timing to unleash devastating attacks, leaving your opponents in awe of your martial prowess.<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">5. Customization and Progression:</h2></strong><br/>Choose your fighter with a variety of outfits, and abilities.<br/><br/>Gear up, step into the shadows, and prepare for an unparalleled gaming experience in "Shadow Strike: Street Combat." The streets are unforgiving, but with your skills and the immersive power of Perspectacles, victory is within reach. Are you ready to dominate the urban battleground?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skyline Sprint: Turbo Tracks</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2702810/Skyline_Sprint_Turbo_Tracks/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2702810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Skyline Sprint: Turbo Tracks</h2><br/>Get ready for an adrenaline-pumping, high-speed racing experience in Skyline Sprint: Turbo Tracks! Strap in and take control of your mini car as you navigate through thrilling aerial tracks filled with ramps, twists, and turns.<br/><br/>Race against AI-generated cars in an action-packed journey through the skies, collecting stars to increase your score and unlock different cars for use. Master the art of aerial maneuvers, hitting ramps, catching air, and soaring through the tracks to gain an edge over your opponents.<br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">High-Flying Racing:</h2></strong> Experience heart-pounding races high above ground level on mesmerizing tracks.<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Star Collection:</h2></strong> Gather stars scattered throughout the tracks to boost your score and unlock a variety of different cars for enhanced gameplay.<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Completion:</h2></strong> Finish levels to unlock new tracks and challenges, advancing further in the aerial racing adventure.<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Aerial Stunts:</h2></strong> Perform daring stunts and maneuvers by hitting ramps and soaring through the air.<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Immersive Experience:</h2></strong> For an enhanced experience, Skyline Sprint: Turbo Tracks is configured to seamlessly integrate with Perspectacles head tracking glasses. Immerse yourself fully in the game as Perspectacles elevate the thrill of high-flying racing to new heights, offering an unparalleled level of immersion and control.<br/><br/>Join the competition, master the tracks, and become the ultimate Skyline Sprint: Turbo Tracks champion. Unlock new cars, conquer levels, and soar through the skies in this exhilarating racing adventure!<i><br/>Note: Perspectacles head tracking glasses are recommended for an immersive experience but not required to play the game.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Island Rush</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2663300/Island_Rush/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2663300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Welcome to Island Rush: Surfing Odyssey!</strong><br/>Embark on an exhilarating adventure in Island Rush, where the sun-kissed waves meet the thrill of the unknown! Choose your avatar, either the crafty fox or the majestic moose, and ride the surfboard towards the distant island where your epic journey begins. Experience the rush of the ocean beneath your feet, guiding your chosen character past perilous obstacles to reach the finish line. Time is of the essence - every moment counts, and if you don’t move swiftly, destruction awaits.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">🏄 Choose Your Champion:</h2></strong> Play as a sly fox or a powerful moose.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">🌊 Ride the Waves:</h2></strong> Feel the pulse of the ocean as you navigate towering waves on your surfboard. Your destination? A mysterious island brimming with challenges and treasures, waiting to be discovered.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">🎮 Race Against Time:</h2></strong> The clock is ticking! Navigate your character past treacherous obstacles, outmaneuvering the dangers that lurk beneath the surface. Speed and precision are your best allies - hesitation could lead to disaster.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">🏝️ Explore Multiple Levels:</h2></strong> Dive into the excitement of three thrilling levels in the initial release, each more daring than the last. Conquer obstacles, solve puzzles, and unlock new paths to reach the ultimate goal.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">🕶️ Perspectacles Adventure:</h2></strong> Immerse yourself fully in the Island Rush experience with Perspectacles, the revolutionary head tracking 3D glasses. With Perspectacles, the vibrant world of Island Rush comes to life, offering an unparalleled level of immersion. Feel the rush of the waves and the thrill of the challenge in stunning three-dimensional reality.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">⏳ Stay Tuned for More:</h2></strong> But the adventure doesn’t stop here! Stay tuned for future updates with additional levels and challenges. As a part of the Island Rush family, all extra levels will be yours for free, ensuring the excitement never ends.<br/><br/>Get ready to ride, dodge, and rush your way to victory! The island awaits, and so does the adventure. Are you up for the challenge?<br/><br/>Island Rush: Where Surfing Meets Adventure - Now in Stunning 3D with Perspectacles!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ARMY BASE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2673730/A_ARMY_BASE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is developed and produced by myself, AndyLaw. As a former FLASH game developer, I began learning UNITY after FLASH was phased out. This is my first UNITY game. Therefore, please understand that there are many imperfections and bugs. Treat it as a practice, and I believe the next version will be more polished.<br>
<br>
Game Overview:<br>
This game is a 2D side-scrolling shooter played from a third-person perspective. It allows single-player gameplay with a keyboard and mouse, as well as local multiplayer with up to 4 gamepad players and 1 keyboard and mouse player, making it perfect for family parties. During the game, you can use a radio to call AI-controlled teammates to join your squad. Players can switch control between squad members, who each have customizable appearances, individual equipment systems, and backpacks. Items can be exchanged between team members. The base contains many cabinets for storing various supplies and equipment, and vehicles have trunks for item storage.<br>
<br>
Instead of traditional health bars, human characters in the game have basic needs such as hunger, thirst, fatigue, and sleep. They bleed, get angry, scared, and can self-heal when injured. The physical condition of characters, such as bleeding and injury treatment, is visibly reflected on them, and they become progressively weaker, eventually crawling or fainting. Use bandages to stop bleeding and medicine for recovery, or sleep to regain health. I am thrilled to have finally implemented the ragdoll physics system in Unity, something I always wanted to do in FLASH development.<br>
<br>
Vehicles in the game can be found as transportable wrecks, which can be placed on a vehicle repair station to be fixed and used. Vehicle appearances can be customized, and they come equipped with weapons and a trunk for storing ammunition and other items.<br/>
<br/>
The game eschews the concept of money. Necessary resources are produced at various workbenches in the base, and the types of items that can be produced are researched in the base's research lab. While initially intended to have a sandbox feel, it has been simplified to its current state.<br/>
<br/>
The game's objective is to manage your squad members in the base to produce materials needed for combat, arm yourselves as much as possible, expand your team, and prepare firearms, melee weapons, grenades, armor, backpacks, and vehicles. Stay in good health because, with each night, more and more zombies will attack. You will control your squad to defend and strike out from the base of the A-troop until all are killed in battle. New A-troop soldiers will then arrive by helicopter to take over the base and continue the fight.<br/>
<br/>
For those interested in more customization and modification options, a DLC modifier is available for purchase, offering enhanced customization features for battles.<br/>
<br/>
Enjoy the game!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evotales</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2264390/Evotales/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2264390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							500 million years ago a Cambrian explosion survivor began the rise of mankind<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Evolve and adapt to challenges that will evolve and adapt to you</strong><br/>Start as an early chordate that hides in the mud and jumps to get out of trouble and become a big fish that can put up a fight.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Explore prehistoric environments and meet those who ruled the world before the fishing rod was invented</strong><br/>Use your wits, be precise and reactive to survive among the extraordinary creatures of the past<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Find friends and take a mass extinction survival course</strong><br/>Cambrian volcanic activity, late Ordovician ice age, Devonian toxic ocean... Overcome the challenges that our ancestors faced and made us who we are today.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Leap out of the water and make a splash!</strong></li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2264390/extras/evotales_bottom.gif?t=1701975152"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aerodangle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2579710/Aerodangle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2579710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2579710/extras/AerodangleGifFromTrailer2.gif?t=1701975008"><br/><br/><strong>Airplanes are a very convenient means of transportation, but not if you are outside of it.</strong><br/>However, the presence of a grappling hook can easily eliminate this disadvantage. <br/>You have to go through a variety of levels, clinging to planes falling apart in the air, using a grappling hook and various abilities.<br/><br/>Explosions, flying, a sense of speed, and a veeery long grappling hook are waiting for you in Aerodangle!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zumba Garden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2589630/Zumba_Garden/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2589630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Your garden has been overrun by hordes of marble-pushing golems... lucky for you. you're armed with a trusty marble cannon with endless ammo, plenty of powerups, and the determination to score as many points as possible :)<br/><br/>A simple, classic sphere-matching recipe for casual fun. Try it!<br/><br/>Game features:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>60 beautiful levels<br/></li><li>14 upgradable powerups<br/></li><li>Clean, pleasant environments<br/></li><li>Relaxing music</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1701985511"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1701985511"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1701985511"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1701985511"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Numbers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2481780/No_Numbers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2481780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>No Numbers is a minimalist, hex-based puzzle game that will rekindle your love for numbers!</strong> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2481780/extras/About_01.gif?t=1701971534"><br/><br/>In <strong>No Numbers</strong> you move numbered tiles around a hex grid, combining them until there are none left. Master the level by clearing them all in as few moves as possible. <strong>No Numbers</strong> features numerous tiles with different mechanics that keep gameplay varied and fresh throughout the 42 handcrafted levels.<h2 class="bb_tag">A relaxing, minimalist ambience</h2> <br/>Immerse yourself in a calming, minimalist ambience. A perfect way to unwind and challenge your mind.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2481780/extras/Mechanic_01_new.gif?t=1701971534"><h2 class="bb_tag">Discover tiles with different mechanics</h2> <br/>Experience evolving gameplay mechanics that keep you engaged. Each level introduces new twists and challenges, keeping your puzzle-solving skills sharp.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2481780/extras/Mechanic_02_new.gif?t=1701971534"><h2 class="bb_tag">42 unique, handcrafted levels</h2> <br/>Dive into 42 meticulously crafted levels, each offering unique challenges. Contemplating solutions ranging from simple to complex, you are in for a varied and rewarding experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2481780/extras/Mechanic_03_new.gif?t=1701971534"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kip and Odosan</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2221440/Kip_and_Odosan/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2221440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Kip run, jump, shoot, swim, and fly her way through the galaxy to save her kidnapped Cat Odosan in this hand-crafted platforming mashup. Enjoy 12 unique levels of platforming challenges through a variety of game play types and unique worlds, all the while piecing together the mystery of who Kip and Odosan really are, and the danger they face.<br/><br/>Play as both Kip and Odosan, each with their unique abilities, and piece together the mystery of who Kip and Odosan really are, and the danger they face.<br/><br/><strong>About the Game:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A single player adventure with beautiful hand drawn worlds, unique enemies, and an all original music soundtrack.<br/></li><li>Play as both Kip and Odosan, each with unique abilities along with fun variety in game play, mechanics, and power ups. Levels range from standard platforming, to run n gun, chase levels, boss fights, hard core platforming, side shooter, and staged boss battles.<br/></li><li>A comic book approach to story that offers twists and turns along the way and changing mechanics.<br/></li><li>Complete with collectibles, speed/timing, and death counts.<br/></li><li>The controls are kept simple and the game play intuitive. Explore, learn, and master as you play! Every death, every failure, brings you closer to solving the mystery, and re-uniting Kip and Odosan at last, and maybe saving the galaxy along the way!</li></ul><br/>Supports both Keyboard and Controller player. For controller support the Generic Gamepad template is recommended. Keyboard support includes:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Movement: Arrow Keys, Z = Jump, V = Shoot (Z = A Button, X = B Button)<br/></li><li>Movement: WASD, U = Jump, P = Shoot (U = A Button, I = B Button)<br/></li><li>Escape, Space Bar to pause or exit game from Menu</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Loves You Too!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1149000/Monster_Loves_You_Too/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1149000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Begin Life as a Tiny Morsel</h2>You're born with FLESH, BRAIN, and GUTS. Grow arms, legs, and teeth. If you survive, you'll get to scavenge for the scraps that larger, meaner Monsters leave behind. Yippee!<br/>‎ ‎<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1149000/extras/mly_doublepan_looping_-_Ichiro_Take_2.gif?t=1701980551"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive using FLESH, BRAIN, and GUTS.</h2>Use these three resources to overcome your Monstrous, impulsive tendencies. Spend them wisely, though, as they <strong>only replenish when you rest or feast</strong>. ‎ ‎<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1149000/extras/mly_utt_short_-_Ichiro_Take_2.gif?t=1701980551"><h2 class="bb_tag">Make Choices!</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The towering, 300-toothed Grattrag scours the ravine below for your friends. Do you fight or hide?<br/></li><li>Join a gang or form your own?<br/></li><li>Eat your friend's arm? (Context: it looks very tasty, and you're famished.)<br/></li><li>Shun the scary loser to look cool... or comfort them and become a "loser" yourself?<br/></li><li>Let Gorry know that a rocket sled would not, in fact, be possible to create? (He'll be heartbroken!)</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1149000/extras/mly_puppets_short_-_Ichiro_Take_2.gif?t=1701980551"><h2 class="bb_tag">Visit the Fantastic Land of Monsters!</h2>Built beneath ancient Human ruins, Asch is your home city, where you'll scavenge and hide among the alleys to survive. The Sharps are where wild Adolescents live free from the shackles of Monstrous society. Join a gang, or form your own. Visit Trade Hill, where shady Monsters meet to exchange precious, deadly Human artifacts.<br/>‏‏‎ ‎<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1149000/extras/mly2_asch_pan.gif?t=1701980551"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courier Chief Tycoon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2225220/Courier_Chief_Tycoon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2225220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2225220/extras/ezgif.com-crop.gif?t=1701968039"><br/><br/><strong>Welcome to Courier Chief Tycoon !</strong><br/><br/>Courier Chief Tycoon is a game that lets you build and operate your own package delivery network. It offers you all the mechanics you need to grow your business.<br/><br/>So what awaits you;<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2225220/extras/KURYE.png?t=1701968039"><br/><br/><strong>-Couriers that you can assign in your company,<br/>-Different features from each other.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2225220/extras/COURIER_software_–_1.png?t=1701968039"><br/><br/><strong>-Panels where you can check your stock status,<br/>-Panels that you can order according to your needs.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2225220/extras/antivirus.png?t=1701968039"><br/><br/><strong>-Qualified software that you can purchase from your internet network,<br/>Each software has its own features.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2225220/extras/BALLGAME.png?t=1701968039"><br/><br/><strong>-The games on the site that you can use to add a new one to your entertainment,<br/>-Some games can earn you balance.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2225220/extras/miningpanel.png?t=1701968039"><br/><br/><strong>-Crypto panels that you can navigate when you activate the secure network access,<br/>-You can provide additional income to your company and accelerate your development.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2225220/extras/antivirus_–_1.png?t=1701968039"><br/><br/><strong>-Engine gallery where you can give your employees an advantage with different engines,<br/>-Interactions where you can strengthen the engines you have.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2225220/extras/CUSTOMER.png?t=1701968039"><br/><br/><strong>-Notification panels where you can check your customers' comments,<br/>-Control panels where you can deal with your customers' orders.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2225220/extras/ezgif.com-crop.gif?t=1701968039"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evil Nun: The Broken Mask</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1460220/Evil_Nun_The_Broken_Mask/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1460220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>THE EVIL NUN EXPERIENCE INCLUDES</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A huge map of a cursed summer camp of a catholic school called Eagle Junior High School.<br/></li><li>Sister Madeline is a very smart &amp; creepy possessed nun. She is constantly chasing you with her infamous hammer.<br/></li><li>Many chapters, escape routes &amp; puzzles to complete.<br/></li><li>Craft different items with the help of the lost children to face the evil nun.<br/></li><li>Minigames &amp; more!</li></ul><br/><strong><i>"This game is fantastic! it gives you enough to be scared and continuously concerned and jumpy, but is also very enjoyable and replayable."</i> - Feeder Junior</strong><br/><br/><strong>HAMMER TIME</strong><br/>Avoid Sister Madeline! A nun who punishes children with her gigantic hammer. You will have to escape from the school at all costs, although along the way you will discover that you are not the only child trapped. Don’t get surprised when Sister Madeline follows you into hard to reach places. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1460220/extras/02_Release.gif?t=1701972302"><br/><br/><strong>WELCOME TO EAGLE JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL</strong><br/>You have been selected to participate in a religious summer camp that promises to be the ideal place to make friends and spend the summer. As soon as you arrive at this place, you realize that it is a hoax. You are locked in a dilapidated school guarded by an evil nun.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1460220/extras/01_Release.gif?t=1701972302"><br/><br/><strong>LABYRINTH OF POSSIBILITIES</strong><br/>Your main goal is to gather all the mask pieces and put them together. But be careful, to accomplish your mission you will need to solve many puzzles &amp; mysteries around this horrifying school. What’s the true story behind the Evil Nun?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1460220/extras/MascaraRES-min.gif?t=1701972302"><br/><br/><strong>6 CHAPTERS 3 ESCAPE ROUTES AND A BUNCH OF MYSTERIES!</strong><br/>Discover what's hidden behind each door of this uncanny school. Plus, a frightening story that will leave you breathless! The clues are all set. Make your own way out of the school, but don’t forget there are quite a few things to do before you leave Eagle Junior High School. Different difficulty levels, minigames and riddles await you. Do you dare?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1460220/extras/04_Release.gif?t=1701972302"><br/><br/><strong>THIS IS EVIL NUN!</strong><br/>One of the most popular horror titles with almost a 100 million downloads comes to Steam completely redesigned with new puzzles, scenes and graphics that will make you live a horror adventure like never before. Content creators are thrilled with this horror game.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1460220/extras/YTRS_Corregido-min.gif?t=1701972302"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1460220/extras/Minibanner_GoodSize.png?t=1701972302"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel in the Dark</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2698560/Hotel_in_the_Dark/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							That's the day it all started on Sept. 13. 2020. In the early morning of the same day, I was already standing at the bus station, waiting for my bus. I had to travel a couple of three hundred kilometers to a small town. I found a hotel quickly. It was quite a modern building at first glance.<br>
Not very high at the bottom was normal such sizes of a signboard, on which the trap hotel Veranda, beautiful luminous letters, went inside. Beautiful small reception, pretty girl behind the counter. It was probably not even five minutes before I had already closed my eyes and fallen asleep. That's where it all started.<br>
As you progress through, you'll need to find keys and open locked rooms. A first-person game with elements of horror. Explore the hotel and its secrets. Collect batteries for your flashlight. Find clues and assemble the whole story into a single picture. The darkness can conceal various mysteries.<br>
<br>
F - flashlight, Tab - inventory<br>
In-game controls WASD - move, left mouse button - pick up an item. Right mouse button - inspect the item.<br>
<br/>
Features:<br/>
- pleasant graphics;<br/>
- simple control;<br/>
- interesting gameplay						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1702000678"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1702000678"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCP-087-B UE Remake</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2676580/SCP087B_UE_Remake/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							SCP-087-B UE Remake is a fan game based on the original SCP-087-B make by Joonas Rikkonen, a single-player horror experience from the point of view of a D-Class sent to explore what lurks below in the unexplored and undocumented depths of an ever-changing brick and concrete staircase. Equipped with only a lighter, the D-Class must navigate dozens of floors until they reach, or rather if they reach, the lowest level. <br/><br/>Much of the audio, graphics and monster design is loosely or directly based on the original design of SCP-087-B, with several more creatures and threats added in beyond the scope of the original.<br/><br/><br/>Foundation Operatives grant all D-Class limited access to the associated documentation on this anomaly before entry, and recommends all subjects to brief themselves with the information before entry:<br/><br/><strong>Item #:</strong> SCP-087-B<br/><br/><strong>Object Class:</strong> Euclid<br/><br/><strong>Special Containment Procedures:</strong> SCP-087-B is located on the campus of [REDACTED]. The doorway leading to SCP-087-B has been disguised to resemble a storage closet consistent with the design of the building. The lock mechanism on the doorknob will not release unless ██ volts are applied in conjunction with counter-clockwise rotation of the key.<br/><br/>Due to the results of the first exploration (see Document 087-B-I), the door handle and locking mechanism have been removed from the inside of the door. Any personnel who enter beyond the threshold of SCP-087-B are presumed dead, and the door must not be opened if motion is detected inside.<br/><br/><strong>Description:</strong> SCP-087-B is an unlit concrete staircase with brick walls. The dark interior of SCP-087-B limits subjects to a visual range of approximately 1.5 meters. A light source is required for any subjects exploring SCP-087-B, as there are no lighting fixtures or windows present. Lighting sources brighter than a lighter flame have shown to be ineffective, as SCP-087-B seems to absorb excess light.<br/><br/>The entrance to SCP-087-B is inside a small room which was formerly used as a storage closet. When two or more subjects enter the room, it appears as a rectangular room with solid concrete walls and a single wooden doorway. Subjects have always described a sense of uneasiness when present within the room, despite having little to no awareness of the anomalous properties of the location.<br/><br/>Subjects who have entered this storage closet alone report observing a brick hallway opposite the entry doorway after they have been sealed within the room. Radio communication with subjects that enter the hallway becomes increasingly difficult as they descend the staircase, and attempts to converse with subjects which have gone beyond the 6th floor has proven difficult. <br/><br/><i>The full extent of SCP-087-B's anomalous properties are unknown, and further expeditions have been approved.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repugnant Bounty</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2652410/Repugnant_Bounty/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2652410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Rosemarie, an alien princess from the planet Nimola seeks genocide on the evil monsters who killed her mother and people. Can you find and kill all 28 target threats?<br>
<br>
Repugnant Bounty is a Metroidvania title heavily inspired by Metroid II, Super Metroid, and Cave Story. Following the game play loop of Metroid II but with the exploration and theming of Super Metroid, many references and Easter Eggs can be found in the game so be on the lookout for them!						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NINJA KATO 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653330/NINJA_KATO_1/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>【first In the Ninja kato Series!】</strong></h2>A 2D action game in the style of 1980s handheld games.<br/>Control the robot ninja Kato and train him to become a full-fledged ninja.<br/><br/>There are a total of 4 stages given to Ninja Kato.<br/>After clearing all stages, Kato will take on an even more difficult stage.<br/><br/>When all training is completed, Kato will make new history!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>【STAGE 01】</strong></h2>Avoid the "kunai" and Get the Items!<br/>The Time Limit Is 650 Seconds!<br/>This is an exercise in quick thinking and good judgment.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653330/extras/screen_shot_small_1.png?t=1701961681"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>【STAGE 02】</strong></h2>Memory Training!<br/>Select the buttons in the order of the items displayed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653330/extras/screen_shot_small_2.png?t=1701961681"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>【STAGE 03】</strong></h2>Get Items Using "shuriken"!<br/>The Time Limit Is 450 Seconds!<br/>Birds Will Get In the Way Of Getting Items!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653330/extras/screen_shot_small_3.png?t=1701961681"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>【STAGE 04】</strong></h2>Finally, Training With the Master!<br/>Avoid the "kunai" fired by your master and get items!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653330/extras/screen_shot_small_4.png?t=1701961681"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>【EXTRA STAGE】</strong></h2>This is an extra stage with increased difficulty!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653330/extras/screen_shot_small_5.png?t=1701961681"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldier Yōki</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2629840/Soldier_Yki/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2629840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Soldier Yōki, is an indie, action and third-person shooter game. Solo or cooperative, up to 4 players, walk the different scenery, with various game experiences.<br>
Face the Alien Alliance and be victorious over the Boss in order to win the game.<br>
<br>
Various maps:<br>
Walk through the different maps of the game, to live a new experience with each game. In colorful or dark universes, be an attacker or defender on some. Lose yourself in science fiction worlds, observe and use the environment to allow yourself victory. <br>
<br>
Character:<br/>
Play as a soldier, accompanied by these brothers in arms to bring down the Alien alliance with your firearm for distance and your lightsaber for melee. Use your dash ability as well as your soldier powers such as fireball, your care for yourself and your friends, the grenade as well as your defensive wall to try to protect yourself in the most difficult moments.<br/>
<br/>
Concept:<br/>
The goal is to survive the Alien alliance. During the battle, the single player mode and the co-op mode are different, but remain the same goal:<br/>
 - Fighting and defeating are the main objectives, but the path will be perilous.<br/>
 - Observe and use your environment wisely.<br/>
<br/>
Are you ready for battle?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky Sojourn</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2543940/Sky_Sojourn/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2543940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2543940/extras/GIF44.gif?t=1701959603"><br/><strong>Welcome to the exciting world of Sky Sojourn!</strong> <br/>In this adventure game you will play as Steve, a brave adventurer who finds himself on a remote deserted island full of mysteries and riddles.<br/><br/>Your task is to climb up a variety of floating islands. To reach the top, you will have to overcome many exciting obstacles. Be ready for unusual challenges!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2543940/extras/GIF11.gif?t=1701959603"><br/>The peculiarity of the game are pushing spheres and elevators that will help you climb to the top! <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2543940/extras/GIF22.gif?t=1701959603"><br/><strong>The higher you go up the more painful it is to fall as there are no saves in the game and if you fall from a great height the game will be over.</strong> But the main thing is not to give up and you will definitely be able to overcome all the obstacles and find out what is at the top!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2543940/extras/GIF33.gif?t=1701959603"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2543940/extras/wishlist-and-follow.gif?t=1701959603"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lies Under Ice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1593390/Lies_Under_Ice/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1593390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Lead the first settlement on Jupiter's frozen moon, Europa! What alien life lurks beneath the ice? Who is sabotaging your mission? Who can you trust?<br/><br/><i>Lies Under Ice</i> is a 200,000-word interactive science fiction novel by Joey Jones, where your choices control the story. It's entirely text-based—without graphics or sound effects—and fueled by the vast, unstoppable power of your imagination.<br/><br/>The year is 2079. Your mission is to build a settlement, explore Europa's treacherous oceans, terraform the moon, and send findings back to Earth.<br/><br/>But political factions within your colony vie for dominance, constantly on the brink of open conflict. While they are technically collaborating on this mission, each one has their own goals for Europa. Will this colony be a site for new trade? A home for Earth's ever-growing population? A clean slate where humans can break free of older social models? How far will each side go to get what they want?<br/><br/>With the most advanced science at your disposal—massive terraforming systems, gene splicing, AI therapy-bots, nerve-connected bionic prosthetics, and more—you can venture from the safety of your spaceship out into the hostile frozen world. Descend beneath the ice of Europa, pilot a submarine through frigid waters that no human has ever seen, and uncover ancient secrets of an alien world.<br/><br/>There's definitely alien life here. But does it pose a danger to you and your fellow settlers, or is it the greatest opportunity that humanity has ever known?<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play as male, female, or nonbinary; gay, straight, bi, or aromantic; poly or monogamous.<br/></li><li>Choose among six distinct professional backgrounds: diplomat, aerospace engineer, arcologist, asteroid miner, pilot, or marine biologist.<br/></li><li>Manage the complex needs of an extraterrestrial base: prioritize the comfort of the workers, maximize scientific output, build luxury domes, dig mazes of ice tunnels, or engage in terraforming.<br/></li><li>Navigate the treacherous politics of Earth’s squabbling factions from millions of miles away!<br/></li><li>Interact with Europa's alien ecosystem: will you release fish as a sustainable food source, bring along cats for companionship, or rely on synthetic creatures to avoid introducing invasive species?<br/></li><li>Run for office in Europa's fledgling government!</li></ul><br/>Delve beneath the ice, and reach for the stars!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
