<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>HoloParade</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2647230/HoloParade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">A lively parade with hololive VTubers and mascot characters!</h2><br/>"HoloParade" is a fan game of hololive and the first title to serve as a test case for "holo Indie". Collect, nurture, and enjoy watching your favorite characters! It's a 2D tower defense game that offers depth, strategy, and can also be enjoyed casually.<br/><br/>What is "holo Indie"?:<br/>It is a general term for a game brand for derivative work games, produced using the "game creator support program" with the aim of co-creating with fans and creators of hololive Production around the world.<h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 1: Simple Yet Deep, Lively Battles</h2>The basic system is a classic 2D tower defense game where you summon characters from your base and march them forward to destroy the enemy's base to win. While the controls are simple, the gameplay is profoundly deep. With over 65 characters, each possessing a variety of abilities like ally healing support and self-destruct attacks, skillful combination and flexible formation are key to enjoying the game.<br/><br/>Additionally, there's an element inspired by parades called the 'Symphony Effect,' where various effects are activated based on the musical instruments played by the characters in march. This adds further strategic depth to the formation of your parade squad and the order of their summoning.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Battle.gif?t=1701417555"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 2: Comprehensive Development Elements</h2>In addition to leveling up and limit breaking, there is a 'Skill' system that allows you to add special abilities not available through regular development. Since you can add up to three types of skills to each character and select them carefully, you can enjoy a unique development process! Furthermore, since you can reset levels and get a full refund of the coins spent, it allows for more freedom in restructuring formations and character development.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Skill_ENG.gif?t=1701417555"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 3: No Gacha Purchases, No Stamina System</h2>The scout gacha, which allows you to acquire characters, can be used by consuming tickets obtained within the game, with no additional purchases required. Also, as there is no stamina system, you are not bound by time and can play as much as you like, whenever you like.<br/><br/>Moreover, the scout gacha allows you to choose from two randomly selected character candidates, enabling players to make selections based on their strategy or preference rather than leaving it entirely to chance.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Gacha_ENG.gif?t=1701417555"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 4: Take a Break with Various Talents and Mini-Games in the Office</h2>When you return to the office, the home screen, you'll be greeted by newly recorded voice lines from Harusaki Nodoka, a staff member of hololive. In the office, talents from hololive may also make appearances, and you might witness some unexpected interactions.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Home_ENG.png?t=1701417555"><br/><br/>Additionally, mini-games with entirely different gameplay from the main story are implemented. These games allow you to collect coins necessary for character strengthening. At the initial release, a mini-game titled "Hurry Up! Miko-Chi!" is available, where Sakura Miko (a VTuber affiliated with hololive) who overslept, dashes at full speed towards her destination while avoiding obstacles. More mini-games are planned to be added in future updates.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/RunMikoti.gif?t=1701417555"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalypse Party</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2351560/Apocalypse_Party/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">The moment of "Apocalypse" approaches, this time... ...you fight for yourself!</h2><br/><strong>「Apocalypse Party」</strong> is distinct from the former 「Project Zero」<br/>In this installment, you will delve deeper into this long-standing battle, with the story gradually becoming incredible! Time travel? Apocalypse? Saving the world? You will face many more unknown challenges... ...<br/>But it still retains our beloved RogueLike + mowing-down-enemies combo, and you will face this catastrophe online with your friends (of course, you can also face it alone)!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Engaging and Deep Mechanics ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT01_Skills_EN.gif?t=1701407236"><br/><br/><strong>Talent pool expanded to 450! And most of them are mechanics that can change the course of battle</strong><br/>Additionally, there are:<br/>- Hundreds of distinct ranged and melee weapons!<br/>- A plethora of divine ultimate skills!<br/>- 35 varied hero characters, hundreds of unique hero skills<br/>The richness has increased by <strong>more than 10 times compared to the former installment</strong>! Can you build the strongest combo?<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Supports Multiplayer, shall we join the hunting party tonight? ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT02_MutiplePlayerMode_EN.gif?t=1701407236"><br/><br/>Support <strong>up to 3</strong> multiplayer online! <br/>Massive hordes of zombies, exhilarating mowing-down action, why enjoy it alone?<br/>Imagine the joy of roaming through a sea of zombies with your friends!<br/>Call them, support each other, move forward or retreat together, survive here!<br/><strong>Of course, we kindly remind you, a "friendship-ends" scenario is not excluded :)</strong><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ You crave some real challenge, don't you? ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT04_Boss_EN.gif?t=1701407236"><br/><br/>In this game, you will face the ultimate challenge.<br/><strong>9 highly challenging Bosses!</strong><br/>Only rapid growth can help you withstand the fierce attacks from the Bosses, accept the challenge, defeat them, and show them who’s boss now!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Perhaps we can do some time traveling! ■</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT05_Medivel_EN.gif?t=1701407236"><br/><br/>A brand new storyline takes you into this familiar yet strange world, continuing a tale of redemption amidst time traveling:<br/>The tragic death of loved ones<br/>The desperate nuclear explosion<br/>The eerie rebirth<br/>The deathly quiet town<br/>The dark dungeons<br/>... ...<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ We are continuously focusing on your gameplay experience! ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT03_Combat_EN.gif?t=1701407236"><br/><br/>We have keenly listened to the feedback from the players of our former installment, reworked the combat system of the game, continuously bringing more fluid gaming experiences to players.<br/>-<i>Mix and use combat methods like melee weapons, firearms, spells, summoning, witchcraft... ...</i>! They will bring you a fun experience.<br/>-<i>Drive vehicles, summon planes, dragon flying, use otherworldly ninjutsu, even use the mysterious Dual-vector Foi</i>, and more easter eggs await your exploration.<br/>-This game encourages an online experience, but undoubtedly, the single-player part can still experience all the systems and joy of this game.<br/><br/>Smooth operation (handling) is also an important part we continuously focus on！<br/>We have made the game’s operation &amp; flow experience more user-friendly.<br/><strong>Easy to get started, yet "easy to learn, hard to master"!</strong><br/><br/><strong>"Since the apocalypse is here, join us for the last revelry."</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/Library_Hero_EN.jpg?t=1701407236"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Truck Simulator - Kansas</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2298430/American_Truck_Simulator__Kansas/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2298430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Introducing Kansas! A U.S State that is home to a truly authentic cowboy culture and miles of land littered with wildflowers. Located in the Midwest of the USA, Kansas is known for its native grasslands, streams, abundant blue skies, and green grassland vistas. <br/><br/>Once considered to be the country’s agricultural heartland, "The Sunflower State" has managed to attract many large businesses and develop in other industrial areas due to its central location and convenient infrastructure for logistics operations. But, as the nickname suggests, nature is certainly doing very well to keep up with technological progress, as the state parks and vast prairies offer unique views with a marvelous atmosphere that will leave every trucker passing by with something to remember.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Deliver to 14 explorable cities including Kansas City, Wichita, or Topeka<br/></li><li>See several landmarks unique to Kansas such as the historic Dodge City, Monument Rocks, and Mount Sunflower<br/></li><li>Become a trucker transporting goods for Kansas' key industries - Salt Mine, Food Factory, Car Factory, Building Material Factory, and Battery Factory<br/></li><li>Deliver cargo to Aerosystem, playing a key role in Wichita's aerospace industry<br/></li><li>Visit Hutchinson and admire the world's largest silos<br/></li><li>Play a crucial role in one of America's largest agricultural states. Transport goods that sustain Kansas' farming legacy<br/></li><li>Enjoy trucking through several scenic towns (settlements)<br/></li><li>Drive through expansive prairies, providing unforgettable views</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Truck Simulator - Farm Machinery</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2638630/American_Truck_Simulator__Farm_Machinery/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Saddle up drivers, because the Farm Machinery DLC for American Truck Simulator has arrived! Transport everything from trusty tractors to forage harvesters across scenic virtual highways and roads. <br/><br/>Featuring 2 in-game brands, Owl &amp; Greenler, you'll be able to deliver a variety of unique cargoes on Lowboy, Dropdeck or Flatbed trailers to a number of agriculture-related industries large and small across the country.<br/><br/>This DLC includes:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Sprayer <br/></li><li>Crawler Tractor <br/></li><li>Forage Harvester <br/></li><li>Fertilizer Spreader <br/></li><li>Grain Trailer<br/></li><li>Autonomous Tractor <br/></li><li>Hay Baler <br/></li><li>Seeding Unit <br/></li><li>Disc Harrow</li></ul><br/>Naturally, we couldn't let you go driving without some themed cabin accessories for your cabin either! <br/><br/>Cabin Accessories<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Lunch Kit<br/></li><li>Scarecrow <br/></li><li>Straw Hat <br/></li><li>Stuffed Autonomous Tractor <br/></li><li>Harvester Toy </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turok 3: Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1996770/Turok_3_Shadow_of_Oblivion_Remastered/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/raptor_jumps.gif?t=1701367237"><br/><br/><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> is a faithful restoration of the classic first-person shooter originally released in 2000 for the Nintendo 64, upgraded through Nightdive Studios’ proprietary KEX Engine for play on modern gaming devices with up to a 4K resolution at 120FPS. <br/><br/>It joins Nightdive Studios and Universal Games popular Turok and Turok 2: Seeds of Evil remasters, capping off the trilogy. <i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> features upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<h2 class="bb_tag">FINISH THE HUNT</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/sniper_one_eye.gif?t=1701367237"><br/><br/><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> is the first title from Nightdive Studios to be remastered using the latest version KEX engine, which utilizes an improved renderer to achieve a higher tier of visual fidelity across 3D models, textures, and graphical effects.<h2 class="bb_tag"><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> Key Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A remastered version of the 2000 classic, available for the first time since its Nintendo 64 release<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS performance<br/></li><li>Advanced rendering features, including anti-aliasing, bloom, ambient occlusion, dynamic shadows, and motion blur	<br/></li><li>Remastered environment art, character models, and updated weapon models<br/></li><li>Brand new Achievements</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/robot.gif?t=1701367237"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinball M</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2337640/Pinball_M/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-1.png?t=1701424473"><br/><br/>The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-2.png?t=1701424473"><br/><br/>- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free<br/>- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage<br/>- Thrilling competition<br/>- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation<h2 class="bb_tag">Sink your teeth into these tables as purchasable DLC: </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">- Chucky's Killer Pinball:</h2> Step into a twisted realm where the innocent becomes sinister, and the playful turns menacing. Navigate through an eerie playfield where Chucky lurks in the shadows, ready to pounce.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Dead by Daylight™️ Pinball:</h2> Become the hunter or even the hunted in a thrilling fusion of classic pinball and the excitement of one of the most popular horror games ever created.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Duke Nukem's Big Shot Pinball:</h2> Enjoy the biggest, grooviest, most BADASS pinball table ever made packed with guns and babes. Push start and play with balls of steel!<h2 class="bb_tag">- The Thing Pinball: </h2>Use your pinball skills and battle against the shape-shifting alien through the arctic chill of U.S. Outpost #31. Can you trust anyone, even yourself?<br/>- Even more coming...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-4.png?t=1701424473"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius - Drukhari</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668040/Warhammer_40000_Gladius__Drukhari/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<i>“What was it like, back then? Just sheer joy, I’m told. Entire civilizations, rendered down for stimulants. Stars drained dry of their power, for a decade-long soiree. Oh, to have been alive and powerful in the last days of Empire - before She-Who-Thirsts…” </i><br/>- Gyrthineus Roche, former Archon of The Last Blade.<br/><br/>The <strong>Drukhari </strong>are an ancient race that fell into degeneracy and depravity, with their remnants only surviving in immense Webway cities. Though they have suppressed the psychic power of their Aeldari kin, they have replaced it with preternatural agility and rapacious cruelty. Their lighting raids from the Webway carry off wealth and captives to dark Commorragh where they suffer intensely throughout their short lives…<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Mechanics </h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Power from Pain</strong>: As pain spreads across the battlefield, Drukhari are invigorated, thriving from the suffering. Their units gain additional bonuses depending on their experience level. <br/></li><li><strong>Corsair Outposts</strong>: The Drukhari rarely venture outside the webway, save to loot realspace resources. Their cities have a reduced growth rate, but it can be improved by controlling more outposts. <br/></li><li><strong>Raid from the Webway</strong>: The Drukhari strike swiftly from the webway, before vanishing with their plunder. Pay influence to create temporary portals and activate webway gates to move your raiding party across the map.<br/></li><li><strong>Raider Fortress</strong>: The Aeldari and Drukhari are forever battling over their access to the webway. Found cities on activated webway gates from which you can unleash your forces on Gladius Prime.<br/></li><li><strong>Soul Hunger</strong>: The souls harvested by the Drukhari are an invaluable resource used for their malevolent schemes. Destroying an enemy unit rewards you with influence that can be traded for economic boosts and combat effects. <br/></li><li><strong>Combat Drugs</strong>: The Drukhari’s foul Haemonculi render down some captives into powerful stimulants. Infantry units can pay with influence and hitpoints for temporary buffs that allow them to outperform their opponents. <br/></li><li><strong>Betrayal Culture</strong>: Drukhari are a vicious race, and only a huge display of riches will convince them to serve—as long as it also serves their interests. Drukhari cities have lower loyalty but gathering influence grants more loyalty. <br/></li><li><strong>Blade Artists</strong>: Blades have an omnipresent place in Drukhari culture, and each commorrite learns this from a young age. Drukhari units get bonus armour penetration in melee. <br/></li><li><strong>Raiders tactics</strong>: When attacking a new prey world, the Drukhari attack en masse from their specially designed vehicles to land troops as close as possible to the fighting. Drukhari transports are all assault transports and Drukhari infantry units can gain combat bonuses when disembarking.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Complete Units Roster </h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Archon <br/></li><li>Cronos<br/></li><li>Haemonculus<br/></li><li>Hellions<br/></li><li>Incubi <br/></li><li>Kabalite Trueborn<br/></li><li>Kabalite Warriors<br/></li><li>Raider<br/></li><li>Ravager<br/></li><li>Razorwing Jetfighter<br/></li><li>Reavers<br/></li><li>Scourges<br/></li><li>Succubus<br/></li><li>Tantalus<br/></li><li>Venom<br/></li><li>Voidraven Bomber<br/></li><li>Webway Portal<br/></li><li>Wracks<br/></li><li>Wyches</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truck &amp; Logistics Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/873840/Truck__Logistics_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Load, drive, and deliver through a huge open world with up to 24 players in cross-platform multiplayer. Join your friends in exciting heavy transport convoys. Jump into the driver's seat of more than 30 unique vehicles and carry out complex loading tasks to deliver a variety of cargo.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Load.gif?t=1701358833"><br/><br/><strong>Load pallets, containers, vehicles &amp; more!</strong><br/>Each mission is unique and comes with its own challenges. Start up your business by loading pallets into vans with a forklift. Then work your way up to loading heavy containers with telescopic handlers onto trailers. Maneuver vehicles such as cars, forklifts, skid-steers, wheel-loaders and more onto your trailers. Hundreds of unique and challenging missions and deliveries await you! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Drive.gif?t=1701358833"><br/><br/><strong>Drive cars, vans, trucks &amp; more!</strong><br/>Drive and customize over 30 unique vehicles. From minivans to heavy trucks, each vehicle has its own detailed interior and realistic driving physics. Vehicles can be damaged, causing axles to bend and making driving difficult. Refuel and repair at service stations to get back on the road in full swing. Make each vehicle your own by customizing it to your liking. Stick to the traffic rules or risk getting fined in random police traffic controls and radar speed cameras. Push your driving skills to the limit in many diverse and challenging missions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Deliver.gif?t=1701358833"><br/><br/><strong>Deliver in an open world with up to 24 friends!</strong><br/>Enjoy the ultimate delivery experience in co-op multiplayer. Join your friends, make convoys, earn money and expand your companies together. Escort other players safely to their destinations using specialized convoy equipment. Explore a vast 28 km² open world, from bustling cities to tranquil rural areas. Explore and uncover hidden secrets scattered across the map. Get ready for a journey into a dynamic and completely open world where the deliveries never end!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 30 unique vehicles with realistic interiors<br/></li><li>Huge 28km² open world (no hidden walls!)<br/></li><li>Cross-platform multiplayer with up to 24 players<br/></li><li>Escort convoys in co-op multiplayer missions<br/></li><li>Full day / night cycle<br/></li><li>Hundreds of different challenging missions<br/></li><li>Realistic driving physics and damage system<br/></li><li>Vehicle customization<br/></li><li>Random police traffic controls &amp; speed cameras</li></ul><br/>Start your company today! Join our community below, see you on the road!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FPCjxFjs" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Discord_2023.gif?t=1701358833"/></a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jurassic World Evolution 2: Cretaceous Predator Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2610980/Jurassic_World_Evolution_2_Cretaceous_Predator_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2610980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Introduce four ferocious new predators to your parks with Jurassic World Evolution 2: Cretaceous Predator Pack. Manage and control these striking dinosaurs as they fight for dominance in your parks and search for their next meal. Unveil the true power of the Cretaceous period to your park guests.<h2 class="bb_tag">Welcome the following extraordinary species:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Gigantoraptor, whose name means “Giant Thief”, is the largest known Oviraptorosaur from the Late Cretaceous era. Featuring an impressive coat of feathers and large elongated legs, the Gigantoraptor can maintain speed for an extended period of time as it chases down its prey.<br/></li><li>Concavenator has a distinctive narrow hump, formed by two extremely large vertebrae, making its profile instantly recognisable. This agile theropod from the Early Cretaceous period is a fierce hunter that will make an exciting addition to your parks.<br/></li><li>Utahraptor, one of the largest dromaeosaurs, is an intelligent and ruthless predator that is sure to impress your guests. With a stunning feather coat and large scythe-like claws, this predator, hailing from Utah, will stop any prey in its tracks.<br/></li><li>Tarbosaurus, is a gargantuan hunter inspired by the Universal Pictures, Amblin Entertainment and DreamWorks Animation Netflix Show, Jurassic World Camp Cretaceous: Hidden Adventure. This unique Tyrannosaurine theropod will need a secure enclosure to protect guests from its powerful jaws.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEVI</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2230650/TEVI/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FZ9KrdFvNRK" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/JoinUsOnDC.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Action-Packed_Combo_System.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/戰鬥動圖.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>The protagonist Tevi is nimble and agile, wielding both her trusty dagger and an oversized wrench for dishing out melee damage in style. Alongside her, companions Celia and Sable manifest as two floating orbitars, ready to unleash a variety of ranged offensive and supportive magic in battle. Adapt your combat style to suit any situation and bring down foes with flashy, dazzling combos!<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Thrilling_Boss_Battles.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Boss.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Every boss fight is a unique challenge requiring different strategies to tackle, all while you dodge their attacks and look for openings to counter-attack. <br/>As bosses change phases, their attack and bullet patterns become increasingly challenging, and they can even unleash devastating ultimates. Continual offense can submit bosses into a vulnerable BREAK state, during which you can deal massive bursts of damage.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Myriad_Abilities,_Equipment,_and_Exploration.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/badge.jpg?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Scattered across the the expansive world, there are over 300 different items and pieces of equipment waiting to be discovered. These items can enhance your abilities or introduce new ones, allowing you to find more methods of navigating the world and finding secrets. A cornucopia of equippable sigils can be freely configured to create builds tailored to your preferences and playstyle.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/A_Rich,_Expansive_Fantasy_World.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/場景6.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Dive into the vibrant world of Az, in which you will discover various towns, regions, peoples, histories, and civilizations, each with their own tale to tell. Along the way, you'll meet a large cast of strange and colorful characters. As their tales unfold and intertwine, you'll be drawn into a tale full of adventure, friendship, mysteries, and danger... <br/><br/>Get ready to embark on an unforgettable adventure, writing your own epic journey alongside Tevi!<br/><br/><a href="https://youtu.be/psxior_WswQ" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/角色介紹.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tevi（VA: Lynn）<br/></li><li>Celia（VA: Yoko Hikasa）<br/></li><li>Sable（VA: Natsumi Fujiwara）<br/></li><li>Zema（VA: Tomokazu Sugita）<br/></li><li>Vena（VA: Rie Kugimiya）</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Suika - Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2671970/My_Suika__Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A fun watermelon merge puzzle game!<br>
<br>
Think you can get 3000 points in this addictive watermelon puzzle game?<br>
<br>
Combine various matching fruits to help Kyo gather watermelons! Unlock new game modes and new fruit skins by obtaining high scores. Compete against other players on the global leaderboards!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call to Arms - Gates of Hell: Liberation</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2447590/Call_to_Arms__Gates_of_Hell_Liberation/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<strong>“Soldiers, Sailors, and Airmen of the Allied Expeditionary Force: you are about to embark upon the Great Crusade!”<br/>This DLC introduces the western front action in 1944, featuring the US faction, as well as German western front content.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/01Sherman.gif?t=1701279518"><br/><br/>Be among the first to scale the Atlantic wall and fight your way through the Bocage. <br/>Be the spearhead that breaks the stalemate in the battle of the Bulge. <br/>Re-live the rush to the Rhine bridge, on the road into the heart of Germany!<br/><br/>Or, fight for the Wehrmacht and be the one that leads the counterattacks, the one that stops the breakout. In other words; be the one that defends “Fortress Europe” facing all the classic dilemmas that come with it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/02Beach.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Single Player</h2>The single player campaigns focus on four legendary western front units: the “Liberation” campaign has the 2nd Rangers and the 3rd Armored Division on the US side. Beside 6 single player missions, this DLC also offers 4 skirmishes for the US faction, which are part of the campaign storyline.<br/>In all of the missions, you will find yourself in intense battles on iconic battlegrounds, recreated to the last detail; get a taste of the bitter fighting against fanatical opposition, liberating western Europe step by hellish step. The action will be intense and the immersion will be up there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/03Nebel.gif?t=1701279518"><br/><br/>The German campaign,  “Festung Europa”, has the 3rd Fallschirmjäger division and 116th Panzer division on the German side in 6 intense and compelling missions.<br/>Be the one that commands the Wehrmacht forces on the western front from Normandy to the last battles in the Ruhr pocket. In the German campaign you will enjoy a lot of new content as well! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/04Maps.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer</h2>“Liberation” adds the USA to multiplayer with 20 brand new western front MP maps, and all of the new weapons, vehicles and tanks; it also adds a new German late war doctrine.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/05Mist.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Conquest</h2>For conquest, 25 western front maps are included. These, like other maps, use the unique set of assets we have created to immerse you in the western front atmosphere. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/06wespe.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Visuals</h2>Liberation pushes the boundary of the visuals of the Gates of Hell universe to a new standard, with hundreds of highly detailed environment models, improved destruction for buildings and beautiful environments. To ensure the historical accuracy of our content, we have collaborated with WW2 Armor in Florida, who provided us with vast amounts of valuable documentation and knowledge.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/07Logo.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Content</h2>The Liberation DLC contains:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>10 US single player missions, including 4 US skirmishes<br/></li><li>6 German single player missions<br/></li><li>150+  new US and German vehicles, cannon, ships, aircraft and tanks<br/></li><li>50 new small arms<br/></li><li>500+ new humanskins<br/></li><li>20 new MP maps<br/></li><li>25 new DCG (Conquest) maps<br/></li><li>500+ new editor assets for the western European theater.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MULLER-POWELL PRINCIPLE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2155770/THE_MULLERPOWELL_PRINCIPLE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FeY9JWyTaAm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_discord.png?t=1701271403"/></a><br/><br/>It is a sci-fi story that takes place in the near future. You are Harry Herman, an employee of Delta Laboratories who researches interdimensional traveling. You had been participating in a project that was supposed to benefit all humanity, but something went wrong. Through the gameplay, you will solve various physics-based puzzles using an energy-manipulating weapon, travel across space and time to explore surrealistic universes and find out the dark truth about this project and your connection to it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_gameplay.png?t=1701271403"><br/>Solve various puzzles and trick enemies using physics interactions and your special tool - the Portable Energy Manipulator. <br/><br/><strong>PHYSICS PUZZLES &amp; INTERACTIVE ENVIRONMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/gameplay_physics.gif?t=1701271403"><br/><br/>Many objects in the game can be picked up, brought somewhere, or manipulated in other ways. Whether it's a computer terminal, a box you can carry, or a simple mug on a table. Explore various interactive environments to find clues and return to the riddle with a solution, which in some cases may be several. Nothing was made for you to solve, there's no cube dispenser or an obvious exit door at the end. It's all for you to figure out.<br/><br/><strong>PORTABLE ENERGY MANIPULATOR</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/gif_photongun.gif?t=1701271403"><br/><br/>The device you carry throughout the game can absorb different energy types from the environment and use them to perform various tasks.<br/><br/>Absorbing energy from a particular source will give the gun its’ properties. The heat energy from fire and radiators will melt glass, security cameras can be blinded by a beam of light, and for powering generators, you can take hazardous radiation from toxic puddles scattered across Delta Labs facilities. And of course, you will make an encounter with the quantum entanglement energy - the mysterious power capable of opening rifts between worlds. <br/><br/>Apart from solving environmental puzzles, your device can also be used against various creatures you'll meet in parallel dimensions. Most of the time you can't defeat your enemies; instead, you can use the Manipulator to outsmart or suspend them. Some enemies can be frozen in place using the force field energy, while others are sensitive to light and can be distracted by shooting a beam at it in the distance. You will require more advanced strategies and combining various energy types to pass them.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_story.png?t=1701271403"><br/>You find yourself in one of Delta Labs' off-world research facilities in an unknown dimension that looks more like a crashing-down laboratory. Your old friends Eugene and Alex try to connect with you shortly, and with their help, you start a journey through various dimensions. You will learn different physics interactions and meet unusual creatures on your way home. Along this, you have to unveil the mysteries of this project and your past. <br/><br/>Experience a non-linear story where your choice always matters. Can you get to the bottom of this, or just try to escape? Who to listen? Who to trust? Which side will you take? And will you finally “break the Principle”? That depends entirely on you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_setting.png?t=1701271403"><br/>Make your way back to Earth through mysterious parallel dimensions littered with puzzles and secrets, uncover mysterious connections between the worlds you visit, and reveal the dark truth about Delta Labs and your involvement with them. Dare to explore?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_features.png?t=1701271403"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Solve various physics-based puzzles<br/></li><li>Unique gameplay mechanics that involve an energy-manipulating weapon <br/></li><li>A mix of sci-fi with surreal and esoteric themes makes the game setting a unique design. Most of the time you'll spend in bizarre alien dimensions<br/></li><li>Deeply thought-out story and lore. Each location and each character in the game has its own story revealed through various notes, environmental narratives, and characters' conversations.<br/></li><li>The game features multiple endings that can be achieved through different choices </li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn around immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Other</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1701359196"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1701359196"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1701359196"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retro Commander</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/338820/Retro_Commander/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/338820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/338820/extras/icon_and_text_v05_-_600x195px.png?t=1700862195"><br/>Retro Commander is a <strong>post-apocalyptic</strong> real-time strategy wargame (RTS). Take command and fight it out in a world where a cataclysmic timeline has transpired on Mother Earth. Wage wars solo, against the AI, or take on your gaming comrades and friends in cross-platform multiplayer matches. Form teams and clans and fight co-op style with the AI and other players for ultimate victory.<br/><br/>As opposed to other real-time strategy game, Retro Commander tries to focus on both, a fun <strong>single player</strong> and a thrilling <strong>multiplayer</strong> experience. The game strives to be easy to learn with a modern user interface. Single player comes with skirmish matches against the AI as well as a comic-based <strong>story campaign</strong>. Multiplayer can be played cross-platform and includes a ranking and rating system.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u>Post-Apocalyptic</u>: Real-time strategy (RTS) played in a post-apocalyptic timeline on Mother Earth. The environment includes day-night cycles, rain, snow, wind and solar flare activity.<br/></li><li><u>Story Campaign</u>: Deep campaign and story line of humanity after a cataclysmic event. Factions come with their own specialized <strong>technologies</strong> such as stealth, robots, drones or shields.<br/></li><li><u>Single &amp; Multiplayer</u>: A challenging AI for both single and multiplayer matches with co-op play. Cross-platform multiplayer including <strong>LAN</strong>/internet. ONLINE play comes with an award and rating system.<br/></li><li><u>Play Modes</u>: In addition to regular skirmish matches, the game supports missions such as elimination, survival, <strong>capture the flag</strong>, defense and <strong>battle royale</strong>. Available in both single and multiplayer also are escort and rescue missions.<br/></li><li><u>Structures &amp; Troops</u>: Common troops for land, sea and air warfare is available to all factions. Specialized elements such as stealth, shields, <strong>EMP</strong> weapons, nukes, <strong>portals</strong>, orbital weapons, assimilator and other troops and structures provide for additional variety.<br/></li><li><u>Research</u>: A <strong>tech tree</strong> and research options enable to build specialized structures and troops. A <strong>Tech Snatcher</strong> can be used to steal enemy technology.<br/></li><li><u>Modding</u>: A map editor is included allowing for player-modded maps including player-modded campaigns. All elements including troops, structures, as well as graphics and sound effects, can be modded if desired.</li></ul><br/>Although some troops are shared, the game is trying not to be a generic RTS-games. There are <strong>faction-specific technologies</strong> each with their strengths and weaknesses.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u>GRA Technology</u>: gives access to <strong>stealth</strong> and cloaking. Included are cloaked agents and spies as well as bombers with EMP and nuclear weapons. Available also are snipers and heavy airlifts. Can build uranium fabricators.<br/></li><li><u>ELC Technology</u>: provides <strong>robots</strong>, <strong>airships</strong> and robo dogs. Available also are a mechanic and heavy airlift. Can build stationary EMP-field generators.<br/></li><li><u>IDB Technology</u>: provides <strong>hovertanks</strong>, <strong>drones</strong> including EMP-field drones and drones equipped with napalm weapons. Can build fusion generators for power.<br/></li><li><u>Mayan Technology</u>: consists of <strong>decoy</strong> capabilities. Included are hologram tanks, transformers, dogs and dolphins. Can build <strong>portals</strong>.<br/></li><li><u>Ancient Technology</u>: provides <strong>shields</strong>, EMP soldiers, assimilators and napalm tanks. Can build matter fabricators.</li></ul><br/><strong>Free vs Paid (DLC or in-game)</strong>: The free version includes unlimited access to over 12+ multiplayer scenarios and Chapter 01 of the single player campaign. Purchasing the DLC <strong>"All Maps &amp; Modding"</strong> grants full access to the game. It includes everything for single player including the story campaign, skirmishing against the AI, ONLINE multiplayer or LAN-play with friends and family.<br/><br/><strong>No DRM</strong>: There is no DRM in the game. You <strong>don't need to connected to the internet</strong> to play single player games or the campaign. You don't need to be logged in to play LAN games either. You don't need to login either for WAN games (locally hosted games over the internet), but you will have to work out your router settings and do the appropriate port-forwarding so your friends can connect from remote.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Stars And Time</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1677310/In_Stars_And_Time/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FZzFSRUBXEC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/discordbanner620.gif?t=1701180941"/></a><br/><br/><strong>What would you do if you were forced to relive your failures over and over again?</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam5_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> tells the story of Siffrin and their adventurer friends—a found family bound together by fate in order to end the tyrannical reign of an evil king. But as victory is just within the party’s grasp, a tragedy occurs, the clock resets, and <strong>they have to do it all again</strong>. <br/><br/>As Siffrin’s the only one who notices this loop, each new start wears away at his cheerful veneer, yet he keeps going in hopes he can end this temporal tragedy once and for all.<br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> is a <strong>time-looping RPG adventure</strong>. With each loop, Siffrin gains a new perspective on the world around them, opening up new solutions to puzzles and allowing them to make better choices in conversation. Equip memories as armor, pray to the Change God to improve your team’s capabilities each loop, and challenge deadly foes to Rock, Paper, Scissors as Siffrin seeks the truth.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam4_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Our Adventurers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Siffrin (he/they):</strong> Stressed, depressed, and under duress. (Don’t worry about it. They’re doing fine.) The punmaster protagonist of our neverending tale.<br/></li><li><strong>Mirabelle (she/her):</strong> A caring and nervous housemaiden mysteriously blessed by the god she so ardently follows.<br/></li><li><strong>Isabeau (he/him):</strong> Defender with a heart of gold. Cares dearly for his people and his friends.<br/></li><li><strong>Odile (she/her):</strong> The mature and nonsensical researcher studying…something. (No, she will not tell you what it is.)<br/></li><li><strong>Bonnie (they/them):</strong> Wait a minute, who brought this kid along???</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Save the world through the power of Rock, Paper, Scissors in <strong>strategic turn-based RPG</strong> combat encounters.<br/></li><li>Ignore the limits of time and space to <strong>fix your past mistakes</strong> by repeating the same two days over and over again.<br/></li><li>Equip the <strong>memories you have of your friends</strong> to make your party stronger in combat. <br/></li><li><strong>Watch the fate of this world unfold</strong> as you escape the twists and turns of this endless(???) loop.<br/></li><li>Eat <strong>samossas</strong> with your friends!<br/></li><li>Get heckled by a <strong>cheeky ethereal being of infinite starlight</strong>.<br/></li><li>Pray to a god for good luck in your travels. <strong>You’re gonna need it.</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam2_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/>If any of this interests you, you might also want to play the game’s initial prototype, <u><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1691420/START_AGAIN_a_prologue/" rel="" target="_blank">START AGAIN START AGAIN START AGAIN: A Prologue</a></u>. While you don’t need to play it to understand In Stars and Time, it’s fun to see the game’s roots.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 5 Tactica</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2254740/Persona_5_Tactica/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join the Phantom Thieves as they lead an uprising of the heart! Assemble a team of beloved heroes in a brand-new story in this thrilling combat adventure set in Persona’s iconic universe. The Persona 5 Tactica: Digital Deluxe Edition includes the following content:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Repaint Your Heart Challenge Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Weapon Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Picaro Summoning Pack + Raoul Persona</li></ul><br/><strong>Ignite your heart— An emotional uprising begins!</strong><br/><br/>After a strange incident, the Phantom Thieves wander into a bizarre realm where its citizens are living under tyrannical oppression. Surrounded by a military group named Legionnaires, they find themselves in grave danger until a mysterious revolutionary named Erina rescues them and offers an enticing deal in exchange for their help. What truth lies behind Erina and the deal she offers to the Phantom Thieves?<br/><br/>Persona 5 Tactica features an all-new story, the return of fan-favorite characters, and brand-new allies and foes. Join the group as they lead an emotional revolution in this thrilling combat adventure!<br/><br/><strong>An Emotional Revolution</strong><br/>Lead an uprising of the heart in a brand-new storyline that takes place in Persona’s iconic universe.<br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Squad</strong><br/>Assemble a team of beloved heroes to fight oppressive armies in thrilling turn-based combat.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Combat</strong><br/>Overthrow your enemies with powerful Personas, an assortment of weapons, and wipe them out with style!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 5 Tactica</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2254740/Persona_5_Tactica/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join the Phantom Thieves as they lead an uprising of the heart! Assemble a team of beloved heroes in a brand-new story in this thrilling combat adventure set in Persona’s iconic universe. The Persona 5 Tactica: Digital Deluxe Edition includes the following content:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Repaint Your Heart Challenge Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Weapon Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Picaro Summoning Pack + Raoul Persona</li></ul><br/><strong>Ignite your heart— An emotional uprising begins!</strong><br/><br/>After a strange incident, the Phantom Thieves wander into a bizarre realm where its citizens are living under tyrannical oppression. Surrounded by a military group named Legionnaires, they find themselves in grave danger until a mysterious revolutionary named Erina rescues them and offers an enticing deal in exchange for their help. What truth lies behind Erina and the deal she offers to the Phantom Thieves?<br/><br/>Persona 5 Tactica features an all-new story, the return of fan-favorite characters, and brand-new allies and foes. Join the group as they lead an emotional revolution in this thrilling combat adventure!<br/><br/><strong>An Emotional Revolution</strong><br/>Lead an uprising of the heart in a brand-new storyline that takes place in Persona’s iconic universe.<br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Squad</strong><br/>Assemble a team of beloved heroes to fight oppressive armies in thrilling turn-based combat.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Combat</strong><br/>Overthrow your enemies with powerful Personas, an assortment of weapons, and wipe them out with style!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Saga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1320140/Small_Saga/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Venture below the streets of London, and you will find the medieval kingdom of rats, mice, moles, squirrels, and shrews known as Rodentia.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G8.gif?t=1700830017"><br/><br/>If the rodents have a cardinal law, it is this: never attack a god. But Verm never had much respect for the rule of law. His tail was stolen by the Yellow God of Death, and now the mouse will have to fight all manner of beasts and titans on his quest to get it back.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G5.gif?t=1700830017"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G1.gif?t=1700830017"><br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Team up with a colorful cast of misfit rodents.<br/></li><li>Encounter awe-inspiring titans. Clash with a swashbuckling water vole, a pious lab rabbit, a poetry-spewing kraken, and many more.<br/></li><li>Meet the hideous vermin who run society, then overthrow them.<br/></li><li>Brandish your tiny weapons in strategic, turn-based combat. <br/></li><li>There is no grinding. Small Saga is a tightly-focused and boss-oriented adventure.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero's Adventure: Road to Passion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1948980/Heros_Adventure_Road_to_Passion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FFPnrtuXddA" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/JOIN_OUR_DISCORD.png?t=1700823813"/></a><br/><br/>In <i>Hero's Adventure:Road to Passion</i>, you commence your journey as an underdog in the tumultuous Jianghu - a vibrant world teeming with martial artists - and are met with a wide array of choices as you navigate your heroic saga. Whether it’s training under a battle-hardened warrior to become a master of martial arts, or following Taoist rituals to reach self-enlightenment, you’re the hero, and this is your adventure.<br/><br/><br/>Play 1.0 Now!<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>[Unexpected Encounters Await]</strong><br/><br/>Throughout your journey, you will run into scripted and unexpected encounters. Perhaps you'll cross paths with an ambitious lieutenant amidst a power struggle at a humble inn, or you’ll run into a retired kung fu master in a nameless village. These will be the experiences you will learn to expect in the ever-changing Jianghu.<br/><br/>Beware, each encounter might associate and change your relationship with the 30+ factions involved in the power struggle in this chaotic Martial World. And remember: every choice you make, every person you befriend (or offend), and every faction you engage will leave a mark.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/Sparring.gif?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[Become the Master of Martial Arts]</strong><br/><br/>Whether you're decoding ancient techniques off a forgotten scroll, or prefer training with a battle-hardened warrior, there’s no correct solution for mastering martial arts. Choose from a variety of weapon types and explore 300+ martial arts skills, the Jianghu will be yours to conquer.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/High-level_Martial_Arts.gif?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[Explore a Living, Breathing World]</strong><br/><br/>In this Wuxia simulator, you'll get to explore 80 cities and villages that bring wuxia to life. Witness how villagers go about their daily routines, and experience the rhythms of ancient Chinese cities.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/Nameless_Village.gif?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[Craft Your Narrative]</strong><br/><br/>To provide an experience where you can embody your own martial spirit, Hero’s Adventure has over 10 distinct endings. Whether you choose to be a noble swordsman, a guardian of the nation, or an agent of chaos, you'll find an ending that aligns with your chosen path in Hero's Adventure. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/武林霸主_1_.png?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[New features that are added in v1.0:]</strong><br/>- New bondable female characters, boosting the total number to 18<br/>- A Homestead system to better manage your recruited characters, inherit your Martial Art and weapons to another playthrough<br/>- 200+ new narrative encounters, and adjusted 400+ of the existing encounters<br/>- New Jianghu Event system ensures your adventure doesn’t end prematurely with major events<br/>- Added duel option against high-rank NPCs for a test of mettle.<br/>- Enhanced customization and upgrades for team characters.<br/>- Early supporters will discover a special accessory as a token of gratitude.<br/>- Controller and steam deck support.<br/>- Steam Workshop 2.0</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naheulbeuk's Dungeon Master</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2005160/Naheulbeuks_Dungeon_Master/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/Reivax_poster_H_en.gif?t=1700585599"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your mission, should you choose to accept it!</h2><br/>Embody Reivax, the servile (or not) steward of the Dungeon of Naheulbeuk. Years before the first incursion of fearless adventurers, you are tasked to build, develop, and populate the wobbly tower. Above all, try not to upset your master, the evil sorcerer Zangdar. Are you up to the task?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_1_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Ascend to days of glory and build the dungeon of your dreams!<br/></li><li>Decorate each room with lots of objects and furniture to attract new patrons and employees!<br/></li><li>Raise your reputation to new heights to become the world-devious dungeon!<br/></li><li>Level up your Tripe adviser reputation to attract new customers to your tavern!<br/></li><li>Display your most precious treasures to earn their benefits! Protect them from jealous neighbors!<br/></li><li>As you grow, unlock new dungeon levels to expand and diversify!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_2_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/></img></li><li>Hire less useless personnel to work, defend, raid, and serve the evil Zangdar.<br/></li><li>The world of Naheulbeuk is inhabited by various and unusual species, each with perks and skills – can you manage them?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_3_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/></img></li><li>Manage the expectations and the needs of your fellow minions to reveal the best or worst of their capabilities!<br/></li><li>Upgrade them to improve their workflow and their satisfaction!<br/></li><li>Deal with strikes and other acts of insubordination the way you like!<br/></li><li>Handle Zangdar frustration to secure your fragile position!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_5_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/></img></li><li>As your dungeon grows and improves its reputation, defend it against adventurers!<br/></li><li>Build treacherous traps and artifices to catch raiders and seal their fate!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_6_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/></img></li><li>Offense is the best defense – send your minions to loot and raid neighboring dungeons!<br/></li><li>Want to eliminate the competition? Send your mercenaries and guards on incursions all around the land of Fangh!<br/></li><li>Many factions exists in Naheulbeuk, try not to frustrate them to much or face reprisals!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_4_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/></img></li><li>Production is key to thriving and achieving a monopoly, so you will need to generate numerous resources to flood the market!<br/></li><li>Tools, weapons, compost, intel, astral energy, and more! Stock or sell them to gain advantages!<br/></li><li>Use the Crac 40 wisely to prosper! <br/></li><li>Unlock the market, giving you access to new items and artifacts!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header_alt_assets_2.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astral Ascent</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1280930/Astral_Ascent/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Astral Ascent is a 2D platformer rogue-lite game set in a modern fantasy world. As one of 4 Heroes with very different personalities, you must escape from <i>the Garden</i>, an astral prison guarded by 12 powerful and vicious bosses, the Zodiacs.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CREATE YOUR OWN PLAYSTYLE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Gif_playstyle.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Unlock dozens of unique spells for your 4 distinct characters. Optimize your own build or try out new ones to take down 12 powerful bosses. Get stronger with time to match up with your foes. Each run will test your skills and your reactivity.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TWELVE ALMIGHTY BOSSES TO FACE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Zodiacs.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The Zodiacs are 12 experienced guardians dispatched over 4 gorgeous worlds. They’ll bring to the battlefield unique attacks, abilities, and patterns, backstories to uncover, and reasons to be fighting you. Get yourself warned!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>4 PLAYABLE CHARACTERS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/4_Character_banniere_steam7.png?t=1700851162"><br/><i>Unique characters. Unique weapons. Unique ways to play.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Ayla:</strong> The sole survivor of her guild of assassins, she uses her twin daggers to eliminate her enemies before they can react. Her speed and proficiency are unmatched.<br/></li><li><strong>Kiran:</strong> This orphan learned life the hard way. He uses his strength to deliver attacks powerful enough to create shockwaves. Brutal.<br/></li><li><strong>Calie:</strong> This talented sculptor wants her freedom back. She will use her magical gemstones to pierce enemy defenses and shred them to bits. She is unforgiving.<br/></li><li><strong>Octave:</strong> Trained by a powerful witch, this young fighter summons ethereal guns to attack his foes. When needed, he can conjure bigger weapons as well. Lethal in all cases.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A STORY THAT OPENS UP, ONE PIECE AT A TIME</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/ZimZim2.png?t=1700851162"><br/>Astral Ascent is a rogue-lite infused with narration. Replayability is part of our story which will be unraveled piece by piece. As you get stronger, you will discover more about the characters, their motivations, and the secrets of the world they’re trapped in.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>LOCAL CO-OP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Coop.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The weight of destiny is too heavy to carry by yourself? Don’t worry and bring a friend to play in our <strong>two-player co-op</strong> mode. Fight and crush your enemies together in local co-op or online using the <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/remoteplay?snr=1_614_615__1601" rel="" target="_blank"><strong>Steam's Remote Play Together</strong></a> feature.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A VAST, COLORFUL FANTASY WORLD WAITING TO BE EXPLORED</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Panning.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Dash across gigantic landscapes. Explore original and hand-crafted areas. Discover the world created by our artists, with a gorgeous art and frame-by-frame animation.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refind Self: The Personality Test Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2514960/Refind_Self_The_Personality_Test_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							All players approach games in varied ways, making different choices.<br/>No one ever plays in exactly the same way. Indeed, how a person plays can be an indicator of their personality...<br/>And Refind Self is a game where you can learn all about that personality.<br/><br/>One play is about one hour.<br/>Just enjoy this simple test during your busy time.<br/>And the third time test will show all your personalities, where the end of the story is also not far away.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/NormalScene.gif?t=1700145463"><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2>You are an android. The story begins with you standing at the grave of the Doctor who created you. The world is populated by robots in various forms, created for numerous purposes.<br/><br/><br/>Travel to places key to your memories of the Doctor, interact with the robots, and unravel the secrets behind the future the Doctor sought and what you were entrusted with.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/ConversationWithRobot.gif?t=1700145463"><h2 class="bb_tag">Important Characters</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/CR_Player_Normal.png?t=1700145463"> <strong>[Protagonist]</strong><br/>The player, a robot created by the Doctor as an EAI: an AI that can take action based on emotions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/CR_Daru.png?t=1700145463"> <strong>[Dull]</strong><br/>A robot clerk at the café. Always lazy due to misconfiguration by the Doctor.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/CR_GOGOscrap.png?t=1700145463"> <strong>[GoGo Scrap]</strong><br/>A robot that collects scraps. Sociable and boylike.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/CR_Inori.png?t=1700145463"> <strong>[Inori]</strong><br/>A shepherd robot created to carry out orders.<h2 class="bb_tag">How to Play</h2>Go wherever you feel like, converse, investigate, play minigames... Simply play as you please. There are no game overs, and there's no right or wrong way to progress.<br/><br/>With each action you take, your personality will be analyzed. Once analysis is 100% complete... Congratulations, you've beaten the game! Your personality results will then be revealed.<br/><br/>If you want to know more about your personality, you can go back to play again and again. Of course, this also goes for those who want to know the truth of the story.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/HowToPlay.gif?t=1700145463"><h2 class="bb_tag">Personality Comparison and Sharing</h2>Your test results are stored in an online database, and you'll be issued a unique results ID. You can share your results ID, and view others' results to compare them with your own.<br/><br/>Perhaps similar personalities mean good compatibility? That's another way of having fun with your results.<br/><br/>*Test result data does not include any personal identifiable information.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/PersonalityComparison.gif?t=1700145463"><h2 class="bb_tag">Examples of Possible Personalities</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514960/extras/seikakuichirei_en.png?t=1700145463"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirate Fighting Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186400/Pirate_Fighting_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pirate Fighting Simulator is a free multiplayer PVP game developed in Unreal Engine 5 in which you fight other players using typical pirate weaponry. There are also cosmetics that you can unlock, these cosmetics can be either hats, weapon skins or in the form of a title that sits underneath your username. The game also includes emotes so you can absolutely boogie down silly style after destroying an enemy gamer. There are also two gamemodes one being TDM (Team Death Match)) and the second being FFA (Free For All).						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1699642767"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1700646226"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons 4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1643310/Dungeons_4/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Once upon a time in a realm far, far away, everything was lush and green. The unicorns mingled among the trees and the elves and humans lived peacefully in harmony with their surroundings. Yet somewhere at the edge of a clearing half-hidden among the trees, obscured by a rising veil of fog in the hazy half-darkness of a weather-beaten hut, a shape huddles over a large and ominously glowing crystal ball. A mumbling voice sings ancient formulae, urging the swirling glowing mists inside the crystal to part and give an insight into the future.<br/><br/>“All is in flux, nothing seems certain. Come, oh vagaries of space and time, separate the veil and show us what is yet to come”, the voice grumbles with the hint of an eye faintly reflecting the glow in front of its hood. The shape’s audience, only barely visible in the dim light, leans in closer and listens intently. “Time ebbs and flows, forming pools and wrinkles… but when the mists part only vague images rise from beyond the veil. Shhhh—don’t come too close, you don’t want to disturb my delicate magical weavings do you?” The shape, still bent over the orb, mutters and shoos the other back a bit more into the shadows. “Ah, now it seems to be clearing a little. I can see… something… several somethings, hints of voices echoing in the haze. A baby, something happening on Hill Doom and the coming together of the Council of Snots – what could all this mean?”<br/><br/>In a flash, the light reflected in the eye turns red and a distant evil laughter echoes through the woods. Stay tuned for the return of the Soothsaying Evil!</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/dungeons-4.gif?t=1701355158"><br/><br/>The Absolute Evil and its trusted *cough* servant, the Dark Elf Thalya, return in <strong>Dungeons 4</strong> after the events of its fabulous predecessor to bring about their triumph over the forces of good once more.<br/><br/><strong>Build a cozy and comfortable Dungeon</strong> to suit your creatures’ needs and rule over them, then send them out into the Overworld to kindly remind the good people living there that the Absolute Evil rules over their lands. <strong>Gather your Evilness</strong> in new and dynamic ways <strong>and unleash it upon</strong> the lush green forests and plains of <strong>the Overworld</strong> to turn them over to the dark side. But make sure that <strong>your Dungeon is well-secured</strong> by traps and defended by your creatures, for those pesky Overworlders won’t just twiddle their thumbs while you <strong>turn their land into the Absolute Evil’s most pleasurable holiday paradise</strong>.<br/><br/>But what is that noise? <i>“Gold, gold, gold and gems, gold and gems and gold!”</i> The ancient song echoes throughout the underworld, accompanied by the clanging steel of hammers and axes. <strong>The Dwarves have arrived</strong> to claim their share of the abundant resources and together with the Elves and Humans of the Overworld, they send out their raiding parties to find the Dungeon’s heart.<br/><br/>Dungeons 4 keeps the spirit of its predecessor, but everything is now <strong>bigger, better, and with even more dynamic Evilness™</strong>.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-1_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Everything is better with Dwarves™:</strong> The Dwarves have arrived to build their underground strongholds and the hardy little fellows (although they don’t like being called that) compete with the Ever-Expanding Evil for space and resources.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-2_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>It makes your Dungeon great again:</strong> Dungeons are up to four times larger than before and there are many more creatures who wait for the All-Commanding Evil’s orders to conquer the Overworld. Now the time has come for massive armies and truly sprawling dungeons!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-3_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Ripe for the taking:</strong> The Overworld is bigger than ever before. Gain Evilness by beating Mini Bosses like the obsessively harmonious Unicorn and use it to transform the Overworld into stunning biomes of pure evil.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-4_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>New and shiny:</strong> An ability-based Perk system for Thalya, the Absolute Evil’s trusted *cough* and most loyal subordinate, grants her impressive new powers. The Absolute Evil can now enjoy taking over the world, governing the creatures and slapping subordinates even more with the customizable Evil Hand.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-5_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Minions, everywhere:</strong> The Horde, the Undead and the Demons wait to do the Absolute Evil’s bidding, with more creatures than ever eagerly following the gesturing Evil’s orders, and Snots will play a much more prominent role this time.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-6_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Many ways to tell the story:</strong> A long campaign, narrated by the beloved English Narrator from previous titles, as well as several skirmish maps all to challenge your rule as the Absolute Evil.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-7_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Change the world:</strong> Spread your Evilness across the Overworld to bring lush and green environments over to the dark side, now shining even more vibrantly and beautifully evil as you spread your evilness across many new biomes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-8_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Work together, slay together:</strong> 2-player co-op multiplayer with both players managing one Dungeon together. All maps from the skirmish mode and the campaign are playable in co-op.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Append</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2437110/Append/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/logo_small.png?t=1701433244"><br/><br/>Append is a 2D top-down arena shooter with online multiplayer. Play as a futuristic hovering space train in a dilapidated space station, fighting other trains over who gets to scavenge the station or something, whatever. The reason is not important. Your roof-mounted cannon can be upgraded by collecting power-ups, which are stored inside your train cars - watch out so the enemy trains don't destroy them!<br/><br/>Shoot the enemies to shrink them, and to snipe their abilities. Go super offensive and obliterate everything, or put everything on defense. Choose your own strategy!<h2 class="bb_tag">HUNDREDS OF WEAPONS</h2> Collect power-ups and combine them into hundreds of unique combinations, all useful in different scenarios and situations. There are also many passive abilities that help you defend or attack more efficiently. Each ability can be upgraded to increase its power.<h2 class="bb_tag">Applicative powers</h2> With applicative powers you can add a debuff to your enemies. These interact in expected ways, fire burns over time, water puts fire out, but also makes electricity spread, snow makes the enemy slower and so on. With each level, the debuff becomes stronger or longer lasting.<br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/waterlightning.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplicative powers</h2> If you want to shoot more bullets, you can use a multiplicative power. There are multiple variants of these depending on whether you want precision or mayhem. With increasing levels the rate of fire becomes higher.<br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/spread.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">Impacting powers</h2> When your bullets hit something, impacting powers make them do something. They can bounce, explode, or even go through walls. With each level, the impact becomes more prominent.<br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/pierce.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">Movement powers</h2> You can also affect the movement of your bullets, like making them faster, chase enemies, or slow down and become a mine. If you combine the mine with other powers, you can even create defense turrets. The movement becomes more pronounced as you get higher levels of the power.<br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/homing.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">Passive powers</h2> There are also lots of passive powers that improve your chances of winning, like faster movement, healing, luck, and segments that shoot back at incoming projectiles. These powers also amplify when you get higher levels.<br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/healing.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">Mystery boxes</h2> Sometimes you will come across a mystery box, where you get to choose from 3 power-ups. If you have collected the luck powerup, you will have a higher chance of getting rare power-ups from the box. This allows you to tailor your arsenal to the opposition, and upgrade to insane levels of destruction.<br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/box.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">ONLINE MULTIPLAYER</h2> Challenge your friends or strangers online, no local server or host required. Each room can fit up to ten players so you can invite all your friends. Create private rooms or allow strangers to join.<br/><br/>If you don't have enough friends you can also play against bots with varying difficulty. <br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/ten.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLE GAME MODES</h2> You can play free-for-all where everyone tries to kill everyone, or team up against each other, for instance humans vs bots. <br/><br/>There is more than one way to win the game. The goal can be to grow as long as possible, to kill as many enemies as possible, or to just shoot as many bullets as possible. <br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/winning.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2> <ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple game modes (Free-for-all, Co-op, etc).<br/></li><li>Configurable goals (Longest train, most kills, etc).<br/></li><li>Online multiplayer without need for server, host, or firewall config.<br/></li><li>Play with your friends or create and join games with strangers.<br/></li><li>Supports mouse/keyboard or controller.<br/></li><li>Original soundtrack.<br/></li><li>Procedurally generated arenas.<br/></li><li>Easy to mod.</li></ul><br/>May the best train win, or survive or whatever. Yay!<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2437110/Append/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2437110/Append/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Psycho: Hospital Escape 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2471110/Dr_Psycho_Hospital_Escape_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2471110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							🏥 In the heart of "Doctor Psycho's Hospital", you find yourself trapped in a horrible nightmare, a captive of your own tormented mind. The hospital that was once just a mirror in your mind is now a living hell — a place where your deepest secrets and darkest fears have come true. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2471110/extras/hospital.gif?t=1701431464"><br/><br/>⚡️Your goal is crystal clear: confront your inner demons, find the hidden items and keys within the hospital's ominous walls and make your way to unlock the escape door that holds your only path to freedom. Escape is your only salvation, but the road is full of danger.<br/><br/>🪓 The survival depends on your stealth, survival skill and quick actions as you navigate the strange halls of a dangerous hospital, when every step you take could be your last. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2471110/extras/doccc1.gif?t=1701431464"><br/><br/>😈 Search for stuff, avoiding the evil Dr. Psycho and his psychopathic patients, Crazy Butcher and Sewer Clown. Explore the deepest psyche of your character as they face a terrifying and overwhelming nightmare twisted to life. Embrace shadows and hide in unusual places like under beds, closets, toilet stalls to avoid unwanted attention. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2471110/extras/doll.gif?t=1701431464"><br/><br/>💡 Can you conquer your inner demons and discover the secrets of this place, freeing yourself from the clutches of the Doctor's Psycho Hospital? <br/>The line between sanity and madness is blurred as you navigate the dangerous realms of your nightmares. <br/><br/>🤯 Your mind and freedom hang in the balance. Good luck.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Favela Zombie Shooter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2622860/Favela_Zombie_Shooter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Get ready for a heart-pounding, action-packed zombie shooting game set in a Brazilian favela. In "Favela Zombie Shooter," you'll face wave after wave of different zombies and have to survive as long as you can.<br>
<br>
Gameplay:<br>
Wave-Based Survival: Brace yourself for relentless waves of the living dead. You must stand your ground and fight off waves of zombies, each with their own unique behaviors and abilities.<br>
<br>
Zombie Types: <br>
To survive, you'll need to adapt to the different zombie types. Slow-moving zombies lumber towards you, but their sheer numbers can overwhelm. Runners sprint at breakneck speed, making them difficult targets. Scratchers, when close, they attack quickly and inflict serious damage. Heavy zombies are nearly impervious to gunfire and require tactical thinking to bring down.<br/>
<br/>
Upgrade System:<br/>
To stay alive, you'll need better weapons. You can earn money in the game and use it to buy stronger guns to help you survive.<br/>
<br/>
Features:<br/>
- Fun and intense zombie shooting action.<br/>
- Different types of zombies to fight.<br/>
- Buy better weapons to survive longer.<br/>
- Four different maps to survive in.<br/>
- Realistic graphics and beautiful environments.<br/>
<br/>
In "Favela Zombie Shooter," you'll need quick reflexes and powerful weapons to survive the zombie onslaught. Can you make it out alive from the favela filled with zombies?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Maiden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391690/Blue_Maiden/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Blue Maiden is a Japanese first person psychological horror game that focuses on exploring and finding answers to the mystery of the old neighborhood.<h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2><br/>You are Tachi Tachibana, a graduated university student, after graduating you decide to return to your neighborhood to help at the family business, you have been dreaming the same nightmare in which you find a mysterious girl, when You finally arrive in your neighborhood, you notice that something is not right, and you must find out what is happening.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/>Most of the time you have to walk and explore different traditional Japanese locations to find clues and solve the mystery of the Blue Maiden.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Immersive Experience:</strong> An Atmospheric Graphics.<br/></li><li><strong>Japanese Theme:</strong> Environment inspired by Japanese horror games.<br/></li><li><strong>Psychological horror:</strong> The game contains some jumpscares that could be disturbing.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elves of Duty</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2061100/Elves_of_Duty/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2061100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Compete with friends or team up to deliver the most gifts</strong></h2><strong>Chaotic platforming. Fast paced PvP combat. Diverse arenas filled with traps and hazards.<br/>A thrilling experience that will surely (maybe, but probably not) ruin friendships.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Features</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 2 Game Modes - Delivery and Brawl<br/></li><li> 14 Arena Levels<br/></li><li> 13 Unique Power-ups<br/></li><li> 2-4 Player Local Multiplayer <u><strong>(Controllers are required for each player in local multiplayer)</strong></u></li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Deploy an Arsenal of Ridiculous Power-ups</strong></h2><br/><strong>Fireball</strong> - Fast. Reliable. Just don't miss.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2061100/extras/elvesofduty_fireball.gif?t=1701428789"><br/><br/><strong>Hammer Swirl</strong> - Big tools for tiny hands. Nailed it.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2061100/extras/elvesofduty_hammerswirl.gif?t=1701428789"><br/><br/><strong>Cluster Duck</strong> - Quack, Quack, BOOM<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2061100/extras/elvesofduty_clusterduck.gif?t=1701428789"><br/><br/><strong>...and many more!</strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balance Helicopter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1964410/Balance_Helicopter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1964410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Balance the helicopter using its two engines! <br>
<br>
17 levels with difficult obsticles!<br>
<br>
Short game with +2 hours of gameplay.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ludde</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2073590/Ludde/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2073590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2073590/extras/family614.png?t=1701427564"><br/><br/>Explore a charming winter world with Ludde and discover various exciting, challenging, and fun activities for all ages!<h2 class="bb_tag">Have fun with snow</h2>Roll big snowballs to create a snowman, snow shovel the yard, have a snowball fight with the neighbors, ice fish, practice slapshots in hockey, rent a snowmobile or put on your skis and ski down the mountain. All of this and much more is possible in Ludde.<h2 class="bb_tag">Be rewarded with golden dog bones</h2>100 golden dog bones connected to 100 different activities to discover and collect. When you have gathered enough bones you'll have access to more items and eventually, you have proven yourself ready to face the evil threat that endangers the peace of Ludde's village.<br/><br/>If you like collectibles then you are in luck. Keep your eye out for coins, chewable pinecones, bulletin boards, and clams, or use your camera to take pictures of snow fairies.<h2 class="bb_tag">Move fast with vehicles and gear</h2>Rentable snowmobiles (including flyable ones) can be found everywhere, but you can also buy your own or use your skis. If you find hot air balloons, you can use them as fast travel points and fast travel there at any time.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Explore a picturesque winter world and play around with snow<br/></li><li> Discover 100 fun and varied activities spread across the world<br/></li><li> Focus on what you enjoy: explore your surroundings at your own pace and choose which activities you wish to complete<br/></li><li> Move around fast by using snowmobiles, skis, your wingsuit, or hot air balloons<br/></li><li> Thanks to the pick-up-and-play concept and multiple difficulty settings, the game is equally enjoyable for all ages</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2073590/extras/mix.gif?t=1701427564"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2073590/extras/snowbile4.gif?t=1701427564"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HotBunz</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229230/HotBunz/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Premise</h2><br/>In a world where twerking is the only way to be respected in society, HotBunz is a game about how a new sport, the Bootylympics, allows the citizens of Buttopia to rise above the ranks by being as crass and show-boaty as they can.<br/><br/>The rules of the <strong>Bootylympics</strong> are as quirky as the Buttopians themselves. Participants must navigate through a series of challenges that showcase their ability to shimmy, shake, and twirl with unmatched finesse. From synchronized booty bouncing to gravity-defying farting, every move is meticulously judged by a panel of esteemed cheek connoisseurs.<br/><br/>Play as your favorite Buttopian in this physics-based 2D Platformer Party Game with your friends and claim all the glory. Always remember, Champion Buttopians always come dressed to kill.<br/><br/><br/>- Play Solo to collect as many coins and buy character skins<br/>- Play against friends in different game modes to really show them who's who<br/>- Fart Fire (Pretty cool, we know)<br/>- Dress your Buttopian up to show up and show off!<br/>- Most Importantly, <strong>HAVE FUN!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Modes</h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Solo</h2>Navigate through varying obstacle courses to collect keys and gold coins in a series of increasingly complex levels.<h2 class="bb_tag">VS (King Of The Hill)</h2>Everybody's your enemy, claim the flag and hold on to it for as long as you can while dodging those other loser Buttopians<h2 class="bb_tag">Co-Op (Capture The Flag)</h2>Play with a team member against an opposing team by capturing as many of their flags as you can. <br/><br/><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/SpaceSaladZA" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229230/extras/Steam_Twitter_Banner.png?t=1701430859"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fve8pCkwRth" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229230/extras/Steam_Discord_Banner.png?t=1701430859"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fspacesaladza" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229230/extras/Steam_Instagram_Banner.png?t=1701430859"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Controls XBOX</h2><br/>A - Fart<br/>B - SuperFart<br/>RT - Grapple<br/>LT - Steal Key From Player<br/>L Analog - Movement<h2 class="bb_tag">Keyboard</h2><br/>WASD - Movement <br/>R Shift - Grapple  <br/>Space Bar - Fart<br/>Next level -  Space Bar						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Arcade</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2430760/Family_Arcade/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2430760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">'Tis the season to be gaming 🎄</h2>Looking for a way to make your next game night or family gathering even more fun? Look no further than Family Arcade.<br/>Our jam-packed collection is the ultimate stress reliever, guaranteed to bring out your inner child and have you laughing all night long.<h2 class="bb_tag">Make your holiday season unforgettable with our selection of games that are sure to get everyone into the Christmas spirit 🎅 </h2>Our games are perfect for all ages and skill levels, so everyone can join in on the fun. From classic party games to the latest hits, Family Arcade has something for everyone:<br/><br/>🎲 Scavenger Hunt is tailored for young minds.<br/>🎲 Pop the Pumpkin is a great game for teens who are looking for a fun and more challenging experience.<br/>🎲 Hyperdrive is crafted for mature players seeking an adrenaline-fueled experience.<br/>🎲 Wordsmith is designed to appeal to seniors who are looking for a fun and mentally stimulating activity.<br/><br/>In addition to our wide selection of Christmas games, our Home screen also features over an hour of Christmas songs to get everyone in the holiday mood!<h2 class="bb_tag">Perfect for family game nights or solo holiday cheer, this pack will bring hours of fun and nostalgia to your home!</h2> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat On The Desktop</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674420/Cat_On_The_Desktop/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Game Content</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>  Cats with 10 different skin types.<br/></li><li>  Hang up and interact with your mouse operation.</li></ul><br/><strong>Game Controls</strong><br/>Double click on the cat's head to pop up a menu; Can set whether to interact or not; Whether to place at the top; Switch skin.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nightscape City</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2673720/Nightscape_City/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/buildClubSteam.png?t=1701425173"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/movie_034_2.gif?t=1701425173"><br/><br/>Improve your club with various items. Place objects on <strong>Isometric Grid</strong> based plane. <br/><br/><strong><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Speakers<br/></li><li>Mixers<br/></li><li>Counters<br/></li><li>Lights<br/></li><li>Dance Tubes<br/></li><li>Furnitures<br/></li><li>Walls<br/></li><li>Seperators<br/></li><li>Floors</li></ul></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/CustomizeSteam.png?t=1701425173"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/ezgif.com-gif-maker__2_.gif?t=1701425173"><br/><br/>Increase the luxury level of your club to satisfy your customers. Design your club with fancy dance floor, different types of lights, build rooms and declare as VIP. Sometimes there may be fights, sometimes people may not like the type of music. Some people prefer techno music but some prefer trance. You can also upload your own music to music playlist. It's your job to take care of all this.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/manageSteam.png?t=1701425173"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/ezgif.com-gif-maker.gif?t=1701425173"><br/><br/>Hire or fire an employees to manage your club. Higher skill requires higher management skill. Your customers want quality service.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/unlockDirnkSteam.png?t=1701425173"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/ezgif.com-gif-maker__1_.gif?t=1701425173"><br/><br/>Unlock various drinks. Some people wants exclusive cocktails, some of them want expensive.<br/><br/><strong><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Juice<br/></li><li>Beer<br/></li><li>Coctail<br/></li><li>Wine<br/></li><li>Tequila<br/></li><li>Rum<br/></li><li>Vodka<br/></li><li>Gin<br/></li><li>Whiskey</li></ul></strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/customEventsSteam.png?t=1701425173"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/ezgif.com-gif-maker__3_.gif?t=1701425173"><br/><br/>Prepare unforgettable nights for your customers by organizing special events. Increase your popularity with concept parties.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeX</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684650/CodeX/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							CodeX is an atmospheric adventure game that doesn't have any hints, in-game marker, quest log or savepoint.<br/><br/>The story is told through Environmental Storytelling and the player has to find out for himself how to progress by using or moving objects and solving small puzzles.<br/><br/>The game is developed by a <strong>very small</strong> Indie Developer on <strong>Unreal Engine 5</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Features</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Environmental Storytelling<br/></li><li>Thrilling Story<br/></li><li>Atmospheric Gameplay<br/></li><li>No Savepoint <br/></li><li>No In-Game Marker How To Progress</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Legend of Ogorets #3: Kikimora</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2577090/The_Legend_of_Ogorets_3_Kikimora/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2577090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are aboard a ship headed straight for the center of the galaxy. The Legend of Ogorets is a series featuring mature, action-packed, character-driven adventures in post-apocalyptic settings. Your choices matter. #3 is the adventure of Kikimora, a mutant creature tortured inside her own home wherever she rests for longer than a little whilst on a migratory path to escape danger she found inside a prison society. The only problem is, everywhere is dangerous for her. Average read time: 50-60 minutes. Some readers may find this content disturbing.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infected: Outpost</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2616040/Infected_Outpost/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2616040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">SUMMARY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2616040/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif.gif?t=1701422120"><br/><strong>INFECTED: OUTPOST</strong> is a 2-12 player social deduction horror game inspired by The Thing, which will test your wits and teamwork. You and your friends are stranded and must work together to escape. However, one of you is infected, and they can shapeshift into their victims. Gather resources, uncover the traitor, and race against time for a thrilling and heart-pounding experience. Will you work together to survive, or will you succumb to the infection?<h2 class="bb_tag">PLAYERS AND NPCs</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2616040/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__2_.gif?t=1701422120"><br/>Each map has a set number of characters. Each character is controlled by either a player or an NPC. To blend in with the NPCs, remember that they walk in straight lines, and cannot run or pick up items.<h2 class="bb_tag">HOW TO WIN</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2616040/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__1_.gif?t=1701422120"><br/><strong>HUMANS</strong><br/>DISINFECTION: Kill the infected player.<br/>ESCAPE: At least one human player escapes the outpost. Each extract has different requirements for fuel, keys, and maps. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2616040/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__3_.gif?t=1701422120"><br/><strong>INFECTED</strong><br/>ASSIMILATION: Kill all human players.<br/>GENERATOR SHUTDOWN: The generator timer reaches zero and the humans freeze to death and the infected wins. Prevent the humans from increasing the time by refueling the generator.<h2 class="bb_tag">TIPS</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2616040/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__4_.gif?t=1701422120"><br/>- The Infected is an alien threat that shapeshifts into its victims.<br/>- The only way to tell if someone is infected is if they cannot shoot the gun.<br/>- The Infected cannot attack while holding an item.<br/>- Items such as keys, flares, fuel, and weapons are randomly placed in chests across the map.<br/>- When you run, your footsteps will be heard. NPCs don't run. Try to blend in.<br/>- When you die, you can spectate the game. Use A and D to switch between players.<br/>- We recommend using any VOIP program to communicate with other players.<h2 class="bb_tag">RULES</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2616040/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__5_.gif?t=1701422120"><br/><strong>- Don't talk when you're dead.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">FUTURE CONTENT</h2>Even after the release of Infected: Outpost, we plan to add even more content to the game, but this will only be possible with enough support from you guys &lt;3<br/>- The return of proximity chat.<br/>- More game modes.<br/>- More maps based on other classic horror films (Alien, The Descent, I Am Legend, and more!) with their own unique items, objectives, and twists on the gameplay.<br/>- Randomized skills and weaknesses for the Infected.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idle Progress</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2685770/Idle_Progress/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2685770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Idle Progress - A free idle game where your task is to produce as many resources as possible, improve your weapons and armor for good attacks, create good fishing rods for a good catch and get legendary stuff by completing legendary quests.<br/><br/>You can either just farm by upgrading your production or equip a weapon and armor to start fighting for better resources, better crafts and to earn the <strong>LEGENDARY ITEMS!</strong><br/><br/>- Over 4 epic legendary quests to complete<br/>- Build infrastructure with resources to increase population <br/>- Try your self at science to create interesting creatures<br/>- Increase your Game Skill by selling/crafting/melting stuff<br/>- Spend some time unboxing treasures to get cool rare items<br/>- Or you can simply relax while you are fishing						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ARMARDISP</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2495970/The_ARMARDISP/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Congratulations on acquiring your Articulated Mobile At-Range Demolition Integration Solutions Platform!<br>
<br>
From a safe distance, launch projectiles at an increasingly unlikely series of constructions to bring them down. The fewer projectiles you need to do it and the more you bring down, the better you did. <br>
<br>
Complete jobs more efficiently to unlock new areas, and become the ARMARDISP operator you have always dreamed of!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pestilence</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2639350/Pestilence/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Pestilence</strong> is a first-person stealth game in which you play as the Lord of the Pestilence, a betrayed God who seeks revenge against his brothers.<br/>To accomplish this, you will need to kill your brothers' <i>Judges</i>, the ruling caste of the city of Trumana. You will traverse the town's shadows as a malevolent force, using your uncanny ability to possess and sow chaos between its people. <br/><br/><strong>FEATURES</strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Find your next host</strong></h2>Take advantage of your possession powers to infiltrate Trumana's souls, becoming the puppeteer of their destiny. Each citizen has access to certain locations depending on their archetype.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639350/extras/gif.gif?t=1701419593"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Infiltrate and reclaim what is yours</strong></h2>Experience heart-pounding stealth gameplay where you use a diverse set of abilities to outsmart your siblings' relentless followers. Create distractions with the infection, scan your surroundings with the pulse, get into hard-to-reach areas by teleporting. Combine these skills to find new ways to overcome each situation.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639350/extras/gif2.gif?t=1701419593"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Find how your legacy has changed</strong></h2>Play as the villain and delve into the depths of Trumana's dark past, where ancient conflicts and sibling rivalries shape the present.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639350/extras/gif3.gif?t=1701419593"><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639350/extras/UTADSTEAM5.png?t=1701419593"><br/>This game is a university project by videogame students at U-tad.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only Up Samarkand</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2649380/Only_Up_Samarkand/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2649380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Only up Samarkand is a parkour game where speed is important.<br>
Strive to reach the top, overcoming a variety of dynamic obstacles.<br>
One mistake and back to the beginning...<br>
Made in Uzbekistan						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Dear Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1071440/Our_Dear_Kingdom/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1071440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Raise your island from a small village to a big kingdom!<br>
<br>
Your decisions will shape the future of  our dear kingdom!<br>
<br>
You will start with an island with few resources and no buildings. Decision after decision you will have to create buildings, gather resources and manage your population!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPIC PIZZA</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2699630/EPIC_PIZZA/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2699630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							EPIC PIZZA - The People of Calzonia are hungry for Pizza. You have to Race against Time to get it to them. <br>
<br>
What if there was an Action/Adventure Movie about Delivering Pizzas and You Were the Star?<br>
Well, Now You can find out!<br>
<br>
This is a fun and challenging Race Game.<br>
You have to Deliver Wave after Wave of Pizzas before the Clock Runs Out!<br/>
<br/>
See the Game Features Below:<br/>
<br/>
- Deliver Lots and Lots of Pizzas, but, Don't run out of Time!<br/>
<br/>
- Get rid of a Ninja Gang!<br/>
<br/>
- Enter a Race!<br/>
<br/>
- Go on a Mission!<br/>
<br/>
- Cool Minimap System!<br/>
<br/>
- Extra Bonus Challenge: Hidden in one of the Buildings is a Special Easter Egg. <br/>
Can You Find it?<br/>
<br/>
* NOTE: Don't Fall into the Water or You will have to start all over again. *						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joy Life 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2649230/Joy_Life_3/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2649230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2649230/extras/形象图片.png?t=1701417750"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game introduction</h2>You have just joined the 100% Hotel. Joy is a popular person in the underground dance party. She is very beautiful and takes good care of you.<br/>However, she and Ovie have a very good relationship, and they often get tired of being together, but recently, because of you, the two have begun to show signs of loosening up.<br/>You just occasionally dance, chat, and hold hands with Joy for a drink.<br/>"Oh, I really didn't expect Sister Ovie to be really angry..."<br/>"...don't pay attention to her"<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>Joy Life 3 is still a casual flop game. In the game, players need to find two cards with the same picture and successfully eliminate them. If the cards on the flop are inconsistent, the cards will not change. If they are the same picture, they will be eliminated. When all the cards in the picture are eliminated, that is You can enter the next level!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soulknight Survivor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2414900/Soulknight_Survivor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414900/extras/banner_new_small.png?t=1701417746"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414900/extras/header_survive.png?t=1701417746"><br/>Fight against hordes of enemies and collect their souls to gain special soulpower attacks. <br/>Try to survive against various monsters for 30 minutes on each of the 5 challenging maps.<br/>You can aim your weapon in all directions with your mouse or the right stick on your gamepad.<br/>But keep your stamina in mind, each swing and dodge drains a part of it. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414900/extras/steamgif2.gif?t=1701417746"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414900/extras/header_level.png?t=1701417746"><br/>Level up your character with the collected souls. <br/>Souls are not just used to fill your soulpower bar and unlock powerful attacks inside an area. <br/>You can also use them to level up your stamina, strength, health and stamina regeneration on the long term. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414900/extras/header_loot.png?t=1701417746"><br/>Loot chests to get new weapons and armor. Enemies drop random loot chests with tasty resources and procedurally generated weapons and armor. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414900/extras/loot.png?t=1701417746"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414900/extras/header_craft.png?t=1701417746"><br/>Mine stones and fell trees to gather resources. Craft powerful weapons and armor at the forge with the collected resources. <br/>Increase your blacksmith skill to become a master blacksmith! <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414900/extras/header_build.png?t=1701417746"><br/>Upgrade your hometown to increase your resource storage, improve the forge and more. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414900/extras/upgrade.png?t=1701417746"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414900/extras/header_features.png?t=1701417746"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Directional combat system<br/></li><li>Soulpowers<br/></li><li>Skill system<br/></li><li>Resource gathering<br/></li><li>Crafting system<br/></li><li>Loot chests<br/></li><li>5 challenging levels with 4 difficulties each<br/></li><li>Earnable medals<br/></li><li>Achievements<br/></li><li>Upgradable hometown </li></ul><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FMHsea9A" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2414900/extras/header_discord.png?t=1701417746"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Garden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2644670/Data_Garden/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2644670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A text-less comic-game hybrid about data, interaction and digital identity. In this click &amp; click adventure you will have a single button to advance in the story: a virtual routine of a content consumer who lives their day through different platforms that harvest their data.<br>
<br>
This data will end up reflected in a garden, the Data Garden. A growing ecosystem where everything endures. A reflection of your digital self that knows more about you than yourself.<br>
<br>
This is the debut game of the narrative studio Shaman Garage. They use the constrains of only using one button as input and no text to bring us this experimental story driven puzzle game. Estimated play time 10-15 minutes.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brush Burial</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2676540/Brush_Burial/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Brush Burial is a lite immersive sim focused on atmosphere, exploration, and surreal storytelling.<br/>You are Fennel, a lithe and limber thief with a suite of unique movement tricks and combat abilities. You are on a mission that transcends the self-serving crimes of your past--to kill the Witch God Yenneloch, and free the woods of her uncanny influence. In return, your own god has promised you a sacred rite of eternal rest. Unless you have other ideas...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676540/extras/yenneloch.gif?t=1701417890"><br/><br/>FEATURES:<br/><br/>- abstract and non-linear levels that allow for exploration and satisfying problem-solving.<br/><br/>- meaningful environmental interactions--grab any object you want; play with fire; use the weapons of slain enemies against their allies.<br/><br/>- an expressive movement system with responsive and precise controls.<br/><br/>- raw but complex melee combat which rewards aggression and speed.<br/><br/>- grimy visuals with a dark science-fantasy slant.<br/><br/>- a roguish array of crooks, scoundrels, and miscreants to befriend, beguile, or otherwise.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2676540/extras/lochlurren_gif.gif?t=1701417890"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HoloParade</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2647230/HoloParade/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">A lively parade with hololive VTubers and mascot characters!</h2><br/>"HoloParade" is a fan game of hololive and the first title to serve as a test case for "holo Indie". Collect, nurture, and enjoy watching your favorite characters! It's a 2D tower defense game that offers depth, strategy, and can also be enjoyed casually.<br/><br/>What is "holo Indie"?:<br/>It is a general term for a game brand for derivative work games, produced using the "game creator support program" with the aim of co-creating with fans and creators of hololive Production around the world.<h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 1: Simple Yet Deep, Lively Battles</h2>The basic system is a classic 2D tower defense game where you summon characters from your base and march them forward to destroy the enemy's base to win. While the controls are simple, the gameplay is profoundly deep. With over 65 characters, each possessing a variety of abilities like ally healing support and self-destruct attacks, skillful combination and flexible formation are key to enjoying the game.<br/><br/>Additionally, there's an element inspired by parades called the 'Symphony Effect,' where various effects are activated based on the musical instruments played by the characters in march. This adds further strategic depth to the formation of your parade squad and the order of their summoning.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Battle.gif?t=1701417555"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 2: Comprehensive Development Elements</h2>In addition to leveling up and limit breaking, there is a 'Skill' system that allows you to add special abilities not available through regular development. Since you can add up to three types of skills to each character and select them carefully, you can enjoy a unique development process! Furthermore, since you can reset levels and get a full refund of the coins spent, it allows for more freedom in restructuring formations and character development.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Skill_ENG.gif?t=1701417555"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 3: No Gacha Purchases, No Stamina System</h2>The scout gacha, which allows you to acquire characters, can be used by consuming tickets obtained within the game, with no additional purchases required. Also, as there is no stamina system, you are not bound by time and can play as much as you like, whenever you like.<br/><br/>Moreover, the scout gacha allows you to choose from two randomly selected character candidates, enabling players to make selections based on their strategy or preference rather than leaving it entirely to chance.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Gacha_ENG.gif?t=1701417555"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 4: Take a Break with Various Talents and Mini-Games in the Office</h2>When you return to the office, the home screen, you'll be greeted by newly recorded voice lines from Harusaki Nodoka, a staff member of hololive. In the office, talents from hololive may also make appearances, and you might witness some unexpected interactions.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Home_ENG.png?t=1701417555"><br/><br/>Additionally, mini-games with entirely different gameplay from the main story are implemented. These games allow you to collect coins necessary for character strengthening. At the initial release, a mini-game titled "Hurry Up! Miko-Chi!" is available, where Sakura Miko (a VTuber affiliated with hololive) who overslept, dashes at full speed towards her destination while avoiding obstacles. More mini-games are planned to be added in future updates.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/RunMikoti.gif?t=1701417555"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XBPlay</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693120/XBPlay/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							Experience gaming freedom like never before with XBPlay — effortlessly stream your console to your device and immerse yourself in your favorite titles anytime, anywhere.<br>
<br>
Features: <br>
- 1080p and 720p Stream Quality.<br>
- Multiple Clarity Boost Algorithms.<br>
- Simulated and Direct Mouse and Keyboard Support.<br>
- Connected Controllers and Touch Input.<br/>
- Many Customizable Settings.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age of Advent</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2679690/Age_of_Advent/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2679690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>This is a free unofficial fangame based on the members of Hololive -Advent-</i><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>WELCOME TO THE AGE OF ADVENT!</strong></h2><br/>Play four minigames based on the members of Hololive -Advent-!<h2 class="bb_tag">Bijem'd</h2><br/>The pickaxes are coming! Help the Moai escape before they get here! Clear the path to the bottom by clicking on groups of matching colors, and rack up combos by saving groups of Moai quickly!<h2 class="bb_tag">The Demon Of Sound and Soup</h2><br/>Is a dance club the best place to make a demonic soup? Maybe not, but it's close enough to a kitchen for Nerissa! Move to the beat of the music and round up <span class="bb_strike">partygoers</span> ingredients. Get the conga line as big as you can, then drop them off in Nerissa's pot! And watch out for the F-bombs. Someone really needs to watch their language...<h2 class="bb_tag">We're Abaubaut to Crash!</h2><br/>Fuwawa and Mococo can't find the brakes! Control both of them at the same time in this multitasking infinite minecart level. Collect gems, avoid pits, bonk Pero, and work together to last as long as you can as the track keeps getting faster and more dangerous!<h2 class="bb_tag">Archival Survival</h2><br/>Farming in the middle of the night? Do plants usually sprout books? Why couldn't they put the seeds next to the water? Well, nevertheless, plant and harvest as many crops as you can tonight. And remember: DON'T. LET. THEM. SEE. YOU.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Cats In Amusement Park</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2563350/Hidden_Cats_In_Amusement_Park/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2563350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2563350/extras/youximiaoshu05.png?t=1701406589"><br/>This is a casual and relaxing hidden object game.<br/>Find cute cats in the amusement park.Can you find them? <br/>That's right，there are a few on the carousel.<br/>Meow Meow...Kittens are calling you！<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2563350/extras/miaoshu04.png?t=1701406589"><br/><br/>· Hand drawn cartoon minimalist style<br/>· More than 600 Cats<br/>· With different postures and expressions<br/>· Explore the entire amusement park<br/>· Some interesting interactive elements<br/>· Drag and zoom the screen view<br/>· Relax and find all the cats<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2563350/extras/youximiaoshu03.png?t=1701406589"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pen Pals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682460/Pen_Pals/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2682460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Things are going HAYwire down at the farm! Corral a herd of particularly round barnyard friends back into the pen. When two matching animals bump into each other, you'll find an even larger animal in their place. Things get crowded quickly, so get a mooove on in Pen Pals!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over a dozen different stages, with unique looks and wacky changes to the game!<br/></li><li>Chain your merges to score extra points. Rack up that combo and impress those animals!<br/></li><li>Three target scores to beat for each level. Go for the gold!<br/></li><li>At least ten adorably round barnyard friends, plus one very judgmental donkey <br/></li><li>Unlock secret goodies as you play! What mysteries await you?</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Castle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1492910/Cloud_Castle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1492910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							《Cloud Castle》It is a strategic tower defense game that builds your defense route by placing and upgrading on a grid map, resisting waves of monsters.<br>
<br>
Map - a battle scene constructed from stylized plots, using turrets to plan the monster's path<br>
<br>
Ores - There are a small number of special ore parcels in each map that can be collected by placing mining caves<br>
<br>
Talent - Every battle will accumulate experience and increase levels, and each level will receive talent points that can be used to unlock more turrets and additional bonuses<br/>
<br/>
Enhancement - Using the collected minerals to strengthen your turret can allow you to achieve higher limits in combat						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaperone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2679590/Chaperone/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2679590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>WARNING:</strong> This game may trigger seizures in people with photosensitive epilepsy. It may cause heart palpitations. It is left to the player's discretion.<br/><br/>"HOW MUCH PATIENCE MAY REQUIRE TO COMPANY A DEAD BODY?"<br/><br/><strong>IMPORTANT NOTE:</strong> The game focuses on exploration and slowly builds tension to create a deeper and more meaningful experience. The story of the game can cause a lot of discomfort as it is supported by light, loud and sudden sounds. Take into consideration that it makes you feel a lot of fear and it is a psychologically difficult game.<br/>CHAPERONE is a first-person psychological horror game.<br/><br/><strong>Environment</strong><br/>In the game where we start our duty as a police officer, the police house consists of two different houses that we will later investigate.<br/><br/><strong>About The Game</strong><br/>In this game, inspired by real events in 2001, your aim is to solve a murder whose cause is unknown, become a companion for the body found in the house at the time, and reach the truth that disturbs the dead body.<br/><br/><strong>Supernatural entities</strong><br/>Paranormal entities that are constantly unknown where and when they will appear.<br/><br/><strong>Developer's comment about the game</strong><br/>Chaperone can leave an impact on your psychology. We recommend that people who are afraid of the dark, have heart disease, or are afraid of being alone should not play alone.<br/><br/><strong>IMPORTANT NOTE:</strong><br/>Chaperone was inspired by a real event that took place in Munich, Germany in 2001. If research is done, you can still find issues similar to this story today...						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalypse Party</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2351560/Apocalypse_Party/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">The moment of "Apocalypse" approaches, this time... ...you fight for yourself!</h2><br/><strong>「Apocalypse Party」</strong> is distinct from the former 「Project Zero」<br/>In this installment, you will delve deeper into this long-standing battle, with the story gradually becoming incredible! Time travel? Apocalypse? Saving the world? You will face many more unknown challenges... ...<br/>But it still retains our beloved RogueLike + mowing-down-enemies combo, and you will face this catastrophe online with your friends (of course, you can also face it alone)!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Engaging and Deep Mechanics ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT01_Skills_EN.gif?t=1701407236"><br/><br/><strong>Talent pool expanded to 450! And most of them are mechanics that can change the course of battle</strong><br/>Additionally, there are:<br/>- Hundreds of distinct ranged and melee weapons!<br/>- A plethora of divine ultimate skills!<br/>- 35 varied hero characters, hundreds of unique hero skills<br/>The richness has increased by <strong>more than 10 times compared to the former installment</strong>! Can you build the strongest combo?<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Supports Multiplayer, shall we join the hunting party tonight? ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT02_MutiplePlayerMode_EN.gif?t=1701407236"><br/><br/>Support <strong>up to 3</strong> multiplayer online! <br/>Massive hordes of zombies, exhilarating mowing-down action, why enjoy it alone?<br/>Imagine the joy of roaming through a sea of zombies with your friends!<br/>Call them, support each other, move forward or retreat together, survive here!<br/><strong>Of course, we kindly remind you, a "friendship-ends" scenario is not excluded :)</strong><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ You crave some real challenge, don't you? ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT04_Boss_EN.gif?t=1701407236"><br/><br/>In this game, you will face the ultimate challenge.<br/><strong>9 highly challenging Bosses!</strong><br/>Only rapid growth can help you withstand the fierce attacks from the Bosses, accept the challenge, defeat them, and show them who’s boss now!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Perhaps we can do some time traveling! ■</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT05_Medivel_EN.gif?t=1701407236"><br/><br/>A brand new storyline takes you into this familiar yet strange world, continuing a tale of redemption amidst time traveling:<br/>The tragic death of loved ones<br/>The desperate nuclear explosion<br/>The eerie rebirth<br/>The deathly quiet town<br/>The dark dungeons<br/>... ...<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ We are continuously focusing on your gameplay experience! ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT03_Combat_EN.gif?t=1701407236"><br/><br/>We have keenly listened to the feedback from the players of our former installment, reworked the combat system of the game, continuously bringing more fluid gaming experiences to players.<br/>-<i>Mix and use combat methods like melee weapons, firearms, spells, summoning, witchcraft... ...</i>! They will bring you a fun experience.<br/>-<i>Drive vehicles, summon planes, dragon flying, use otherworldly ninjutsu, even use the mysterious Dual-vector Foi</i>, and more easter eggs await your exploration.<br/>-This game encourages an online experience, but undoubtedly, the single-player part can still experience all the systems and joy of this game.<br/><br/>Smooth operation (handling) is also an important part we continuously focus on！<br/>We have made the game’s operation &amp; flow experience more user-friendly.<br/><strong>Easy to get started, yet "easy to learn, hard to master"!</strong><br/><br/><strong>"Since the apocalypse is here, join us for the last revelry."</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/Library_Hero_EN.jpg?t=1701407236"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yeah! Wow! Hey!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2622540/Yeah_Wow_Hey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Tired of endless climbing? Congratulation you have a new option! This is a high difficulty 3D platform jumping game. The high demand for directional control coupled with minimal room for error makes for more challenging levels. Reaching the top is no easy task.Don't expect any edge climbing to give you any hope to survive, in this game, there are no such lucky ways. All you can do is move, jump, and sprint.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622540/extras/demo01.gif?t=1701398622"><br/>Sounds simple, right? Different from traditional platform jumping games, the control of the view plays a crucial role. The view is closely related to each of your operations and determines your moving direction, sprinting direction, and bouncing or propelling direction. I bet no one has ever thought of playing a platform jumping game like a FPS, relying on precise mouse movement. In addition to this, traditional platform jumping games require precision in timing jumps, avoiding moving obstacles, and taking advantage of sprint distance and direction in order to reach the next platform. These features are all emphasized in this game. Fully utilizing special surfaces for bouncing or propelling is your only way to reach the other side.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622540/extras/demo02.gif?t=1701398622"><br/>Do these blue and green bubbles remind you of another widely acclaimed game? That's right, feel the challenge in a 3D environment, an extension of a dimension. The level is full of various usable mechanisms, so don't rush to take your steps. Carefully observe and judge, taking advantage of these mechanisms, or even shortcuts, are essential for masters.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622540/extras/demo03.gif?t=1701398622"><br/>Don't worry, not that cruel. The game has checkpoints, but not saves. A little mistake will only cost a bit of time. What, you just want to show off having the shortest time? Well, never mind. Take it from me, a true champion who jumps to the top in one breath does not need the lifeboat of saves.<br/>As for the game graphics...what can I say...the trailer and screenshots are hanging right there above.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622540/extras/demo05.png?t=1701398622"><br/>Supports up to 8 players online（maybe more in the future）, will you regard others as competitors or partners? I believe everyone will have a different answer.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622540/extras/multiplayer.png?t=1701398622"><br/>Enjoy!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-4 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">4-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with three other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1701398130"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1701398130"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1701398130"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1701398130"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1701398130"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1701398130"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoeMoni Land</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2651080/MoeMoni_Land/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game tells the story of the creepy great demons from the "Night Parade of One Hundred Demons"... having a happy childhood?!<br/>Hey there! Just how adorable can young monster forms be? In "Monster Tot Kindergarten," you can see the young forms of 21 well-known monsters like Tengu, Shuten Doji, Tamamo no Mae, and more. They possess incredible skills yet have their own unique quirks. You and your friends can play as these little monsters and put on a thrilling and fun social deduction drama.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651080/extras/配图1_-631.png?t=1701397324"><br/><br/>"MoeMoni Land" is a social deduction game with a gameplay foundation based on deduction. It blends a Japanese-style world of monsters and folklore, creating a system with three camps: "students," "demons," and "neutrals." You can choose from 21 adorable little monster characters, each with 17 different talented professions, making the already suspenseful school more strategic. Play with 6-12 players online, complete mission goals with your friends from the same camp, and strive for victory together!<h2 class="bb_tag">◆ 21 Super Popular Cute Monsters ◆</h2>21 incredibly popular monster kids, transformed into adorable, chibi-style kindergarten children. Each little monster has unique skills with gorgeous interactive effects when using their abilities.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651080/extras/配图2-600.gif?t=1701397324"><h2 class="bb_tag">◆ Explore Diverse and Fun Missions ◆</h2>Throughout the game, there are creative mini-games to discover, which can be triggered as little monster characters. These mini-games are full of creative fun and are incredibly engaging.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651080/extras/配图3-600.gif?t=1701397324"><h2 class="bb_tag">◆ Students or Demons - Three Major Camps ◆</h2>Students, demons, and neutrals, three major camps with a gathering of experts! Will you be a righteous student, a sly little villain, or a mischievous prankster? It's your choice!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651080/extras/配图4-600.gif?t=1701397324"><h2 class="bb_tag">◆ Righteous or Sly - Various Professions ◆</h2>With 17 different professions, initiate the most exciting deduction party. Win as you like, start a meeting with a single tap, and the rest depends on your fantastic acting skills!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651080/extras/配图5-600.gif?t=1701397324"><h2 class="bb_tag">◆ Text or Voice - Two-way Discussion ◆</h2>The game supports both voice and text discussions, offering diverse social gameplay options. Overcome social anxiety in an instant!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651080/extras/配图6-600.gif?t=1701397324"><br/><br/>⚑ Scan to follow Monster Tot Kindergarten's official Bilibili &amp; Weibo accounts for the latest information ⚑<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651080/extras/POPO20231109-142932.png?t=1701397324"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651080/extras/yzyzy-600.png?t=1701397324"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stimmings</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1910950/Stimmings/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1910950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A strategic rouge like simulation in the fantasy genre. <br/>Lead your villagers 'Stimmings' against the relentless forces of entropy in this cellular automata simulation where the parameters of the sim are altered every run.<br/><br/>The only resource you have are your villagers, and each villager takes up a cell in the simulation.<br/>Due to unfortunate medical circumstances, the villagers are required to be stimming themselves at all times and they cannot stop moving.<br/><br/>Build up your Stimmings and defend them against the enemies and work towards a limited number of castles on the map.<br/><br/>Defeat each Legendary Opponent in these castles to obtain relics that will be vital for survivial in the next levels.  <br/><br/>If you find a portal squeeze as many Stimmings inside as you can to ensure the next round is not impossible to navigate.<br/><br/>You the player usually end up balancing your home economy with refreshing farms, navigating environmental hazards, and the offensive required to overtake an enemy structure.<br/><br/>If you find the modern world unstimulating and consider yourself completely desensitized to any information coming from a screen and speakers, this game is for you.  Designed to swallow hours of your day and being left with no real recollection of what happened or where you are at the end of rounds.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1910950/extras/AboutThisSImulationText.png?t=1701395928"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Procedural map generation from one of three biomes determines the initial land scape and resource/hazards locations<br/></li><li> Every map has a <strong>portal</strong> that requires a certain amount of your Stimmings to activate (this generates the next level)<br/></li><li> Stimmings (villagers) throw themselves onto blueprints you place to create structures that can span many squares<br/></li><li> Unique relics provide relief in tight or stressful spots<br/></li><li> Get to level 10!  <br/></li><li> Stim! <br/></li><li> MAINTAIN SANITY</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
