<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>MechWarrior 5: Mercenaries - Solaris Showdown</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2782050/MechWarrior_5_Mercenaries__Solaris_Showdown/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							SOLARIS SHOWDOWN<br/>Fresh off a successful mission for the notorious Mercenary Star, Mason and crew journey to the Hardcore system where they collide with 'Mech pilot Duncan Fisher embarking on a quest to secure a spot in the FedCom Unification Tournament. Forming an unlikely alliance, Mason and Fisher traverse the shadows of Solaris, engage in harrowing 'Mech duels, and race against the clock to save the day - a true Solaris Showdown.<br/><br/>Join Duncan Fisher in a race against time to thwart the overthrow of the Solaris Council, discover the new Loader King 'Mech, collect 11 new Gladiator 'Mech variants, select new weapons and equipment tailored for close-quarter engagements, and help save the very future of Solaris<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Assist Duncan Fisher on his zany adventures, and witness his ascension as the official and iconic Voice of Solaris<br/></li><li>Seek fortune and Fame with new Arena Missions and reward system<br/></li><li>Solaris Showdown adds the new Loader King 'Mech chassis with 6 variants, including the mighty Hero LDK-IDM 'Indomitable'<br/></li><li>Collect 11 new 'Mech variants designed specifically for the intense Gladiator-style combat of the BattleMech arenas<br/></li><li>Select from an array of new Gladiator-style weaponry and equipment<br/></li><li>Enhancements to MechLab, AI Improvements, and various other free QoL updates</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dune: Imperium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1689500/Dune_Imperium/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Header.png?t=1710364055"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body0_2.png?t=1710364055"><br/>Experience the ultimate blend of strategy and intrigue as you navigate the treacherous landscapes of Arrakis in the award-winning board game <i>Dune: Imperium</i>!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle online, locally with AI, or against the formidable House Hagal.<br/></li><li>Earn Achievements that showcase your prowess as a leader.<br/></li><li>Embark on more than a dozen Challenges that will test your wit and cunning.<br/></li><li>Compete for badges in the rotating Skirmish Mode where no two games are the same!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body1_2.png?t=1710364055"><br/>Arrakis. Dune. Desert Planet. Raise your banner above the vast wasteland before you. As the Great Houses of the Landsraad marshal their forces and their spies, whom will you influence, and whom will you betray? A tyrannical Emperor. The secretive Bene Gesserit. The shrewd Spacing Guild. The ferocious Fremen of the Deep Desert. The power of the Imperium can be yours, but war is not the only way to claim it.<br/><br/><i>Dune: Imperium</i> blends deck-building and worker placement in a deeply thematic new strategy game where the fate of the Empire hangs on your decisions. Will you seek political allies or rely upon military might? Economic strength or subtle intrigues? A council seat… or a sharpened blade? The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body2_2.png?t=1710364055"><br/>In <i>Dune: Imperium</i>, you'll step into the role of one of the leaders of the Great Houses of the Imperium in a struggle to control the planet Arrakis and the invaluable Spice it provides.<br/><br/>The game plays out in a series of ten rounds, each of which is defined by a new Conflict on the surface of the planet; some award critical resources, and some provide Victory Points that will propel you to dominance. But choose your battles wisely: spread your forces too thin, and you'll find your enemies growing too strong to oppose.<br/><br/>Each round, you'll draw a hand of five cards from your deck, which will get stronger over the course of the game as you acquire new cards. Each card can be played in one of two ways: To send an Agent out into the Imperium to gather resources, or to Reveal at the end of the round to purchase new powerful cards. You must maintain a careful balance to get the most of the resources available to you. How will you find your path?<br/><br/>As your game progresses, you'll vie for Influence with four factions of the Imperium: The Emperor, the economically powerful Spacing Guild, the mysterious Bene Gesserit, and the ferocious Fremen of the deep deserts. Earning Influence among the various groups helps you to earn the Victory Points you need...but will you compete with your rivals for their favor, or abandon alliances to pursue other opportunities?<br/><br/>Many strategies are at your disposal, and many paths to victory. The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Footer.png?t=1710364055"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead by Daylight - All Things Wicked Chapter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2661270/Dead_by_Daylight__All_Things_Wicked_Chapter/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Main_Banner.gif?t=1710259123"><br/><br/>Dead by Daylight’s All Things Wicked delves into the depths of analog horror with <strong>new Killer, The Unknown</strong>, and <strong>new Survivor, Sable Ward</strong>. A new Map, <strong>Greenville Square</strong>, is available for all players. Purchasing this add-on unlocks 2 exclusive Cosmetics: <strong>The Unknown’s Garden Casual</strong> and <strong>Sable Ward’s Designer Corset</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Killer_Power.jpg?t=1710259123"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE UNKNOWN</h2>If you hear a soft voice crying out for help in the woods, stay the hell away. The true nature of The Unknown remains a mystery, barring one fatal certainty: to cross its path is to risk an unknowable fate.<br/><br/><strong>The Unknown’s Power: UVX (Unknown Venom X)</strong><br/><br/>Charge and launch a burst of UVX, which bounces once and creates a Blast Area upon impact. If they touch the Blast Area, they will become Weakened against your Power.   <br/>If a Survivor is Weakened, they will lose a Health State whenever they touch a Blast Area. Survivors can lose the Weakened status by successfully looking at The Unknown for a brief duration.<br/><br/><strong>Special Ability: Hallucinations</strong><br/><br/>During a Trial, The Unknown will intermittently create Hallucinations and leave them in its wake. The Unknown can highlight and teleport to any Hallucination, leaving behind a temporary Decoy version of itself. Survivors can Dispel Hallucinations, but only by staring at one while standing completely still. Weakened Survivors will take longer to Dispel a Hallucination, and any incomplete attempt will reveal their location through Killer Instinct. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Killer_Perks.jpg?t=1710259123"><br/><br/>The Unknown comes with <strong>3 new perks.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Unbound</h2>Unbound activates for a duration when a Survivor becomes injured. During this time, you’ll gain a brief speed boost whenever you Vault a Window.<h2 class="bb_tag">Unforeseen</h2>When you kick a Generator, your Terror Radius transfers to it for a duration. During this time, your Terror Radius increases and you become Undetectable.<h2 class="bb_tag">Undone</h2>Gain Tokens whenever a Survivor misses a Skill Check. When you damage a Generator, all Tokens will be consumed. For each Token consumed, the Generator loses 1% total progress and becomes blocked for 1 second.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Survivor_Perks.jpg?t=1710259123"><h2 class="bb_tag">SABLE WARD</h2>While some fear the darkness, Sable Ward embraces it. Fascinated by horror and drawn to all things wicked, Sable was among the few Survivors to willingly step into The Fog in search of her best friend Mikaela.<br/>Sable Ward comes with <strong>3 new perks.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Invocation: Weaving Spiders</h2>This Invocation can only be performed in the Basement and takes a considerable duration of time to complete. Survivors can see your Aura during the process and can join you, increasing the Invocation’s speed.  <br/>Once complete, all Survivors will gain a boost of Repair progress. On the other hand, you’ll be Injured and Broken for the remainder of the Trial.<h2 class="bb_tag">Strength in Shadows</h2>When in the basement, you can quickly heal without a Med-Kit. Afterward, the Killer’s Aura is briefly revealed.<h2 class="bb_tag">Wicked</h2>Gain the ability to successfully unhook yourself from Basement Hooks. When you successfully do so, the Killer’s Aura is briefly revealed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_New_Map.jpg?t=1710259123"><h2 class="bb_tag">NEW MAP: GREENVILLE SQUARE*</h2><br/>A slice of small-town Americana, long abandoned, long forgotten. Now, something wanders freely along the overgrown streets: a writhing creature responsible for a string of disappearances across the country.<br/>*This map is free for all players.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Exclusive_Item_Killer.jpg?t=1710259123"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXCLUSIVE CHAPTER KILLER ITEM: GARDEN CASUAL</h2>Her prize-winning peonies wilted and died without someone to care for them. The All Things Wicked Chapter includes an exclusive item for The Unknown, the <strong>Garden Casual Outfit</strong>, only available as part of the DLC. Please note that this item cannot be purchased separately.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2661270/extras/Chapter31_Exclusive_Item_Survivor.jpg?t=1710259123"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXCLUSIVE CHAPTER SURVIVOR ITEM: DESIGNER CORSET </h2>Once she saw it in the store window, she knew she had a reason to save her money. The All Things Wicked Chapter includes an exclusive item for Sable, the <strong>Designer Corset</strong>, only available as part of the DLC. Please note that this item cannot be purchased separately.<br/><br/><br/><i>If you’re seeing this, your fate has been sealed.</i> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contra: Operation Galuga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2235020/Contra_Operation_Galuga/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2235020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A new entry in the legendary Contra series is here! Contra: Operation Galuga is a thorough reimagining of the classic run-'n'-gun action game from the '80s, featuring modern graphics and sound, new stages, new enemies and bosses, new play mechanics, an updated weapons system, and explosive co-op combat for up to two players in Story Mode or four players in Arcade Mode!<br>
<br>
When the Red Falcon terrorist group takes over the Galuga Islands off the coast of New Zealand, elite Contra commandos Bill Rizer and Lance Bean springs into action, initiating an all-out war in which the fate of mankind hangs in the balance!<br>
<br>
Run, jump, and shoot your way through eight levels using a devastating arsenal - including the spread shot, laser, and homing missiles - now with stackable upgrades and awesome Overload abilities! The intense action is customizable with three difficulty settings plus a variety of additional challenge options. The true Contra legacy begins now!<br>
<br/>
Key Features:<br/>
•The original run-'n'-gun game is back, reimagined and more action-packed than ever!<br/>
•Attack aggressively across eight explosive stages! Infiltrate the jungle, ascend the waterfall, speed through an enemy base on a hovercycle, and more!<br/>
•Multiple playable characters with distinct abilities!<br/>
•Epic, screen-filling boss battles!<br/>
•New and fan-favorite weapons, now with stackable upgrades and incredible Overload abilities!<br/>
•Multiple difficulty options and a wealth of extra content						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMERHOUSE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2533960/SUMMERHOUSE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2533960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2533960/extras/summerhouse_new_store_page.gif?t=1709984408"><br/><br/>SUMMERHOUSE is a small-scale building game and a love letter to the feeling of long lost summer afternoons.<br/><br/>Craft a neighbourhood of tiny, beautiful lived-in homes in a variety of settings: the sea, the city, or the mountains. While there are some little secrets to uncover, there are no rules, and you can’t win or lose. Just chill out, build to your heart’s content and soak up the atmosphere.<br/><br/>If relaxation and creation are your thing, this is a game for you :)<br/><br/><i>Please keep in mind that this is a small game with no goals or challenges, created by a single person🙂</i> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORE BLASTERS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/BORE_BLASTERS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/BLAST.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_blast_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Blast your way through rocks and dirt with your machinegun drill. Carve through the ground to uncover precious ores and defeat menacing foes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/LOOT.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_loot_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Uncover ancient relics and artefacts hidden in the deep. Amass a fortune in rare gems &amp; ores.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/UPGRADE.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_mortar_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Invest in powerful upgrades and unlock new abilities, turning your humble gyrocopter into a fearsome force to be reckoned with.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/DISCOVER.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_discover_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Explore a diverse range of biomes, from treacherous volcanic caverns to lush overgrown underground forests, each with its own unique challenges and rewards.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/FEATURES.png?t=1709907021"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Intense mining action with fast-paced blasting<br/></li><li> Constant progress - even failed runs aren't punishing<br/></li><li> Diverse biomes to explore<br/></li><li> Purchase upgrades to overpower your gyrocopter<br/></li><li> Navigate the overworld to unlock new mine shafts<br/></li><li> Collect and loot rare gems, ores, and artefacts to upgrade your gear and abilities<br/></li><li> Endless replayability with procedurally generated levels</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_drones_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/><br/>Drawing inspiration from mining games like Motherload and Galactic Mining Corp, Bore Blasters takes the genre to the next level with high octane action and fast paced gameplay. Fans of digging and collecting will find plenty to love, while the addition of deadly enemies and mysterious artefacts will keep even the most seasoned miners on their toes.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/WL_arrow.gif?t=1709907021"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_missiles_frame.gif?t=1709907021"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Realm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1330000/Stolen_Realm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/GreenDragon.gif?t=1710364112"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TURN-BASED STRATEGY MEETS ACTION RPG IN THIS DUNGEON CRAWLING LOOTER</strong></h2><br/><br/>Stolen Realm is a <strong>simultaneous turn-based tactical dungeon crawling looter with action RPG elements</strong> where you control up to <strong>6 heroes, solo or through online co-op</strong>, venturing forth in adventures set in a high-fantasy, low-poly world. <br/><br/>Stolen Realm features an <strong>innovative turn-based combat system</strong> where <strong>simultaneous turns</strong> allow every team to take their actions at once, creating quick combat encounters that blend the tactical depth of titles like Divinity: Original Sin with the thrill of a fast-paced action RPG. Every battle scales based on the number of players involved, so you can easily jump in and out of the game even in the same playthrough!<br/> <br/>With a <strong>highly customisable class system</strong>, Stolen Realm allows you to create traditional RPG classes or break the mold to forge a unique champion of your own as you draw from a pool of hundreds of possible skills. Make a spell-slinging assassin, a priest born of frost, or a shadow-infused knight. Further customize your build by earning and reforging <strong>loot that truly changes the way you play</strong>: wield Abbadon the Soul Crusher, a mythic mace that raises slain enemies as skeletal warriors to fight for you, or unsheath the Bloodletter, a cursed sword that grants additional power at the cost of your lifeblood. D&amp;D-like events where attribute-based rolls will have permanent effects on your character add yet another layer to building a character that is truly your own. Anything is possible in this title that keeps compelling choices at the forefront of your experience.  <br/><br/>Keeping the core appeal of RPGs at its forefront, Stolen Realm ensures you spend all your time, fighting, building your characters and making compelling choices that determine your immediate path or effect your character, rather than getting bogged down in side quests and other RPG-bloat.   After each battle, pick your path between story events, resource gathering, shops and treasure rooms, until you get to the final boss of each <strong>procedurally generated adventure.</strong> If you’re up to a challenge, crank the difficulty up with <strong>6 different difficulty levels</strong> – or pick <strong>Hardcore Mode with permadeath</strong>, where every battle can be the last!<br/><br/>Also features <strong>Roguelike Mode</strong>, a fast paced version of the game where you can mix and match builds that are simply not possible in the traditional campaign!<br/><br/>Carve a place in history with your sword and magic. Rise to honor and glory in the battlefield. <strong>Recover the Stolen Realm.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/CycloneKick.gif?t=1710364112"><h2 class="bb_tag">PRAISE FOR STOLEN REALM</h2><br/>“The tactical depth of Divinity: Original Sin” - GamesRadar+<br/><br/>“we’re losing our evenings to… Stolen Realm” - TheXboxHub<br/><br/>“A gorgeous looking game” - PC Gamer<br/><br/>“You can be a fire warrior. You can be a healing necromancer. You can do all sorts of weird s**t.” - <strong>Sacriel</strong><br/><br/>“What I like about this game is it’s straight to the point. You just go in, you’re building your character, you’re getting items…and you just fight. There’s no bulls**t.” - <strong>Shroud</strong><br/><br/>“It’s rad” - <strong>Sequisha</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/Dwarven_Warmachine.gif?t=1710364112"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>KEY FEATURES</strong></h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play solo or with friends in up to 6 player online co-op, allowing you and your friends to wreak havoc amongst your foes<br/></li><li>Experience thrilling and fast-paced turn-based battles thanks to a simultaneous team turn system<br/></li><li>Full story campaign, roguelike mode and streamer mode<br/></li><li>Use over 300 skills in 10 distinct skill trees allowing for complete and flexible character customization<br/></li><li>Navigate hex-based battlefields where positioning is key due to battle shrines with special effects, exploding barrels and movable crates<br/></li><li>Find and loot over 700 unique items, fully customizable with modifiers, as you explore a wonderful world full of magic, secrets and unexpected dangers<br/></li><li>Co-op focused design keeps gameplay fast paced and strategic for up to 6 players <br/></li><li>Easy drop-in, drop-out design and automatic scaling that allows you to join or drop out mid-quest <br/></li><li>D&amp;D-like attribute-based rolls in special events that have permanent character effects<br/></li><li>Fight against over 200 types of enemies in battles that will be different every time: thanks to the Enemy Modifications feature, every creature you face on the battlefield will be unique<br/></li><li>A world that changes on each expedition, from frosty peaks guarded by the elusive Blue Dragon to overgrown jungles where the rock giants roam. <br/></li><li>Pick your path between battles, choosing where to go between story events, resource gathering, shops, fights, and treasure rooms until you get to the final boss of each adventure<br/></li><li>6 different difficulty levels<br/></li><li>Choose between Normal Mode and Hardcore Mode with permadeath if you want a real challenge!</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE 2K24</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2315690/WWE_2K24/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2315690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							FORTY YEARS OF WRESTLEMANIA<br>
<br>
WrestleMania is the biggest event in sports entertainment, where Superstars become WWE Legends. Experience a gripping retelling of WrestleMania’s greatest moments in 2K Showcase of the Immortals, where you can relive a collection of some of the most unforgettable, career-defining matches.<br>
<br>
AN ICONIC ROSTER<br>
<br>
WWE 2K24 boasts a star-studded roster featuring WWE Legends like “Stone Cold” Steve Austin, Undertaker, and Andre the Giant, alongside current WWE Superstars like “The American Nightmare” Cody Rhodes, John Cena, Rhea Ripley, and Roman Reigns, whose larger-than-life entrances and signature moves are heightened by ultra-realistic graphics.<br>
<br>
NEW MATCH TYPES<br>
<br>
From Guest Referee to Casket, Gauntlet, and Ambulance matches, there are a bevy of new match types to experience in WWE 2K24, including support for multiple Superstars in Backstage Brawl.<br>
<br>
PROVE YOURSELF IN MyRISE<br>
<br>
Unleash your raw talent and become the undisputed champ in MyRISE, featuring two thrilling career arcs and original storylines chronicling your ascent to WWE stardom from the men's and women’s divisions.<br>
<br>
BUILD YOUR FACTION<br>
<br>
Assemble your favorite WWE Superstars and Legends in MyFACTION. Acquire cards, build a dominant faction, compete in online multiplayer and the all-new ranked quickplay. Plus, earn exciting promotional and final rank rewards as you climb the new seasonal leaderboard!<br>
<br>
CONTROL THE WWE UNIVERSE<br>
<br>
Develop feuds, weekly shows, and more in Universe mode, WWE 2K24’s ultimate sandbox, with expanded rivalry actions, all-new cutscenes, and support for double-title matches!<br>
<br>
CALL THE SHOTS IN MyGM<br>
<br>
Oversee the biggest brands and Superstars in sports entertainment as you challenge rival general managers for the top spot in MyGM. Explore more match types, more brands, and new general managers. Trade Superstars between brands, make executive decisions on contracts, and amp up the drama.<br/>
<br/>
**Online play including MyFACTION requires an internet connection and 2K Account. Terms apply.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duelists of Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1664200/Duelists_of_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/DoE_EVO_Trailer_-_steam_gif_short_30fps.gif?t=1710102934"><br/>Duelists of Eden is a card-grid-fighting game set after the events of One Step From Eden. Build your custom deck and battle online in real-time action! There are over 14 unique characters with strengths and weaknesses to encourage creative spell combinations and synergies. Will you combo slashes, fire, or even use bombs to eliminate your competition?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/SaffronWitch_steam_header-features.gif?t=1710102934"><h2 class="bb_tag">Deckbuilding</h2>Fight in a mix of strategy and real-time action! Create your own unique combination of spells to take down the competition. <br/>Save and edit an unlimited amount of decks in the editor!<h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic cardtridge and combo system</h2>Create combos on the fly, adapting the scenario and what spells you and your opponent have.<h2 class="bb_tag">Tutorial and training mode</h2>Learn the ropes in the tutorial mode and deep dive into the mechanics via training mode. <br/>Training mode includes hitboxes, character states, quick deck edits, speed modifiers, and more!<h2 class="bb_tag">Custom rollback netcode</h2>The game was completely rebuilt to support custom rollback netcode, for the smoothest experience possible.<h2 class="bb_tag">Replay mode</h2>Review your matches in replay mode!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/Selicy_OSFE_gif_steam.gif?t=1710102934"><br/><br/>Local multiplayer may require a controller.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals Zero Hour</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732960/Command__Conquer_Generals_Zero_Hour/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals Zero Hour brings you closer to the enemy than ever before. Engage opposing forces at hot spots around the globe as you match strategies and arsenals against the new masterminds of modern war.<br/><br/><strong>Arsenal.</strong> Unleash the next generation of 3D new units and 20 new upgrades including China's ECM Tank, GLA's BattleBus and the USA's Spectre Gunship.<br/><br/><strong>Missions.</strong> Take on 15 new missions and make tomorrow's headlines. Root out a splinter cell in Cairo, steal deadly toxins from a U.S. lab and more.<br/><br/><strong>Generals.</strong> Match strategies and arsenals against 9 enemy commanders with unpredictable personalities and tactics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Tiberian Sun™ and Firestorm™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229880/Command__Conquer_Tiberian_Sun_and_Firestorm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Second Tiberium War begins in this legendary sequel to the original Command &amp; Conquer. <br/><br/>With his forces stronger than ever, arch villain and leader of The Brotherhood of Nod - Kane - is pitched in an epic battle against the world's war machine - the Global Defense Initiative. Now you must orchestrate the fate of mankind.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on Dynamic Battlefields. Nature itself provides tactical opportunities - destroyable and deformable terrain, forest fires, treacherous ice fields and many more surprises that help or hinder your strategies.<br/></li><li>Exciting New Strategies and Units. Jump Jet Infantry, Hover Tanks, Tunneling APCs, Hunter Seekers, Laser Fences, Mechanized Battle Units and many more.<br/></li><li>The "Veterancy" Factor. Units can become faster and stronger as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>New Kinetic Battlefields. Flying shrapnel, shock waves and crashing debris are just a few of the exciting new technologies developed to enhance the in-game experience.<br/></li><li>The mood and attitude of the battlefield comes alive like never before - covert night missions, searchlights and new defenses intensify the thrill and excitement.</li></ul><br/>Then take the battle further in <strong>Firestorm, the official expansion pack for the game</strong>. Includes all-new campaign missions, cinematics, and units to decide the future of mankind.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Renegade™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229890/Command__Conquer_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer gets up close and personal in this classic First Person Shooter for one of the most iconic franchises.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wreak Havoc</strong> - Experience the Command &amp; Conquer universe on foot as Havoc, wise-cracking GDI Commando.<br/></li><li><strong>Make Your Own Rules</strong>  - Take on the evil Brotherhood of Nod using your own mix of brute force, stealth, and strategy.<br/></li><li><strong>Assault at Ground Level</strong>  - Dish out the damage in either first or third person.<br/></li><li><strong>Total Access</strong>  - Sneak inside and explore full-scale structures, like immense Tiberium Refineries and the ominous Hand of Nod.<br/></li><li><strong>Grind the Gears</strong>  - Beef up your arsenal by commandeering lethal vehicles, such as Nod Buggies, Flame Tanks, and Mammoth Tanks.<br/></li><li><strong>Weapons of Mass Destruction</strong>  - Choose from a multitude of weapons, including the Tiberium Auto Rifle, Chemical Sprayer, and the devasting Personal Ion Cannon.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ and The Covert Operations™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229830/Command__Conquer_and_The_Covert_Operations/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The legendary RTS game which started it all. Will you side with the humanistic GDI or bring the world to its knees with Kane and the Brotherhood of Nod. Your adversaries are without mercy. And so are you.  <br/><br/>Includes the <strong>The Covert Operations</strong> expansion pack with a range of challenging new missions.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potions: A Curious Tale</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/378690/Potions_A_Curious_Tale/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Add Potions: A Curious Tale to your wishlist!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/Wishlist_616.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/LunaCombatGif.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Use your wits to strategize conflict resolution that goes beyond pure combat-- you’ll have to think on your feet and act quickly to sidestep danger and trick, charm, and scare your opponents into dropping valuable resources. <br/><br/>As powerful as your potions are, you’ll find yourself up against monsters that can shrug off your most powerful attacks. Manage your resources carefully and use the environment and even other monsters to defeat your enemies, or you may find yourself with an empty satchel when you need your elixirs the most.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/SteamCraftingVideoFullPotTitleNX.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>On her path to potions mastery, Luna must gather rare ingredients even before she brews her first potion. While her grandmother and friends teach her basic skills and recipes, Luna must fill her vials through experimentation and discovery. <br/><br/>Explore the deep crafting system as you discover new ingredients across 7 biomes to craft over 100 unique potions with different element combinations. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/PuzzleGifTitle.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Solve devious puzzles and mysteries with your wits and your arsenal of mystical potions. With a little help from your grandmother (a powerful witch in her own right) and Helios, your cat familiar, you’ll overcome the challenges of these enchanted lands.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/StoryTitle.png?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Growing up is hard, and it’s even harder when you’re a witch! Encounter fairy tale and folklore characters as you guide Luna on her quest to become a potions master. With her sharp-tongued familiar at her side, Luna learns important coming-of-age lessons: Respect is earned, advice can be deceiving, and adults aren't always right.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FQS2SN55CC4" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/SteamHeaderDiscord616.png?t=1709876407"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/PetCatHeart.gif?t=1709876407"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Saboteur™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/24880/The_Saboteur/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/24880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Not all wars are fought on the open battlefield. Download The Saboteur to visit 1940s Nazi-occupied Paris, as you play tough Irish racecar mechanic Sean Devlin. Working with the French Resistance, Sean is out for revenge against ruthless Nazi Colonel Kurt Dierker, who executed Sean’s best friend.<br/><br/>This open-world action thriller takes you through the seedy streets of Paris as you seek to undermine the German authority and lead a rebellion. Fight across rooftops and through dangerous alleys, and operate a wide variety of vehicles as you navigate your terrain. You can even climb the Eiffel Tower or Notre Dame Cathedral for a sniping mission.<br/><br/>Use stealth and disguise to strike at the heart of the Nazi war machine by disabling trains, destroying bridges, and blowing up enemy facilities. As you work to remove the oppressive forces from parts of the city, the drab black-and-white palette gives way to bright colors, signifying that you’ve inspired the townspeople. The more you incite the people, the more they’ll aid you by intervening in fights or providing a quick getaway from pursuing Germans. The Saboteur presents a fresh take on World War II and features dramatic cinematic elements. The action and intrigue is yours to experience via download on the PC now.<br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>First Ever Open-World Paris</strong> — Climb the Eiffel Tour, snipe from Notre Dame Cathedral, and brawl on the Champs d’Elysee as you sabotage your enemies. Fight, climb, and prowl through the dark alleys, rooftops, burlesque houses, and seedy streets of the City of Lights — the ultimate playground for the Saboteur.<br/></li><li><strong>The Art of Sabotage</strong> — Being the Saboteur is all about attacking while staying unnoticed. Get your mission intel at underground clubs and cabarets. Eliminate your adversaries with stealth attacks, disguise, distractions, and explosives. Master a variety of weapons, automobiles, and skills to sabotage enemy operations. <br/></li><li><strong>The Will to Fight</strong> — An action-packed experience and thrilling storyline are made even more engaging by an innovative visual style, characters, and the new “Will to Fight” technology. Experience how the city reacts and changes around you as you free it from Nazi oppression. Only you can restore hope and grandeur to Paris.<br/></li><li><strong>French Resistance Strikes</strong> — Call for support from The Underground in the form of getaway cars, weapon deliveries, distractions, and much more.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 March Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2845260/100_March_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🌸🌹 WELCOME TO 100 MARCH CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌷🐈</h2><br/>Join the cutest adventure in the Lovely world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of romantic 8 march themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x200.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 March Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁 DLC List for this game 🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Extra.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867620/100_March_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867640/100_March_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x1.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_15" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sixty Four</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2659900/Sixty_Four/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F7YXd3tScqS" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/discord.png?t=1710217001"/></a><br/><br/>Created by a solo developer, Sixty Four is a clicker game that gradually becomes more idle with every machine you unlock, up to the the ultimate goal of full automation. Upgrade a factory in an extraordinary world. Progress to unlock new resources and machines, leading to new ways to expand and grow.<br/><br/><strong>❒ From Foundation to Complexity</strong><br/><br/>Begin your journey with a simple machine generating distinct cubes. Use combinations of cubes to unlock advanced machinery and new gameplay elements.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_3a_smaller.gif?t=1710217001"><br/><br/><strong>❒ An Evolving Factory Adventure</strong><br/><br/>Your factory is not just a collection of simple machines; it's a dynamic environment of challenges and strategy. Face new situations and discover opportunities with every innovative and abstract machine you encounter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_4a_smaller.gif?t=1710217001"><br/><strong>❒ A Fresh Mix of Gaming Mechanics</strong><br/><br/>Sixty Four combines simple yet engaging elements from idle, incremental, and strategy games. Pursue constant improvement and unravel the secrets behind messages from an unknown entity.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_5a_smaller.gif?t=1710217001"><br/><br/>Music by Jake Chudnow						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Thaumaturge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1684350/The_Thaumaturge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Thaumaturge_accolade_616x320_steam.png?t=1709742147"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/TT_claim_EN_small.png?t=1709742147"><br/><strong>The Thaumaturge is an isometric, story-rich RPG with a unique take on turn-based combat, character development features, and investigation mechanics</strong>, facing you with morally ambiguous choices – set in a world teeming with mysterious powers and strange ethereal beings called <strong>salutors</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/City_3-01.gif?t=1709742147"><br/><br/>The year is 1905. Warsaw lives under the yoke of imperial Russian tsardom. Its inhabitants constitute a diverse group of different ancestries, views, and beliefs with often conflicting interests: Russian soldiers, Jewish merchants, Polish townspeople, and more. Despite the circumstances, the city is a buzzing metropolis, where one can attend a breathtaking party with the high society, and later get robbed in one of the dark alleys of the Praga district. A city of great hopes and dreams on one hand and dark desires on the other.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Buka_2.gif?t=1709742147"><br/><br/>A <strong>thaumaturge</strong> bears both a gift and a burden at the same time. This parallel holds true for <strong>Wiktor Szulski</strong>, the game’s titular protagonist, who is drawn back to the tumultuous streets of 20th-century Warsaw by family matters. The gift of thaumaturgy is intertwined with family legacy, passed down through one's ancestors. This mystical inheritance significantly shapes Wiktor’s life journey tied around a pursuit of unearthly entities and their hosts. As only a thaumaturge can tame these ethereal entities - known to a select few as <strong>salutors</strong> - utilizing their mystical abilities to discover secrets hidden within the human soul and speak to the Darkness, no one understands quite like Wiktor how everyone suffers their own demons.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Wiktor_3-01.gif?t=1709742147"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Shape your story</strong> – as a full-fledged RPG, it allows you to alternate your choices and make you deal with the aftermath. <br/></li><li><strong>Develop your character</strong> – creating your own version of the thaumaturge will allow you to approach situations in different ways. <br/></li><li><strong>Experience unique turn-based combat</strong> and defeat your foes using human attacks and skills as well as psychic strikes delivered by salutors.<br/></li><li><strong>Influence and manipulate</strong> the temperaments of other characters to bend their will to your liking. <br/></li><li><strong>Tame the power of salutors</strong> – use the unique set of their skills to gain an advantage while exploring the world and when bringing your adversaries to their knees. <br/></li><li><strong>See the world that’s inevitably gone</strong> – explore the uncommon, heavily researched historic period of the early XX century Warsaw, where crime and luxury are often two sides of the same coin. Meet historical figures and learn about their involvement in the story. <br/></li><li><strong>Created in Unreal Engine 5</strong> to deliver a detailed &amp; beautifully crafted world.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Grindea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/269770/Secrets_of_Grindea/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/269770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Secrets of Grindea</i> is an old-school Action RPG with co-op support for up to 4 players. It is a tribute to and sometimes a parody of the old SNES games so many of us grew up with and loved! Journey through fantastical lands, and battle tons of different enemies and bosses in your quest for truth, friendship and, above all, finding the world's rarest treasures!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A rich world filled with 300+ unique, colorful characters and an engaging story to drive your journey forward.<br/></li><li>Co-op support for up to four players! Enjoy the entire storyline with your friends or call someone in to help with the more difficult challenges.<br/></li><li>Customization, customization, customization - design a character that represents you, then mix and match any of the 31 spells and skills across 9 different categories.<br/></li><li>30+ epic boss fights! Overgrown slimes, giant robots, mimics - we have it all!<br/></li><li>Side content - design your own home, fish, craft items, tame pets, partake in mini-games, grow plants - there’s plenty to keep you entertained when you want a break from the main story.</li></ul><br/>And last but not least:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Arcade Mode - Separate from Story Mode, the game includes a <strong>full roguelite</strong> version where you need to battle your way to the top on a single life, building a town of your own as you progress.  How far can you get?</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON BALL FighterZ</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/678950/DRAGON_BALL_FighterZ/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/extras/GIF_DBFZ_STEAM.png?t=1710262330"><br/><br/>DRAGON BALL FighterZ is born from what makes the DRAGON BALL series so loved and famous: endless spectacular fights with its all-powerful fighters.<br/><br/>Partnering with Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ maximizes high end Anime graphics and brings easy to learn but difficult to master fighting gameplay.<br/><br/>High-end Anime Graphics<br/>Using the power of the Unreal engine and the talented team at Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ is a visual tour-de-force.<br/><br/>3vs3 Tag/Support<br/>Build your dream team and sharpen your skills to master high-speed tag combinations.<br/><br/>Thrilling Online Features<br/>Ranked matches, interactive lobby, crazy 6-player Party Match... There is something for every taste!<br/><br/>Exclusive Story Mode<br/>Discover a never-seen-before scenario featuring Android 21, a brand new character whose creation was supervised by Akira Toriyama himself.<br/><br/>Spectacular Fights<br/>Experience aerial combos, destructible stages and famous scenes from the DRAGON BALL anime in 60FPS and 1080p resolution!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1709723687"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1709723687"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709723687"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709723687"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR WARS™: Dark Forces Remaster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2292260/STAR_WARS_Dark_Forces_Remaster/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_8.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/><i>Star Wars</i>™: Dark Forces Remaster has been brought to life by the team at <strong>Nightdive Studios</strong>, fully remastered through its proprietary KEX engine, allowing the game to run on modern gaming devices at up to 4K resolution at 120FPS. New and returning players will enjoy <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces Remaster’s upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<br/><br/>The original 1995 <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces raised the bar for FPS games, offering players a significant degree of movement and interactivity, a large selection of items and power-ups, and engaging environments. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_10.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/>In the first <i>Star Wars</i> FPS video game, players assume the role of Kyle Katarn, a defector of the Galactic Empire turned mercenary for hire. Katarn joins the Rebel Alliance’s covert operations division tasked with infiltrating the Galactic Empire, where he discovers the secret Dark Trooper Project. The development of this powerful new series of Imperial battle droids and power-armored stormtroopers stands to strengthen the Empire’s grip on the galaxy unless Katarn and the Rebel Alliance intervene.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>All fourteen original levels, featuring <i>Star Wars</i>™ worlds and capital ships<br/></li><li>Use your ability to jump, duck, and crawl to solve puzzles and defeat enemies<br/></li><li>Your Personal Digital Assistant provides you with in game information such including map, inventory, and mission briefing<br/></li><li>Engaging first-person ground combat featuring ten weapons and twenty types of enemies<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS visuals<br/></li><li>Advanced 3D rendering enables updated lighting and atmospheric effects<br/></li><li>Modern gamepad support adds a new weapon wheel, and rumble<br/></li><li>Controller Support - vibration and gyro controls <br/></li><li>A variety of power-ups are made available to the player, including health, shields, weapons and ammunition<br/></li><li>For combat, the player may use fists, explosive landmines and thermal detonators, as well as blasters and other ranged weapons<br/></li><li>Includes immersive environmental puzzles and mazes </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_1.gif?t=1709278523"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709870080"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myth of Empires</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1371580/Myth_of_Empires/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple Civilizations</h2>We are developing tech trees for multiple civilizations, which will include armor, weapons, buildings, crafting stations, and more. Greece, Persia, Rome, and Egypt will be added, with Greece and Persia scheduled to make their debut soon.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/多文明时代，即将来临！.gif?t=1710228527"><h2 class="bb_tag">Embark Upon a Thrilling Journey</h2>Explore a land with diverse landscapes, ecologies, and weather, as well as a realistic day/night cycle. The v1.0 release of Myth of Empires also features a new map – Dongzhou Island, offering new adventures and challenges.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/11111探索之旅，发现新世界的惊险旅程.gif?t=1710228527"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Own Empire From the Ground Up</h2>Myth of Empires features sandbox gameplay with a high degree of freedom; the game has 1300+ different crafting recipe, allowing you to build your own empire. The v1.0 release adds new recipes, including mechanical tools and base defenses, as well as a new planting system. The possibilities are endless.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/2【替换Gif】自由创造，打造你的帝国.gif?t=1710228527"><h2 class="bb_tag">Recruit NPCs, Tame Wildlife</h2>In-depth taming and training systems allow players to recruit or subdue additional forces to aid them in combat and production. The v1.0 release adds new boss NPCs and powerful beasts. In addition, smaller types of animals can be used to help power your base’s defenses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/333333驯服万物，NPC、马匹与野生动物.gif?t=1710228527"><h2 class="bb_tag">Wage Epic Wars on Ancient Battlefields</h2> Myth of Empires features hundreds of different weapons, armor, and large-scale engineering equipment. Pick the weapons that best suit your playstyle, or utilize your strategic capabilities to build an army. The v1.0 release introduces powerful mechanical base defenses, wooden oxen, and other new combat equipment to further enrich the game’s deep war experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/4【替换Gif】史诗战争体验，挑战百变的古代战场.gif?t=1710228527"><h2 class="bb_tag">Engage in Cross-server Battles </h2>Establish administrative regions, fight for the position of county magistrate, and compete to expand your territory through Fortress Battles. Craft the perfect guild and utilize your diplomatic prowess to ensure its long-term stability.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/555555跨服征战，共同创造历史.gif?t=1710228527"><h2 class="bb_tag">Write Your Own Legend </h2>With 25 different development paths, a 16-level title system, and more than 100 achievements, you have complete freedom in growing your character. Become a legendary military commander, or content yourself with the life of a simple farmer – the choice is yours.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/6【替换Gif】传奇生涯，定制独特的人生.gif?t=1710228527"><h2 class="bb_tag">Play Multiple Gameplay Modes Offering Endless Possibilities </h2>Myth of Empires supports official servers, custom servers, as well as solo and hosted modes. Creative players are also able to use the game’s robust mod editor to tailor the game to their dream experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/no7多样玩法.gif?t=1710228527"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Epoch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/899770/Last_Epoch/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Epoch combines time travel, exciting dungeon crawling, engrossing character customization and endless replayability to create an Action RPG for veterans and newcomers alike. Travel through the world of Eterra’s past and face dark empires, wrathful gods and untouched wilds – to find a way to save time itself from The Void.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Gameplay.gif?t=1709060046"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>15 Mastery Classes</strong><br/>Embark on your adventure as one of five powerful classes and, through your journey, ascend into a unique Mastery Class that unlocks more specialized abilities and build-options. <br/></li><li><strong>120+ Skill Trees</strong><br/>Every skill has its own augment tree that will allow you to control, alter, and empower your playstyle. Transform your skeletons into archers, your lightning blast into chain lightning, or make your serpent strike summon snakes to fight alongside you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Nodes.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Hunt Rare &amp; Powerful Loot</strong><br/>Fill your arsenal with magic items that you may craft to perfection, change the rules of your build with powerful unique and set items, and always have that next upgrade just on the horizon with Last Epoch's deep and randomized loot system.<br/></li><li><strong>Rewarding Crafting System</strong><br/>The items you wield are yours to forge! Last Epoch’s community-revered crafting system allows you to control your character's power progression, featuring robust and deterministic upgrade mechanics.<br/></li><li><strong>Uncover the Past, Reforge the Future</strong><br/>Travel to different moments of time where you will discover the many factions and secrets that exist within the world of Eterra and fight to set the timeline onto a new path.<br/></li><li><strong>Endless replayability</strong><br/>With a wealth of classes and skills to customize, deep game systems, randomized loot, and continuing development, Last Epoch is a game that will keep you coming back for years to come.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Monolith.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Easy to Learn, Hard to Master</strong><br/>We’re committed to making gameplay approachable for new and veteran players alike by allowing you to jump into the fray quickly and providing many in-game resources. Though don’t be fooled, Eterra has many dangers waiting for you that require a mastery of combat and build-crafting.<br/></li><li><strong>Zero Pay-To-Win</strong><br/>Last Epoch will never offer gameplay advantages by being able to spend real money. We believe in creating a fair environment for all players. </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminator: Dark Fate - Defiance</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1839950/Terminator_Dark_Fate__Defiance/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif1.gif?t=1709216510"><br/><strong>Terminator: Dark Fate – Defiance</strong> is a <strong>real-time strategy game</strong> based on the Terminator: Dark Fate universe that follows the war between humanity and Legion's synthetic intelligent machine network.<br/><br/>In the<strong> single-player campaign</strong>, you take the role of a commander in the Founders, a force made up of the remnants of the US military and guide your army in an attempt to foil Legion's plan to exterminate the last remnants of humanity. In skirmish and multiplayer modes, play as three very diverse factions: Founders, Movement and Legion.<br/><br/>Take control of an army carried over from mission to mission on a series of large strategic maps. Make decisions about unit placement, battle tactics and abilities so that you don’t just survive but can become the leader of the resistance against the machines. Hone your skills and military expertise by replaying and achieving the best possible outcomes.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic battlefields: realistic tactics and consequences</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif2.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>Engage in complex, realistic battles where your <strong>tactical decisions</strong> are vital to your survival and ultimate victory. Use a variety of military equipment, vehicles and ammunition types in your battles against the enemy. Recruit and train new units, assign new skills and acquire new weapons and equipment to continue the resistance.<br/><br/>Encounter tense battles. Your battlefield tactics and choices have deep consequences that will impact through the campaign, with other factions and characters either joining you or fighting against you, and with certain missions being available or not depending on your actions. <br/><br/><strong>Your resources are limited</strong> and you must protect your army. Weapons of war receive damage through a modular component damage system where armour characteristics, component malfunctions and hull structure all affect if your troops survive.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Lead the survival of mankind</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif3.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>Recruit others to your cause and <strong>grow your army</strong>. Mix and match the composition of your troops to fit your preferred battle tactics. Use infantry units, heavy armoured military vehicles, plasma cannon technology, drones and other flying units and even human skirmishers to achieve victory.<br/><br/>Use the battlefield to your advantage! <strong>Physics-based building demolition</strong> lets you generate a realistic set of tactical consequences, especially in urban areas.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer Mayhem: Skirmish and Online Battles</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif4.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>The excitement amplifies in <strong>skirmish and multiplayer modes</strong>, where <strong>you can play as three distinct factions</strong>: Founders, Movement, and Legion. <br/><br/>Engage in epic battles across vast strategic landscapes, testing your skills and military expertise. Every decision matters, impacting alliances, missions, and the overall survival of mankind.<br/><br/>Challenge your skills in skirmish and online multiplayer matches, facing off against AI or real-life human opponents in intense 1v1 and 2v2 battles.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penny’s Big Breakaway</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1955230/Pennys_Big_Breakaway/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ready. Set. YO! - Join Penny &amp; Yo-Yo in a kinetic 3D-platformer bursting with innovative gameplay! Showcase your catalog of tricks and chain impressive combos to deliver Penny &amp; Yo-Yo's perfect breakout performance. Take the stage with this vibrant pair in Penny’s Big Breakaway.<br/><br/>Penny is a street performer with big dreams; she has her own spin on what it takes to be a star! When Eddie the Emperor calls for new Palace Court Performers, Penny gets herself tangled in an audition she’ll never forget. A strange encounter with a Cosmic String transforms Penny’s Yo-Yo into a living creature with an appetite for snacks— and mayhem! Use Yo-Yo to help Penny clear her name, outrun the Emperor’s penguin army, and unravel the mystery of the Cosmic String. <br/><br/>Burst onto the scene in the fluorescent world of Macaroon, home to this over-and-under escape! Discover your true star power in this easy-to-play, difficult-to-master challenge. Penny’s Big Breakaway is the debut title from Evening Star.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-01-Supertitles.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Key Features: <br/><br/>Walk the Dog: Yo-Yo’s big appetite will earn an even bigger reward with snack power-ups! Use these tasty treats to temporarily transform Yo-Yo, granting it the abilities to improve movement speed, protect Penny from harm, and much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-02-WalktheDog.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Around the World: Flee from Eddie the Emperor’s massive penguin army as they chase you clear across the planet! These clumsy flightless birds patrol the halls, come bursting through walls, and will stop at nothing to seize you! Help out friendly denizens along the way and make use of your spectacular surroundings to evade your capturers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-03-AroundTheWorld.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Encore Stage: Play your way with multiple game modes! Show off your skills as you chain awesome combos and rack up multipliers in Story Mode. Take on the ultimate speedrunning challenge and dominate the leaderboard in Time Attack Mode. Redeem coins for bonus items, secret stages, and more unlockable extras.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-04-EncoreStage.gif?t=1708524042"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2379780/Balatro/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Balatro is a poker-inspired roguelike deck builder all about creating powerful synergies and winning big.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Endless_Possibility.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Combine valid poker hands with unique Joker cards in order to create varied synergies and builds. Earn enough chips to beat devious blinds, all while uncovering hidden bonus hands and decks as you progress. You’re going to need every edge you can get in order to reach the boss blind, beat the final ante and secure victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Jokers_Clean_Thin.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The definitive poker roguelike experience.<br/></li><li>Endless possibilities - every pick-up, discard and joker can dramatically alter the course of your run.<br/></li><li>In-depth campaign mode complete with 8 difficulties, as well as challenge, daily and seeded runs. </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Break_The_Game.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Deftly deploy an array of potent tools: different Decks, Jokers, Tarot cards, Planet cards, Spectral cards, and Vouchers. Use these versatile instruments to ignite a combo frenzy and turbocharge your poker hands, crafting electrifying, adrenaline-fueled synergies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro_5_Aces_GIF__HQ_.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 Jokers, each with their own unique abilities<br/></li><li>15 Decks with distinct modifiers to choose from for each run<br/></li><li>5 potential variants of each Joker which add further abilities<br/></li><li>22 Tarot cards variants that can enhance your regular playing cards<br/></li><li>11 Planet cards that help level up your possible poker hands<br/></li><li>32 Voucher cards to help provide permanent buffs for your current run</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Find_Your_Flow.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in Balatro’s distinctive psychedelic world. Let the synthwave soundtrack wash over you -  wind down, escape the daily grind and prepare to enter the ultimate roguelike flow state.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improve your collection and discover new cards and secrets with every single run.<br/></li><li>Make use of the in-depth stats screen to study your best hands, most used Jokers, and more!<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the CRT fuzz and enjoy detailed, hand-crafted pixel art.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Spectral_Pack.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F5mH3dNhjx2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro-join_the_discord.png?t=1710160593"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Life of Logic</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2791740/A_Life_of_Logic/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a journey of intellect and emotion with "A Life of Logic", a narrative-driven game intricately woven around an elegant logic puzzle. In this captivating experience, your mission is to fill the board with the binary dance of 0s and 1s, all while mastering three deceptively simple rules:<br>
   + No Three Consecutive Same Numbers<br>
   + Balance in Rows and Columns:<br>
   + No identical rows or columns<br>
<br>
As you immerse yourself in solving these brain-teasing puzzles, a charming story unfolds, revealing a life adorned with memorable milestones and extraordinary moments. Each level you conquer peels back a layer of the narrative, enticing you to venture deeper into the tale of this extraordinary life.<br>
<br/>
Welcome to a new dimension of puzzle-solving, where the elegance of logic meets the richness of storytelling. A Life of Logic not only challenges your analytical prowess but also rewards you with hidden images, seamlessly blending the thrill of puzzle-solving with a captivating narrative.<br/>
<br/>
Key Features:<br/>
<br/>
Elegant Logic-Based Puzzle: ALOL introduces a binary puzzle that transcends the ordinary, providing an engaging challenge that surpasses the enjoyment found in traditional games like Sudoku.<br/>
<br/>
Story-Based Game: Immerse yourself in a narrative tapestry where each successfully solved puzzle unveils a hidden image, contributing to the enchanting story of an extraordinary life.<br/>
<br/>
Memorable Milestones: Revel in the joy of discovery as each puzzle brings you closer to unraveling the secrets of a life filled with remarkable milestones.<br/>
<br/>
Are you ready to embrace the harmony of logic and storytelling? Welcome to the immersive world of A Life of Logic!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corbid! A Colorful Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1034020/Corbid_A_Colorful_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/corbid_help_V2_ENG_V2.png?t=1710370857"><br/><br/>Dive into this exciting and colorful adventure! Help Corbid overcome the challenging mazes and secure his place as champion. Get ready to have fun as you embark on this colorful and exciting mission, where you'll have to use your dexterity and skills to solve the intricate puzzles in the huge gardens.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/CORBID_01_.gif?t=1710370857"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/corbid_obstacles_V2_ENG.png?t=1710370857"><br/>The gardens are full of fun riddles and puzzles in which you will have to do your best to advance. Use all your resources, feel the speed and the frenzy of the jumps to get as far as you can. Also, let yourself be advised by different allies and even help some of them to unlock new areas.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/Corbid_caja.gif?t=1710370857"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/corbid_friends_V2_ENG.png?t=1710370857"><br/>Find adventure companions on your journey to help you complete fun scenarios and become more effective against dangers. Combine skills to achieve unique moves and solve more complex puzzles. Above all, make friends!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/Corbid_boton.gif?t=1710370857"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/corbid_2_enemies.png?t=1710370857"><br/><br/>Get ready to fight in thrilling battles against terrifying final bosses. Use Corbid's skills to find the enemies' weaknesses and defeat them in a battle that will keep you on the edge of your seat - don't give up, stay focused and secure victory against these formidable opponents!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/CORBID_02_.gif?t=1710370857"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/corbid_3_ENG.png?t=1710370857"><br/><br/>Embark on an adventure through lush and vibrant worlds filled with creatures of every color imaginable. Dive into the mysteries hidden in the vast gardens and unravel the secrets they hold. Enjoy a wonderful journey where the magic of color will surprise you around every corner.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1034020/extras/CORBID_03_.gif?t=1710370857"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knife To Meet You</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1663650/Knife_To_Meet_You/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1663650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>CAN YOU HIT THE APPLE ON THE HEAD?</strong><br/>Be the knifemaster who makes the most stunning tricks! You can do whatever you want, and complete a level in different ways. All in bullet time slow mo! You can play only for fun or competitively online: in any 10 sec game you have a chance to break the World Record, visible for all players! You have 2 knives at start. Earn gold to buy other weapons by completing story levels, achievements, online battle levels, finding treasures, winning challenges.<br/><strong>And a mega bonus for inviting your friend. We reward every invite with 50X multiplier now!</strong><br/><br/><strong>TRICKS YOU CAN DO:</strong><br/>- Stuck, Slice, Pierce, Pin objects - all can be part of a multi combo!<br/>- Hat Trick: hit your friend's hat without hitting him!<br/>- Team Trick: pass a knife to your friend who finishes the job!<br/>- Underhand Trick: Throw with reverse spin and hit a target!<br/>- Spin Trick: Spin the knife at least 450 degrees before hitting the target!<br/>- Overtake Trick: Triple combo an object but in different order!<br/>- Sacrifice Trick: Quickly hit your partner after you have completed the level.<br/><br/><strong>FEATURES:</strong><br/>- 50 Story Levels<br/>- 3000+ online map levels<br/>- XP and gold system<br/>- 48 weapons (No-Spin Knife, Spin Knife, Axe, Fork, Cleaver, Nails, Card, Sickle, Scythe, Sword, Shuriken, Sawblade, Sabre, Dart, Spear, Tomahawk, Swiss Knife, Frisbee, Boomerang, Crossbow, Pistol, etc)<br/>- Leaderboard for each weapon, each level!<br/>- Survival levels: how far can you get?<br/>- Daily challange: one-chance circus: online challenge each day where you can try only once (new levels each day).<br/>- Level Editor and Community Levels<br/><br/><i>CAUTION Cut Hazard: Product has functional sharp edges. Contact may result in injury. Always keep blades away<br/>from fingers and body. Handle with care. Use with adult supervision.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Order of the Snake Scale</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2451470/The_Order_of_the_Snake_Scale/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> <u> !!! WARNING !!! </u></strong><br/><strong> <u> !!! Indie Retro Horror !!! </u></strong><br/>"Tank control" - player control system!<br/>Old school style puzzles!<br/>Self-created 3D models!<br/>For convenience, it is recommended to play on a xbox compatible controllers.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451470/extras/lov.gif?t=1710362335"><br/><br/><strong> <u> Discover a surreal world inspired by Lovercraft</u></strong><br/>Explore a dystopian world that accurately alludes to current world events.<br/>The universe describes one of the paths that humanity can follow. Every decision has its consequences. In this universe, power over humanity is exercised by Unions of States and Corporations.<br/>The prohibition of religion, mass sterilization, the appropriation of people's property, eugenics, the subjugation of humanity to the NML Corporation, this is the new world order.<br/>Are you ready to experience it?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451470/extras/story.gif?t=1710362335"><br/><br/><strong> <u> A suspenseful story</u></strong><br/>During the game, you will learn about the history of the Universe and the heroes who live in it.<br/>With each step in the game, you will discover the semi open world, its history and receive tips to help you solve the Happy Rock case.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451470/extras/niestandardowe_obrazy.gif?t=1710362335"><br/><br/><strong> <u> First, survive</u></strong><br/>A mysterious murder, monsters, rooms where you will definitely not be safe, corpses everywhere. <br/>It's easy to die in this world... Especially in the least expected moments.<br/>Stock up your inventory, collect clues, fight, make decisions and survive.<br/><br/><strong> <u> Explore and solve puzzles</u></strong><br/>Explore the atmospheric, unique, nooks and crannies of Happy Rock. Delve into the mystery of this place and the doomed world.<br/>Solve logic puzzles, combine facts to solve a murder case, demonstrate your skills during arcade missions.<br/>A dark world is waiting to draw you in. Perhaps forever.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the machine</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2775220/Inside_the_machine/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2775220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2775220/extras/feature_robot.gif?t=1710361702"><br/><br/><strong>Inside the machine</strong> is a simple yet challenging puzzle game with over 20 unique levels. You are playing a soul, jumping from machine to machine and controlling them to reach your goal until finally you get back to your original body.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2775220/extras/feature_switch.gif?t=1710361702"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echo of Ayllu</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1670240/Echo_of_Ayllu/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1670240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							After the last great galactic war, humanity plunges into darkness and the last survivors struggle for their lives, in a world where robots have seized power. Play as the resistance, opposing forces or friendly little aliens and... back the tide of history.<br/><br/><strong>ENTER THE BATTLEFIELD</strong><br/>Build a supercharged deck made up of 8 characters: 7 Allies and 1 Champion.<br/>Games are fully customizable, live against your opponent!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1670240/extras/steamplayscreen2.gif?t=1710372084"><br/><br/><strong>FULL CONTROL</strong><br/>In Echo of Ayllu, <strong> you decide your own way to win</strong> with <i>Artifacts</i>:<br/>- <i>Thunder </i>: Win the game by stealing all the opposing energies.<br/>- <i>Domination </i>: Smash the opposing characters!<br/>- <i>Tempus</i>: Control the battlefield across space and time!<br/><br/>The traditional mana system is over too.<br/>Each character placed on the board bring an amount of <i>Power Particles</i> in play that the player can use as they wish. The <i>Powers Particles</i> boost your characters by multiplying their attack and can unlock powerful abilities. Use them wisely, these resources are precious.<br/><br/><strong>THREE FACTIONS</strong><br/><i>- Terra (Earth)<br/>- Proxima<br/>- Elysia. </i><br/><br/><strong>MULTI-MODES</strong><br/>Many modes have been implemented: Standard, Reversal, Mirror, Draft, Unlimited ... have fun everytime, everywhere!<br/><br/><strong>INTERPLAYER MARKET</strong>.<br/>Fed up with paying boosters all the time when new cards are released? Echo of Ayllu offers you an in-game market where all players can meet to buy, trade or sell their cards. Do business, collect, or have fun speculating if you want, everything is possible. Echo of Ayllu is a real trading card game!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1670240/extras/steamcollec.gif?t=1710372084"><br/><br/><strong>LEADERBOARD</strong><br/>Climb the seasonal leaderboard, earn rewards in tournaments, control the galaxy!<br/><br/><strong>ADVENTURE</strong>.<br/>Dive into a spectacular vision of the future of our humanity. And make history.<br/>The magnificent adventure mode will introduce you to the basic mechanics of the game, but also to the liabilities of the main characters . Sit back, get ready to take off.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1670240/extras/steamadventure.gif?t=1710372084"><br/><br/><strong>Social</strong><br/>Join colonies, form your crew, build alliances.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F6XuK7GS" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1670240/extras/whited.png?t=1710372084"/></a><br/>Let's talk! Discover the news around the game, and get your beta access!<br/><br/><i><br/>"My friend and I have been walking in the vast Siberian desert for several weeks. The burning days passed by - the freezing nights too. And yet, we were still there. Nothing could have overcome our determination. It guided our steps. The atrocities of the new wars, all these repeated invasions have brought up in us old visceral forces that we should never have known. And despite all that, there was nothing we could do to prevent it ... this genocide ... The whole earth is nothing more than a vast ruin, a shadow of a civilization that it has housed ... at the mercy of a planet that owes it everything.<br/>We didn't know it yet, but my companions and I weren't alone. We thought we were the last bastion of invisible resistance. In reality, we were the very first link.<br/>Billions of billions of kilometers away; allies, friends ... whole armies were preparing. A science from another time came to us and we were not only going to change the course of our destiny, but also that of all of humanity. All... of... Humanity. But that we didn't know yet."</i>  - Rover Hamilton, October 2417						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Shire: Room One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517850/Toy_Shire_Room_One/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FkhSxB2MSgD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/Toy_Shire_-_Discord_Banner.png?t=1710352808"/></a><br/><br/><br/>Play through the <strong>three levels in Kevin's Room</strong> and defend your room against your old toys. Face Memphis-X in the final level and put a stop to his assault as he crushes your soldiers in an attempt to get to your base.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyVengeance.png?t=1710352808"><br/>You received new toys from your family. Isn't that lovely? Oh, it's for sure... <br/>Your old toys, though, aren't getting along as well. They are no longer cared for and have been forgotten. So what follows next? They're going to join together against you and assault your brand-new toys, so be prepared. But never worry! You're in luck since your brand-new toys are troops of green soldiers. They still require your aid though! Control, strengthen, and defeat the opposing forces! However, focus with care, the enemies you encounter might not be your old playthings!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/InteractiveTowerDefense.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Tower building alone won't be sufficient to repel incoming attackers. Build up your own troops in the best feasible positions, then unleash attacks into enemy territory. Never abandon your towers, and deploy your troops in accordance with the traits of the enemy. First, the attacking forces will attempt to get past your defenses. Build and improve towers to aid your army. By using unique abilities, you can support your troops and towers as well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/EpicBattles.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Safeguard your base against waves of attackers. You need to pick the right troops if you would like to prevail. Clean the paths and guard any open routes. Upgrade your troops and unlock new ones to take down the waves and claim victory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyRealm.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Enter a world and a narrative built around the toys that enriched your youth, including toy soldiers, dinosaur sets, robots, building blocks, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_3.gif?t=1710352808"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uootoy 3671</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1947440/Uootoy_3671/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1947440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The legendary comical action puzzle game 'Uootoy' -- which was first published in the August 1984 issue of I/O Magazine (published by Kougaku-sha), gained popularity on the FM-7, PC-88, and Sharp X1. Now the ultimate evolution has arrived in the form of 'Uootoy 3671'.<br>
<br>
The objective of the game is simply to arrive at the goal. However, a plethora of obstacles stand in your way. Simplistic yet amazingly varied, every stage is bound to keep you entertained.<br>
<br>
TENTEN-kun, the star of the original 'Uootoy', will be joined by TELTEL-chan. As either the hero or heroine, players can take on all 100 of the original Uootoy's stages. An even greater challenge awaits in the story mode, which contains 100 new stages. A map editor is also included, ensuring many sleepless nights for dedicated players.<br>
<br>
Uootoy 3671 features a team of massively talented musicians. WING, whose credits include the 'Mega Drive Mini 2' and previous Mindware titles, has produced the sound system. Junko Ozawa, the legendary Namco composer.<br>
<br/>
*  WING, whose credits include the 'Mega Drive Mini 2' and previous Mindware titles, is the producer of the game's sound system."<br/>
* Junko Ozawa, the legendary NAMCO composer who has worked on Nintendo classics such as 'Rhythm Heaven' &amp; 'Tomodachi Collection'."<br/>
*  Daisuke Shiiba, another fantastic artist responsible for works on 'Rhythm Heaven', 'Tomodachi Collection', and the 'Final Fantasy Pixel Remastered' series."						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StepByStep</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2642870/StepByStep/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2642870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a multi-person co-created online painting game, by the members of the word relay painting, to complete a number of complete paintings together, quickly call on friends to draw your story!<h2 class="bb_tag"> Painting in 3d scene: </h2><br/>Paint in 3d scenes, intertwine fantasy with reality with a paintbrush, and more scenes await you to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Special brush: </h2><br/>With a special brush, you can paint a wider variety of pictures, perhaps with more variety.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Work with others: </h2><br/>Multiple people work together, you can continue to create on other people's paintings, and complete a story together.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Create your own brush: </h2><br/>You can easily customize your brush, and your own brush may be more convenient to use.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Collect flowers: </h2><br/>You can give flowers to others in multiplayer, or receive flowers from others as proof of recognition.<h2 class="bb_tag"> Create your own artwork: </h2><br/>Create your own portfolio and paint to your heart's content.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patchouli's Adventure In Doll's House</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2299750/Patchoulis_Adventure_In_Dolls_House/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2299750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Patchouli and Alice are a couple.<br/>One day, when Patchouli visited Alice's house - the Doll's House, she found her mischievous partner had hidden away.<br/>Moreover, she had set up various wonderful mechanical puzzles around the Doll's House, which needed to be solved to find her...<h2 class="bb_tag">《Patchouli's Adventure in Doll's House》</h2><br/>This is a room escape puzzle game and a derivative work of "Touhou Project."<br/>Playing as <strong>"The Witch of Seven-Elements" Patchouli</strong>, explore the wonderful doll's house, find key items, solve the puzzles, and find the hidden <strong>"The Puppeteer of Seven-Color" Alice</strong>.<br/>In addition to the fun and interesting puzzles, don't miss the sweet interactions between the witches.<h2 class="bb_tag">※ Game Features ※</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Easy to play, no skills needed to enjoy the game.<br/></li><li> Relaxing atmosphere, cute storyline, contains no horror or startling elements, suitable for everyone.<br/></li><li> No chase, no health bar, <strong>NO GAMEOVER</strong>, simply enjoy the warm and sweet story and elegant puzzles.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">※ Character Introduction ※</h2><strong>Patchouli</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2299750/extras/PatchouliForSteam.png?t=1710345718"><br/>The witch who visits the Doll's House.<br/>She is skilled in the magic of "The Seven-Elements" - Sun, Moon, Water, Fire, Wood, Metal, and Earth.<br/>She likes Alice, but often gets pranked by her.<br/><br/><strong>Alice</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2299750/extras/AliceForSteam.png?t=1710345718"><br/>The host of the Doll's House.<br/>She is skilled in making dolls move as if they were alive, delicate and elegant "Doll Manipulation."<br/>She likes Patchouli and often pranks her.<br/><br/><strong>Shanghai Doll</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2299750/extras/ShangHaiForSteam.png?t=1710345718"><br/>Alice's doll. Usually helps Alice with housekeeping.<br/>Can she help Patchouli find Alice this time?<h2 class="bb_tag">Q&amp;A</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Can I play this game without understanding the "Touhou Project"?<br/>Yes, you can. Of course, if you are familiar with the "Touhou Project," some content may make you smile; but you can just treat it as a regular room escape game (with a bit of Yuri).<br/><br/></li><li> Will there be a Bad End?<br/>Absolutely not, it's 100% Good End. Please feel free to play.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yubu: The Shoeventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2487000/Yubu_The_Shoeventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Yubu: The Shoeventure" is a 3D platformer with a twist - It let's you build your own playstyle with equipable movesets!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487000/extras/storegif3.gif?t=1710347671"><br/><br/>Yubu, a brave young Footarian, embarks on a mission to dismantle the Reseller's dominion over the Maibli Isles, using an unexpected weapon: shoes!<br/><br/>In this epic quest, your mission is clear aid Yubu in his battle against the Reseller, a foe seeking to disrupt harmony in the shoeless society of Footaria. With your help, Yubu will navigate challenging platforms, uncover hidden secrets, and unleash his extraordinary shoe-based abilities.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487000/extras/Customizethewayyouplay.png?t=1710347671"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487000/extras/yubugif4.gif?t=1710347671"><br/><br/>Make Yubu's journey your own with customizable movesets and special moves. Equip different shoe enhancements to alter his abilities. Whether you prefer enhancing agility, boosting jumping power, or a balanced approach, the choice is in your hands. Mix and match these abilities to overcome obstacles and enemies in creative ways.<br/><br/>With each decision, Yubu's skills adapt to your playstyle, making every run through the game unique. Your strategy will determine the outcome of each challenge.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487000/extras/buildyourshoesup.png?t=1710347671"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487000/extras/yubugif5.gif?t=1710347671"><br/><br/><strong>Special Moves for Special Moments</strong><br/>Boost Yubu's agility and power with special move shoe parts. Propel upwards with a burst of water, soar through the skies, or perform high-speed slides into enhanced jumps.<br/><br/><strong>Control the way your shoe hit</strong><br/>Discover shoe parts that do more than complement footwear. Some parts scattered around Maibli Isles can cause explosions upon impact, trap enemies in ice, or release devastating lightning strikes.<br/><br/><strong>Tactical Throwing Mechanics</strong><br/>Master the art of the throw with shoe parts that offer unique throwing patterns. Whether targeting the nearest enemy, a circle pattern, or bouncing off enemies.<br/><br/><strong>Innovative Movement Options</strong><br/>Personalize Yubu with different shoe parts that affect Yubu's basic movements!<br/><br/>Customize your shoe, combine four different attributes and find what suits you!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Llamasoft: The Jeff Minter Story</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2236680/Llamasoft_The_Jeff_Minter_Story/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2236680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Gridrunner</i>.<i> Revenge of the Mutant Camels</i>. <i>Tempest 2000</i>.<i> Llamatron</i>. In the British gaming universe of the 80s and 90s, nobody made games like Jeff Minter. Now, in a new interactive documentary from Digital Eclipse, you can play the history of one of the weirdest, wildest game developers to ever exist – a man who loved shooters and sheep, lasers and llamas.<br/><br/><strong>LLAMASOFT</strong><br/><br/>Journey back in time to an era of cassette tapes, photocopied zines, and README.TXT. An era in which a kid with a Commodore VIC-20 and dreams of radioactive sheep could become one of Britain's best-known game makers. A virtual museum of design documents, playable games, and all-new video features tell the fascinating story of a true independent game designer.<br/><br/><strong>PLAY THE ACCLAIMED ORIGINALS</strong><br/><br/><i>Llamasoft: The Jeff Minter Story</i> includes 42 classic games from 8 different platforms, from Jeff Minter's earliest work on the Sinclair ZX81 and Commodore VIC-20, to later work on the Spectrum, Commodore 64 and Atari 800, and deep into the 16-bit era with the Atari ST and Atari Jaguar. <br/><br/><strong>GRIDRUNNER: REMASTERED</strong><br/><br/>Jeff's signature shooter masterpiece <i>Gridrunner</i> gets an all-new look from Digital Eclipse, updated into thrilling modern graphics and sound – while still running the core of the Commodore 64 version for 100% gameplay accuracy.<br/><br/><strong>GAMES, GAMES, GAMES</strong><br/><br/><i>Sheep In Space</i>. <i>Andes Attack</i>. <i>Attack of the Mutant Camels</i>. <i>Matrix</i>. <i>Metagalactic Llamas Battle at the Edge of Time</i>. <i>Hellgate</i>. <i>Laser Zone</i>. And many more. All the Minter classics you've heard of (and several you probably haven't), now with new quality-of-life features to make playing them more fun than ever before.<br/><br/>Two of Jeff Minter's earliest "light synthesizers," <i>Psychedelia</i> and <i>Colourspace</i>, are also included, with all-new options and features optimized for controller-based play. Finally, Jeff's demo of <i>Attack of the Mutant Camels</i> for the unreleased Konix Multi-System console is also included.<br/><br/><strong>THE GOLD MASTER SERIES</strong><br/><br/>New from Digital Eclipse (<i>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Cowabunga Collection</i>, <i>Atari 50: The Anniversary Celebration</i>, <i>The Making of Karateka</i>), the Gold Master Series presents iconic games in an innovative "interactive documentary" format, putting the shared history of games and their creators into one comprehensive package.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dune: Imperium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1689500/Dune_Imperium/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Header.png?t=1710364055"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body0_2.png?t=1710364055"><br/>Experience the ultimate blend of strategy and intrigue as you navigate the treacherous landscapes of Arrakis in the award-winning board game <i>Dune: Imperium</i>!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle online, locally with AI, or against the formidable House Hagal.<br/></li><li>Earn Achievements that showcase your prowess as a leader.<br/></li><li>Embark on more than a dozen Challenges that will test your wit and cunning.<br/></li><li>Compete for badges in the rotating Skirmish Mode where no two games are the same!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body1_2.png?t=1710364055"><br/>Arrakis. Dune. Desert Planet. Raise your banner above the vast wasteland before you. As the Great Houses of the Landsraad marshal their forces and their spies, whom will you influence, and whom will you betray? A tyrannical Emperor. The secretive Bene Gesserit. The shrewd Spacing Guild. The ferocious Fremen of the Deep Desert. The power of the Imperium can be yours, but war is not the only way to claim it.<br/><br/><i>Dune: Imperium</i> blends deck-building and worker placement in a deeply thematic new strategy game where the fate of the Empire hangs on your decisions. Will you seek political allies or rely upon military might? Economic strength or subtle intrigues? A council seat… or a sharpened blade? The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body2_2.png?t=1710364055"><br/>In <i>Dune: Imperium</i>, you'll step into the role of one of the leaders of the Great Houses of the Imperium in a struggle to control the planet Arrakis and the invaluable Spice it provides.<br/><br/>The game plays out in a series of ten rounds, each of which is defined by a new Conflict on the surface of the planet; some award critical resources, and some provide Victory Points that will propel you to dominance. But choose your battles wisely: spread your forces too thin, and you'll find your enemies growing too strong to oppose.<br/><br/>Each round, you'll draw a hand of five cards from your deck, which will get stronger over the course of the game as you acquire new cards. Each card can be played in one of two ways: To send an Agent out into the Imperium to gather resources, or to Reveal at the end of the round to purchase new powerful cards. You must maintain a careful balance to get the most of the resources available to you. How will you find your path?<br/><br/>As your game progresses, you'll vie for Influence with four factions of the Imperium: The Emperor, the economically powerful Spacing Guild, the mysterious Bene Gesserit, and the ferocious Fremen of the deep deserts. Earning Influence among the various groups helps you to earn the Victory Points you need...but will you compete with your rivals for their favor, or abandon alliances to pursue other opportunities?<br/><br/>Many strategies are at your disposal, and many paths to victory. The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Footer.png?t=1710364055"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avoo</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2765250/Avoo/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2765250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Avoo is a trivia game for 1-4 players in which players collaborate to repopulate a forest by watering it with their knowledge.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Test your knowledge: More than a thousand questions about culture, cinema, history, mathematics, literature and other categories.<br/></li><li>Water the seed of knowledge: Each correct answer allows you to water the trees and repopulate the forest.<br/></li><li>Go through the seasons: Play in 5 different maps and answer the questions correctly to repopulate the forest.<br/></li><li>Up to 4 players: Play alone or with up to 4 players.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>revere</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1956330/revere/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1956330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1956330/extras/LoadingLogoVHSsteam.gif?t=1710337498"><br/><br/><i>An abandoned chapel. <br/>An old generator that won't start. <br/>Someone or something else. <br/>And not just one of them.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1956330/extras/pcgif.gif?t=1710337498"><br/><br/>The hours here feel like weeks, but you have to endure it. You must find out the truth. About what? Even you don't really remember that well.<br/>"revere" is a found footage survival horror game that takes the point and click mechanics of Five Nights at Freddy's and combines them with puzzles and minigames.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1956330/extras/padlockGIF.gif?t=1710337498"><br/><br/> With each stage you have a different objective and a new added foe to fight. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1956330/extras/monsterGIF.gif?t=1710337498"><br/><br/>The one thing that stays the same is that you still have to keep 'them' away. At all costs. The question is, do you have what it takes?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1956330/extras/LoadingLogoVHSsteam.gif?t=1710337498"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OG Memory: Synthwave Boats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2855450/OG_Memory_Synthwave_Boats/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>OG Memory: Synthwave Boats</strong> is an casual memory game with stunning images. You have to find all of the correct pairs to complete the game. your best round will be count and always be displayed in game, to compare your rounds. try to reduce your turns every game and set up your new record.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 12 stunning different memory cards<br/></li><li> 24 memory cards in total<br/></li><li> casual memory adventure<br/></li><li> auto saving<br/></li><li> count of ur best round<br/></li><li> simple mouse control<br/></li><li> 100 steam awards</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OG Memory: Synthwave Cars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733740/OG_Memory_Synthwave_Cars/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2733740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>OG Memory: Synthwave Cars</strong> is an casual memory game with stunning images in the synthwave style. You have to find all of the correct pairs to complete the game. your best round will be count and always be displayed in game, to compare your rounds. try to reduce your turns every game and set up your new record.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 12 stunning different memory cards<br/></li><li> 24 memory cards in total<br/></li><li> casual memory adventure<br/></li><li> auto saving<br/></li><li> count of ur best round<br/></li><li> simple mouse control<br/></li><li> 100 steam awards</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Horse: Bonded Spirits - Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626970/My_Horse_Bonded_Spirits__Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626970/extras/click_follow3.gif?t=1710330967"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2376970/My_Horse_Bonded_Spirits/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2376970/My_Horse_Bonded_Spirits/</a><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2487060/Anonymous_Hacker_Simulator/" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2487060/Anonymous_Hacker_Simulator/</a><br/><br/><strong>Welcome to the Prologue of My Horse: Bonded Spirits! The prologue is only part of the full game and is completely free. Every player will be able to play it and see what awaits them in the full version of the game.</strong><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FamfcqNcaqD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626970/extras/DISCORD.png?t=1710330967"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Your story</strong></h2>Begin your adventure as the reluctant future heir of a stud farm. Prove that you are more than just a spoiled brat. Start from scratch and learn how to keep and manage a stud farm; it will be a challenge that will prove incredibly rewarding – return the stud farm to its former glory! Along your journey, discover that nothing is as lasting as the bond with your horses!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626970/extras/01._Your_Story.gif?t=1710330967"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Manage your stud farm and return it to its former glory!</strong></h2>Your stud farm is not in a good shape – your job is to rebuild it, which will require quite a bit of skill and knowledge about keeping a stud farm. Develop your skills and gain knowledge to bring the farm up to scratch and learn how to maintain it. Manage your employees and other horses. Watch the stud farm transform from a ruin into a home for you and your horses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626970/extras/02._Manage_your_stud_farm_and_return_it_to_its_former_glory.gif?t=1710330967"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Your horse isn’t the only friend you can make!</strong></h2>Saddle up and explore the idyllic open world of Chestnut Glen and its surrounding landscape. Help rebuild the run-down stud farm by trotting around and meeting the village’s residents –  hang out with them and complete tasks for them to improve your and the stud farm’s reputation. Remember, not everybody you meet will want to be friends with you. Some people don’t even like horses! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626970/extras/03._Your_horse_isn’t_the_only_friend_you_can_make.gif?t=1710330967"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Your dream horse</strong></h2>In My Horse: Bonded Spirits - Prologue, you can change not only your appearance but also your horse’s and the stud farm’s. Choose various accessories, hairstyles, and saddles for your horse, so that you can gallop through the world in style. Place decorations and renovate the stud farm to beautify not only the stables but also the whole surrounding area!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626970/extras/04._Your_dream_horse.gif?t=1710330967"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Prove yourself in various competitions</strong></h2>Do you think the bond with your horse is strong enough to win competitions? The more trust there is between the two of you, the more easily your horse will learn new skills and the less afraid they will be of new challenges.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626970/extras/05._Prove_yourself_in_various_competitions.gif?t=1710330967"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micro Dungeon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2813460/Micro_Dungeon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2813460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">You Have the Role Of An Adventurer!</h2><br/>In this game you have a limited number of actions. By spending them, you must try to become stronger and not die!<h2 class="bb_tag">Main game features: </h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Random floor generation<br/></li><li> Ability to select (disable/enable) enemies<br/></li><li> Each hero and enemy has its own unique passive abilities<br/></li><li> Different difficulty levels<br/></li><li> Depending on the difficulty level, the intelligence of enemies also changes<br/></li><li> Lots of different items</li></ul><br/>It is very important to build tactics for each enemy! After all, you know in advance how many action points he has and you can roughly understand where he will move. Force your enemies to play by your rules!<br/><br/>If you miss, the enemy will open the chest and take your loot instead of you!<br/><br/>Not all items are equally useful. However, you won’t know until you pick it up, right?<br/><br/>We have prepared interesting locations for you in which you will have to work hard to emerge victorious!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angler Quest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2859920/Angler_Quest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2859920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the fantastical world of Marendum, where giant fish and other aquatic animals are top of the food chain! You play as an Angler, a specialized hunter of these great beasts for the sake of both the common people and the interests of the guild you work for. Fish, craft and battle your way to victory as you move through ranks in the guild and get ever closer to finally beating the dreaded Vermundus, King of the Depths.<br>
<br>
Angler Quest is a monster hunting game inspired by the Monster Hunter series, Souls games and classic turn-based RPGs like Pokemon and Final Fantasy. Hunt fish to get materials, use materials to craft better weapons and armor and experiment with different builds, all while engaging in a strategic combat system in which you must manage your stamina, make every move count and narrowly avoid defeat at every turn.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
-10 to 15 hours of gameplay with 4 classes to choose from and thus lots of replayability!<br>
-20 unique aquatic monsters to fight, each the equivalent of a boss encounter in another game + 17 more encounters with variant monsters with new stats, combat styles and gimmicks to overcome.<br>
-Heaps of armor and weapons to chose from, as well as an armor augmentation system to customize your build and exploit enemy weaknesses!<br/>
-A charming game world and characters.<br/>
-A crafting system for both equipment and much needed items.<br/>
-6 unique maps to explore and find unique fish and crafting materials alike.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psalm 5:9-13</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1837220/Psalm_5913/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1837220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1837220/extras/logo5.png?t=1710319899"><br/>In the game "<strong>Psalm 5:9-13</strong>" you have to plunge into a terrifying place, at first glance it is quite normal, but the further you go, the more it reveals its essence. This horror game is a first-person walking simulator with a VHS effect and a tense atmosphere, explore the location, find anomalies, and move on. Frightening things will await you along the way, are you ready to face THIS?<br/><br/>The average time to complete the game is 30 minutes<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1837220/extras/gif.gif?t=1710319899"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features:</h2>-Walking simulator<br/>-VHS filter<br/>-High quality sounds<br/>-Realistic graphics						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sea under the sea under the sea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2718030/Sea_under_the_sea_under_the_sea/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2718030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The year is 2082. Most of the planet is covered with water, and the composition of marine fauna has changed dramatically. Humanity has about 500 million people, most of whom live where the mountains used to be.<br/>You are in the Carpathian port. A team of researchers found an anomaly in the Black Sea. The signal shows that part of the seabed has begun to rise. Everything indicates that a new island has formed on the surface. You are an underwater team worker. Your task is to investigate the anomaly.<br/><br/>Sea under the sea under the sea is an exploration plot-driven game where you will be spooked in the deepest corners of the sea!<br/><br/>Features:<br/>- 3d space traversing<br/>- Retro graphics  <br/>- Unique moody underwater locations<br/>- Spooky fish<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2326720/Brutalism22" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2326720/Brutalism22</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anominal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667880/Anominal/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667880/extras/gif-1.gif?t=1710318521"><br/>Point. Click. Teleport.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 70 levels, each telling its own unique gameplay story.<br/></li><li>Action and puzzle requiring both brains and brawls.<br/></li><li>A different kind of platforming using both mouse and keyboard.<br/></li><li>Elegant minimalism and simplicity. <br/></li><li>A tale about anonymity seeking hope.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Krosfighter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635820/Krosfighter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Xelor, god of time, is a gambler. He's decided to organize a tournament bringing together the best fighters from every universe. He wants to have a good time, so why limit himself?<br/>Take your pick of 14 characters and duke it out with your friends in the arena!<br/><br/>Krosfighter is an intense, no-holds-barred party game where you and your friends get to shoot each other, then start over with another character to test different shooting styles. <br/>Be the best fighter to make it into the rankings and earn the blessing of the gods. The gods themselves might even drop in sometime during the game to turn everything upside down, blow things up, or reshuffle the deck! Players who are falling behind can take advantage of the chaos to get back in the game!<br/><br/>Krosfighter is fun for everyone, no matter what your level!<h2 class="bb_tag"> MAIN FEATURES:</h2><br/>•	<strong>A FUN, NO-HOLDS-BARRED PARTY SHOOTER</strong> – Go head-to-head against your friends in two-to-four-player, steady but pressure-free battles where everyone can have fun and win!<br/><br/>•	<strong>14 DIVERSE CHARACTERS</strong> – Every style to satisfy every player!<br/><br/>•	<strong>CASUAL AND EXPERT PLAYERS MEET IN THE ARENA</strong> – The most valiant fighters achieve victory by the sweat of their brow. The less adept can always call on the gods to help them win!<br/><br/>•	<strong>UNPARALLELED PARTY GAME ATMOSPHERE </strong>– Laugh your heads off as you try to kill each other!<br/><br/>•	<strong>EXPONENTIAL POWER</strong> – Each character has their own style and a power that demands to be unleashed.<br/><br/>•	<strong>HEROS FROM KROSMOZ AND BEYOND</strong> – Yugo, Lance Dur, and their friends aren't the only ones to descend on the arena: Seth, Sherlock, and more have also joined the party!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burning Ass</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2852210/Burning_Ass/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2852210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"> Burning Ass - A Race for Survival </h2><br/>Step into a world of deadly traps in "Burning Ass", a thrilling multiplayer game where survival is the ultimate prize.<br/><br/>Navigate through treacherous landscapes teeming with intricate challenges designed to test even the most seasoned players. Be the first in this desperate race for water, the lifeblood of this dying world.<br/><br/><strong>Unravel the Mysteries:</strong><br/><br/>Hidden hints whisper forgotten secrets, their solutions scattered across each treacherous level. Decipher cryptic clues and unlock the truth behind the world's enigmatic past.<br/><br/><strong>Master the Deadly Dance:</strong><br/><br/>Razor-sharp blades, crushing gears, and sharp spikes, demanding precise timing and split-second decisions. Only the swift and the skilled will survive.<br/><br/><strong>The Final Rush:</strong><br/><br/>Be the first to cross the finish line, outrun the dangers, and outsmart your rivals. Claim your reward - a precious bottle of water - and secure your right to live another day.<br/>But remember, survival is just the beginning. As you conquer challenges and unravel the mysteries, a deeper truth awaits. Will you crack the code and unlock the secrets of this enigmatic world, or will you succumb to its deadly embrace?<br/><br/><strong>"Burning Ass" awaits. Are you ready to face the challenge?</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Blood, Gore, Fun</h2> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poorzzle - Puzzle Alive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2782600/Poorzzle__Puzzle_Alive/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782600/extras/600-1.jpg?t=1710313271"><br/>Welcome to Poorzzle, a pure speculative puzzle game. Here, simple lines outline the ultimate purity, and 12 crafted puzzles will subvert your way of thinking.<br/><br/>Here, you will become a savior, unlocking the seal of the Prophet's fragment, in order to obtain the key to immortality. In-depth analysis of the logic and secrets behind the puzzle. Try, make mistakes, try again, every challenge and failure is the only way to the truth. However, reality seems to be hinting to you: this is a scam...<br/><br/>In the process, you will discover your special abilities: prediction, insight, imagination and good luck. These abilities will help you and make you more comfortable on the road to solving puzzles.<br/><br/>Poorzzle has no bloody battles, no lengthy walks. There is only a pure dialogue between you and the puzzle, a battle of challenge and wisdom. The difficulty is moderate and there is no need to worry about getting stuck. It allows you to enjoy the fun of solving puzzles while constantly challenging your own thinking.<br/><br/>Finally, may this key to immortality always be by your side, making every challenge the most beautiful memory in your life. Let us embark on this immortal journey full of wisdom and fun!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHERE SAFETY ENDS *R*</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2823140/WHERE_SAFETY_ENDS_R/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2823140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">*INTRO*</h2><br/>I would like to introduce you to SAFETY, a place for the unfortunate! You must be quite the special guest since our doors only open to those who truly commit to the cause. I can only hope you know what I mean...<br/><br/>You are most welcome (even encouraged) to talk with the rest of our precious participants, but be mindful, they DO not like whining. <br/><br/>Enjoy your stay ~~~<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2823140/extras/ezgif.com-animated-gif-maker.gif?t=1710310593"><h2 class="bb_tag">*DESCRIPTION*</h2><br/>This is a short game that explores the concept of SAFETY. You will awaken in a room with three strangers and no knowledge of what has happened to you. In isolation, you are to communicate with them to find out what this place is and why you are here. This story has five different endings, the outcome of which will be determined by the choices you make. Do you think you are brave enough to leave? And, what awaits past the door? Perhaps, you and I are not so different, it may be that we have met in SAFETY before.<br/><br/>And for those of you still there, I hope this short story will aid you on your journey.<br/><br/>Please consult the Readme file in the games folder for the controller button layout.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calendar Notess</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2845970/Calendar_Notess/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Calendar Notess: Transform Your Daily Plans into Art</h2>"Calendar Notess" turns calendar management into art. Taking notes on days, adding tags, tracking completion statuses, adding special icons to the calendar, visualizing all this information with graphs, and the ability to export to PDF... All these features offer an experience that goes beyond just organizing your daily life.<h2 class="bb_tag">Main Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li><strong>Tagging and Status Tracking:</strong> Add tags to your notes and mark your tasks as 'Done' to easily manage and track all your tasks.<br/> </li><li><strong>Customizable Icons:</strong> Add special icons to your days to personalize your calendar. Quickly recognize important days and tasks with visual cues.<br/> </li><li><strong>Advanced Graphing:</strong> Visualize your notes and tags with various graphs. Easily analyze your progress and efficiency.<br/> </li><li><strong>PDF Export:</strong> Export your calendar and notes to PDF. Save and share your plans outside the digital world.</li></ul>How Does It Make a Difference?<br/>"Calendar Notess" is not just a calendar app, but also a tool that enriches your daily life. It contains all the details that will make your day more efficient, whether in your personal or professional life. It maximizes time management by keeping your events, meetings, tasks, and special moments together.<br/>Who Is It For?<br/>It's ideal for people of all ages and professions. Students, professionals, managers, home administrators, and more... If you want to manage your time effectively, visualize your plans, and enjoy every moment, "Calendar Notess" is the right choice for you.<br/><strong>Get Started!</strong><br/>Managing your time and organizing your life has never been this easy and enjoyable. Transform your plans into art with "Calendar Notess" and live every day with maximum efficiency. Download now and discover the innovative face of calendar management!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProtectHeart</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2791010/ProtectHeart/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							ProtectHeart is a strategy and defense game. Your objective is to protect the heart from various enemies, from turtles to fighter jets. You'll get experience points for defeating each enemy, once you have enough points you'll be given an upgrade opportunity that will last for the rest of the game! You need to pick carefully, it could be the difference between surviving and failing.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Forged Wedding</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2656650/My_Forged_Wedding/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a Steam version of a hit visual novel game released on the mobile reader app Love 365: Find Your Story by Voltage Inc. It is a collection of romantic, richly illustrated interactive stories with the following premise:<br/><br/>On a whim, the heroine ends up in a fake marriage to a man she's just met. The two move in together and play at wedded bliss, but spending each day together brings them inevitably closer. What was once just pretend starts to feel real... <br/>Enjoy the will-they-won't-they excitement of newlywed life that begins with a lie in My Forged Wedding!<br/><br/>An opening movie and adventure feature have been added to the Steam release, so even players that have previously read the app version will discover more things to enjoy.<br/><br/><strong>The Story:</strong><br/>"Marry me... Only a month would do."<br/><br/>Due to a twist of fate, you're now pretending to be the wife of a man you've just met. At first, you're against the idea of this fake marriage, but as the days go on and you get to know one another, your mutual attraction deepens...<br/><br/><strong>Characters:</strong><br/>Yamato Kougami  "Physics teacher"<br/>Takamasa Saeki  "Author"<br/>Ren Shibasaki     "Scientist"<br/>Takao Maruyama "Lawyer"<br/>Yuta Kajima        "Comedian"<br/><br/><br/><strong>Contents:</strong><br/>Includes "Main Stories" in the App "Love 365: Find Your Story."<br/>Follows Yamato, Saeki, Ren, and Takao's stories up to "Honeymoon: Epilogue."<br/>Stories for Yuta are included up until "Wedding Bells: Epilogue."						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ElbmarKs</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1856830/ElbmarKs/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1856830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>After surviving more than 3000 years of dissension, fighting, and self-destruction finally we learned to leave together with mother nature and each other, but now mankind needs to face a new, never seen, powerful, external enemy.<br/><br/>Nobody knows where they came from but we realized quickly we have to fight to survive.<br/><br/>A small talented scout team gave their life to localize the base of the alien intruders, scientists working day and night created an enhanced version of our probably biggest invention of all time, a teleport that can send the brave human fighters right inside the enemy base.<br/><br/>But the crux is just coming right now, our heroes must search and acquire all the possible information about the enemy base to hopefully be able to destroy it ...</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1856830/extras/Cover_base.png?t=1710367463"><br/><br/>During the game, you must, destroy lurking enemies, or just avoid or take over them, find and use hidden aids, destroy, deactivate, and avoid different kinds of gates, get through enemy waves, and be patient, accurate, and quick when it's needed, test your memory in the labyrinths.<br/>Do not forget to collect the missing pieces of the enemy base blueprint on each level to get to the next one and be able to unlock new spaceships!<br/><br/>You can select from 3 Difficulty levels, Practice, Normal, and Classic. <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> In Practice difficulty mode you have checkpoints saved to continue from a given part of a level, and 5 lives to complete each and every level<br/></li><li> In Normal difficulty mode you have 3 lives to complete each and every level<br/></li><li> In Classic difficulty mode you only have 3 lives to complete the whole game</li></ul><br/>The game now has a Leaderboard too, but only Normal, and Classic mode results are participating, sorry ;)<h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Spoiler Alert! </u></h2>The game has a physics-based movement system so your space-ship moves with a bit of inertia, it could take a while to get familiar with it, figure out how to avoid or take over e.g. the enemy missiles, but do not give up, it is worth the effort I promise ;)<br/>Precision and accuracy are also key to getting through the levels and you will need stamina too as in Normal Difficulty mode you only have 3 lives to solve a single level, and in the good old Classic mode only 3 to finish the whole game!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multicrash!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2792820/Multicrash/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2792820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">What is Multicrash!</h2>Multicrash! is a simple retro-arcade-survival game where the goal is to get as many points as possible. Manage up to four roads, swapping the ship between two lanes on each road to avoid obstacles, pick up coins for points, or spawn another road. Each round starts off easy, but the speed of the game accelerates over time until surviving on just one road becomes almost unmanageable. However, there are ways to keep the round alive even after reaching max speed. Both spawning new roads and crashing will reset the game speed (yes, crashing can be good!) but remember, more roads = more points: Obviously having more roads means more coins spawn, but each coin is also worth the number of roads alive. This means that with four roads up, (4x coins spawn) x (4x coin value) = (16x efficiency!). The round ends when the last remaining road crashes. See how you compare by competing with others on the global leaderboard.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAT &amp; ONION</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781210/CAT__ONION/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781210/extras/heading9.gif?t=1710271480"><br/>A warm and whimsical cat adventure where you climb, talk, fly and smack your way to places where no cat has ever gone before!<br/><br/>Go on a short yet cosmic journey packed with curious characters, imaginative environments and good vibes.​<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781210/extras/square616_2.gif?t=1710271480"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781210/extras/features.gif?t=1710271480"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>You play as a cat!<br/></li><li>Talk, find items and use your abilities to go where no cat has ever gone before!<br/></li><li>Meet a cast of entertaining characters<br/></li><li>No combat, unless you count smacking stuff with a baseball bat<br/></li><li>An imaginative world<br/></li><li>Takes 30-60 minutes to finish: You'll experience a lot in a short time!<br/></li><li>A jazzy soundtrack<br/></li><li>Secret cat things for curious cats<br/></li><li>Made by one person<br/></li><li>Enjoy chunky pixelart, with a grand total of 8 colors!<br/></li><li>Cat</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781210/extras/seeyou4.gif?t=1710271480"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subterrain: Mines of Titan</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1573100/Subterrain_Mines_of_Titan/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FERRSBJafXZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/extras/SUB-Discord-Banner.gif?t=1710261009"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/extras/SUB-Steam-banner-about-EN.png?t=1710261009"><br/><br/>After a massive meteor strikes the icy surface of Titan, nothing is left but a vast deposit of rare minerals. The TECC mining company rushes to establish a colony on Titan and successfully tap the riches, until the colony goes dark. It takes years to mount a salvage expedition to the far flung moon of Saturn, so make it count. Restart the flow of resources and figure out what happened to the first wave of colonists.<br/><br/>Stand between the sole survivors of Camp Huygens and total obliteration by Saturn's darkest mysteries. Every turn counts in the desperate struggle for survival, as Titan will not wait around - and neither should you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/extras/SUB-Steam-banner-titanic-EN.png?t=1710261009"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Titan is an unrelenting dynamic, persistent world. Every action and step advances time and brings Camp Huygens closer to collapse, unless someone intervenes.<br/></li><li> Help surviving colonists with their tasks, assign key jobs, harvest materials, and organize crafting stations to keep the doom at bay.<br/></li><li> Manage food and water intake, keep tabs on oxygen and energy levels, and treat any sustained injuries, all while penetrating the abandoned mining tunnels beneath the surface.<br/></li><li> Track the passage of time efficiently or it might turn out that the greatest threat to Camp Huygens isn't Titan or its monsters... but you!</li></ul> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/extras/SUB-Steam-banner-darkest-EN.png?t=1710261009"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Unearth the mysteries of Saturn's most famous moon and go deep beneath its surface to face off against its many horrors.<br/></li><li> Fight the monstrosities using intuitive, brisk turn-based combat. Do you make the fight close and personal, risking death as you go toe to toe? Or plink from afar, hoping that ammo won't run out at the wrong time?<br/></li><li> Harness the power of nanomachines to unleash devastating abilities against foes, but also sacrifice the ability to physically pummel monsters into submission?<br/></li><li> Gain experience and power alongside the celestial creatures underground. Evolve and adapt tactics, or perish in the darkness of Titan's mines!</li></ul> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1573100/extras/SUB-Steam-banner-applied-EN.png?t=1710261009"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Craft an endless array of items thanks to a small handful of allies like weapons and elbow grease.<br/></li><li> Salvage what you can, break it down into materials, and produce tools like melee weapons, firearms, protective gear, explosives, and countless survival upgrades.<br/></li><li> Enhance yourself with medical supplies and continue research to develop even better versions.<br/></li><li> Survive long enough to unearth the terrible truth of what happened to the first wave of colonists or find a way to get off the doomed moon, no one said you get both...</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Love Lost</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1873120/No_Love_Lost/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1873120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1873120/extras/Looter-and-player-fight-616x230-_256-colors_-gif-with-title.gif?t=1710265988"><br/><br/><strong>Choose your crew and shuttle down to your battleground:</strong> In this exhilarating third-person, action-adventure, a carnivorous alien planet with a vicious bite awaits your arrival! There’s only one reason to risk your life on Drosera – the lucrative resource called Nectar. Pick 1 of 2 crews to join and get ready to raid! <br/><br/>In 15-minute sessions, race through a vibrant planet with over 4 lush biomes on state-of-the-art hoverboards. Compete in quests to garner your team more Nectar and dodge perilous dangers deep within Drosera. When night falls and the real monsters come out, get back on your extraction ship stat or be left behind to become one with the planet forever!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1873120/extras/Raptor-chase-616x230-_256-colors_-with-title.gif?t=1710265988"><br/><br/><strong>Claw your way to the top: </strong>Choose your gear wisely! With a wide array of both melee and ranged weapons, as well as traps and gadgets, the chance to bring your team to victory is never out of reach…or certain fate.  <br/><br/><strong>Harvest smart or risk it all: </strong>Only those who make it on the extraction ship will leave with their Nectar, so optimize your tactics, rally your crew and use ANY means necessary to get your nectar onboard! <br/><br/><strong>Death is NOT the end:</strong> Our respawn system keeps you and your friends together in the action for the entire raid! Revive fallen teammates and plot your revenge to steal that Nectar back!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1873120/extras/whatdoesntkillyou.gif?t=1710265988"><br/><br/><strong>What kind of Raider will you be? </strong>For every day that you survive, gain perks to strengthen your resolve for the next round! Mix and match builds to get the perfect perk combination but beware! Getting stranded on Drosera means losing your perks until your next successful run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1873120/extras/Horizongif2.gif?t=1710265988"><br/><br/><strong>Discover all the planet has to offer: </strong>Drosera is a world full of mystery and much of it has yet to be revealed! Keep your eye open for continuous updates (such as new biomes, characters and gameplay additions,) being added to the world!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>FEATURES: </strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore a dangerous planet rich with sweet, sweet Nectar in 15-minute sessions!<br/></li><li>Race through DROSERA with top-of-the-line hoverboards and hoverbikes.<br/></li><li>Take part in competitive questing alongside your team and your enemies!<br/></li><li>Experience simultaneous PvP and PvE! Go head-to-head against the other crews and take on Droserian wildlife for bigger rewards!<br/></li><li>Trade in your nectar for fancy hoverboard and weapon skins, express yourself with extra emotes and more!<br/></li><li>Build your perks after every successful extraction to dominate the Raider ranks!<br/></li><li>Experience a new adventure in every game with procedurally generated quest chains!</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goblin Stone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1521970/Goblin_Stone/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FdF7NZJvSuA" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_Discord_00_Banner_616180.gif?t=1710379933"/></a><br/>Goblin Stone entrusts players with the fate of the last goblins to escape annihilation by cruel adventurers. To avoid extinction, they must build their numbers, venture back into the world, and put an end to the adventurers who hunt them. Embark on a heartwarming journey to rebuild a goblin lair and help them thrive in a turn-based roguelite where every decision counts.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_StoreGifs_5f.gif?t=1710379933"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_About_01_Bullets_Combat.png?t=1710379933"><br/>Craft the perfect goblin party by mixing classes, abilities, and genetics. Experience an innovative turn-based combat system, where the order of actions is determined by the strategic positioning of combatants.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_StoreGifs_1f.gif?t=1710379933"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_About_02_Bullets_Adventure.png?t=1710379933"><br/>Guide a merry party of goblins as they battle relentless adventurers, pompous elves, and surly dwarves. Dive into a world with nostalgic, storybook-inspired visuals, accompanied by an epic soundtrack composed by Hearthstone's Peter McConnell.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_StoreGifs_2f.gif?t=1710379933"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_About_03_Bullets_Colony.png?t=1710379933"><br/>Manage a thriving goblin colony and build your lair chamber by chamber, from the Barracks to the War Room. Carefully breed your favorite goblins, combining the finest genes and traits to cultivate a formidable lineage.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_StoreGifs_3f.gif?t=1710379933"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_About_04_Bullets_Choices.png?t=1710379933"><br/>Venture through procedurally generated adventures, where permadeath heightens the stakes. Difficult choices await as you decide which path to take and which goblins to sacrifice for survival.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_StoreGifs_4f.gif?t=1710379933"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_Infographic_Steam_EN_2.png?t=1710379933"><br/><br/>Receive exclusive news, updates, and perks by joining our active community on the <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FdF7NZJvSuA" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Goblin Stone Discord</a>.<br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FdF7NZJvSuA" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1521970/extras/GS_Discord_00_Banner_616180.gif?t=1710379933"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
