<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>SteamWorld Build</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2134770/SteamWorld_Build/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-Homestead.png?t=1701446569"><br/>One final landrush! The planet is dyin', Astrid, and it's dig or die trying! <br/><br/>That mine under our town is sitting empty, and wouldn't you know there's rumours of ancient tech down there that might help us out of this predicament. Round up the posse, circle the wagons, and let's get to buildin' a new home! Collect resources above ground and ores down below so we can get those wealthy bots in here to help us build bigger, and we can get the heck out of here!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_1.gif?t=1701446569"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_manage.png?t=1701446569"><br/>As your borders expand, new steamfolk will find their way to you! Every bot is crotchety in their own way, and it's up to you to keep them steaming along. Barter to boost efficiency, keep goods flowing to and from the mines and keep everyone happy to make them work their darndest and hardest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_2.gif?t=1701446569"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-DIG-DEEP.png?t=1701446569"><br/><br/>Stare into the abyss long enough and it might just stare back... we're going looking for riches and something down there doesn't want to share! Have gun, dig gravel, and make sure the mines don't collapse upon you as you defend yourselves from the creepy crawlies that lurk within...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_3.gif?t=1701446569"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_features.png?t=1701446569"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break ground on a bustling SteamWorld town, inspired by the Old West.<br/></li><li>Keep your steambots from getting cranky by ensuring their complex needs get met<br/></li><li>Dig deep and spread wide to produce resources to aid your search for ancient technologies<br/></li><li>Defend your mine from the creepy varmints that lurk deep below your town<br/></li><li>Trade resources at the local train stop and welcome special visitors who'll lend a hand<br/></li><li>Five distinct maps littered with secrets for the discerning SteamWorld explorer to find<br/></li><li>Developed from the ground up for both mouse and controller, whichever takes yer fancy.<br/></li><li>Four difficulty levels, including a sandbox difficulty for when you just want to Build!</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HoloParade</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2647230/HoloParade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">A lively parade with hololive VTubers and mascot characters!</h2><br/>"HoloParade" is a fan game of hololive and the first title to serve as a test case for "holo Indie". Collect, nurture, and enjoy watching your favorite characters! It's a 2D tower defense game that offers depth, strategy, and can also be enjoyed casually.<br/><br/>What is "holo Indie"?:<br/>It is a general term for a game brand for derivative work games, produced using the "game creator support program" with the aim of co-creating with fans and creators of hololive Production around the world.<h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 1: Simple Yet Deep, Lively Battles</h2>The basic system is a classic 2D tower defense game where you summon characters from your base and march them forward to destroy the enemy's base to win. While the controls are simple, the gameplay is profoundly deep. With over 65 characters, each possessing a variety of abilities like ally healing support and self-destruct attacks, skillful combination and flexible formation are key to enjoying the game.<br/><br/>Additionally, there's an element inspired by parades called the 'Symphony Effect,' where various effects are activated based on the musical instruments played by the characters in march. This adds further strategic depth to the formation of your parade squad and the order of their summoning.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Battle.gif?t=1701417555"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 2: Comprehensive Development Elements</h2>In addition to leveling up and limit breaking, there is a 'Skill' system that allows you to add special abilities not available through regular development. Since you can add up to three types of skills to each character and select them carefully, you can enjoy a unique development process! Furthermore, since you can reset levels and get a full refund of the coins spent, it allows for more freedom in restructuring formations and character development.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Skill_ENG.gif?t=1701417555"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 3: No Gacha Purchases, No Stamina System</h2>The scout gacha, which allows you to acquire characters, can be used by consuming tickets obtained within the game, with no additional purchases required. Also, as there is no stamina system, you are not bound by time and can play as much as you like, whenever you like.<br/><br/>Moreover, the scout gacha allows you to choose from two randomly selected character candidates, enabling players to make selections based on their strategy or preference rather than leaving it entirely to chance.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Gacha_ENG.gif?t=1701417555"><h2 class="bb_tag">Feature 4: Take a Break with Various Talents and Mini-Games in the Office</h2>When you return to the office, the home screen, you'll be greeted by newly recorded voice lines from Harusaki Nodoka, a staff member of hololive. In the office, talents from hololive may also make appearances, and you might witness some unexpected interactions.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/Home_ENG.png?t=1701417555"><br/><br/>Additionally, mini-games with entirely different gameplay from the main story are implemented. These games allow you to collect coins necessary for character strengthening. At the initial release, a mini-game titled "Hurry Up! Miko-Chi!" is available, where Sakura Miko (a VTuber affiliated with hololive) who overslept, dashes at full speed towards her destination while avoiding obstacles. More mini-games are planned to be added in future updates.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2647230/extras/RunMikoti.gif?t=1701417555"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Truck Simulator - Kansas</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2298430/American_Truck_Simulator__Kansas/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2298430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Introducing Kansas! A U.S State that is home to a truly authentic cowboy culture and miles of land littered with wildflowers. Located in the Midwest of the USA, Kansas is known for its native grasslands, streams, abundant blue skies, and green grassland vistas. <br/><br/>Once considered to be the country’s agricultural heartland, "The Sunflower State" has managed to attract many large businesses and develop in other industrial areas due to its central location and convenient infrastructure for logistics operations. But, as the nickname suggests, nature is certainly doing very well to keep up with technological progress, as the state parks and vast prairies offer unique views with a marvelous atmosphere that will leave every trucker passing by with something to remember.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Deliver to 14 explorable cities including Kansas City, Wichita, or Topeka<br/></li><li>See several landmarks unique to Kansas such as the historic Dodge City, Monument Rocks, and Mount Sunflower<br/></li><li>Become a trucker transporting goods for Kansas' key industries - Salt Mine, Food Factory, Car Factory, Building Material Factory, and Battery Factory<br/></li><li>Deliver cargo to Aerosystem, playing a key role in Wichita's aerospace industry<br/></li><li>Visit Hutchinson and admire the world's largest silos<br/></li><li>Play a crucial role in one of America's largest agricultural states. Transport goods that sustain Kansas' farming legacy<br/></li><li>Enjoy trucking through several scenic towns (settlements)<br/></li><li>Drive through expansive prairies, providing unforgettable views</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Truck Simulator - Farm Machinery</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2638630/American_Truck_Simulator__Farm_Machinery/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Saddle up drivers, because the Farm Machinery DLC for American Truck Simulator has arrived! Transport everything from trusty tractors to forage harvesters across scenic virtual highways and roads. <br/><br/>Featuring 2 in-game brands, Owl &amp; Greenler, you'll be able to deliver a variety of unique cargoes on Lowboy, Dropdeck or Flatbed trailers to a number of agriculture-related industries large and small across the country.<br/><br/>This DLC includes:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Sprayer <br/></li><li>Crawler Tractor <br/></li><li>Forage Harvester <br/></li><li>Fertilizer Spreader <br/></li><li>Grain Trailer<br/></li><li>Autonomous Tractor <br/></li><li>Hay Baler <br/></li><li>Seeding Unit <br/></li><li>Disc Harrow</li></ul><br/>Naturally, we couldn't let you go driving without some themed cabin accessories for your cabin either! <br/><br/>Cabin Accessories<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Lunch Kit<br/></li><li>Scarecrow <br/></li><li>Straw Hat <br/></li><li>Stuffed Autonomous Tractor <br/></li><li>Harvester Toy </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turok 3: Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1996770/Turok_3_Shadow_of_Oblivion_Remastered/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/raptor_jumps.gif?t=1701367237"><br/><br/><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> is a faithful restoration of the classic first-person shooter originally released in 2000 for the Nintendo 64, upgraded through Nightdive Studios’ proprietary KEX Engine for play on modern gaming devices with up to a 4K resolution at 120FPS. <br/><br/>It joins Nightdive Studios and Universal Games popular Turok and Turok 2: Seeds of Evil remasters, capping off the trilogy. <i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> features upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<h2 class="bb_tag">FINISH THE HUNT</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/sniper_one_eye.gif?t=1701367237"><br/><br/><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> is the first title from Nightdive Studios to be remastered using the latest version KEX engine, which utilizes an improved renderer to achieve a higher tier of visual fidelity across 3D models, textures, and graphical effects.<h2 class="bb_tag"><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> Key Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A remastered version of the 2000 classic, available for the first time since its Nintendo 64 release<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS performance<br/></li><li>Advanced rendering features, including anti-aliasing, bloom, ambient occlusion, dynamic shadows, and motion blur	<br/></li><li>Remastered environment art, character models, and updated weapon models<br/></li><li>Brand new Achievements</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/robot.gif?t=1701367237"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinball M</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2337640/Pinball_M/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-1.png?t=1701438722"><br/><br/>The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-2.png?t=1701438722"><br/><br/>- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free<br/>- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage<br/>- Thrilling competition<br/>- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation<h2 class="bb_tag">Sink your teeth into these tables as purchasable DLC: </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">- Chucky's Killer Pinball:</h2> Step into a twisted realm where the innocent becomes sinister, and the playful turns menacing. Navigate through an eerie playfield where Chucky lurks in the shadows, ready to pounce.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Dead by Daylight™️ Pinball:</h2> Become the hunter or even the hunted in a thrilling fusion of classic pinball and the excitement of one of the most popular horror games ever created.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Duke Nukem's Big Shot Pinball:</h2> Enjoy the biggest, grooviest, most BADASS pinball table ever made packed with guns and babes. Push start and play with balls of steel!<h2 class="bb_tag">- The Thing Pinball: </h2>Use your pinball skills and battle against the shape-shifting alien through the arctic chill of U.S. Outpost #31. Can you trust anyone, even yourself?<br/>- Even more coming...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-4.png?t=1701438722"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Gladius - Drukhari</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668040/Warhammer_40000_Gladius__Drukhari/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<i>“What was it like, back then? Just sheer joy, I’m told. Entire civilizations, rendered down for stimulants. Stars drained dry of their power, for a decade-long soiree. Oh, to have been alive and powerful in the last days of Empire - before She-Who-Thirsts…” </i><br/>- Gyrthineus Roche, former Archon of The Last Blade.<br/><br/>The <strong>Drukhari </strong>are an ancient race that fell into degeneracy and depravity, with their remnants only surviving in immense Webway cities. Though they have suppressed the psychic power of their Aeldari kin, they have replaced it with preternatural agility and rapacious cruelty. Their lighting raids from the Webway carry off wealth and captives to dark Commorragh where they suffer intensely throughout their short lives…<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Mechanics </h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Power from Pain</strong>: As pain spreads across the battlefield, Drukhari are invigorated, thriving from the suffering. Their units gain additional bonuses depending on their experience level. <br/></li><li><strong>Corsair Outposts</strong>: The Drukhari rarely venture outside the webway, save to loot realspace resources. Their cities have a reduced growth rate, but it can be improved by controlling more outposts. <br/></li><li><strong>Raid from the Webway</strong>: The Drukhari strike swiftly from the webway, before vanishing with their plunder. Pay influence to create temporary portals and activate webway gates to move your raiding party across the map.<br/></li><li><strong>Raider Fortress</strong>: The Aeldari and Drukhari are forever battling over their access to the webway. Found cities on activated webway gates from which you can unleash your forces on Gladius Prime.<br/></li><li><strong>Soul Hunger</strong>: The souls harvested by the Drukhari are an invaluable resource used for their malevolent schemes. Destroying an enemy unit rewards you with influence that can be traded for economic boosts and combat effects. <br/></li><li><strong>Combat Drugs</strong>: The Drukhari’s foul Haemonculi render down some captives into powerful stimulants. Infantry units can pay with influence and hitpoints for temporary buffs that allow them to outperform their opponents. <br/></li><li><strong>Betrayal Culture</strong>: Drukhari are a vicious race, and only a huge display of riches will convince them to serve—as long as it also serves their interests. Drukhari cities have lower loyalty but gathering influence grants more loyalty. <br/></li><li><strong>Blade Artists</strong>: Blades have an omnipresent place in Drukhari culture, and each commorrite learns this from a young age. Drukhari units get bonus armour penetration in melee. <br/></li><li><strong>Raiders tactics</strong>: When attacking a new prey world, the Drukhari attack en masse from their specially designed vehicles to land troops as close as possible to the fighting. Drukhari transports are all assault transports and Drukhari infantry units can gain combat bonuses when disembarking.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Complete Units Roster </h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Archon <br/></li><li>Cronos<br/></li><li>Haemonculus<br/></li><li>Hellions<br/></li><li>Incubi <br/></li><li>Kabalite Trueborn<br/></li><li>Kabalite Warriors<br/></li><li>Raider<br/></li><li>Ravager<br/></li><li>Razorwing Jetfighter<br/></li><li>Reavers<br/></li><li>Scourges<br/></li><li>Succubus<br/></li><li>Tantalus<br/></li><li>Venom<br/></li><li>Voidraven Bomber<br/></li><li>Webway Portal<br/></li><li>Wracks<br/></li><li>Wyches</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truck &amp; Logistics Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/873840/Truck__Logistics_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Load, drive, and deliver through a huge open world with up to 24 players in cross-platform multiplayer. Join your friends in exciting heavy transport convoys. Jump into the driver's seat of more than 30 unique vehicles and carry out complex loading tasks to deliver a variety of cargo.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Load.gif?t=1701358833"><br/><br/><strong>Load pallets, containers, vehicles &amp; more!</strong><br/>Each mission is unique and comes with its own challenges. Start up your business by loading pallets into vans with a forklift. Then work your way up to loading heavy containers with telescopic handlers onto trailers. Maneuver vehicles such as cars, forklifts, skid-steers, wheel-loaders and more onto your trailers. Hundreds of unique and challenging missions and deliveries await you! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Drive.gif?t=1701358833"><br/><br/><strong>Drive cars, vans, trucks &amp; more!</strong><br/>Drive and customize over 30 unique vehicles. From minivans to heavy trucks, each vehicle has its own detailed interior and realistic driving physics. Vehicles can be damaged, causing axles to bend and making driving difficult. Refuel and repair at service stations to get back on the road in full swing. Make each vehicle your own by customizing it to your liking. Stick to the traffic rules or risk getting fined in random police traffic controls and radar speed cameras. Push your driving skills to the limit in many diverse and challenging missions.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Deliver.gif?t=1701358833"><br/><br/><strong>Deliver in an open world with up to 24 friends!</strong><br/>Enjoy the ultimate delivery experience in co-op multiplayer. Join your friends, make convoys, earn money and expand your companies together. Escort other players safely to their destinations using specialized convoy equipment. Explore a vast 28 km² open world, from bustling cities to tranquil rural areas. Explore and uncover hidden secrets scattered across the map. Get ready for a journey into a dynamic and completely open world where the deliveries never end!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 30 unique vehicles with realistic interiors<br/></li><li>Huge 28km² open world (no hidden walls!)<br/></li><li>Cross-platform multiplayer with up to 24 players<br/></li><li>Escort convoys in co-op multiplayer missions<br/></li><li>Full day / night cycle<br/></li><li>Hundreds of different challenging missions<br/></li><li>Realistic driving physics and damage system<br/></li><li>Vehicle customization<br/></li><li>Random police traffic controls &amp; speed cameras</li></ul><br/>Start your company today! Join our community below, see you on the road!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FPCjxFjs" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/873840/extras/Discord_2023.gif?t=1701358833"/></a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEVI</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2230650/TEVI/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FZ9KrdFvNRK" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/JoinUsOnDC.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Action-Packed_Combo_System.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/戰鬥動圖.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>The protagonist Tevi is nimble and agile, wielding both her trusty dagger and an oversized wrench for dishing out melee damage in style. Alongside her, companions Celia and Sable manifest as two floating orbitars, ready to unleash a variety of ranged offensive and supportive magic in battle. Adapt your combat style to suit any situation and bring down foes with flashy, dazzling combos!<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Thrilling_Boss_Battles.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Boss.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Every boss fight is a unique challenge requiring different strategies to tackle, all while you dodge their attacks and look for openings to counter-attack. <br/>As bosses change phases, their attack and bullet patterns become increasingly challenging, and they can even unleash devastating ultimates. Continual offense can submit bosses into a vulnerable BREAK state, during which you can deal massive bursts of damage.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Myriad_Abilities,_Equipment,_and_Exploration.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/badge.jpg?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Scattered across the the expansive world, there are over 300 different items and pieces of equipment waiting to be discovered. These items can enhance your abilities or introduce new ones, allowing you to find more methods of navigating the world and finding secrets. A cornucopia of equippable sigils can be freely configured to create builds tailored to your preferences and playstyle.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/A_Rich,_Expansive_Fantasy_World.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/場景6.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Dive into the vibrant world of Az, in which you will discover various towns, regions, peoples, histories, and civilizations, each with their own tale to tell. Along the way, you'll meet a large cast of strange and colorful characters. As their tales unfold and intertwine, you'll be drawn into a tale full of adventure, friendship, mysteries, and danger... <br/><br/>Get ready to embark on an unforgettable adventure, writing your own epic journey alongside Tevi!<br/><br/><a href="https://youtu.be/psxior_WswQ" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/角色介紹.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tevi（VA: Lynn）<br/></li><li>Celia（VA: Yoko Hikasa）<br/></li><li>Sable（VA: Natsumi Fujiwara）<br/></li><li>Zema（VA: Tomokazu Sugita）<br/></li><li>Vena（VA: Rie Kugimiya）</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Suika - Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2671970/My_Suika__Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A fun watermelon merge puzzle game!<br>
<br>
Think you can get 3000 points in this addictive watermelon puzzle game?<br>
<br>
Combine various matching fruits to help Kyo gather watermelons! Unlock new game modes and new fruit skins by obtaining high scores. Compete against other players on the global leaderboards!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call to Arms - Gates of Hell: Liberation</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2447590/Call_to_Arms__Gates_of_Hell_Liberation/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<strong>“Soldiers, Sailors, and Airmen of the Allied Expeditionary Force: you are about to embark upon the Great Crusade!”<br/>This DLC introduces the western front action in 1944, featuring the US faction, as well as German western front content.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/01Sherman.gif?t=1701279518"><br/><br/>Be among the first to scale the Atlantic wall and fight your way through the Bocage. <br/>Be the spearhead that breaks the stalemate in the battle of the Bulge. <br/>Re-live the rush to the Rhine bridge, on the road into the heart of Germany!<br/><br/>Or, fight for the Wehrmacht and be the one that leads the counterattacks, the one that stops the breakout. In other words; be the one that defends “Fortress Europe” facing all the classic dilemmas that come with it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/02Beach.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Single Player</h2>The single player campaigns focus on four legendary western front units: the “Liberation” campaign has the 2nd Rangers and the 3rd Armored Division on the US side. Beside 6 single player missions, this DLC also offers 4 skirmishes for the US faction, which are part of the campaign storyline.<br/>In all of the missions, you will find yourself in intense battles on iconic battlegrounds, recreated to the last detail; get a taste of the bitter fighting against fanatical opposition, liberating western Europe step by hellish step. The action will be intense and the immersion will be up there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/03Nebel.gif?t=1701279518"><br/><br/>The German campaign,  “Festung Europa”, has the 3rd Fallschirmjäger division and 116th Panzer division on the German side in 6 intense and compelling missions.<br/>Be the one that commands the Wehrmacht forces on the western front from Normandy to the last battles in the Ruhr pocket. In the German campaign you will enjoy a lot of new content as well! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/04Maps.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer</h2>“Liberation” adds the USA to multiplayer with 20 brand new western front MP maps, and all of the new weapons, vehicles and tanks; it also adds a new German late war doctrine.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/05Mist.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Conquest</h2>For conquest, 25 western front maps are included. These, like other maps, use the unique set of assets we have created to immerse you in the western front atmosphere. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/06wespe.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Visuals</h2>Liberation pushes the boundary of the visuals of the Gates of Hell universe to a new standard, with hundreds of highly detailed environment models, improved destruction for buildings and beautiful environments. To ensure the historical accuracy of our content, we have collaborated with WW2 Armor in Florida, who provided us with vast amounts of valuable documentation and knowledge.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2447590/extras/07Logo.gif?t=1701279518"><h2 class="bb_tag">Content</h2>The Liberation DLC contains:<ul class="bb_ul"><li>10 US single player missions, including 4 US skirmishes<br/></li><li>6 German single player missions<br/></li><li>150+  new US and German vehicles, cannon, ships, aircraft and tanks<br/></li><li>50 new small arms<br/></li><li>500+ new humanskins<br/></li><li>20 new MP maps<br/></li><li>25 new DCG (Conquest) maps<br/></li><li>500+ new editor assets for the western European theater.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MULLER-POWELL PRINCIPLE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2155770/THE_MULLERPOWELL_PRINCIPLE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FeY9JWyTaAm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_discord.png?t=1701271403"/></a><br/><br/>It is a sci-fi story that takes place in the near future. You are Harry Herman, an employee of Delta Laboratories who researches interdimensional traveling. You had been participating in a project that was supposed to benefit all humanity, but something went wrong. Through the gameplay, you will solve various physics-based puzzles using an energy-manipulating weapon, travel across space and time to explore surrealistic universes and find out the dark truth about this project and your connection to it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_gameplay.png?t=1701271403"><br/>Solve various puzzles and trick enemies using physics interactions and your special tool - the Portable Energy Manipulator. <br/><br/><strong>PHYSICS PUZZLES &amp; INTERACTIVE ENVIRONMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/gameplay_physics.gif?t=1701271403"><br/><br/>Many objects in the game can be picked up, brought somewhere, or manipulated in other ways. Whether it's a computer terminal, a box you can carry, or a simple mug on a table. Explore various interactive environments to find clues and return to the riddle with a solution, which in some cases may be several. Nothing was made for you to solve, there's no cube dispenser or an obvious exit door at the end. It's all for you to figure out.<br/><br/><strong>PORTABLE ENERGY MANIPULATOR</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/gif_photongun.gif?t=1701271403"><br/><br/>The device you carry throughout the game can absorb different energy types from the environment and use them to perform various tasks.<br/><br/>Absorbing energy from a particular source will give the gun its’ properties. The heat energy from fire and radiators will melt glass, security cameras can be blinded by a beam of light, and for powering generators, you can take hazardous radiation from toxic puddles scattered across Delta Labs facilities. And of course, you will make an encounter with the quantum entanglement energy - the mysterious power capable of opening rifts between worlds. <br/><br/>Apart from solving environmental puzzles, your device can also be used against various creatures you'll meet in parallel dimensions. Most of the time you can't defeat your enemies; instead, you can use the Manipulator to outsmart or suspend them. Some enemies can be frozen in place using the force field energy, while others are sensitive to light and can be distracted by shooting a beam at it in the distance. You will require more advanced strategies and combining various energy types to pass them.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_story.png?t=1701271403"><br/>You find yourself in one of Delta Labs' off-world research facilities in an unknown dimension that looks more like a crashing-down laboratory. Your old friends Eugene and Alex try to connect with you shortly, and with their help, you start a journey through various dimensions. You will learn different physics interactions and meet unusual creatures on your way home. Along this, you have to unveil the mysteries of this project and your past. <br/><br/>Experience a non-linear story where your choice always matters. Can you get to the bottom of this, or just try to escape? Who to listen? Who to trust? Which side will you take? And will you finally “break the Principle”? That depends entirely on you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_setting.png?t=1701271403"><br/>Make your way back to Earth through mysterious parallel dimensions littered with puzzles and secrets, uncover mysterious connections between the worlds you visit, and reveal the dark truth about Delta Labs and your involvement with them. Dare to explore?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2155770/extras/art_features.png?t=1701271403"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Solve various physics-based puzzles<br/></li><li>Unique gameplay mechanics that involve an energy-manipulating weapon <br/></li><li>A mix of sci-fi with surreal and esoteric themes makes the game setting a unique design. Most of the time you'll spend in bizarre alien dimensions<br/></li><li>Deeply thought-out story and lore. Each location and each character in the game has its own story revealed through various notes, environmental narratives, and characters' conversations.<br/></li><li>The game features multiple endings that can be achieved through different choices </li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn around immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Other</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1701359196"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1701359196"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1701359196"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retro Commander</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/338820/Retro_Commander/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/338820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/338820/extras/icon_and_text_v05_-_600x195px.png?t=1700862195"><br/>Retro Commander is a <strong>post-apocalyptic</strong> real-time strategy wargame (RTS). Take command and fight it out in a world where a cataclysmic timeline has transpired on Mother Earth. Wage wars solo, against the AI, or take on your gaming comrades and friends in cross-platform multiplayer matches. Form teams and clans and fight co-op style with the AI and other players for ultimate victory.<br/><br/>As opposed to other real-time strategy game, Retro Commander tries to focus on both, a fun <strong>single player</strong> and a thrilling <strong>multiplayer</strong> experience. The game strives to be easy to learn with a modern user interface. Single player comes with skirmish matches against the AI as well as a comic-based <strong>story campaign</strong>. Multiplayer can be played cross-platform and includes a ranking and rating system.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u>Post-Apocalyptic</u>: Real-time strategy (RTS) played in a post-apocalyptic timeline on Mother Earth. The environment includes day-night cycles, rain, snow, wind and solar flare activity.<br/></li><li><u>Story Campaign</u>: Deep campaign and story line of humanity after a cataclysmic event. Factions come with their own specialized <strong>technologies</strong> such as stealth, robots, drones or shields.<br/></li><li><u>Single &amp; Multiplayer</u>: A challenging AI for both single and multiplayer matches with co-op play. Cross-platform multiplayer including <strong>LAN</strong>/internet. ONLINE play comes with an award and rating system.<br/></li><li><u>Play Modes</u>: In addition to regular skirmish matches, the game supports missions such as elimination, survival, <strong>capture the flag</strong>, defense and <strong>battle royale</strong>. Available in both single and multiplayer also are escort and rescue missions.<br/></li><li><u>Structures &amp; Troops</u>: Common troops for land, sea and air warfare is available to all factions. Specialized elements such as stealth, shields, <strong>EMP</strong> weapons, nukes, <strong>portals</strong>, orbital weapons, assimilator and other troops and structures provide for additional variety.<br/></li><li><u>Research</u>: A <strong>tech tree</strong> and research options enable to build specialized structures and troops. A <strong>Tech Snatcher</strong> can be used to steal enemy technology.<br/></li><li><u>Modding</u>: A map editor is included allowing for player-modded maps including player-modded campaigns. All elements including troops, structures, as well as graphics and sound effects, can be modded if desired.</li></ul><br/>Although some troops are shared, the game is trying not to be a generic RTS-games. There are <strong>faction-specific technologies</strong> each with their strengths and weaknesses.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><u>GRA Technology</u>: gives access to <strong>stealth</strong> and cloaking. Included are cloaked agents and spies as well as bombers with EMP and nuclear weapons. Available also are snipers and heavy airlifts. Can build uranium fabricators.<br/></li><li><u>ELC Technology</u>: provides <strong>robots</strong>, <strong>airships</strong> and robo dogs. Available also are a mechanic and heavy airlift. Can build stationary EMP-field generators.<br/></li><li><u>IDB Technology</u>: provides <strong>hovertanks</strong>, <strong>drones</strong> including EMP-field drones and drones equipped with napalm weapons. Can build fusion generators for power.<br/></li><li><u>Mayan Technology</u>: consists of <strong>decoy</strong> capabilities. Included are hologram tanks, transformers, dogs and dolphins. Can build <strong>portals</strong>.<br/></li><li><u>Ancient Technology</u>: provides <strong>shields</strong>, EMP soldiers, assimilators and napalm tanks. Can build matter fabricators.</li></ul><br/><strong>Free vs Paid (DLC or in-game)</strong>: The free version includes unlimited access to over 12+ multiplayer scenarios and Chapter 01 of the single player campaign. Purchasing the DLC <strong>"All Maps &amp; Modding"</strong> grants full access to the game. It includes everything for single player including the story campaign, skirmishing against the AI, ONLINE multiplayer or LAN-play with friends and family.<br/><br/><strong>No DRM</strong>: There is no DRM in the game. You <strong>don't need to connected to the internet</strong> to play single player games or the campaign. You don't need to be logged in to play LAN games either. You don't need to login either for WAN games (locally hosted games over the internet), but you will have to work out your router settings and do the appropriate port-forwarding so your friends can connect from remote.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Stars And Time</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1677310/In_Stars_And_Time/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FZzFSRUBXEC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/discordbanner620.gif?t=1701180941"/></a><br/><br/><strong>What would you do if you were forced to relive your failures over and over again?</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam5_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> tells the story of Siffrin and their adventurer friends—a found family bound together by fate in order to end the tyrannical reign of an evil king. But as victory is just within the party’s grasp, a tragedy occurs, the clock resets, and <strong>they have to do it all again</strong>. <br/><br/>As Siffrin’s the only one who notices this loop, each new start wears away at his cheerful veneer, yet he keeps going in hopes he can end this temporal tragedy once and for all.<br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> is a <strong>time-looping RPG adventure</strong>. With each loop, Siffrin gains a new perspective on the world around them, opening up new solutions to puzzles and allowing them to make better choices in conversation. Equip memories as armor, pray to the Change God to improve your team’s capabilities each loop, and challenge deadly foes to Rock, Paper, Scissors as Siffrin seeks the truth.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam4_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Our Adventurers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Siffrin (he/they):</strong> Stressed, depressed, and under duress. (Don’t worry about it. They’re doing fine.) The punmaster protagonist of our neverending tale.<br/></li><li><strong>Mirabelle (she/her):</strong> A caring and nervous housemaiden mysteriously blessed by the god she so ardently follows.<br/></li><li><strong>Isabeau (he/him):</strong> Defender with a heart of gold. Cares dearly for his people and his friends.<br/></li><li><strong>Odile (she/her):</strong> The mature and nonsensical researcher studying…something. (No, she will not tell you what it is.)<br/></li><li><strong>Bonnie (they/them):</strong> Wait a minute, who brought this kid along???</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Save the world through the power of Rock, Paper, Scissors in <strong>strategic turn-based RPG</strong> combat encounters.<br/></li><li>Ignore the limits of time and space to <strong>fix your past mistakes</strong> by repeating the same two days over and over again.<br/></li><li>Equip the <strong>memories you have of your friends</strong> to make your party stronger in combat. <br/></li><li><strong>Watch the fate of this world unfold</strong> as you escape the twists and turns of this endless(???) loop.<br/></li><li>Eat <strong>samossas</strong> with your friends!<br/></li><li>Get heckled by a <strong>cheeky ethereal being of infinite starlight</strong>.<br/></li><li>Pray to a god for good luck in your travels. <strong>You’re gonna need it.</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam2_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/>If any of this interests you, you might also want to play the game’s initial prototype, <u><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1691420/START_AGAIN_a_prologue/" rel="" target="_blank">START AGAIN START AGAIN START AGAIN: A Prologue</a></u>. While you don’t need to play it to understand In Stars and Time, it’s fun to see the game’s roots.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bluey: The Videogame</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2078350/Bluey_The_Videogame/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2078350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2078350/extras/Bluey_PLAYTIME_615x80_ENG_v2.png?t=1700751917"><br/><br/>Join the fun with Bluey and her family in Bluey: The Videogame! <br/><br/>Play a brand-new story set across 4 interactive adventures. For the first time ever, explore iconic locations such as the Heeler House, Playgrounds, Creek and a bonus beach location. Play your favourite games from the TV show, including Keepy Uppy, Chattermax Chase, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2078350/extras/Play_time_gif_Bluey.gif?t=1700751917"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2078350/extras/Bluey_CO-OP_615x80_ENGv3.png?t=1700751917"><br/><br/>The fun doesn't stop there! This game won't be trifficult, just a lot of fun. Experience the joy and wonder of Bluey's world, with local multiplayer you can play with friends and family in story mode and free play!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2078350/extras/Co-op_gif_Bluey.gif?t=1700751917"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2078350/extras/Bluey_EXPLORE_615x80_ENGv3.png?t=1700751917"><br/><br/>Explore and collect items for your sticker book, unlock outfits and uncover the many secrets and hidden references throughout each location. Recreate iconic scenes or create your very own Bluey inspired adventures and games. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2078350/extras/Explore_gif_Bluey.gif?t=1700751917"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play time - Play as Bluey and her family including Chilli, Bingo and Bandit.<br/><br/></li><li>Co-op play - Play with your family and friends in a variety of exciting games and challenges.<br/><br/></li><li>Explore -  Recreate iconic moments from the TV series and immerse yourself in Bluey’s world</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 5 Tactica</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2254740/Persona_5_Tactica/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join the Phantom Thieves as they lead an uprising of the heart! Assemble a team of beloved heroes in a brand-new story in this thrilling combat adventure set in Persona’s iconic universe. The Persona 5 Tactica: Digital Deluxe Edition includes the following content:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Repaint Your Heart Challenge Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Weapon Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Picaro Summoning Pack + Raoul Persona</li></ul><br/><strong>Ignite your heart— An emotional uprising begins!</strong><br/><br/>After a strange incident, the Phantom Thieves wander into a bizarre realm where its citizens are living under tyrannical oppression. Surrounded by a military group named Legionnaires, they find themselves in grave danger until a mysterious revolutionary named Erina rescues them and offers an enticing deal in exchange for their help. What truth lies behind Erina and the deal she offers to the Phantom Thieves?<br/><br/>Persona 5 Tactica features an all-new story, the return of fan-favorite characters, and brand-new allies and foes. Join the group as they lead an emotional revolution in this thrilling combat adventure!<br/><br/><strong>An Emotional Revolution</strong><br/>Lead an uprising of the heart in a brand-new storyline that takes place in Persona’s iconic universe.<br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Squad</strong><br/>Assemble a team of beloved heroes to fight oppressive armies in thrilling turn-based combat.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Combat</strong><br/>Overthrow your enemies with powerful Personas, an assortment of weapons, and wipe them out with style!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loddlenaut</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1644940/Loddlenaut/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1644940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Loddlenaut is an ocean cleanup adventure set on a vibrant alien planet. Play as an interstellar custodian who is tasked with cleaning up the pollution left behind by spacefaring mega-corporation. Befriend local axolotl-like creatures and explore sunken corporate ruins as you revive the planet’s lush ecosystems.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1644940/extras/MarchHeroGif_Steam.gif?t=1701254395"><br/><br/>🚀 <strong>Explore</strong> an open-world alien planet<br/>🐠 <strong>Raise</strong> aquatic critters called “loddles” that grow based on what they eat<br/>🔫 <strong>Clean up</strong> icky goop and floating debris with your bubble gun<br/>🌟 <strong>Unlock</strong> special gadgets to clean different types of ocean pollution<br/>🛠️ <strong>Recycle</strong> collected trash to craft useful items and upgrades<h2 class="bb_tag">BRING GUP-14 BACK TO LIFE</h2>Your mission: Clean up the ocean planet of GUP-14 after it was abandoned by GUPPI, a mega-corporation that makes and sells everything from soda to spaceships. When you first arrive on the planet, you’ll find yourself amid murky waters, oil spills, and scattered junk.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1644940/extras/MarchCleanupGif_Steam.gif?t=1701254395"><br/><br/>Within the polluted environments, you’ll find remnants of GUPPI’s buildings, ships, and machinery all sunken to the ocean floor. Discover clues about the planet’s past inhabitants as you clean up the mess they left behind using an assortment of high-tech gadgets.<h2 class="bb_tag">BEFRIEND ALL THE LODDLES</h2>As you clean up the planet, you’ll run into axolotl-like aliens known as “loddles.” Protect them from the polluted waters and feed them aquatic fruits while you make their planet habitable again. Depending on their diet, loddles will grow in different ways and develop unique traits and abilities that will further enable them to survive on this polluted planet.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1644940/extras/LoddleEvoGif_BestBorder.gif?t=1701254395"><br/><br/>When the loddles are strong enough and the waters are cleaner, release them back into the wild and watch them thrive! You may even come across eggs that you can incubate to raise more loddles.<br/><br/><i>0.05GBP per sale on Steam is donated to WDC, Whale and Dolphin Conservation. WDC is a UK registered charity no. 1014705.</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Saga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1320140/Small_Saga/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Venture below the streets of London, and you will find the medieval kingdom of rats, mice, moles, squirrels, and shrews known as Rodentia.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G8.gif?t=1701437888"><br/><br/>If the rodents have a cardinal law, it is this: never attack a god. But Verm never had much respect for the rule of law. His tail was stolen by the Yellow God of Death, and now the mouse will have to fight all manner of beasts and titans on his quest to get it back.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G5.gif?t=1701437888"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1320140/extras/G1.gif?t=1701437888"><br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Team up with a colorful cast of misfit rodents.<br/></li><li>Encounter awe-inspiring titans. Clash with a swashbuckling water vole, a pious lab rabbit, a poetry-spewing kraken, and many more.<br/></li><li>Meet the hideous vermin who run society, then overthrow them.<br/></li><li>Brandish your tiny weapons in strategic, turn-based combat. <br/></li><li>There is no grinding. Small Saga is a tightly-focused and boss-oriented adventure.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero's Adventure: Road to Passion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1948980/Heros_Adventure_Road_to_Passion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FFPnrtuXddA" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/JOIN_OUR_DISCORD.png?t=1700823813"/></a><br/><br/>In <i>Hero's Adventure:Road to Passion</i>, you commence your journey as an underdog in the tumultuous Jianghu - a vibrant world teeming with martial artists - and are met with a wide array of choices as you navigate your heroic saga. Whether it’s training under a battle-hardened warrior to become a master of martial arts, or following Taoist rituals to reach self-enlightenment, you’re the hero, and this is your adventure.<br/><br/><br/>Play 1.0 Now!<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>[Unexpected Encounters Await]</strong><br/><br/>Throughout your journey, you will run into scripted and unexpected encounters. Perhaps you'll cross paths with an ambitious lieutenant amidst a power struggle at a humble inn, or you’ll run into a retired kung fu master in a nameless village. These will be the experiences you will learn to expect in the ever-changing Jianghu.<br/><br/>Beware, each encounter might associate and change your relationship with the 30+ factions involved in the power struggle in this chaotic Martial World. And remember: every choice you make, every person you befriend (or offend), and every faction you engage will leave a mark.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/Sparring.gif?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[Become the Master of Martial Arts]</strong><br/><br/>Whether you're decoding ancient techniques off a forgotten scroll, or prefer training with a battle-hardened warrior, there’s no correct solution for mastering martial arts. Choose from a variety of weapon types and explore 300+ martial arts skills, the Jianghu will be yours to conquer.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/High-level_Martial_Arts.gif?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[Explore a Living, Breathing World]</strong><br/><br/>In this Wuxia simulator, you'll get to explore 80 cities and villages that bring wuxia to life. Witness how villagers go about their daily routines, and experience the rhythms of ancient Chinese cities.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/Nameless_Village.gif?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[Craft Your Narrative]</strong><br/><br/>To provide an experience where you can embody your own martial spirit, Hero’s Adventure has over 10 distinct endings. Whether you choose to be a noble swordsman, a guardian of the nation, or an agent of chaos, you'll find an ending that aligns with your chosen path in Hero's Adventure. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1948980/extras/武林霸主_1_.png?t=1700823813"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>[New features that are added in v1.0:]</strong><br/>- New bondable female characters, boosting the total number to 18<br/>- A Homestead system to better manage your recruited characters, inherit your Martial Art and weapons to another playthrough<br/>- 200+ new narrative encounters, and adjusted 400+ of the existing encounters<br/>- New Jianghu Event system ensures your adventure doesn’t end prematurely with major events<br/>- Added duel option against high-rank NPCs for a test of mettle.<br/>- Enhanced customization and upgrades for team characters.<br/>- Early supporters will discover a special accessory as a token of gratitude.<br/>- Controller and steam deck support.<br/>- Steam Workshop 2.0</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Faith</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1274600/The_Last_Faith/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The wicked and the blessed will be judged the same - let nothing stand in your way.<br/><br/>Often brutal, always empowering, The Last Faith is an unholy alliance of metroidvania and soulslike. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/extras/GIF_5.gif?t=1701261553"><br/><br/>The Last Faith thrives on merciless and precise combat, with a huge range of custom executions to perform.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/extras/GIF_4.gif?t=1701261553"><br/><br/>Discover a formidable arsenal of melee weapons, arcane spells, and long-range firearms, allowing you to carve a path your own way. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/extras/KUMISOULS_THELASTFAITH_GIF_02.gif?t=1701261553"><br/><br/>Nonlinear exploration is at the core of The Last Faith. Gorgeous pixel art depicts an imposing gothic landscape. Journey along snow-dusted mountains and castles bathed in moonlight. Discover and upgrade a formidable range of tools for destruction.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/extras/GIF_8.gif?t=1701261553"><br/><br/>Step into The Last Faith’s ravaged world as Eryk, who awakens with no recollection of his immediate past. Soon he will discover he is in a race against time as his mind and conscience begins to deteriorate. His desire for salvation from this affliction sets him on a cursed mission that crosses paths with ancient religions and divinities. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1274600/extras/KUMISOULS_THELASTFAITH_GIF_01.gif?t=1701261553"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naheulbeuk's Dungeon Master</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2005160/Naheulbeuks_Dungeon_Master/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/Reivax_poster_H_en.gif?t=1700585599"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your mission, should you choose to accept it!</h2><br/>Embody Reivax, the servile (or not) steward of the Dungeon of Naheulbeuk. Years before the first incursion of fearless adventurers, you are tasked to build, develop, and populate the wobbly tower. Above all, try not to upset your master, the evil sorcerer Zangdar. Are you up to the task?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_1_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Ascend to days of glory and build the dungeon of your dreams!<br/></li><li>Decorate each room with lots of objects and furniture to attract new patrons and employees!<br/></li><li>Raise your reputation to new heights to become the world-devious dungeon!<br/></li><li>Level up your Tripe adviser reputation to attract new customers to your tavern!<br/></li><li>Display your most precious treasures to earn their benefits! Protect them from jealous neighbors!<br/></li><li>As you grow, unlock new dungeon levels to expand and diversify!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_2_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/></img></li><li>Hire less useless personnel to work, defend, raid, and serve the evil Zangdar.<br/></li><li>The world of Naheulbeuk is inhabited by various and unusual species, each with perks and skills – can you manage them?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_3_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/></img></li><li>Manage the expectations and the needs of your fellow minions to reveal the best or worst of their capabilities!<br/></li><li>Upgrade them to improve their workflow and their satisfaction!<br/></li><li>Deal with strikes and other acts of insubordination the way you like!<br/></li><li>Handle Zangdar frustration to secure your fragile position!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_5_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/></img></li><li>As your dungeon grows and improves its reputation, defend it against adventurers!<br/></li><li>Build treacherous traps and artifices to catch raiders and seal their fate!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_6_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/></img></li><li>Offense is the best defense – send your minions to loot and raid neighboring dungeons!<br/></li><li>Want to eliminate the competition? Send your mercenaries and guards on incursions all around the land of Fangh!<br/></li><li>Many factions exists in Naheulbeuk, try not to frustrate them to much or face reprisals!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2005160/extras/GIF_4_en.gif?t=1700585599"><br/><br/></img></li><li>Production is key to thriving and achieving a monopoly, so you will need to generate numerous resources to flood the market!<br/></li><li>Tools, weapons, compost, intel, astral energy, and more! Stock or sell them to gain advantages!<br/></li><li>Use the Crac 40 wisely to prosper! <br/></li><li>Unlock the market, giving you access to new items and artifacts!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header_alt_assets_2.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1701052270"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirate Fighting Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186400/Pirate_Fighting_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pirate Fighting Simulator is a free multiplayer PVP game developed in Unreal Engine 5 in which you fight other players using typical pirate weaponry. There are also cosmetics that you can unlock, these cosmetics can be either hats, weapon skins or in the form of a title that sits underneath your username. The game also includes emotes so you can absolutely boogie down silly style after destroying an enemy gamer. There are also two gamemodes one being TDM (Team Death Match)) and the second being FFA (Free For All).						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1699642767"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1700646226"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons 4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1643310/Dungeons_4/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Once upon a time in a realm far, far away, everything was lush and green. The unicorns mingled among the trees and the elves and humans lived peacefully in harmony with their surroundings. Yet somewhere at the edge of a clearing half-hidden among the trees, obscured by a rising veil of fog in the hazy half-darkness of a weather-beaten hut, a shape huddles over a large and ominously glowing crystal ball. A mumbling voice sings ancient formulae, urging the swirling glowing mists inside the crystal to part and give an insight into the future.<br/><br/>“All is in flux, nothing seems certain. Come, oh vagaries of space and time, separate the veil and show us what is yet to come”, the voice grumbles with the hint of an eye faintly reflecting the glow in front of its hood. The shape’s audience, only barely visible in the dim light, leans in closer and listens intently. “Time ebbs and flows, forming pools and wrinkles… but when the mists part only vague images rise from beyond the veil. Shhhh—don’t come too close, you don’t want to disturb my delicate magical weavings do you?” The shape, still bent over the orb, mutters and shoos the other back a bit more into the shadows. “Ah, now it seems to be clearing a little. I can see… something… several somethings, hints of voices echoing in the haze. A baby, something happening on Hill Doom and the coming together of the Council of Snots – what could all this mean?”<br/><br/>In a flash, the light reflected in the eye turns red and a distant evil laughter echoes through the woods. Stay tuned for the return of the Soothsaying Evil!</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/dungeons-4.gif?t=1701355158"><br/><br/>The Absolute Evil and its trusted *cough* servant, the Dark Elf Thalya, return in <strong>Dungeons 4</strong> after the events of its fabulous predecessor to bring about their triumph over the forces of good once more.<br/><br/><strong>Build a cozy and comfortable Dungeon</strong> to suit your creatures’ needs and rule over them, then send them out into the Overworld to kindly remind the good people living there that the Absolute Evil rules over their lands. <strong>Gather your Evilness</strong> in new and dynamic ways <strong>and unleash it upon</strong> the lush green forests and plains of <strong>the Overworld</strong> to turn them over to the dark side. But make sure that <strong>your Dungeon is well-secured</strong> by traps and defended by your creatures, for those pesky Overworlders won’t just twiddle their thumbs while you <strong>turn their land into the Absolute Evil’s most pleasurable holiday paradise</strong>.<br/><br/>But what is that noise? <i>“Gold, gold, gold and gems, gold and gems and gold!”</i> The ancient song echoes throughout the underworld, accompanied by the clanging steel of hammers and axes. <strong>The Dwarves have arrived</strong> to claim their share of the abundant resources and together with the Elves and Humans of the Overworld, they send out their raiding parties to find the Dungeon’s heart.<br/><br/>Dungeons 4 keeps the spirit of its predecessor, but everything is now <strong>bigger, better, and with even more dynamic Evilness™</strong>.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-1_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Everything is better with Dwarves™:</strong> The Dwarves have arrived to build their underground strongholds and the hardy little fellows (although they don’t like being called that) compete with the Ever-Expanding Evil for space and resources.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-2_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>It makes your Dungeon great again:</strong> Dungeons are up to four times larger than before and there are many more creatures who wait for the All-Commanding Evil’s orders to conquer the Overworld. Now the time has come for massive armies and truly sprawling dungeons!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-3_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Ripe for the taking:</strong> The Overworld is bigger than ever before. Gain Evilness by beating Mini Bosses like the obsessively harmonious Unicorn and use it to transform the Overworld into stunning biomes of pure evil.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-4_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>New and shiny:</strong> An ability-based Perk system for Thalya, the Absolute Evil’s trusted *cough* and most loyal subordinate, grants her impressive new powers. The Absolute Evil can now enjoy taking over the world, governing the creatures and slapping subordinates even more with the customizable Evil Hand.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-5_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Minions, everywhere:</strong> The Horde, the Undead and the Demons wait to do the Absolute Evil’s bidding, with more creatures than ever eagerly following the gesturing Evil’s orders, and Snots will play a much more prominent role this time.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-6_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Many ways to tell the story:</strong> A long campaign, narrated by the beloved English Narrator from previous titles, as well as several skirmish maps all to challenge your rule as the Absolute Evil.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-7_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Change the world:</strong> Spread your Evilness across the Overworld to bring lush and green environments over to the dark side, now shining even more vibrantly and beautifully evil as you spread your evilness across many new biomes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-8_EN.png?t=1701355158"><br/><strong>Work together, slay together:</strong> 2-player co-op multiplayer with both players managing one Dungeon together. All maps from the skirmish mode and the campaign are playable in co-op.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1701448167"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1701448167"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Mashup</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1800000/Unreal_Mashup/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1800000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I am attempting to create a shooter experience tailored to our community's wishes. So what you see is what we all are looking for.<br>
<br>
Fast dynamic lateral movement and ideal projectile randomness incorporated with stylized animations which are generated dynamically via Unreal Engine's animation montage system, which by the way, is eye candy. <br>
<br>
We are using the Lyra shooter project as our base and as we go. I am planning to create customizable guns and characters along with providing stat based ranking and comparative match making.<br>
<br>
This will be the first game Ive created by myself so be aware Ill do my best to make this something good. This project was created for our community to have fun in a semi private way. As well this is a test of the unreal engines main shooter template LYRA which I'll be modifying as we go so updates will be a thing however I also know this thing is buggy! lol There are some audio glitching happening during respawns. Might just wanna turn that music volume down till I can get a fix for that.<br/>
<br/>
Now this is a basic third person shooter with a litany of baked in and ready to utilize features that over time I am going to learn and hopefully be able to modify and implement.<br/>
<br/>
I also want to point out that the networking system is janky ATM so we use Epic to run the game server hosting experience.<br/>
<br/>
All and all The game, so far, is functional and very small at a whopping 1.8 gigs<br/>
<br/>
So technically almost anyone can play it! <br/>
<br/>
Im hoping to have cross platform and VR worked out at some point in the future and honestly it could be working already however I have not been able to test it in that format yet. <br/>
<br/>
There are currently 10 maps included. Demon Station, Big Star Station, Convolution, Expanse, Space station, Soul Slum Forest, Soul Slum, Soul Cave, Shooter Gym and Overworld.<br/>
<br/>
There are currently 7 guns included. They are: Pistol, Shotgun, Rifle, Auto Sniper, Grenade, Grenade launcher, Rocket launcher.<br/>
<br/>
Health pickups are a thing as well.<br/>
<br/>
I hope you enjoy the project and Thanks in advance for any form of feedback going forward.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Red Juggernaut</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2638290/The_Red_Juggernaut/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638290/extras/trj-title.gif?t=1701447039"><br/><br/>A retro-style <strong>JPRG</strong> crossed with a<strong> modular ship building</strong> &amp; combat game.<br/><br/>Level up your ship, build it bigger...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638290/extras/trj-builder.gif?t=1701447039"><br/><br/>Battle enemy ships...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638290/extras/trj-battle.gif?t=1701447039"><br/><br/>Explore the solar system...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2638290/extras/trj-explore.gif?t=1701447039"><br/><br/>And save the human race!<h2 class="bb_tag">Detailed Info:</h2><br/>You start off with three blocks (engine, mounting block, cockpit) that you can rearrange as you like, when you defeat enemies you gain XP, can level up to get more blocks to add to your ship. You also get money for defeating enemies, and you can buy things at space stations. Mountable weapons (<strong>guns, machine guns, lasers, launchers</strong>), a mountable <strong>shield</strong>, ammo (<strong>torpedoes and emp torpedoes</strong>), and consumable items for heating and in-battle stats increases. You can also find weapons and other items in certain places in the map.<br/><br/>You must make your way through the map and the various "dungeons" to find and defeat the Red Juggernaut. There are <strong>over 30</strong> types of enemy ships that you will encounter as you travel, with a varying degree of difficulty. In battle, once you drop their defense screens you can damage blocks individually. If you destroy a component that causes a large portion of the enemy ship to be detached from it's cockpit, those orphaned blocks will be destroyed as well. You can also evade torpedo strikes, and make yourself less vulnerable to attack by using your engines. As well, you can utilize <strong>EMP strikes</strong> to take down enemy shields, and disable enemy weapons temporarily.<h2 class="bb_tag">Controls:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Supports XBOX style controllers: DPad, A, B<br/> </li><li> Keyboard: Arrow Keys, Space/Enter for A, Z/Escape for B</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Credits:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> chadams - Coding, art, music, sfx<br/> </li><li> Lil Lyon - Beta testing<br/> </li><li> LZ - Beta testing</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idle Percent</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696530/Idle_Percent/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2696530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Idle Percent</strong> is something fresh in games of this genre. Unusual mathematics with various features and possibilities make this game worth trying!<br/><br/>Every upgrade in this game is a percent which is added to the upgradable value. Your progression is slow at the beginning but with time your income will become higher and higher!<br/><br/>Buy upgrades, discover complex prestige system and use other features to maximize your income. And unlike other idle games, you can complete this one!<h2 class="bb_tag">GAMEPLAY</h2>Click or wait for idle income. Upgrade your interest income or maximize click profit. Play as you want!<h2 class="bb_tag">PERCENTAGE PROGRESSION</h2>Unique mathematics based on percentages with a smooth increase in prices and income.<h2 class="bb_tag">UPGRADES AND PRESTIGE</h2>Buy base upgrades to increase your stats and income. Use prestige system to reset your progress and get powerful permanent improvements.<h2 class="bb_tag">SUPER PRESTIGE</h2>Even prestige upgrades can be improved! Buy super upgrades to maximize prestige power.<h2 class="bb_tag">GRAPHICS</h2>Nice minimalistic graphics and clean UI so nothing distracts you. You can even select your own background!<h2 class="bb_tag">MUSIC</h2>Dozens of calm ambient music tracks for your joy.<h2 class="bb_tag">ACHIEVEMENTS</h2>55 Steam achievements are waiting for you! Will you be able to collect them all?<br/><br/><strong>Idle Percent</strong> is not as simple as is looks. Try something really unusual and get guaranteed pleasure!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Conflict TD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2698320/Zero_Conflict_TD/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for an out-of-this-world gaming experience in "Zero Conflict TD," the ultimate tower defense game that pits you against a relentless alien invasion! The fate of Earth hangs in the balance, and it's up to you to lead the charge and protect our planet from these extraterrestrial aggressors.<br>
<br>
In a not-so-distant future, humanity has made contact with advanced civilizations among the stars. While most alien races are peaceful, a malevolent force known as the Ximarats has set its sights on Earth, seeking to conquer and exploit our precious resources. With their technologically superior weapons and relentless onslaught, they pose a formidable threat.<br>
<br>
As the commander of Earth's last line of defense, you'll embark on an epic journey to save our world. Your mission is to strategically place an array of powerful towers, each with unique weapons, across key locations on the planet. These towers will serve as your primary means of thwarting the alien invasion.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loading Screen Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2332450/Loading_Screen_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2332450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You've already been inundated with every type of simulator possible. Well, at least you thought that was the case. Like most everyone else, we think the simulator genre has gone too far (We're looking at you, KFC Dating Sim....).  However, instead of rallying against the deluge of downright weird simulators, we've decided to add to the growing abyss of them. Loading Screen Simulator started out as a joke between family members about the madness of the current simulator genre. Now it's progressed to a functional alpha build with goals to have a full game released by the end of the year. Keep checking back, as it's going to keep getting better? How, you ask? More loading screens, of course! Yes, there will be easter eggs for those of you that get through the first few loading screens. Will there be jump scares? Maybe. You'll have to progress through the loading screens to find out. Will there be some cool trivia hidden somewhere in the midst of all the loading screen madness? Possibly, if we can figure out how to code that. What's our end goal? World domination through a large amount of non-functional loading screens, of course! (We may be joking here, or there may be a Chinese spy balloon in there somewhere...If you're the CIA or any government agency reading this, we're just kidding! There's no spyware here). We just hope that our end product is as absurd as it sounds!<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
o Loading Screen images rotate randomly<br>
o Hundreds of loading screen images at launch, with more being added every day<br>
o Interactive loading screens (maze challenges, puzzles, and more!) that can be turned on or off<br>
o Real-life and fantasy scenery!<br/>
o Can be used as a safety screen in many situations. <br/>
o Music that can be turned on or off throughout the screens						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roll &amp; Ball</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2534470/Roll__Ball/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2534470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2534470/extras/gif_punt_003.gif?t=1701444320"><br/><br/>Roll &amp; Ball is an American Football board game where you can call plays and control a playmaker. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 2 Playbook Offense (11, 21)</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 2 Playbook Defense (34, 43)</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 30+ weather</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 24h cycle</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIES FLIES FLIES</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2330490/FLIES_FLIES_FLIES/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2330490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">An episodic, queer, sci-fi comedy visual novel</h2><br/>One day, before he can even graduate high school, Finn Flynn wakes up in the body of a housefly. Without the use of his voice, he'll have to enlist his prankster ex-boyfriend, and his dads, an insectophobic mad scientist and a punk rocker, to solve the mystery of his transformation, and maybe get his life back?<br/><br/>FLIES FLIES FLIES will contain 6 episodes of roughly 25 minutes' playtime each. 2 episodes will be available at launch, and the rest will be released as free updates throughout 2023 and 2024.<br/><br/><strong>FLIES FLIES FLIES is a linear, scripted experience.</strong> There are <strong>no</strong> player choices, alternate endings, etc.<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dark sci-fi comedy story full of twists and turns<br/></li><li>A diverse cast of lovable oddballs<br/></li><li>Eclectic collage art style<br/></li><li>Fully voice-acted with subtitles<br/></li><li>Sound captions<br/></li><li>You'll laugh<br/></li><li>You'll cry<br/></li><li>You'll turn into a fly??<br/></li><li>Just kidding<br/></li><li>But only about that last one</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoking Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2691390/Smoking_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2691390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Have you ever wanted to relax and have a good smoke in an atmospheric village? Then you are exactly at the right place - take a drag on your cigarette and go ahead and explore our wonderful world. It doesn’t matter whether you are an esthete or an amateur, everyone will find a piece of happiness in the Smoking Simulator, only here you can smoke a lot without any negative consequences, or you can go explore the atmospheric village, looking at the works of art on the walls and nature, as your heart desires.<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br>
-You can smoke 24/7 without any penalties/negative consequences<br>
-Relaxing soundtrack<br>
-You can take a running jump into the snow from a hill without fear of crashing<br>
-Atmosphere and humor<br/>
-Various references<br/>
-Beautiful next-gen graphics<br/>
<br/>
All similarities with real people, countries, places, etc. are purely coincidental. The game takes place in a fictional country - Cigaretteland.<br/>
<br/>
Enjoy!)						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat Leather Jackets</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1673830/Cat_Leather_Jackets/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1673830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cat Leather Jackets is a linear visual novel and music game about being a teenager in a punk rock band. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1673830/extras/CLJGameplayGifSteam.gif?t=1701443030"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1673830/extras/synopsis.png?t=1701443030"><br/><br/>Follow Priya and her bandmates Ian and Dave as they get together to write and rehearse songs, try to find gigs and ultimately an audience for their music – all the while trying to find independence and figuring out what they want to do with their lives.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1673830/extras/priya_bus.gif?t=1701443030"><br/><br/>The game features ten original tracks with gameplay segments, intertwining a kinetic novel style narrative with an indie comic book/ graphic novel aesthetic. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1673830/extras/features.png?t=1701443030"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A <strong>Story Mode</strong>: get to know Priya, Ian and Dave and play CLJ's setlist at their first gig;<br/></li><li>In Story Mode, win or lose in the<strong> Punk Mode</strong>. Just want to enjoy the story? Try the <strong>Default Mode</strong>.<br/></li><li>Play any and all unlocked songs for the highest score in the <strong>Practice Mode</strong>;<br/></li><li>Unlock all Steam Achievements;<br/></li><li>And enjoy <strong>ten completely original punk, ska and alternative rock playable beatmaps</strong>.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Christmas Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687190/100_Christmas_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687190/100_Christmas_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687190/100_Christmas_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/Wish+Follow.png?t=1701442822"><h2 class="bb_tag">⛄🌟 WELCOME TO 100 CHRISTMAS CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🎄🎨</h2>🎄 Dive into the most festive adventure in the heart of holiday cheer! 🌟 Discover the enchanting hand-drawn scenes of a holiday cityscape as you set out on a quest to uncover 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎅🎨<br/>😸 Test your attention and focus in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag"> 🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈 </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/Cats.png?t=1701442822"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🎮 1 Extra Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 More Extra Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 2 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🏆 Many Leaderboards <br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Christmas Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692090/100_Christmas_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100ChristmasCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/Extra.png?t=1701442822"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692080/100_Christmas_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100ChristmasCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1701442822"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692100/100_Christmas_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=100ChristmasCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/Artbook.png?t=1701442822"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692110/100_Christmas_Cats__Donaiton_S/?utm_source=100ChristmasCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/Donation.png?t=1701442822"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/600x1.png?t=1701442822"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687190/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1701442822"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687190/100_Christmas_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetBot" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687190/100_Christmas_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetBot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Void Guard</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692960/Void_Guard/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Follow the Void Guardian as she inspects a space station after receiving a distress beacon from it. In Void Guard, you play as the Void Guardian to discover the space station's secret and vanquish the hidden evil.<br>
<br>
"Void Guard" is a Top-Down Metroidvania shooter/puzzle game where the Void Guardian can be moved with WASD. As the Guardian explores the station and the planetoids below, she will find the cause of the station's crew vanishing, encountering mind-bending puzzles, hostile fauna, and exciting suit upgrades. Some environments may be more hostile, and she might have to figure out how to survive. The combination of dangerous technology and biology will be an exciting challenge to overcome. <br>
<br>
In "Void Guard," there are many abilities, such as a gun, a suit upgrade, and a hidden dash ability. You may find some planetoids are more dangerous than others. The final challenge may be impossible to beat with just a gun, but you may find another solution along the way. <br>
<br>
Mouse and Keyboard Supported.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOTICE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2565260/NOTICE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2565260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>NOTICE </strong>is a short interactive experience that follows the story of having a panic attack, then using <strong>awareness </strong>and <strong>presence </strong>to overcome it. As you get home and start to breathe, you take control over your thoughts. By clicking on each object, <strong>you start to become aware of everything in your space and what it means to you.</strong><br/><br/>Each object has its own <strong>style</strong>, <strong>musical note</strong> and <strong>meaning </strong>- whether that be the can of soda lying on your desk or the guitar gifted to you from a friend back home.<br/><br/><strong>Headphones recommended.</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beneath The Earth - Backrooms</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2654040/Beneath_The_Earth__Backrooms/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/extras/About600x174.png?t=1701440416"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/extras/wishlist_follow.gif?t=1701440416"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/extras/DESCRIPTION.png?t=1701440416"><br/>Beneath The Earth - Backrooms is a Co-Op horror game that can be played with at least 1 and up to 4 players. Where you and your friends will fight to escape from the different levels of the backrooms, solving different puzzles with different mechanics in each one.<br/>This game is based on the famous "horrifying creepypasta of cursed dreams" with many real references implemented such as iconic entities and important elements. Explore the seemingly infinite expanse of eerily familiar levels in the backrooms.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/extras/Co-opMultiplayer.png?t=1701440416"><br/>Beneath The Earth - Backrooms with a team of up to 4 players. Be careful: players on your team may not be able to get to other maps, and each member of your team must find the exit alive to escape.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/extras/RealisticGraphics.png?t=1701440416"><br/>The best graphics in the co-op horror genre you'll ever play. Developed with Unreal Engine 5.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/extras/Levels.png?t=1701440416"><br/>The game currently has 5 levels, each level is huge and is designed to be more difficult than the previous one and each one with different puzzles and mechanics. Levels will be added in the future.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654040/extras/RichContent.png?t=1701440416"><br/>The game is rich in different mechanics, levels, interactive things, monsters, you won’t be bored...						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Into The Noid</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2675610/Into_The_Noid/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2675610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to a visual and atmospheric, Noid-like arcade experience in this classical brick-breaker genre turned VR.  <br>
<br>
Including physics-based gameplay and a cerebral visual experience through a host of 16 diverse and atmospheric, stylized levels.  <br>
<br>
Simple mechanics make for an enjoyable game that's also skill based.  It starts as a relaxing, colourful VR romp that's casual then demands higher levels of skill from the player, eventually evolving into a brick-breaker that is as challenging as it is fun.  Walls slide closer to the player, multiple balls appear, explosive balls help destroy the bricks while bonuses in the form of extra lives, larger and dual paddles fly at the player. <br>
<br>
The levels are visceral and the environments provide ample food for the senses.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racing the Gods - Beyond Horizons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1886990/Racing_the_Gods__Beyond_Horizons/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1886990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">The most epic race of all time is about to start.</h2>You have been selected as one of the drivers representing Earth. <br/>It’s a race of life and death as only the fastest will survive. <br/>Do you have what it takes?<h2 class="bb_tag">The ultimate racing tournament beyond time and space awaits!</h2>The gods of our galaxy have opened the gates of their habitats. <br/>They are inviting one driver from each planet to show off their racing skills in a sheer limitless world striking with beauty, extreme contrasts, and breathtaking constructions. <br/>But there is a lot on the line - the losing planets will be eliminated.<h2 class="bb_tag">Race in a vibrant and ever-evolving world beyond imagination</h2>The tournament features 27 tracks through a world beyond our imagination. <br/>It is unlike anything you have ever seen and only inhabited by titans - giant creatures that have been deemed worthy of staying within the realm of the gods. <br/>Racing has never been this epic!<h2 class="bb_tag">What to expect:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A fast-paced racing experience<br/></li><li>27 different tracks through the world of the gods<br/></li><li>Each world has a unique design and twist on the racing experience<br/></li><li>Giant structures, monuments, and monsters are just some of the obstacles that you have to overcome<br/></li><li>Different weapons to clear the way and fight against the other racers<br/></li><li>A unique art style and the most vibrant and interactive racing world<br/></li><li>Many cool upgrades and improvements for your hoverbike</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Boy and His Blob Retro Collection</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1147360/A_Boy_and_His_Blob_Retro_Collection/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1147360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							TROUBLE ON BLOBOLONIA™<br/><br/>Team up with an extraterrestrial lifeform named Blobert (affectionately known as Blob) to save Blob’s home planet! The evil emperor of Blobolonia™ is threatening to rule the planet with his army of minions. Thwart his plans for total conquest while forging an unbreakable bond by using the power of jelly beans! <br/><br/>Find hidden treasures across Blobolonia™ by discovering new secrets and gathering enough resources to buy new jellies. These tasty treats will give Blob the power to undergo miraculous transformations and help you save the world together. Sounds like a daunting task, right? Not with Blob by your side!<br/><br/>Try different jellybean flavors to see what effect they have on Blob. Overcome obstacles by transforming Blob into the right tool for the job! This shape-shifting ability becomes their ultimate weapon, enabling them to conquer seemingly insurmountable challenges. With enough jellybeans and flavors, the possibilities are endless!<br/><br/><br/>THE RESCUE OF PRINCESS BLOBETTE<br/><br/>Join the boy and his extraordinary companion, Blob, as they embark on a quest to save the beloved Princess Blobette from the clutches of the wicked Antagonistic Alchemist, who harbors grand ambitions of becoming Emperor of Blob’s home planet, Blobolonia™. But our heroes won't let that happen.<br/><br/>Imprisoned within the tower of the Royal Castle, the fate of Princess Blobette hangs in the balance, and it's up to you to ensure her freedom. But the Alchemist has laid a suite of treacherous traps to impede the boy and Blob’s progress. Join our dynamic duo as they encounter secret rooms, clever traps, and dangerous obstacles in the labyrinthine depths of the castle. <br/><br/>Fortunately, the Alchemist remains oblivious to our heroes’ hidden advantage—feeding Blob different flavors of jelly beans can transform him into various shapes. Armed with this knowledge, unlocking the tower's door becomes a mere trifle for our heroes, provided the right jelly bean is at hand. Blob’s ability to magically transform shapes will help this intrepid pair get past almost anything the Alchemist can conjure up!<br/><br/>FEATURES OF THIS RETRO COLLECTION:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Includes US and Japanese versions of both games.<br/></li><li> Music Player. Enjoy the original soundtrack of both games.<br/></li><li> Use save states in the game for the first time! No need to start over from the beginning each time. <br/></li><li> Our new launcher gives players different aesthetic options and filters to enjoy the game!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SteamWorld Build</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2134770/SteamWorld_Build/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-Homestead.png?t=1701446569"><br/>One final landrush! The planet is dyin', Astrid, and it's dig or die trying! <br/><br/>That mine under our town is sitting empty, and wouldn't you know there's rumours of ancient tech down there that might help us out of this predicament. Round up the posse, circle the wagons, and let's get to buildin' a new home! Collect resources above ground and ores down below so we can get those wealthy bots in here to help us build bigger, and we can get the heck out of here!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_1.gif?t=1701446569"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_manage.png?t=1701446569"><br/>As your borders expand, new steamfolk will find their way to you! Every bot is crotchety in their own way, and it's up to you to keep them steaming along. Barter to boost efficiency, keep goods flowing to and from the mines and keep everyone happy to make them work their darndest and hardest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_2.gif?t=1701446569"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-DIG-DEEP.png?t=1701446569"><br/><br/>Stare into the abyss long enough and it might just stare back... we're going looking for riches and something down there doesn't want to share! Have gun, dig gravel, and make sure the mines don't collapse upon you as you defend yourselves from the creepy crawlies that lurk within...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_3.gif?t=1701446569"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_features.png?t=1701446569"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break ground on a bustling SteamWorld town, inspired by the Old West.<br/></li><li>Keep your steambots from getting cranky by ensuring their complex needs get met<br/></li><li>Dig deep and spread wide to produce resources to aid your search for ancient technologies<br/></li><li>Defend your mine from the creepy varmints that lurk deep below your town<br/></li><li>Trade resources at the local train stop and welcome special visitors who'll lend a hand<br/></li><li>Five distinct maps littered with secrets for the discerning SteamWorld explorer to find<br/></li><li>Developed from the ground up for both mouse and controller, whichever takes yer fancy.<br/></li><li>Four difficulty levels, including a sandbox difficulty for when you just want to Build!</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutation Madness</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2571650/Mutation_Madness/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2571650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2571650/extras/gameplay1.gif?t=1701438237"><br/><br/><strong>Enter the World of Mutation Madness!</strong><br/>Equip yourself with a powerful disinfectant gun and stand against hordes of mutant viruses to rescue Cell City from a devastating outbreak. Upgrade your weapon, unveil hidden secrets, and immerse yourself in non-stop action. Prepare for an epic battle of intensity and strategy!<br/><br/><strong>Thrilling Gameplay: </strong> As a skilled scientist armed with a disinfectant gun, navigate diverse levels and maps to eliminate waves of mutant viruses in exhilarating combos.<br/><br/><strong>Powerful Items:</strong> Use tactical in-game items like vaccines and antivirals to strategically enhance your gameplay and combat abilities.<br/><br/><strong>Weapon Upgrades:</strong> Enhance your arsenal by unlocking powerful upgrades for your disinfectant gun, allowing you to tackle tougher challenges with greater firepower.<br/><br/><strong>Mascot Companions: </strong> Team up with cute and fearless mascots to fight the virus and restore safety to the city!<br/><br/><strong>Special Modes:</strong> Engage in special game modes, including the thrilling Infinite Mode, where you'll face endless hordes of viruses, testing your skills and endurance to the limit.<br/><br/><strong>Virus Information:</strong> Unveil hidden secrets and gather crucial information about the virus outbreak as you progress, piecing together the mysteries behind the Madvirus.<br/><br/><strong>Hard Mode:</strong> Take on the outbreak's deadliest waves in Hard Difficulty mode. Prove your expertise as you battle mutating viruses on a whole new level.<br/><br/><strong>Achievements:</strong> Conquer levels, defeat foes, and accomplish special feats to earn a range of achievements. Demonstrate your mastery of the outbreak and earn well-deserved recognition.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Savanna Story Diamond  Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2666490/Savanna_Story_Diamond__Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2666490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							For MAC and Linux users, I highly recommend running the game through local files! And you are guaranteed to run the game! Because through the Library the game may not run due to the lack of support for 32 bit games of some devices of these operating systems!<br>
Savanna Story Diamond  Edition -  It is a non-linear visual novel with elements of drama. The action of the game takes place in 2012! Savannah is on the brink of war! The fate of Savannah is in your hands! This is a remake of the game Lionessy Story (Maltakreuz,Goodsir,Maxim Garagulin). This edition features absolute 4k and HDR graphics, you will be instantly immersed in Savannah! Benefits of Savanna Story Diamond  Edition:<br>
1) Beautiful music!<br>
2) HDR and 4K graphics!<br>
3) Highly interactive!<br>
4) One of the few Savannah-themed visual novels!<br>
5) Play as multiple characters!<br/>
6) Boss battles!<br/>
7) Good dramatization!<br/>
8) In-depth plot!<br/>
Also visit my website!<br/>
I hope for your support! I will do more global projects in the future! But without your help I won't be able to give you these projects! Take care of your family and friends with love Irbis!<br/>
I will also add! The game does not want to offend anyone, all the facts that seemed offensive to you are just fiction that in no way refers to real life! That's all for sure now! We wish you a pleasant purchase!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EscapeMONO</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2438930/EscapeMONO/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2438930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Story:</strong><br/>Locked rooms, strange creatures.<br/>You know this is not a good place to stay long.<br/>Probably it won't be too difficult to escape. <br/>But you need to do something important before you go...<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay:</strong><br/>This is an escape room game with black and white pixel art style.<br/>You will be exploring in a dark laboratory. <br/>You can point &amp; click to find clues, pick up items, and interact with strange creatures.<br/>Try figure out every password, unlock the doors and solve the puzzles, and find a way out.<br/><br/><strong>Saving system:</strong><br/>The game can be saved and exited at any time from the settings menu.<br/>Start game from beginning will clear previous progress.<br/>Load game after ending will start from the last scene before the ending.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DVR Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1335370/DVR_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1335370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							DVR Simulator is a Drone Racing FPV Simulator. Are you already an FPV pilot? Start your training now with the Freestyle and Racing modes.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Freestyle Mode<br/></li><li> Racing Mode<br/></li><li> Physics Editor<br/></li><li> Virtual Reality</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Physics Editor</h2>The in-game physics editor allows you to change a lot of parameters such as drag, gravity, motor power, etc.<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Drag, Angular Drag, Interpolation times, Gravity<br/></li><li> Rates and Throttle mid/expo<br/></li><li> 3D settings<br/></li><li> More</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Virtual Reality</h2>Do you have a VR headset? Use it to simulate FPV goggles! Real FPV goggles use the same image for both eyes resulting in no motion sickness. <br/>This is the default behavior when VR is enabled, it's like watching a big movie screen, there is no motion sickness.<br/>Of course, you can enable the stereo mode and experiment with a new level of FPV immersion. This mode is not comfortable and is subject to motion sickness.<h2 class="bb_tag">Inputs</h2>The simulator works with both gamepads and real radio transmitters. A calibration process helps you to configure your radio transmitter.<br/>Calibrations are stored in a file that can be shared with friends that have the same radio transmitter.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tunnet</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2286390/Tunnet/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2286390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Have you ever wanted to be a lonely underpaid network technician who works 24/7 in an underground facility?</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Design and Build a Network</h2><br/><i>Tunnet</i> is a short game where you wake up as a robot technician in an underground complex.<br/>You quickly meet your supervisor, who tasks you with building a computer network to connect the different bunkers of the facility.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2286390/extras/tunnet_store_page_build.gif?t=1701434519"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Bunkers</h2><br/>You are equipped with a state-of-the-art drill that allows you to dig tunnels and find new bunkers to connect to the network.<br/>The more endpoints you connect to the network, the more credits you receive.<br/>But who knows what awaits you in this underground world?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2286390/extras/tunnet_store_page_dig.gif?t=1701434519"><h2 class="bb_tag">Optimize and Debug</h2><br/>As you connect more endpoints, the network topology has to be carefully designed to route the packets efficiently and maintain a decent performance level.<br/>Use the credits you have earned to unlock new devices to better manage and monitor the traffic.<br/>Network incidents can occur at any time: get ready to debug and troubleshoot mysterious issues.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2286390/extras/tunnet_store_page_config_filter.gif?t=1701434519"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Build, optimize and debug</strong> a computer network in a first-person 3D environment.<br/></li><li> <strong>Dig</strong> tunnels to access the different bunkers and connect them to the network.<br/></li><li> <strong>Explore</strong> the facilities and unveil the secrets of the underground complex.<br/></li><li> <strong>Find</strong> a way to access the computers guarded by the creepy monsters that haunt the bunkers.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2286390/extras/portrait.png?t=1701434519"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAPE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2267500/SHAPE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2267500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2267500/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif.gif?t=1701434297"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">S H A P E</h2></strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2267500/extras/demo1.gif?t=1701434297"><br/><br/><strong>Minimalism style</strong> - Minimalism design room in 2D view.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2267500/extras/imageedit_33_2638563913.png?t=1701434297"><br/><br/><strong>Classisc platformer</strong> - Classic 2D platformer style.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2267500/extras/demo2.gif?t=1701434297"><br/><br/><strong>Take word</strong> - Take the word of the NPC<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2267500/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__1_.gif?t=1701434297"><br/><br/><strong>Connect word mechanism</strong> - change the rule of the game by connecting different words.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2267500/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__2_.gif?t=1701434297"><br/><br/><strong>Facing your fears</strong> - you may be gonna lost focus and have dementia.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2267500/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__3_.gif?t=1701434297"><br/><br/>Shape: Mind of Thinker tells the story of a negative thinker stuck inside his/her state of mind. <br/>Everything in the state of Mind is not normal. Sometimes a text, a shape, it even has rain inside.<br/>The thinker realizes they are stuck inside the room where objects become text-like from BOX to their thought.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2267500/extras/imageedit_44_8202448164.png?t=1701434297"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Classic platformer</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Minimalism design</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Solve puzzle</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Connect word mechanism</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>All things in your Mind are words even BOXES</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Append</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2437110/Append/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/logo_small.png?t=1701433244"><br/><br/>Append is a 2D top-down arena shooter with online multiplayer. Play as a futuristic hovering space train in a dilapidated space station, fighting other trains over who gets to scavenge the station or something, whatever. The reason is not important. Your roof-mounted cannon can be upgraded by collecting power-ups, which are stored inside your train cars - watch out so the enemy trains don't destroy them!<br/><br/>Shoot the enemies to shrink them, and to snipe their abilities. Go super offensive and obliterate everything, or put everything on defense. Choose your own strategy!<h2 class="bb_tag">HUNDREDS OF WEAPONS</h2> Collect power-ups and combine them into hundreds of unique combinations, all useful in different scenarios and situations. There are also many passive abilities that help you defend or attack more efficiently. Each ability can be upgraded to increase its power.<h2 class="bb_tag">Applicative powers</h2> With applicative powers you can add a debuff to your enemies. These interact in expected ways, fire burns over time, water puts fire out, but also makes electricity spread, snow makes the enemy slower and so on. With each level, the debuff becomes stronger or longer lasting.<br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/waterlightning.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplicative powers</h2> If you want to shoot more bullets, you can use a multiplicative power. There are multiple variants of these depending on whether you want precision or mayhem. With increasing levels the rate of fire becomes higher.<br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/spread.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">Impacting powers</h2> When your bullets hit something, impacting powers make them do something. They can bounce, explode, or even go through walls. With each level, the impact becomes more prominent.<br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/pierce.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">Movement powers</h2> You can also affect the movement of your bullets, like making them faster, chase enemies, or slow down and become a mine. If you combine the mine with other powers, you can even create defense turrets. The movement becomes more pronounced as you get higher levels of the power.<br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/homing.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">Passive powers</h2> There are also lots of passive powers that improve your chances of winning, like faster movement, healing, luck, and segments that shoot back at incoming projectiles. These powers also amplify when you get higher levels.<br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/healing.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">Mystery boxes</h2> Sometimes you will come across a mystery box, where you get to choose from 3 power-ups. If you have collected the luck powerup, you will have a higher chance of getting rare power-ups from the box. This allows you to tailor your arsenal to the opposition, and upgrade to insane levels of destruction.<br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/box.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">ONLINE MULTIPLAYER</h2> Challenge your friends or strangers online, no local server or host required. Each room can fit up to ten players so you can invite all your friends. Create private rooms or allow strangers to join.<br/><br/>If you don't have enough friends you can also play against bots with varying difficulty. <br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/ten.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLE GAME MODES</h2> You can play free-for-all where everyone tries to kill everyone, or team up against each other, for instance humans vs bots. <br/><br/>There is more than one way to win the game. The goal can be to grow as long as possible, to kill as many enemies as possible, or to just shoot as many bullets as possible. <br/><br/><br/>                          <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437110/extras/winning.gif?t=1701433244"><h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2> <ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple game modes (Free-for-all, Co-op, etc).<br/></li><li>Configurable goals (Longest train, most kills, etc).<br/></li><li>Online multiplayer without need for server, host, or firewall config.<br/></li><li>Play with your friends or create and join games with strangers.<br/></li><li>Supports mouse/keyboard or controller.<br/></li><li>Original soundtrack.<br/></li><li>Procedurally generated arenas.<br/></li><li>Easy to mod.</li></ul><br/>May the best train win, or survive or whatever. Yay!<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2437110/Append/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2437110/Append/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Psycho: Hospital Escape 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2471110/Dr_Psycho_Hospital_Escape_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2471110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							🏥 In the heart of "Doctor Psycho's Hospital", you find yourself trapped in a horrible nightmare, a captive of your own tormented mind. The hospital that was once just a mirror in your mind is now a living hell — a place where your deepest secrets and darkest fears have come true. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2471110/extras/hospital.gif?t=1701431464"><br/><br/>⚡️Your goal is crystal clear: confront your inner demons, find the hidden items and keys within the hospital's ominous walls and make your way to unlock the escape door that holds your only path to freedom. Escape is your only salvation, but the road is full of danger.<br/><br/>🪓 The survival depends on your stealth, survival skill and quick actions as you navigate the strange halls of a dangerous hospital, when every step you take could be your last. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2471110/extras/doccc1.gif?t=1701431464"><br/><br/>😈 Search for stuff, avoiding the evil Dr. Psycho and his psychopathic patients, Crazy Butcher and Sewer Clown. Explore the deepest psyche of your character as they face a terrifying and overwhelming nightmare twisted to life. Embrace shadows and hide in unusual places like under beds, closets, toilet stalls to avoid unwanted attention. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2471110/extras/doll.gif?t=1701431464"><br/><br/>💡 Can you conquer your inner demons and discover the secrets of this place, freeing yourself from the clutches of the Doctor's Psycho Hospital? <br/>The line between sanity and madness is blurred as you navigate the dangerous realms of your nightmares. <br/><br/>🤯 Your mind and freedom hang in the balance. Good luck.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Favela Zombie Shooter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2622860/Favela_Zombie_Shooter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Get ready for a heart-pounding, action-packed zombie shooting game set in a Brazilian favela. In "Favela Zombie Shooter," you'll face wave after wave of different zombies and have to survive as long as you can.<br>
<br>
Gameplay:<br>
Wave-Based Survival: Brace yourself for relentless waves of the living dead. You must stand your ground and fight off waves of zombies, each with their own unique behaviors and abilities.<br>
<br>
Zombie Types: <br>
To survive, you'll need to adapt to the different zombie types. Slow-moving zombies lumber towards you, but their sheer numbers can overwhelm. Runners sprint at breakneck speed, making them difficult targets. Scratchers, when close, they attack quickly and inflict serious damage. Heavy zombies are nearly impervious to gunfire and require tactical thinking to bring down.<br/>
<br/>
Upgrade System:<br/>
To stay alive, you'll need better weapons. You can earn money in the game and use it to buy stronger guns to help you survive.<br/>
<br/>
Features:<br/>
- Fun and intense zombie shooting action.<br/>
- Different types of zombies to fight.<br/>
- Buy better weapons to survive longer.<br/>
- Four different maps to survive in.<br/>
- Realistic graphics and beautiful environments.<br/>
<br/>
In "Favela Zombie Shooter," you'll need quick reflexes and powerful weapons to survive the zombie onslaught. Can you make it out alive from the favela filled with zombies?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Maiden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391690/Blue_Maiden/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Blue Maiden is a Japanese first person psychological horror game that focuses on exploring and finding answers to the mystery of the old neighborhood.<h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2><br/>You are Tachi Tachibana, a graduated university student, after graduating you decide to return to your neighborhood to help at the family business, you have been dreaming the same nightmare in which you find a mysterious girl, when You finally arrive in your neighborhood, you notice that something is not right, and you must find out what is happening.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/>Most of the time you have to walk and explore different traditional Japanese locations to find clues and solve the mystery of the Blue Maiden.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Immersive Experience:</strong> An Atmospheric Graphics.<br/></li><li><strong>Japanese Theme:</strong> Environment inspired by Japanese horror games.<br/></li><li><strong>Psychological horror:</strong> The game contains some jumpscares that could be disturbing.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elves of Duty</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2061100/Elves_of_Duty/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2061100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Compete with friends or team up to deliver the most gifts</strong></h2><strong>Chaotic platforming. Fast paced PvP combat. Diverse arenas filled with traps and hazards.<br/>A thrilling experience that will surely (maybe, but probably not) ruin friendships.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Features</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 2 Game Modes - Delivery and Brawl<br/></li><li> 14 Arena Levels<br/></li><li> 13 Unique Power-ups<br/></li><li> 2-4 Player Local Multiplayer <u><strong>(Controllers are required for each player in local multiplayer)</strong></u></li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Deploy an Arsenal of Ridiculous Power-ups</strong></h2><br/><strong>Fireball</strong> - Fast. Reliable. Just don't miss.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2061100/extras/elvesofduty_fireball.gif?t=1701428789"><br/><br/><strong>Hammer Swirl</strong> - Big tools for tiny hands. Nailed it.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2061100/extras/elvesofduty_hammerswirl.gif?t=1701428789"><br/><br/><strong>Cluster Duck</strong> - Quack, Quack, BOOM<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2061100/extras/elvesofduty_clusterduck.gif?t=1701428789"><br/><br/><strong>...and many more!</strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balance Helicopter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1964410/Balance_Helicopter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1964410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Balance the helicopter using its two engines! <br>
<br>
17 levels with difficult obsticles!<br>
<br>
Short game with +2 hours of gameplay.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ludde</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2073590/Ludde/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2073590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2073590/extras/family614.png?t=1701443745"><br/><br/>Explore a charming winter world with Ludde and discover various exciting, challenging, and fun activities for all ages!<h2 class="bb_tag">Have fun with snow</h2>Roll big snowballs to create a snowman, snow shovel the yard, have a snowball fight with the neighbors, ice fish, practice slapshots in hockey, rent a snowmobile or put on your skis and ski down the mountain. All of this and much more is possible in Ludde.<h2 class="bb_tag">Be rewarded with golden dog bones</h2>100 golden dog bones connected to 100 different activities to discover and collect. When you have gathered enough bones you'll have access to more items and eventually, you have proven yourself ready to face the evil threat that endangers the peace of Ludde's village.<br/><br/>If you like collectibles then you are in luck. Keep your eye out for coins, chewable pinecones, bulletin boards, and clams, or use your camera to take pictures of snow fairies.<h2 class="bb_tag">Move fast with vehicles and gear</h2>Rentable snowmobiles (including flyable ones) can be found everywhere, but you can also buy your own or use your skis. If you find hot air balloons, you can use them as fast travel points and fast travel there at any time.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Explore a picturesque winter world and play around with snow<br/></li><li> Discover 100 fun and varied activities spread across the world<br/></li><li> Focus on what you enjoy: explore your surroundings at your own pace and choose which activities you wish to complete<br/></li><li> Move around fast by using snowmobiles, skis, your wingsuit, or hot air balloons<br/></li><li> Thanks to the pick-up-and-play concept and multiple difficulty settings, the game is equally enjoyable for all ages</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2073590/extras/mix.gif?t=1701443745"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2073590/extras/snowbile4.gif?t=1701443745"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HotBunz</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229230/HotBunz/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Premise</h2><br/>In a world where twerking is the only way to be respected in society, HotBunz is a game about how a new sport, the Bootylympics, allows the citizens of Buttopia to rise above the ranks by being as crass and show-boaty as they can.<br/><br/>The rules of the <strong>Bootylympics</strong> are as quirky as the Buttopians themselves. Participants must navigate through a series of challenges that showcase their ability to shimmy, shake, and twirl with unmatched finesse. From synchronized booty bouncing to gravity-defying farting, every move is meticulously judged by a panel of esteemed cheek connoisseurs.<br/><br/>Play as your favorite Buttopian in this physics-based 2D Platformer Party Game with your friends and claim all the glory. Always remember, Champion Buttopians always come dressed to kill.<br/><br/><br/>- Play Solo to collect as many coins and buy character skins<br/>- Play against friends in different game modes to really show them who's who<br/>- Fart Fire (Pretty cool, we know)<br/>- Dress your Buttopian up to show up and show off!<br/>- Most Importantly, <strong>HAVE FUN!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Modes</h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Solo</h2>Navigate through varying obstacle courses to collect keys and gold coins in a series of increasingly complex levels.<h2 class="bb_tag">VS (King Of The Hill)</h2>Everybody's your enemy, claim the flag and hold on to it for as long as you can while dodging those other loser Buttopians<h2 class="bb_tag">Co-Op (Capture The Flag)</h2>Play with a team member against an opposing team by capturing as many of their flags as you can. <br/><br/><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/SpaceSaladZA" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229230/extras/Steam_Twitter_Banner.png?t=1701430859"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fve8pCkwRth" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229230/extras/Steam_Discord_Banner.png?t=1701430859"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fspacesaladza" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229230/extras/Steam_Instagram_Banner.png?t=1701430859"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Controls XBOX</h2><br/>A - Fart<br/>B - SuperFart<br/>RT - Grapple<br/>LT - Steal Key From Player<br/>L Analog - Movement<h2 class="bb_tag">Keyboard</h2><br/>WASD - Movement <br/>R Shift - Grapple  <br/>Space Bar - Fart<br/>Next level -  Space Bar						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Arcade</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2430760/Family_Arcade/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2430760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">'Tis the season to be gaming 🎄</h2>Looking for a way to make your next game night or family gathering even more fun? Look no further than Family Arcade.<br/>Our jam-packed collection is the ultimate stress reliever, guaranteed to bring out your inner child and have you laughing all night long.<h2 class="bb_tag">Make your holiday season unforgettable with our selection of games that are sure to get everyone into the Christmas spirit 🎅 </h2>Our games are perfect for all ages and skill levels, so everyone can join in on the fun. From classic party games to the latest hits, Family Arcade has something for everyone:<br/><br/>🎲 Scavenger Hunt is tailored for young minds.<br/>🎲 Pop the Pumpkin is a great game for teens who are looking for a fun and more challenging experience.<br/>🎲 Hyperdrive is crafted for mature players seeking an adrenaline-fueled experience.<br/>🎲 Wordsmith is designed to appeal to seniors who are looking for a fun and mentally stimulating activity.<br/><br/>In addition to our wide selection of Christmas games, our Home screen also features over an hour of Christmas songs to get everyone in the holiday mood!<h2 class="bb_tag">Perfect for family game nights or solo holiday cheer, this pack will bring hours of fun and nostalgia to your home!</h2> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat On The Desktop</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674420/Cat_On_The_Desktop/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Game Content</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>  Cats with 10 different skin types.<br/></li><li>  Hang up and interact with your mouse operation.</li></ul><br/><strong>Game Controls</strong><br/>Double click on the cat's head to pop up a menu; Can set whether to interact or not; Whether to place at the top; Switch skin.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nightscape City</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2673720/Nightscape_City/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/buildClubSteam.png?t=1701425173"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/movie_034_2.gif?t=1701425173"><br/><br/>Improve your club with various items. Place objects on <strong>Isometric Grid</strong> based plane. <br/><br/><strong><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Speakers<br/></li><li>Mixers<br/></li><li>Counters<br/></li><li>Lights<br/></li><li>Dance Tubes<br/></li><li>Furnitures<br/></li><li>Walls<br/></li><li>Seperators<br/></li><li>Floors</li></ul></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/CustomizeSteam.png?t=1701425173"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/ezgif.com-gif-maker__2_.gif?t=1701425173"><br/><br/>Increase the luxury level of your club to satisfy your customers. Design your club with fancy dance floor, different types of lights, build rooms and declare as VIP. Sometimes there may be fights, sometimes people may not like the type of music. Some people prefer techno music but some prefer trance. You can also upload your own music to music playlist. It's your job to take care of all this.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/manageSteam.png?t=1701425173"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/ezgif.com-gif-maker.gif?t=1701425173"><br/><br/>Hire or fire an employees to manage your club. Higher skill requires higher management skill. Your customers want quality service.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/unlockDirnkSteam.png?t=1701425173"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/ezgif.com-gif-maker__1_.gif?t=1701425173"><br/><br/>Unlock various drinks. Some people wants exclusive cocktails, some of them want expensive.<br/><br/><strong><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Juice<br/></li><li>Beer<br/></li><li>Coctail<br/></li><li>Wine<br/></li><li>Tequila<br/></li><li>Rum<br/></li><li>Vodka<br/></li><li>Gin<br/></li><li>Whiskey</li></ul></strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/customEventsSteam.png?t=1701425173"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673720/extras/ezgif.com-gif-maker__3_.gif?t=1701425173"><br/><br/>Prepare unforgettable nights for your customers by organizing special events. Increase your popularity with concept parties.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeX</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684650/CodeX/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							CodeX is an atmospheric adventure game that doesn't have any hints, in-game marker, quest log or savepoint.<br/><br/>The story is told through Environmental Storytelling and the player has to find out for himself how to progress by using or moving objects and solving small puzzles.<br/><br/>The game is developed by a <strong>very small</strong> Indie Developer on <strong>Unreal Engine 5</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Features</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Environmental Storytelling<br/></li><li>Thrilling Story<br/></li><li>Atmospheric Gameplay<br/></li><li>No Savepoint <br/></li><li>No In-Game Marker How To Progress</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
