<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Flame: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517810/The_Last_Flame_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_1.png?t=1704771070"><br/>The Last Flame is a roguelike auto-battler which focuses on build creation, strategy and decision making. Recruit special heroes, fight deadly encounters, loot and craft powerful gear, discover and create unique synergetic builds! Every run, you will need to create powerful builds that will take down your foes!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_A3.gif?t=1704771070"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_2.png?t=1704771070"><br/>The Last Flame offers an incredible amount of build diversity. Combine heroes, items, relics and origins together to create amazing builds! Hero and team building have been designed with flexibility and freedom at their core which allows you to discover and create unique synergetic builds every single run!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Builds.gif?t=1704771070"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_3.png?t=1704771070"><br/>In between the automated combats, you will have to cleverly guide your heroes through the adventure by making the smart decisions! Manage your resources, choose the optimal path in the map, make powerful builds, and strategically position and plan the combat phase!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Tactical.gif?t=1704771070"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/comingToFullVersion.png?t=1704771070"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get access to a lot more stuff! Make amazing builds with over 250 items, 55 heroes, 120 relics and 55 origins.<br/></li><li>Continue the adventure in the third act, and meet the final boss in a special act!<br/></li><li>Face 30 challenging enemies and 10 bosses!<br/></li><li>Progress through 5 difficulties which will challenge your knowledge and strategy!<br/></li><li>Push your builds to their limit in the endless mode, a mode where you try to reach the highest floor!<br/></li><li>Experience the game in diverse and fun new ways with the challenge modes!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_ENDLESS.gif?t=1704771070"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portal: Revolution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/601360/Portal_Revolution/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Portal: Revolution is a fan-made mod for Portal 2 which plays before the events of Portal 2 in the dead and decaying Aperture facility.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/ezgif-7-f507c3c464_1_.gif?t=1704560425"><br/><strong>Over 40 new puzzles</strong><br/>The campaign contains 40 brand new puzzles making use of new test elements and presents existing mechanics in a new way not seen in Portal 2.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resurrected "Pneumatic Diversity Vent" element<br/></li><li> New laser cube variant<br/></li><li> Over 15 puzzles using only the blue Portal-Gun<br/></li><li> Gel Cleansing Field</li></ul><br/><strong>Difficulty</strong><br/>Portal: Revolutions puzzle difficulty starts where Portal 2 stops, but fear not. All new mechanics and advanced portal tricks are taught to you. We have ensured through rigorous playtesting that every player can solve the puzzles. Although very few chambers require portals to be fired mid-air, no puzzles require advanced tricky movement.<br/><br/>Depending on your experience with Portal 2 mechanics, you can expect about 5 to 7 hours of playtime.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/banner_story_2.gif?t=1704560425"><br/>Set inbetween Portal and Portal 2, Portal: Revolution tells a brand new story using new characters. You play as a test subject who is awoken by a personality sphere called Stirling and join his mission to find a powerful device capable of restoring Aperture to its former glory.<h2 class="bb_tag">ENGINE</h2>Portal: Revolution uses a modified version of Portal 2: Community Edition's engine, which is a custom version of the Counter-Strike: Global Offensive Source Engine branch using licensed source code provided by Valve Software.<br/><br/>This allowed us to introduce many mechanics and improvements to the engine to create an experience which would be impossible in Portal 2.<br/><br/>-----------------------------------<br/><br/>Something you want to say? <br/>Email us: <a href="mailto:hello@secondfacesoftware.com">hello@secondfacesoftware.com</a><br/>Support: <a href="mailto:support@secondfacesoftware.com">support@secondfacesoftware.com</a> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Memories</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2495450/Winter_Memories/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1704773760"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Header_EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter-Memories-Cards_GIF.gif?t=1704773760"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Trading_Others_EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_1-EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/>After the unforgettable summer memories you’ve made half a year ago, Yui, Rio, and Miyuki are back. With the change of seasons and the cold falling snow, a new page to your story is about to begin. <br/><br/>Revisit the peaceful, seaside town, and spend time catching up with your family and friends.<br/><br/>What new memories will you make this winter?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_3-EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Miyuki_EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Rio_EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Yui_EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_4-EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/><strong>A Relaxing, Adventure RPG<strong><br/><br/><strong>Explore the Beautiful, Seaside Town<strong><br/><br/><strong>Manage How You Spend Your TIme<strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Esports Godfather Origin</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2739460/Esports_Godfather_Origin/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/游戏简介英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>"Esport Godfather" is a management simulation card game that revolves around the theme of MOBA esports. In this game, you will assume the role of a coach in an esports club and personally build your own team! Starting from scratch, what kind of playstyle will you devise for your team? In a constantly evolving meta, can you derive a unique understanding of what it takes to win? How will you unlock the potential of your handpicked athletes and mold them into superstars?<br/><br/>Ultimately, will you be able to become a legendary figure in the esports industry, crafting your own esports story and lifting the championship trophy?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/选手培养英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>Each athlete is unique! They all have their own strengths and weaknesses.<br/>If an athlete's efficiency in earning money increases over time, they are undoubtedly a skilled late-game specialist.<br/>Successful ambushes can unlock hidden potential, propelling some athletes onto the path of godlike.<br/>As a coach, it's your responsibility to analyze each athlete's characteristics, devise training plans tailored to their needs, and guide them on their journey to becoming superstars!<br/><br/>· Every athlete possesses distinct abilities that will impact their performance on the battlefield!<br/>· An athlete's hero pool is crucial for Ban &amp; Pick strategies!<br/>· The tactic cards utilized by athletes in matches serve as the foundation of all strategies!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/版本变更英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>The meta environment is ever-changing!<br/>Changes in the equipment pool, the structure of economic income, and the source of decisive advantages, even slight alterations to the rules can drastically shift the priorities of Ban &amp; Pick and alter the strategic approach!<br/><br/>· Equipment will be added or removed as the versions change!<br/>· The timing of crucial team fights will shift with each version update, making team composition crucial!<br/>· Does harassment grant more gold? Do kills damage towers? Each gameplay rule brings a fresh experience!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/指挥战斗英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>You have the power to command the battlefield, with athletes attentively listening to your orders.<br/>Should you play it safe and focus on farming under the towers, or launch aggressive assaults and initiate attacks?<br/>Perfect team composition requires perfect leadership! The game is ever-changing, and you must face your opponents head-on!<br/><br/>· Each hero and athlete possesses their own tactic cards. It is through creative combinations and strategic application that they become unstoppable!<br/>· Offense or defense? Aggression or caution? The outcome rests in your hands. Formulate strategies and implement tactics!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/其他内容英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>· Over 50 unique heroes in the starting lineup, each with their own special abilities!<br/>· 200+ tactic cards, granting you control over the battlefield!<br/>· Diverse athlete training options! As a mentor, it's important to tailor your teachings to each individual!<br/>· Unearth young talents and cultivate new forces in the youth training camp!<br/>· Choose sponsors, a top-tier club deserves the support of top-tier sponsors!<br/>· Trash-talking sessions, asserting dominance is a must before crucial matches!<br/>· Abundance of events, includes unexpected occurrences, athlete communication, team pep talks!<br/>· Training match plans, knowing your opponents inside out ensures victory after victory!<br/>· Regular season, playoffs, transfer periods—different decisions await you at different times!<br/>· When athletes reach their limits, you must help them break through and reach new heights!<br/>· Create a custom team logo for your club!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/工作室LOGO英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones: NWO Wars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2487350/Alex_Jones_NWO_Wars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Play the OFFICIAL Alex Jones video game! Save the world from the evil globalists’ plot to turn everyone into bug-eating pod-dwelling libtards! STAY TUNED FOR FUTURE BONUS LEVELS AND CHARACTERS.<br/><br/><strong>Classic Run-and-Gun Gameplay</strong>: Enjoy fast-paced action, intricate animations, and detailed environments as you blast your way through waves of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>Unique Levels</strong>: Battle in various environments like secret underground bases, globalist conferences, and mind control facilities, all inspired by real events. Stay tuned for future levels.<br/><br/><strong>Challenging Boss Fights</strong>: Face off against the elite henchmen of the New World Order, including lizard overlords, secret society leaders, and genetically modified creatures.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Voice Lines</strong>: Featuring iconic and often humorous catchphrases from Alex Jones himself, adding flavor to every combat scenario. Special guest vocals by Ryan Katsu Rivera.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_06.png?t=1704518222"><h2 class="bb_tag">JOIN ALEX AND HIS ALLIES </h2><br/>Every day the deep state sues, lies, defames, and KILLS law-abiding patriots who threaten their power!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_05.png?t=1704518222"><h2 class="bb_tag">DEFEAT BIG TECH CUCKS and MORE</h2><br/>And other anti-American communist bosses throughout this adrenaline-inducing adventure!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_04.png?t=1704518222"><h2 class="bb_tag">PLAY AS ALEX!</h2><br/>For the first time in history, experience the world through Infowars leader Alex Jones’ eyes and see the WAR he fights!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/new_screenshot_03.jpg?t=1704518222"><h2 class="bb_tag">SAVE THE BABIES</h2><br/>It’s no secret the NWO REPTILES are after our children. Play NWO Wars now to help save these innocent victims from these MONSTERS!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_02.png?t=1704518222"><br/><br/>“They’re turning the friggin frogs gay!”<br/><br/>Only Alex Jones can stop this madness and restore balance in the Brain Force!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_01.png?t=1704518222"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>kings call</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674290/kings_call/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Kings call is a free-to-play, trading-card  . Playable through a browser, the game allows players to take the role of the Lord of Silver Heron Ridge, and obtain and use cards to summon creatures, cast spells, and defeat monsters as they battle through different regions and protect their kingdoms.<br>
Card-Based Battles | Choose from hundreds of different monster and spell cards, and fuse them together to make them more powerful.<br>
Protect Your Kingdom | Manage your kingdom's resources to obtain better cards, weapons, and equipment for your character.<br>
Player-vs-Player | Engage in Kings call' 1v1, 2v2, and 4v4 PvP arenas, or test your tactics against AI opponents.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowbreak: Containment Zone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668080/Snowbreak_Containment_Zone/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Snowbreak: Containment Zone is a 3D sci-fi RPG-shooter powered by the Unreal Engine 4 that offers a next-gen, cross-platform gaming experience, sharing your progress across all of your devices. <br/><br/>The Descent of the Titans turned a once-vibrant city into the devastated wasteland of Containment Zone Aleph. As the Adjutant of Heimdall Force, bravely undertake missions alongside Manifestations with the powers of gods and unique personalities, seeking to bring this bitter winter to an end...<br/><br/>[Enjoy Hybrid Combat]<br/>Snowbreak's weaponry injects realism into a sci-fi setting, with designs closely simulating future firearms technology. This combines with the otherworldly, RPG-like skill mechanic to create a refreshing combat experience.<br/><br/>[Take on Titans]<br/>The Descent of the Titans completely changed the world, and the battlefield. Feel the thrill of battling giants in this dystopian future!<br/><br/>[Befriend Operatives]<br/>Spend time with your Heimdall Force companions in the Base system. Decorate, chat, and give gifts to grow closer!<br/><br/>[Play Co-Op in Gigalink] <br/>Tired of exploring alone? Join up with friends and fight enemies together!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few Nights More: Genesis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713070/Few_Nights_More_Genesis/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Please note: This is a free prologue and it includes act 1, and only 1 playable character and blood school is playable, The maximum heritage gained is limited to 50, and the maximum difficulty can be set to 2. As well only one castle will be available. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Blood3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Conquer castles and claim your birthright!</strong><br/> <br/>The fight to reclaim your place in this world begins. Rebuild lost ruins, make them stronger and defend them against your enemies. After you regain your strength, move on to conquer more territories and eventually claim your birthright.<br/><br/>Few Nights More offers the unique fusing of castle management and turn based rogue-like combat. Fight against humanity, the undisputed masters of this world in your absence. Choose between eight different Vampire Lords, each with their own ambition and history. Find your trinkets, skills and perks along your way. Design your very own castle by placing the right rooms, adding decors that directly contribute to your army and your Vampire Lord. Conquer more castles so your influence and power grow, until you claim your birthright.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Ferocity3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Core Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Design your castle by adding new Rooms, Traps and Minions. Stack up on some buffs with shiny decors to get ready for the invasion screen to defend it to the end of every night!<br/> <br/></li><li> Choose among 7 different Vampire Lords with unique History, Gameplay and Abilities.<br/> <br/></li><li> Master 1 out of 3 Disciplines each time you play, each with 60 unique skills.<br/> <br/></li><li> Acquire new random skills, perks and trinkets to survive the nights.<br/> <br/></li><li> Excel in either being a Prestigious Vampire, a Seductive one, or master a Terrifying presence against your enemies.<br/><br/></li><li> Test the builds you made against a variety of Hunters, Veterans and Unique Bosses in an action packed turn based combat system.<br/> <br/></li><li> Endure three acts across 12 difficulty levels, striving to survive and progress. Accumulate Heritage Points to enhance your lord's starting stats, skills, and unlock new castles and talents unique to each lord.<br/><br/></li><li> Engage in the boundless challenge of Infinity Mode, where you can continuously test your limits without relying on a castle. Each night, you will be presented with three options to advance, growing stronger as you push yourself to see how far you can go.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703868247"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1704804364"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1704380508"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1704380508"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1703493452"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1703493452"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1703186631"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goofy Gorillas</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2627570/Goofy_Gorillas/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2627570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Goofy Gorillas, the largest (and greatest) nostalgia-driven virtual play centre!<br/><br/>Do you want to play Hide and Seek with your friends? Maybe you'd want to play Hide and Seek with dodgeballs, inflatable hammers and boxing gloves to raise the stakes a little more? Why not turn your friends into enemies in a free-for-all battle with all of the items mentioned? You and your friends can partake in these activities while also earning GP (Goofy Points). Levels are gained through earning GP, which can then be used to unlock unique cosmetic items to show off while you're winning in your game mode of choice!<br/><br/>If you just want to chill without the fear of being chased or you don't feel like turning your friends into enemies just yet, we have you covered! Goofy Gorillas prioritizes creating a social hub before any game mode begins, so you're able to do whatever you want to do - with small mini-games that can be played at any time too! <br/><br/>Goofy Gorillas is fitted with a football (soccer) pitch with a working score counter hidden within the play area, a bowling alley with two lanes also hidden within the play area, 2 large ball pits with large slides and there are some basketball hoops scattered around the entire venue - some easier to dunk than others! We hope there is something here for everyone!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>GAMEMODES</strong></h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Hide &amp; Seek</h2><br/>The classic game that everyone knows so well. Seekers must find all of the Hiders in the given time, and every round, both teams swap sides! Sounds simple, right? Well in Goofy Gorillas, we take it to the next level! Featuring an economy just for this gamemode, Hiders and Seekers have access to a shop with items and utility that will help them defend themselves as a Hider, or help catching the Hiders in style as a Seeker. <br/><br/>You want to make the Seekers slip on a banana peel? You can totally do that! <br/><br/>You want to hit the Hiders with an inflatable hammer? We highly encourage you to do that!<h2 class="bb_tag">Infector</h2><br/>Infector is another classic game. It plays just like Hide &amp; Seek, just without the economy. One player is chosen as the Infector, and by catching the Runners, they too will become an Infector. Once everyone has been caught, the Infector team will win... or lose if there's just a single player still standing. The first player that gets caught will be the Infector in the next round.<br/><br/>Be careful who you trust in this gamemode; once your "friend" has been caught, they will not be your friend anymore!<h2 class="bb_tag">Free For All</h2><br/>The standard of any multiplayer game. This is the perfect gamemode for those who want to mindlessly cause chaos with friends! Just spawn in with an item, get stuck in the brawl and come out on top, or just respawn with another item if you weren't successful! The first player to reach the score limit wins, or if no one reaches that, then the time limit will decide who becomes victorious!<br/><br/><br/>With all of these activities included, we hope you enjoy your time here at Goofy Gorillas!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SteamWorld Build</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2134770/SteamWorld_Build/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-Homestead.png?t=1702026390"><br/>One final landrush! The planet is dyin', Astrid, and it's dig or die trying! <br/><br/>That mine under our town is sitting empty, and wouldn't you know there's rumours of ancient tech down there that might help us out of this predicament. Round up the posse, circle the wagons, and let's get to buildin' a new home! Collect resources above ground and ores down below so we can get those wealthy bots in here to help us build bigger, and we can get the heck out of here!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_1.gif?t=1702026390"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_manage.png?t=1702026390"><br/>As your borders expand, new steamfolk will find their way to you! Every bot is crotchety in their own way, and it's up to you to keep them steaming along. Barter to boost efficiency, keep goods flowing to and from the mines and keep everyone happy to make them work their darndest and hardest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_2.gif?t=1702026390"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-DIG-DEEP.png?t=1702026390"><br/><br/>Stare into the abyss long enough and it might just stare back... we're going looking for riches and something down there doesn't want to share! Have gun, dig gravel, and make sure the mines don't collapse upon you as you defend yourselves from the creepy crawlies that lurk within...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_3.gif?t=1702026390"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_features.png?t=1702026390"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break ground on a bustling SteamWorld town, inspired by the Old West.<br/></li><li>Keep your steambots from getting cranky by ensuring their complex needs get met<br/></li><li>Dig deep and spread wide to produce resources to aid your search for ancient technologies<br/></li><li>Defend your mine from the creepy varmints that lurk deep below your town<br/></li><li>Trade resources at the local train stop and welcome special visitors who'll lend a hand<br/></li><li>Five distinct maps littered with secrets for the discerning SteamWorld explorer to find<br/></li><li>Developed from the ground up for both mouse and controller, whichever takes yer fancy.<br/></li><li>Four difficulty levels, including a sandbox difficulty for when you just want to Build!</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Expanse: A Telltale Series</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1708010/The_Expanse_A_Telltale_Series/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1708010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the exciting universe of The Expanse like never before in Telltale’s latest adventure, The Expanse: A Telltale Series. Take on the role of Camina Drummer and explore the dangerous and uncharted edges of the Belt aboard the Artemis. From scavenging wrecked ships in a zero-g environment, to surviving a mutiny, to combating fearsome pirates, you make the difficult choices and reveal Camina Drummer’s resolve in this latest Telltale adventure.<br/><br/><strong>A TELLTALE STORY LIKE NO OTHER</strong><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in the role of Camina Drummer, the Executive Officer aboard the Artemis, a scavenging ship hunting for a big score in the outer regions of the Belt. You must corral a crew rife with tense relationships and powerful personalities, and make tough decisions that will decide everyone’s fate.<br/><br/><strong>EXPLORE THE BELT IN ZERO-G</strong><br/><br/>Scour shipwrecks, use mag boots to walk on walls and ceilings, and utilize zero-g thrusters to float through the void. As you fly through sections of ships and the open expanse of space, interact with objects in the world and converse with members of the crew in the largest and most immersive exploration of any Telltale game to date.<br/><br/><strong>DIFFICULT CHOICES, GRAVE CONSEQUENCES</strong><br/><br/>Contend with the unforgiving brutality of space, the politics of a corrupt solar system, the animosities of your crew, and Drummer’s own conflicting responsibilities to the people she cares about and the Belt she has sworn to protect. There is no right or wrong path - only your choices and the consequences they unleash.<br/><br/><strong>INCLUDES ALL 5 EPISODES</strong><br/><br/>Episode 1: Archer's Paradox<br/>Episode 2: Hunting Grounds<br/>Episode 3: First Ones<br/>Episode 4: Impossible Objects<br/>Episode 5: Europa's Folly						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1704392583"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1704392583"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1704392583"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1702747783"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MechAvenger</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2716730/MechAvenger/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							MechAvenger is a fast paced VR shooter and platformer about fighting robots after the end of humanity. Shoot, punch, jump and climb your way through the enemy horde, and shut down their factory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716730/extras/combat1.gif?t=1704898938"><br/><br/>Take down enemies with 9 unique weapons, using your quick reload belt to keep them firing! Bash your enemies with weapons and fists to knock them to the ground. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716730/extras/Stun1.gif?t=1704898938"><br/><br/>The robotic horde is plentiful, but ammo is not.  Search your environment for extra weapons and ammo. Kill stunned enemies with a melee hit for an ammo bonus!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716730/extras/combat2.gif?t=1704898938"><br/><br/>Navigate platforming sections by climbing and flinging yourself off walls. Swing with the grappling hook to cross long pits and build speed. Get yourself out of harms way with your servo powered dodge.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716730/extras/climbing5.gif?t=1704898938"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOAR - Appeteaser</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2074490/MOAR__Appeteaser/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2074490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							💛 The Appeteser offers endless fun with wave and arena shooters spiced with mini games and an upcoming ingame level builder. Multiplayer is also among future plans.<br/><br/>💛 You will fight a horde of various zombies with different kind of ranged and melee weapons. <br/><br/>💛 You can collect points to unlock new guns, levels and power ups.<br/><br/>💛 It is an easy going fun in which you can jump in any time and enjoy a bit of mayhem.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2074490/extras/fly_in_a_spaceboat.png?t=1704898389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2074490/extras/GIF_SpaceShip.gif?t=1704898389"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2074490/extras/expand_your_arsenal.png?t=1704898389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2074490/extras/GIF_Weapons.gif?t=1704898389"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2074490/extras/Play_minigames.png?t=1704898389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2074490/extras/GIF_BreakSaber.gif?t=1704898389"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2074490/extras/FightAnEndlessHorde_PNG.png?t=1704898389"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2074490/extras/EndlessWaveOfEnemies.gif?t=1704898389"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despair: Blood Curse</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1629350/Despair_Blood_Curse/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1629350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A third-person survival horror game featuring non-linear gameplay, puzzles, and enemies from the depths of hell. Soon after the arrival of an unexpected guest back home, Anna's mother suddenly falls ill and passes away. Quickly dismissed by doctors as another casualty of the pandemic, Anna receives a worrying letter from her sister suggesting that not all is as it seems. Will she uncover the truth behind her mother’s death?<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Use Anna's axegun to defeat enemies from a distance or up-close. <br/></li><li> Non-linear gameplay. Explore and solve puzzles to unlock the mysteries of the mansion and beyond.<br/></li><li> Limited inventory space. Carefully manage your inventory while always being ready for the unknown.<br/></li><li> A location-based damage system. Don't waste precious ammo shooting arms and legs. Aim for the head.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beer Factory</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1782570/Beer_Factory/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1782570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2000160/Music_Store_Simulator/" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2000160/Music_Store_Simulator/</a><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2394250/Rich_Dad_Simulator/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2394250/Rich_Dad_Simulator/</a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FhspAGgT7WD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1782570/extras/discord_join_us.png?t=1704895307"/></a><br/><br/>Beer Factory is a business simulation and management game. Take the challenge and manage your own beer factory, employees, production lines, as well as the import and export of merchandise.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Logistics to manage</strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1782570/extras/Logistics_to_manage.gif?t=1704895307"><br/><br/>Manufacture usually requires a production line, some resources, storage options, and transportation. In Beer Factory, where your goal will be to produce beer, you will need to import and store the raw materials, refine, brew in tanks, store beer, bottle it and finally send it to the client.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Recruit and manage your employees</strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1782570/extras/Recruit_and_manage_your_employees.gif?t=1704895307"><br/><br/>When you want to develop your business, nothing will work better than hiring staff to help you with your day-to-day tasks. The employees in your factory can handle most jobs, but it is up to you to tell them what to do. Don't forget to monitor their progress!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A realistic economy</strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1782570/extras/A_realistic_economy.gif?t=1704895307"><br/><br/>Every action has a cost and it's up to you to manage your finances. From recruitment to transportation to taxes, the whole finance system in Beer Factory has been designed to be as close to reality as possible.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Customize and upgrade your factory</strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1782570/extras/Customize_and_upgrade_your_factory.gif?t=1704895307"><br/><br/>In order to make beer, you need all kinds of machines. Once you have invested in new machinery, you will be able to exploit it, improve it, and use its maximum potential to produce even more! Then you can expand your factory to grow your business into an empire!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat Palette: Merging Colorful Kittens</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2578280/Cat_Palette_Merging_Colorful_Kittens/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2578280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>"Cat Palette: Merging Colorful Kittens"</strong> is an exciting puzzle computer game that will immerse you in a world of cute and fluffy cats capable of amazing transformation! In this game you will become a master at mixing colorful kitties and solving fascinating puzzles.<br/><br/>The main feature of the game is unique and diverse cats, each of which has its own color and character. Starting levels will introduce you to the basics of the game: swipe the cats in different directions so that they mix with each other and create a new cat with a new shade. But be careful, not all cats want to mix with each other, and some combinations may not work out the way you expect! As you progress through the levels, the complexity of the puzzles and the number of cats will increase.<br/><br/>You will find colorful graphics, gentle background music and an incredibly cute atmosphere!<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Main features:</strong></h2><li><strong>Cute atmosphere and visual style</strong> - the main feature of the game is its charming and cozy atmosphere. The graphics are made in bright and saturated colors that fill the game with joy and warmth. Each cat has a unique design, and the design of the game is filled with comfort and cute details. Soft music will create a calm and relaxing atmosphere.<br/></li><li><strong>Different cats</strong> - the game features a variety of colorful cats, from classic black and white to bright orange, green and blue. Each cat interacts with each other in different ways, so not all can be mixed with each other. All cats are united by their unique and cute design.<br/></li><li><strong>Exciting puzzles</strong> - the game has 150 levels with different difficulty, where you have to prove your skills in mixing and puzzles. You will need to combine cats of different colors in the color combinations you need to complete the level. With each level, the difficulty will increase, and you will need more logical thinking and creativity to solve the problem.<br/></li><li><strong>Simple interface</strong> - the game is designed with the convenience of the players in mind, and it is easy to master even for beginners.<br/></li><li><strong>Collectible achievements</strong> - the game rewards you for your creativity and effort. For successfully mixing cats and completing difficult levels, you will receive achievements and new cats for further experimentation. </li></ul><br/><strong>"Cat Palette: Merging Colorful Kittens" </strong> is the perfect game for those who love puzzle games, cute cats and cozy atmosphere. It is designed to give you a lot of joy, fun and creativity, wrapped in cute and fluffy creatures.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trash Top Down Racing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2752650/Trash_Top_Down_Racing/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2752650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Story:</h2>Race against 3 other AI racers in 10 different racing tracks in this 2d top down racing games. All races are 3 laps long in different areas. Also game contains result list. So be the fastest driver and beat ai opponents<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2>- 10 tracks<br/>- Steam Achievements<br/>- 3 AI opponents						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Out Joey !</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384890/Get_Out_Joey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384890/Get_Out_Joey" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384890/Get_Out_Joey</a><br/><br/>Help arrogant Joey rise to the surface. In a unique, gigantic maze-like world, you'll have to use your concentration and skill to avoid losing out to the dangers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384890/extras/introgif.gif?t=1704869237"><h2 class="bb_tag">Joey's graceful movements</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Of course you can jump! Jumping is an essential part of the gameplay. Short jumps, long jumps, millimetric jumps, always. Watch out for the fall!<br/></li><li>Hey ho, you can rush too! Jump too short? Platform too far? Go for it! But watch out for the fall!<br/></li><li>Swing! With your spear, you'll be able to hold on to certain parts of the scenery and swing to progress through your adventure. This technique is often essential for crossing huge chasms. But, once again: BEWARE OF FALLS!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384890/extras/gifAout.gif?t=1704869237"><h2 class="bb_tag">What Joey doesn't know, but you do, now</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The world is spinning. Regularly, gravity will knock you off your feet. The closer you get to the top, the harder the fall.<br/></li><li>You can activate checkpoints. Just so you don't rage too often. That would be a shame.<br/></li><li>There's also a drop counter to depress you and compare you to your buddies.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Joey's final word:<br/><i>"- I'm great, I've got a big bag and a magic spear. <br/>But I'm stuck here, and I've got to get out. Hurry!"</i><br/><br/>(Joey is arrogant)</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buriedbornes2 - Dungeon RPG -</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1581950/Buriedbornes2__Dungeon_RPG/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1581950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Easy to play ✕ Severe adventure again</h2>.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1581950/extras/gif1-mov2.gif?t=1704866501"><br/>Buriedbornes2 is the sequel to the easy-to-play turn-based dungeon RPG series.<br/>The popular series, which has surpassed 2.5M total users, has evolved in a form that is easier to play and more freely enjoyable.<br/>Choose between 2 options for the room you want to progress in, decide which items you want to obtain, choose from up to 5 skills to use next, and more...<br/>The simple, non-real-time operation allows you to enjoy a serious adventure where death is the only thing you have to worry about.<h2 class="bb_tag">The battle of the dead and the cooperative "Union"</h2>.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1581950/extras/gif4-unions-slow.gif?t=1704866501"><br/>The world is on the brink of ruin due to the invasion of the "Ancient Overlord" and his army of corpses, a threat suggested by the most ancient prophecies.<br/>You will repeatedly challenge dangerous dungeons by acquiring corpses, altering them, and using the forbidden "Buriedbornes" art of possessing their souls.<br/>It is a hopeless battle with no redemption or end, yet mankind has not given up on everything yet.<br/>In various parts of the world, communities of survivors, each with their own goals, continue to resist.<br/>By helping each other with them, we may find hope.<h2 class="bb_tag">Races, jobs, origins, equipments, skills, runes... countless combinations</h2>.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1581950/extras/gif3-runes-slow.gif?t=1704866501"><br/>At the start of the adventure, character creation is possible by selecting the race, job, and origin of the corpse to be used.<br/>Each legendary equipments that can be found in each dungeon has its own unique abilities.<br/>Up to 5 skills can be held, each of which can be set with up to 5 skill runes that can also be obtained in dungeons.<br/>These elements allow you to build your tactics freely from a myriad of options.<br/>You can build your builds systematically, or you can improvise and discover powerful builds through unexpected coincidences.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISOLAND4: The Anchor of Memory</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2700230/ISOLAND4_The_Anchor_of_Memory/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"ISOLAND4: The Anchor of Memory" belongs to which part of the ISOLAND series? Does it continue the story from "ISOLAND3: The Dust of the Universe," or does it start a new chapter? Can it truly unravel the past and present of the Lost Island?<br/><br/>You'll only know after you've played it yourself. Wait a moment... even after playing, you might not necessarily know. :)<br/><br/>Since the first ISOLAND, this journey has been full of twists and turns, both in the game and in real life.<br/><br/>ISOLAND4 continues to pay homage to literature, art, and music like its predecessors, with more intricate maps and puzzles. However, the foundation lies in richer Easter eggs, more mystical dialogues, and more abundant emotions.<br/><br/>This installment emphasizes the characters in the story, featuring both familiar and new faces. They assist you in rediscovering the island's secrets while unraveling their own life mysteries.<br/><br/><strong>Do not overlook any detail; do not miss any conversation.</strong><br/><br/>Things that seem useless may offer players more contemplation on the fate of life.<br/><br/>This ISOLAND is dedicated to my mother.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700230/extras/游戏封面图.jpg?t=1704853795"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOLL EYE: CHAPTER ONE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2575360/DOLL_EYE_CHAPTER_ONE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2575360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i>DOLL EYE: CHAPTER ONE</i> is the first part of a dialogue-based, story-driven psychological horror game made in RPG Maker MZ.</strong><br/><br/><i>"Where did this all start?"</i><br/><br/>Tomorrow is the anniversary of your son's death, but you can't let that distract you from your everyday life.<br/>Your daughter has just sent you a message asking you to pick her up near that one shark dude's bar. Worry not - your guardian angel can keep you company... Wait, who the hell is that? <br/><br/><i>"I think..."</i><br/><br/>This game features original art/music and is about one hour long. This might depend on your reading speed, how many things you check, your choices, etc. <br/>This game has one ending.<br/><br/><i>"...I think I realize it, now."</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Lair Depths</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2407160/Dragon_Lair_Depths/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2407160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build and upgrade your own hero team. On the 9x9 board, use limited action points in each round, manipulate heroes with different abilities, play coordination, guard earth vein, and destroy enemies.<br/><br/><strong>Game highlights:</strong><br/><br/><strong>1. Racial heroes of various elemental powers:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Nagas: Control the use of flames to ignite the enemy.<br/></li><li>Elf: Powerful recovery, and generate spirit grass traps to control enemies<br/></li><li>Water: can summon the water grid that reduces the enemy's movement<br/></li><li>Rock: use rocks to control the enemy's progress, and fight cattle across mountains<br/></li><li>Thunderclan: Summons thunderclouds that deal damage every turn<br/></li><li>Stay tuned</li></ul><br/><strong>2. Unexpected reactions between elements/terrains:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Ignite the grass, all connected grass will catch fire<br/></li><li>Grasslands affected by lightning will also catch fire<br/></li><li>Water grid can conduct electricity</li></ul><br/><strong>3. High difficulty strategy battle:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Victory: Destroy all enemies<br/></li><li>Failure: All our heroes are dead, or all earth vein are destroyed<br/></li><li> Enemy Intention: Each enemy will display the behavior intention of the next round, and the enemy will only perform one behavior in each round of movement/attack/skill<br/></li><li> Action Points: Action Points shared by all our heroes, reset and refreshed every round<br/></li><li>Going into battle/Going out of battle: Heroes can spend action points to go out of battle to avoid damage, and go into battle to any grid in our area</li></ul><br/><strong>4. Mild rogue experience:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Replay value: every round is a new experience, no outside development<br/></li><li>Random events: several random events<br/></li><li>build: Dozens of relics with different abilities can be obtained, equipped with heroes to produce various chemical reactions<br/></li><li>Permanent death: When a hero dies, a point of HP will be deducted from the upper limit. If the upper limit is 0, the hero will die permanently</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Borderwatch: Dark Armada</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2260100/Borderwatch_Dark_Armada/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2260100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Borderwatch is a 3rd person co-op zombie survival game. The world is invaded by infected creatures. As <br/>a result of this invasion, the union of nations has decided to leave the world. After the decision to leave <br/>Earth, a final call has been made for the survivors. Helicopters will take off from all capitals in the world <br/>every 10 days. The people who catch up with this helicopter will survive.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build your team, Loot and Survive!</h2>The world has been under the influence of infected creatures. The United Nations has recognized that the world has become unlivable. To catch the last call, it is necessary to go to the nearest capital and get on the escape helicopter. It is a very tough fight against this infected virus that is getting stronger day by day.<h2 class="bb_tag">Attention!</h2>Infected creatures carry the characteristics of the regions they are in. The United Nations has so far performed autopsies on 2 infected creatures. As a result of the autopsy, it was determined that one of the infected creatures was pregnant and could reproduce. As a result of research on the creature that was born, it was determined that it was much stronger than its previous generation.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Team</h2>Team of 4 with surrounding survivors.<br/>Organize, act strategically and be the one to increase your chances of survival in the apocalypse.<h2 class="bb_tag">Loot</h2>The only way to get rid of the infected creatures is to get on the helicopter 10 days later. In the process, use everything you find around to stay alive. Weapons, ammo, traps, medical equipment, food and water. Volunteer pilots regularly deliver supplies to the area, showing them a sign of survival.<h2 class="bb_tag">Listen to Other Survivors.</h2>Listen to radio signals from other survivors for information on the area and cooperate with them to stop the epidemic. The United Nations stated that time is running out for survivors.<br/>Note:<br/>It's the only device in the area that provides the generator radio link. Make sure the generator is running. Caution, it's unclear where the radio signals are coming from. Try to survive by making the right decisions.<h2 class="bb_tag">Survive</h2>Use limited consumables carefully, count your ammo, and be fast to survive the zombie raids that are getting harder every day!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Realistic post-apocalyptic graphics<br/></li><li>Strategy based 3rd person gameplay<br/></li><li>Co-op Multiplayer for up to 4 players<br/></li><li>immersive game<br/></li><li>Game mechanics improvement.<br/></li><li>3 maps: İstanbul, Abu Dhabi, Moscow and more capitals</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Martha's Dolls</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2614380/Marthas_Dolls/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614380/extras/Banner.png?t=1704841221"><br/><br/>Martha's Dolls is a first-person horror game where you play as a player who has ventured into an abandoned village rumored to be cursed by the haunted dolls of an old woman named Martha. The village is full of these dolls, and those who enter the village are never able to leave.<br/><br/>Your goal is to investigate the village and uncover the secrets behind Martha's dolls and the curse that plagues the village. However, you must be careful, as the dolls are not to be underestimated. They are said to be possessed by Martha's vengeful spirit, and they will stop at nothing to protect their village and its secrets.<br/><br/>As you explore the village, you will encounter a variety of different dolls, each with its own unique abilities and behaviors. Some dolls will simply wander the village, while others will actively hunt you down. You will need to use your wits and survival skills to avoid the dolls and stay alive.<br/><br/>In addition to the dolls, you will also need to be wary of the village itself. The village is full of traps and hazards, and it is easy to get lost in its maze-like streets. You will need to carefully navigate the village and avoid the traps in order to find your way out.<br/><br/>Martha's Dolls is a challenging and suspenseful horror game that will test your nerves. If you are looking for a truly terrifying experience, then Martha's Dolls is the game for you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614380/extras/Game_Details.png?t=1704841221"><br/><br/>Here are some of the features of Martha's Dolls:<br/><br/>- Variety of different dolls, each with its own unique abilities and behaviors.<br/>- Challenging and suspenseful horror experience.<br/>- Maze-like village full of traps and hazards.<br/>- Dark and atmospheric world to explore.<br/>- Gripping story to uncover.<br/>- Realistic Horror Experience !<br/>- All what you need ( Inventory System , Player Items , Puzzles ...)<br/><br/><br/>If you are a fan of horror games, then Martha's Dolls is a must-play. It is a truly terrifying and unforgettable experience.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Dino Standing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2724780/Last_Dino_Standing/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Dino Standing is a hand-drawn 2D casual game where your goal is just to stay alive avoiding the crazy elements that fall from the sky. You're the <strong>last Tyrannosaurus</strong> alive in the dinosaur extinction event. We already know how this story ends, but you need to survive as long as you can.<h2 class="bb_tag">Main features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Funny visuals.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Simple accurate movements.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>4 difficulty levels to choose from.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Timer system.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Map variations.</li></ul><br/>and more secrets to discover.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evil Seal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1516940/Evil_Seal/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1516940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Evil Seal is an action horror game inspired by the Apocalypse of St. John.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1516940/extras/Evil_Seal_GIF_4.gif?t=1704881530"><br/><br/>The story begins when the first of the Seven Seals is broken and the first of the Four Knights begin to spread confusion and destruction on Earth.<br/>The new Messiah, the devil's son, manages to create a new religious cult by performing initial miracles, with many followers. The "miracle-people" discover the price they have to pay soon: a few months after the miracle, their bodies are emptied of all traces of humanity. The new religious order followers will be transformed into beings with no rationality or control, hungry for human flesh and incapable of feeling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1516940/extras/Evil_Seal_GIF.gif?t=1704881530"><br/><br/>Adam is a man deeply in love with his sweet half, Eve. But fate is cruel: when the first seal of the apocalypse is broken, Eve is kidnapped by dark forces.<br/><br/>Thus, with a broken heart and an incredible determination, Adam embarks on a desperate journey to find the love of his life. Along the way, he will face epic challenges and unveil dark secrets, battling evil creatures and overcoming insurmountable obstacles.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1516940/extras/Evil_Seal_GIF_2.gif?t=1704881530"><br/><br/>A real estate agent, with a past in the marines, helps Adam to find Eve in a city devastated by demons and infernal creatures.<br/>And the story continues...<br/>What will happen when the other seals are broken?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1516940/extras/Evil_Seal_GIF_3.gif?t=1704881530"><br/><br/>This game is the first of a trilogy that provides for the breaking of the 7 seals of the apocalypse.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1516940/extras/logo-01-steam.png?t=1704881530"><br/><br/>Raffaele Mandese created this video game entirely on his own, covering all aspects from graphics, gameplay, sounds, to the story. The team Mandese Games is the name of the team he formed, but currently, it only has him as a member.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KinitoPET</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2075070/KinitoPET/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Join the Discord!</strong></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FGZfJqdM7au" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/GZfJqdM7au</a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enter the Everlasting Fun!</strong></h2>Would you like a friend? Yes? Well, I have something special for you.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075070/extras/BoxSpin.gif?t=1704834493"><br/>KinitoPET invites you to their wonderfull world of fun and excitement!<br/>Where he will be your very own virtual friend and personal helper! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075070/extras/KinitoWelcome.png?t=1704834493"><br/>Kinito is able to walk, talk, browse, adapt, and play games as Kinito is like no other with its adaptive technology! Kinito is h̶i̶d̶i̶n̶g̶ ̶a̶ ̶d̶a̶r̶k̶ ̶s̶e̶c̶r̶e̶t a friend you'll never forget with its critically acclaimed react respond algorithm to make your experience in̶d̶e̶f̶i̶n̶i̶t̶e truly unique. Where d̶i̶d̶ he ̶g̶o else can you find a friend like Kinito with its multitude of great features and friendly love! <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2075070/extras/SteamImageLowerRes.png?t=1704834493"><br/>Kinito will be your friend and you can s̶t̶o̶p̶ ̶i̶t be there's! <br/>So why wait as with your new virtual assistant and friend you can have f̶o̶r̶e̶v̶e̶r everlasting fun!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elemental Engagements</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748400/Elemental_Engagements/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748400/extras/Steam_About_Image.png?t=1704824159"><br/>Wield god powers and command legions of elemental thralls against your friends! Elemental Engagements is a split screen, versus, real-time-strategy game. Gain favor with the elemental gods to use their 16 powers, battle on 3 maps, and play with either Keyboard or Controller!<h2 class="bb_tag">Elemental God Powers</h2>As a major wind god, you'll wield wind powers. However, winning the favor of the other gods will grant you fire, water, and earth god powers.<br/>Use wind to control the battlefield! Use fire to damage your opponent! Use water to support your units! Use earth to deny enemy movement!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748400/extras/GodPowerExample_SteamDescription.gif?t=1704824159"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sacrifice and Gain Favor</h2>As a match progresses, you can choose which elements you will sacrifice your thralls to. The more territory you capture, the more favor and god powers you will gain for the associated elements, but you can only have a limited amount! This means that no game will play the same and each player must choose their sacrifices wisely.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748400/extras/FavorExample_SteamDescription.gif?t=1704824159"><h2 class="bb_tag">Pick Up &amp; Play</h2>Elemental Engagements is a progressively-faster paced game on match by match basis. This means that most matches will last 5-20 minutes. The controls are designed specifically for the gamepad and split-screen gameplay, so RTS veterans and casual players alike will find tons of fun and room to strategize!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748400/extras/Steam_About_Image_End.png?t=1704824159"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RC Revolution: High Voltage - 免费玩</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2663450/RC_Revolution_High_Voltage/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2663450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Dive into RC Revolution High Voltage, the exhilarating free version of RC Revolution </h2>Select from three dynamic cars, unlock a fourth, and challenge our AI for a fifth. Customize for style and performance, and get ready for stunt-filled tracks and nitro-fueled speed craze. Your high-nitro adventure awaits!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2663450/extras/New_Text_L_drive_into.gif?t=1704822490"><h2 class="bb_tag">Experience the Thrill of RC Revolution High Voltage</h2>Discover RC Revolution High Voltage – the ultimate free RC racing adventure! Choose your car, master stunts, and unleash nitro speeds. This game blends strategy with exhilarating action, offering a unique, timeless racing experience. Dive into a world of speed, skill, and style!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2663450/extras/2_text_R_giant_world.gif?t=1704822490"><h2 class="bb_tag">Exhilarating Stunts and Individual Triumphs</h2>Master extreme jumps, twists, and flips in this solo racing adventure. Customize for peak performance, conquer challenging tracks, and elevate your racing prowess. Every race is a chance to defy gravity and make your mark!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2663450/extras/01_Text_L_car+electro.gif?t=1704822490"><h2 class="bb_tag">Exclusive Cars, Diverse Tracks, and Personalized Customization</h2>Start with three specialized cars and unlock two more as you progress. Each track offers unique challenges to test your skills. Customize your select vehicles to match your racing style and see the impact on your track performance.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2663450/extras/Text_L_1v_strip_race.gif?t=1704822490"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Summit Library</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2604300/The_Summit_Library/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Welcome, Keeper.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604300/extras/tsl_banner_steam.png?t=1704822147"><br/><br/>...To the wonders of the Summit Library; the largest and most important Library in the Eawin Empire. Your trade has been suffering under the rule of the current Emperor -- but with the Summit requesting your services things are looking up.<br/><br/>Except when you arrive you suddenly find yourself in a dangerous magical mystery. Something's wrong with the books, and the Library is falling apart at the seams. <br/><br/>Also, there might be a war? But the Summit Library is situated on neutral territory, so that doesn't affect you.  <br/><br/>...Right? <br/><br/>As you set out the uncover the Library's secrets, you get drawn into the complexities of the Empire's politics; rebellion, betrayal, underground organisations, and more. Meet the various people residing at the Summit Library; make alliances and enemies; fall in love and get your heart broken. <br/><br/>Make choices that matter and explore all the multiple routes and endings, as well as the secrets you can record in your Codex.<br/><br/>May you live to see the end of this tale written.<br/><br/>*<br/><br/><strong>Meet the Residents</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604300/extras/ber_tsl.png?t=1704822147"><br/><br/><i>Berit - the High Librarian</i><br/>Overworked and underappreciated, Berit is slowly being crushed by the expectations put on her shoulders.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604300/extras/aias_tsl.png?t=1704822147"><br/><br/><i>Aias - the Cynical Investigator</i><br/>Standoffish and unfriendly, Aias doesn't seem to have much taste for his work, using his position as Librarian to discover hidden truths instead.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604300/extras/riv_tsl.png?t=1704822147"><br/><br/><i>River - the Shrewd Politician</i><br/>Calculating, charming, and a little too interested in the secrets of your trade, River's true intentions remain a mystery.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604300/extras/yak_tsl1.png?t=1704822147"><br/><br/><i>Yakyar - the Rebel Survivor</i><br/>Escaping a bloody fate, Yakyar wields magic of their own -- and seems to know far more about yours than possible. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604300/extras/thas_tsl1.png?t=1704822147"><br/><br/><i>Thasar - the Runaway Soldier</i><br/>Weary of killing and made bitter by the blood on his hands, all Thasar wants is to turn his back on the world.<br/><br/>*<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A magical mystery set in a fantasy-rich world<br/></li><li>Choices that matter; have your actions and relationships with others shape the story<br/></li><li>A customisable MC; choose your name, appearance, pronouns, and place of origin<br/></li><li>A diverse LGBTQ+ cast<br/></li><li>Collectible CGs<br/></li><li>Unlockable information for your codex<br/></li><li>Optional mature intimacy scenes</li></ul><br/>Content warnings: <br/>Fantasy violence, death, blood, strong language, screenshakes, sexual themes and language.<br/><br/>This game will feature mature content and mature intimacy scenes in the future, and is intended for 18+ audiences. These scenes can always be skipped without penalty and are completely optional for gameplay.<br/><br/>Currently Chapter 1 is out and free to play! Check back soon for the next installment.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Lovey-Dovey Demon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2183430/My_LoveyDovey_Demon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2183430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2183430/extras/story.png?t=1704824741"><br/><br/>Taiki is your average guy. He’s nineteen years old, in his first year of university, and he’s just starting to learn what it means to be an adult.<br/><br/>During the summer vacation, Taiki goes to the countryside to stay with his grandparents alongside his siblings: the haughty, fashionable Chiharu; the tomboyish troublemaker Nene; and the sweet, shy Reza.<br/><br/>Taiki wants to have a relaxing summer, but his hopes are dashed when Nene breaks into their grandfather’s study, which is strictly out of bounds. Inside his study, Nene finds a treasure trove of dusty old books, including a tome full of instructions on how to summon demons.<br/><br/>Nene sets about this demonic summoning ritual at once, and calls upon a fearsome figure from the deepest, darkest depths of Hell…<br/><br/>Who just so happens to be a cute girl with pink hair and an impressive bust?!<br/><br/>Now Taiki’s in a real pinch. Not only does he have to look after his siblings, but he also has his demonic guest, Elisabeth, to worry about – and she’s completely besotted with him! What in the world is Taiki going to do now?!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2183430/extras/features.png?t=1704824741"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 80k of text (approx 4-6 hours of reading)<br/></li><li> A kinetic story with no choices or branches<br/></li><li> Detailed character artwork<br/></li><li> A lot of pretty backgrounds of the Japanese countryside<br/></li><li> A soothing OST<br/></li><li> A very cute demon girl<br/></li><li> A light, sweet, fluffy romance story!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2183430/extras/chuu.png?t=1704824741"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystic Strife</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2452720/Mystic_Strife/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2452720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2452720/extras/description-logo.png?t=1704819657"><br/><br/>Mystic Strife is a fast-paced chaotic party fighting game for up to eight friends. Choose one of six characters with unique abilities and prepare yourself for a simple yet surprisingly deep platforming deathmatch!<h2 class="bb_tag">Characters:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Ranger:</strong> Equipped with a bow and three recoverable arrows.<br/></li><li> <strong>Wizard:</strong> Slings a torrent of fireballs and can cast a powerful long-range magic beam.<br/></li><li> <strong>Necromancer:</strong> Raises the dead to muster a legion of skeletons that persist through rounds.<br/></li><li> <strong>Rogue:</strong> Eqipped with a hookshot to quickly manuever around the stage and to pull in her foes.<br/></li><li> <strong>Engineer:</strong> Equiped with a reloadable musket and can build repairable turrets.<br/></li><li> <strong>Dragoon:</strong> Weilding a lance, she can take to the skies with a mighty leap and come crashing down with a powerful shockwave.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Tight platforming controls that are simple to learn, hard to master.<br/></li><li> Deflect physical projectiles back at your opponents with a well-timed strike.<br/></li><li> Pick up various powerups like shields, speed boosts and more.<br/></li><li> Six unique characters.<br/></li><li> Nine playable stages.</li></ul> <br/><strong>PLEASE NOTE: This game has no single-player content. It must be played with your buddies IRL or through Steam Remote Play.</strong> (Buddies not included)						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tick, Tank, Boom</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2237950/Tick_Tank_Boom/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2237950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Tick, Tank, Boom is an arcade multiplayer-shooter where players fight each other in various game modes like free for all, domination or capture the flag. A large selection of tanks will give you everything you need to find your perfect playstyle to succeed on the battlefield.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2237950/extras/multiplayer.png?t=1704819622"><br/><br/>In Tick, Tank, Boom you battle other players from around the world online, or host a LAN party with your friends - the choice is yours! With a large selection of game modes and custom rule settings, you can have exactly the experience you want.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hertz</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2343820/Hertz/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2343820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2343820/extras/wl_eng.gif?t=1704815356"><br/><br/>Launch into a relentless roguelike action experience in this top-down shooter with bombs!<br/><br/>In a robotic world, control Lizzy and their band of unlockable beasty bots, each hungry for upgrades to enhance their abilities. However, the precious resources required are guarded by Steel Sentinels, guardians of the arena. Your mission is to outmaneuver these sentinels, collect valuable upgrades, and create powerful, game-changing synergies. Will you outsmart these mechanical wardens and survive the treacherous arena to build the ultimate beasty bot?<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Many weapons</strong>: bombs, mines, missiles, and special bullet ammunition types like metal, poison, fire, and ice.<br/></li><li> <strong>Resource gathering</strong>: Destroy enemies and breakable blocks to get resources necessary to upgrade your animal bot.<br/></li><li> <strong>Customizable Upgrades</strong>: Combine over 60+ unique upgrades for powerful and diverse gameplay strategies.<br/></li><li> <strong>Varied Encounters</strong>: Experience diverse gameplay with randomized enemy types, spawn points, and resource distribution within levels, creating unique encounters each playthrough.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">LIZZY BOT</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2343820/extras/LizzyBot.png?t=1704815356"><h2 class="bb_tag">BAMBI BOT (unlockable)</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2343820/extras/BambiBot.png?t=1704815356"><h2 class="bb_tag">FOXY BOT (unlockable)</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2343820/extras/FoxyBot.png?t=1704815356"><h2 class="bb_tag">RABBY BOT (unlockable)</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2343820/extras/RabbyBot.png?t=1704815356"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Need More Steam!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2745080/We_Need_More_Steam/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build and design your power plant for the town. The demand for electricity is constantly increasing, and you are tasked with supplying that power. Turn water into steam and steam into electricity with the use of water pumps, boilers, tanks, and nuclear reactors.<br>
<br>
Each town has different demands and a limited amount of space to build your power plant. Planning ahead is necessary as you manage space, money, and supply versus demand of electricity. <br>
<br>
Unlock each level by meeting the town's electricity demands and scoring enough to satisfy the endless demand for power.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Splat!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2680370/Splat/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2680370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Character, Story, Lore, the building blocks of every great game...<br>
But that's really hard to make.<br>
<br>
SPLAT! Race your way your down a series of increasingly difficult levels avoiding obstacles and trying to reach the end without going Splat!<br>
<br>
Gameplay:<br>
You fall through levels avoiding obstacles, and using powerups to try and reach the end. There are no lives but if you don't beat the level before the time runs out you lose. Obstacles may move and trick you so be careful where you aim!<br>
<br/>
Once the game is complete you can replay all levels and try and beat your best scores!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooter for Dummies</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1680390/Shooter_for_Dummies/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1680390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Shooter for Dummies puts players in the perspective of a dummy. Play the most iconic FPS PvP maps: CTF, Team Deathmatch, Kill confirmed... where the winning is not the common goal: The dummy with less receiving damage wins! But don't worry dummies, you can punch players almost off the map!<br/><br/>Play in teams of 5 players to the different game modes:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Capture the flag<br/></li><li> Team deatchmatch<br/></li><li> Rush<br/></li><li> Kill confirmed<br/></li><li> Conquest<br/></li><li> King of the hill</li></ul><br/>There are always 2 ways to finnish a map: by completing the map objectives, or after 5 minutes of game. Dummies, you are the target! Only you can score for your team, and also your health is the most important element on this game. Avoid taking damange, don't let the players attack you!<br/><br/>Players, you are not forgotten either. You will have access to a set of temporal bonus abilities both,  to attack and protect the dummies... or the other players... Use of the 4 characters and demonstrate your FPS skills on this game changing experience.<br/><br/>Shooter for Dummies does never ends as it starts! Tactics and strategy will be more important than ever to win.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Santa's Gift Grab</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2642120/Santas_Gift_Grab/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2642120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2642120/extras/gif.gif?t=1704799191"> <br/><br/>Santa Gift Grab: Step into a snowy world with our straightforward collector's game. Featuring clean low-poly graphics and soothing Christmas tunes, your task is to help Santa gather his misplaced gifts. But be quick! Time is running out. Can you collect them all?<br/><br/>Features:<br/>• 3 Levels - Play through 3 levels with increasing difficulty.<br/>• Cookies - Collect cookies to ensure you don't run out of time.<br/>• Gifts - Gather all of Santa's gifts to complete each level.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAID: Shadow Legends</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2333480/RAID_Shadow_Legends/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2333480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The realm of Teleria trembles beneath the shadow of the Dark Lord Siroth. You have been called upon by the Arbiter, the immortal guardian of Teleria, to stop him. Heed the call!<br/><br/>Dive into a deep turn-based RPG with 8 exciting game modes and extensive character customization. Enjoy a story-driven campaign, competitive PvP clashes with players from across the world, and constant new challenges with our stream of updates. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2333480/extras/625x100_1.png?t=1704795886"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>KEY GAME FEATURES</strong> </h2><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SUMMON 800+ CHAMPIONS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2333480/extras/2_champions.gif?t=1704795886"><br/>Collect hundreds of unique Champions from 15 playable factions and combine them into unstoppable teams to take down your enemies. Dark elves, Ogryn warlords, Lizardmen, and more can all join your ranks – if you earn their loyalty.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>MASTER TACTICAL TURN-BASED GAMEPLAY</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2333480/extras/3_master_tactical.gif?t=1704795886"><br/>Kit out your Champions with epic gear you loot along the way and customize their masteries for millions of possible builds. Level up your team and play them your way, unleashing a barrage of powerful skills and game-changing support abilities.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>PROVE YOURSELF IN 3 PvP MODES</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2333480/extras/4_teamup_with_friends.gif?t=1704795886"><br/>Enter the Arena and go head-to-head with other players to unlock special gear and climb up the leaderboards. Then, really put your skills to the test in real-time PvP battles with Live Arena.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>EXPLORE ENGAGING PvE CONTENT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2333480/extras/5_PvE_content.gif?t=1704795886"><br/>Tear your way through a visually stunning campaign accompanied by a rich, fully-voiced dark fantasy narrative. Conquer the forces of Darkness as well as 13 challenging Dungeon bosses, fast-paced Faction Wars, and the notorious Doom Tower to earn valuable loot.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TEAM UP WITH FRIENDS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2333480/extras/6_teamup.gif?t=1704795886"><br/>Join forces with your fellow players to take on Clan Bosses for exclusive gear, Shards to summon new Champions, and more. Once you’re strong enough, you can also compete against 4 other Clans in the epic Hydra Clash.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>GET LOST IN THE LORE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2333480/extras/7_lore.gif?t=1704795886"><br/>Learn about the inhabitants of Teleria through their unique backstories as well as the world itself. Immerse yourself even further by checking out the animated limited series RAID: Call of the Arbiter on YouTube.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMUZA</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2600790/SAMUZA/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Welcome to the world of SAMUZA! </h2>In this time attack obstacle course game, you play as one of the "SAMUZA" series of robots who tries to restore the lost world by finding it's allies.<br/><br/><strong>Story</strong><br/>The year is 299X. Humanity has perished, and the world is ruled by a runaway artificial intelligence.<br/>Foreseeing the end, the last Engineer made 9 keys, each with a piece of code, to be used when all else failed to restore the world to it's prevous state.<br/>You are Humanity's last hope, the robot series "Samuza-L800". You must find the 9 special robots scattered around the world and collect their keys.<br/>The ruling AI will surely interfere. You must overcome it's traps, collect the keys and use their combined code to reset the world.<br/>I wish you luck!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600790/extras/mode_story.jpg?t=1704793025"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>Compete in several game modes with different levels from the game's story and the community.<br/>Each level has a track you must complete while avoiding a series of obstacles. <br/><br/><strong>Story Mode</strong><br/>The game's story campaign. Complete a series of premade levels and unlock new blocks to use in your creations.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600790/extras/level_1p.png?t=1704793025"><br/><br/><strong>Endless Mode</strong><br/>Complete random community made levels. Be careful not to fall off the course, as you will lose one life each time you reset. See how far you can go!<br/><br/><strong>Search Mode</strong><br/>Use this to find community made levels. Use a code to find specific levels or follow other creators to easilly find their levels.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600790/extras/level_2p.png?t=1704793025"><br/><br/><strong>2P Versus Mode</strong><br/>Play with your friends in split screen local multiplayer.<br/>You will get random levels from the community. In this mode there are no lives, have fun with your friends any way you want to.<br/><br/><strong>2P Search Mode</strong><br/>Play any specific level with a friend in split screen local multiplayer.<br/>Here you can search and play community made levels.<br/>You can play against your friends on the levels you created! Prepare a difficult course and compete against your friends!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600790/extras/mode_creator.png?t=1704793025"><h2 class="bb_tag">Creator Mode</h2><strong>Make your own content!</strong><br/>You can create your own original levels in the Creator Mode! <br/>Here you can choose from a collection of blocks and combine them to make your unique levels.<br/>Unlock new blocks by playing the Story Campaign and Endless Modes!<br/><br/><strong>Build at your pace</strong><br/>Take your time in the creator mode. Test your progress at any time inside the Creator.<br/>Save your progress locally or to your account. Once complete, you can upload your levels and share them with your friends and the community!<br/>Let everyone around the world play in your original levels!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue Frontiers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/814730/Rogue_Frontiers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/814730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/814730/extras/RF_Fight_350_small_feather.gif?t=1704771856"><br/>Embark on a bone-chilling journey of survival and terror with your comrades, as you traverse a perilous realm filled with unfathomable horrors lurking in every corner. Brace yourself for heart-pumping battles against bloodthirsty beasts, honing your skills and mastering your craft to emerge victorious in the face of insurmountable odds.<br/><br/>With every step you take, you'll encounter diverse locales, each more treacherous than the last, and daunting obstacles that will test your mettle to the core. But you'll have no choice but to press on, constructing an unbreachable fortress to shield you from the darkness that threatens to consume you.<br/><br/>And yet, even your fortress may not be enough to withstand the unrelenting onslaught of your foes. You must hone your tactics, refine your strategy, and outwit the most cunning of enemies if you hope to survive.<br/><br/>In Rogue Frontiers, there is no room for error. Every decision you make could mean the difference between life and death. But with each victory, you'll grow stronger, more resilient, and better equipped to face the next challenge.<br/><br/>And with frequent updates featuring bug fixes, balance adjustments, and fresh content drops, Rogue Frontiers is an ever-evolving nightmare, where your feedback and input will help shape the future of the game. So join the fray now, and leave your mark on the annals of horror gaming forever. But be warned: once you enter, there may be no escape.<br/><br/><strong>EXPLORE THE WORLD</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/814730/extras/RF_Temple_Orc_350.gif?t=1704771856"><br/>Unleash your sense of adventure and step into a world steeped in mystery and intrigue. Explore a vast and varied landscape, brimming with dangerous foes to conquer, precious resources to gather, and hidden secrets to uncover.<br/><br/>Prepare to battle bloodthirsty monsters at every turn, as you journey through treacherous terrain, encountering unique adversaries with their own deadly abilities and cunning tactics. Only the bravest and most skilled adventurers will survive the perils that lie ahead.<br/><br/>But the greatest rewards await those who dare to venture into the most perilous dungeons, facing the most challenging creatures in their quest for glory. These ancient, labyrinthine tombs are filled with untold riches, rare artifacts, and coveted crafting recipes, but they are also home to the deadliest monsters in the land.<br/><br/>Surviving these harrowing encounters will require every ounce of skill and strategy you possess, as you adapt to ever-changing circumstances and employ every weapon in your arsenal. Only those with the courage and fortitude to persevere will emerge victorious, earning their place among the greatest adventurers of all time.<br/><br/>So prepare to immerse yourself in a world of endless possibility, where danger and reward go hand in hand. Gather your wits, arm yourself to the teeth, and embark on a journey unlike any other. The fate of the realm rests in your hands.<br/><br/><strong>DEFEND YOUR STRONGHOLD</strong><br/>Forge unbreakable fortresses, the last bastion of hope in a world teeming with danger and chaos. With a comprehensive building system, you can personalize both the interior and exterior of your structures, creating a safe haven from the perils that lie ahead.<br/><br/>But it won't be easy. As you advance through building tiers, enhancing and expanding your stronghold, you'll have to stay one step ahead of the hostile Horde, who launch regular assaults on your base.<br/><br/>To fend off these relentless attackers, you'll need to construct traps and defensive structures that will keep them at bay. Every decision you make could mean the difference between life and death, so you'll need to employ all your ingenuity and strategic thinking to survive.<br/><br/>But the rewards are worth the risk. With every upgrade to your fortress, you'll become stronger, more resilient, and better able to withstand the onslaught of your enemies. And as you progress through the game, you'll unlock new and more powerful building options, allowing you to customize your stronghold to suit your playstyle.<br/><br/>So gather your materials, fire up your imagination, and set to work building the ultimate fortress. The Horde may be relentless, but with the right combination of traps and defensive structures, you can hold them off indefinitely. Do you have what it takes to survive in this hostile world? The fate of your fortress, and your survival, rests in your hands.<br/><br/><strong>GATHER, CRAFT AND SURVIVE</strong><br/>Survival is the name of the game in this harsh and unforgiving world, and you'll need all your wits and resourcefulness to make it through each day. Collect materials from the environment and fashion them into weapons, armor, tools, and defenses that will help you stay alive and fend off the dangers that lurk around every corner.<br/><br/>But survival isn't just about brute strength and firepower. You'll need to be able to cultivate crops and vegetables, cook food, concoct drinks and potions, and upgrade your living space to create a safe and comfortable haven in this hostile world.<br/><br/>As you progress through the game, you'll face more formidable foes, and you'll need to discover new items to craft in order to stay ahead of the game. With each new challenge you overcome, you'll gain experience and become more skilled at gathering, crafting, and surviving.<br/><br/>But be warned: the challenges will be many, and the stakes will be high. You'll need to be able to adapt quickly to changing circumstances and make split-second decisions that could mean the difference between life and death.<br/><br/>So strap on your boots, grab your tools, and get ready for an unparalleled experience of gathering, crafting, and survival. This world is unforgiving, but with the right combination of skill, luck, and determination, you just might make it out alive.<br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Venture forth into an enormous, meticulously crafted world where every locale boasts a distinct ambience, unique foes, and resources.<br/></li><li>Embark on your odyssey solo or team up with up to 32 players on player-hosted servers and brace yourself for scaling enemy difficulty.<br/></li><li>Explore extraordinary biomes, each offering its own special ingredients to gather, monsters to battle, and dungeons to delve into.<br/></li><li>Indulge in a highly detailed crafting system where you can hone your skills and create hundreds of items, unlocking endless possibilities.<br/></li><li>Choose from dozens of weapons and armor types, progressing through various tiers as you journey through the world.<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in stamina-based combat that rewards preparation and skill. Utilize weapon types with unique attacks, different blocking styles, ranged combat, dodges, and parries to combat your enemies.<br/></li><li>Fuel your adventure with a rewarding food system where you gain health, stamina, and regeneration buffs depending on the foods you consume.<br/></li><li>Experience a flexible building system that takes structural integrity into account, allowing you to create anything from a small shelter to an entire village, claim abandoned buildings as your own, and customize them to your liking.<br/></li><li>Protect your base from the Horde, who will launch attacks on all your bases. Or, make sacrifices to them beforehand and they will skip an attack, adding a whole new level of strategic gameplay. Get ready for the ultimate survival adventure!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Party 丧尸派对</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2507630/Zombie_Party/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Zombie Party" is an anti-superhero-themed strategy game. You need to play the role of a chaotic ability user GRAVEDIGGER, and use your super power to summon the zombie army to destroy the land that is governed by the government and the PARLIAMENT OF FIVE, The established order of power.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/小标题文字1_EN.png?t=1704796559"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/1.gif?t=1704796559"><br/>You can use your superpowers to summon thousands of zombies and form an army of the living dead loyal to you. But be aware that once summoned, most of them will tend to act according to their bloodthirsty instincts. At this time, you need to summon more powerful special infected. They will perform their respective duties and become an important aid for you to fight against the enemy.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/小标题文字2_EN.png?t=1704796559"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/2.gif?t=1704796559"><br/>Using your powerful Chaos abilities on the battlefield, whether it is to amplify friendly troops or let them self-destruct and damage enemies, will have a vital impact on the entire battle situation.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/小标题文字3_EN.png?t=1704796559"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/3.gif?t=1704796559"><br/>In a secret corner where no one is watching, you will build a refuge for those with super powers. Configure upgrade modules for various instruments and buildings to make your abilities more powerful<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/小标题文字4_EN.png?t=1704796559"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/4.gif?t=1704796559"><br/>The conflict and hatred could no longer be suppressed. He embarked on the road of revenge and fought fiercely with more than a dozen heroes. Become a [gravedigger] to destroy all this hypocrisy and injustice, and sound the death knell for the sanctimonious superhero.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primateria</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1397130/Primateria/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1397130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1397130/extras/FUSION_EDIT.gif?t=1704851139"><br/><br/>Embark on an epic journey in Primateria, a game redefining the roguelike deckbuilder with a nod to classic Yu-Gi-Oh! experience. Fuse cards, battle divine beings, and navigate through a universe teeming with challenges and surprises. Embrace the thrill of endless combinations and tactical depths.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Revolutionary Infinite Fusion:</strong> Primateria redefines deck-building with its innovative infinite fusion system. You can infinitely merge cards to create more potent tokens, breaking free from the confines of traditional turn-based mechanics. This system, while drawing inspiration from classics like Yu-Gi-Oh!, introduces a distinct and innovative twist.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Unleash High Attack Combos: </strong>Primateria empowers you to unleash powerful combo attacks through the unique abilities of each card, providing a thrilling and satisfying gameplay experience that captures the essence of the most dramatic moments in card battle games.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Strategic Fusion Summoning:</strong> Elevate your summoning tactics by perfectly matching levels for fusion. Every decision you make, every move you plan, becomes a crucial part of your strategic journey, demanding your tactical foresight and mastery.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Balanced Risk and Reward with Card Devolution:</strong> Face the unique challenge where high-level cards, upon defeat, transform back into their original forms rather than being destroyed. This balanced risk-reward system keeps your strategic play dynamic and engaging, constantly calling for your tactical adaptability.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Adaptive Mana Pool System:</strong> Primateria introduces a unique mana pool system tied to the fusion mechanic. This system doesn’t just govern card play but also powers up your special abilities, adding an additional layer of strategy to your gameplay.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>“Dual Graveyard” Dynamics: </strong>Primateria introduces a dual graveyard system – the "Damage Pile" and "Discard Pile," adding complexity to the management of defeated and discarded cards and introducing a new strategic element to the gameplay.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Protection &amp; Repositioning Mechanic: </strong>The game's design incorporates frontline and backline battle dynamics, forcing you to think critically about card placement and repositioning strategies, enhancing the depth of tactical play.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Rich, Expansive Universe: </strong>Set in a beautifully crafted world, Primateria offers a narrative-rich experience. Players, as "Polupus," embark on a journey filled with divine entities and mythical challenges, making each playthrough not just a game but a story unfolding.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Roguelike Elements for Endless Replayability: </strong>With a variety of relics, consumables, and ever-changing maps, the game offers you immense replayability, ensuring that no two playthroughs are the same.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Almighty Legendary Cards:</strong> To make playing cards even more exciting, new legendary cards can be summoned by fulfilling very specific conditions and challenges during a run. These incredibly powerful cards have amazing new art and represent the divine characters in the game.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1397130/extras/legendary_cards.png?t=1704851139"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here's some of the new and exciting things you can expect on the full game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A complete story mode with 9 unique quests, a thrilling story and a bunch of characters!<br/></li><li>100+ cards, with hundreds of effects, mechanics and endless combos!<br/></li><li>43 Steam achievements for you to challenge yourselves and unlock!<br/></li><li>12 unique pre-built decks with specific archetypes for you to explore, including a Random Deck for experienced players to challenge their might!<br/></li><li>20+ special items that can be found and used in runs to enhance your chances of reaching the surface!<br/></li><li>10+ challenging nodes for exploration!<br/></li><li>A new and improved Endless Mode with challenging bosses, enemy encounters, exploration and much more!<br/></li><li>A gallery system that serves as a compendium for all cards, items and unlockables in the game so you can track your progress!<br/></li><li>A meta-progression system that allows you to gain experience, level up, and unlock all sorts of magical items and cards for your Primateria journey!<br/></li><li>And much, much more!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before The Sun Rises</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2648370/Before_The_Sun_Rises/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2648370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Before the Sun Rises is a 3D exploration and platform game about connection with nature and others. You play as a water drop, born from the misty dew of dawn. Can you restore the forest of your birth before the sun rises?<br>
<br>
In single player, explore the landscape to find and collect the water that you need to bloom trees and move onto the next area. In multiplayer, connect with friends or strangers online, help each other find water sources, and work together to restore the forest! <br>
<br>
NOTE: The current version of Before the Sun Rises is a demo and work in progress. While multiplayer is available, it is still being tested and is currently in beta.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARCH ALL - FLIES</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2749720/SEARCH_ALL__FLIES/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2749720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">SEARCH ALL - FLIES</h2> is a hidden object game in which you need to find all the flies in a large location. The flies will be located in a variety of places, from the most prominent to barely noticeable places. The entire game location looks lively because of the animation elements. Find all the flies! Don't let them go unnoticed :)<br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/>- Animation elements on location;<br/>- 100 flies to find;<br/>- Pleasant soundtrack;<br/>- The gameplay can be interrupted at any time, and the game will automatically save the result;<br/>- Implemented hints! If you find it difficult to find an item, use the hint!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searching For Rest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2338240/Searching_For_Rest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2338240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							When you died your body could not be found, a funeral was held and an empty casket was lowered into your grave. Many years later your soul has brought you back from death to finally find eternal rest.<br/><br/><strong>50+ Unlocks</strong><br/>Advance your Necropolis and unlock game altering upgrades as you play. Discover Curses that influence your gameplay in different ways.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2338240/extras/NecropolisGIF.gif?t=1704751296"><br/><br/><strong>Strategic Gameplay</strong><br/>Fight fearsome foes and gain unique abilities each time you venture through the cemetery. Uncover the mystery of your unending search and fight powerful bosses in the Catacombs.<br/><br/><strong>Deckbuilding and Upgrades</strong><br/>Create the perfect graveyard and obtain powerful upgrades on your search for rest. Mix and match different upgrades each time you play to create unstoppable builds.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2338240/extras/UpgradeGIFSFR.gif?t=1704751296"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chat Guess Games</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2523390/Chat_Guess_Games/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2523390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Chat Guess Games is a community game for Twitch Streamers. A game for your community to battle it out and see who truly knows the most about video games!<br/><br/>Screenshots, artwork, genres, release year and more are displayed on screen and chat races to guess the correct game first!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Rounds can be started with chat commands, from within the game, or users can use their channel points to redeem a round.</li><li>Autoplay mode where the rounds keep coming, perfect for engaging viewers during breaks.</li><li>Channel Leaderboards to encourage competition in your community and Global Leaderboards to compete against other channels and see which community is best at game trivia.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
