<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Snowbreak: Containment Zone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668080/Snowbreak_Containment_Zone/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Snowbreak: Containment Zone is a 3D sci-fi RPG-shooter powered by the Unreal Engine 4 that offers a next-gen, cross-platform gaming experience, sharing your progress across all of your devices. <br/><br/>The Descent of the Titans turned a once-vibrant city into the devastated wasteland of Containment Zone Aleph. As the Adjutant of Heimdall Force, bravely undertake missions alongside Manifestations with the powers of gods and unique personalities, seeking to bring this bitter winter to an end...<br/><br/>[Enjoy Hybrid Combat]<br/>Snowbreak's weaponry injects realism into a sci-fi setting, with designs closely simulating future firearms technology. This combines with the otherworldly, RPG-like skill mechanic to create a refreshing combat experience.<br/><br/>[Take on Titans]<br/>The Descent of the Titans completely changed the world, and the battlefield. Feel the thrill of battling giants in this dystopian future!<br/><br/>[Befriend Operatives]<br/>Spend time with your Heimdall Force companions in the Base system. Decorate, chat, and give gifts to grow closer!<br/><br/>[Play Co-Op in Gigalink] <br/>Tired of exploring alone? Join up with friends and fight enemies together!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milo and the Christmas Gift</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2716140/Milo_and_the_Christmas_Gift/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							After his adventure in Milo and the Magpies, Milo is looking forward to spending a cosy Christmas at home. But a Christmas gift is about to upset his holiday celebrations, especially when said gift disappears after a little misunderstanding! Can you help Milo bring home the lost Gift and save Christmas for Marleen… and himself?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_playing_1.gif?t=1703496663"> <br/><br/>Milo and the Christmas Gift is a free-to-play short and atmospheric point-and-click adventure game created by artist Johan Scherft. The game is a spin-off story following the events in Milo and the Magpies. The game has 5 chapters and a gameplay time of around 30 minutes!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/>■ Relaxing yet stimulating game-play<br/>Join Milo in his home and revisit some of the neighbouring gardens, but this time in a wintery Christmas wonderland! Interact with the festive environment and solve small point-and-click / hidden-object puzzles.<br/><br/>■ Captivating artistic atmosphere<br/>Each hand-painted, interior and snowy garden Milo has to search through has its unique personality, reflecting that of Milo’s owners and next-door neighbours respectively.<br/><br/>■ Atmospheric soundtrack<br/>Each chapter has its own festive theme song composed by Victor Butzelaar.<br/><br/>■ Average playtime: 15-30 minutes<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_snow_1.gif?t=1703496663"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few Nights More: Genesis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713070/Few_Nights_More_Genesis/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Please note: This is a free prologue and it includes act 1, and only 1 playable character and blood school is playable, The maximum heritage gained is limited to 50, and the maximum difficulty can be set to 2. As well only one castle will be available. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Blood3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Conquer castles and claim your birthright!</strong><br/> <br/>The fight to reclaim your place in this world begins. Rebuild lost ruins, make them stronger and defend them against your enemies. After you regain your strength, move on to conquer more territories and eventually claim your birthright.<br/><br/>Few Nights More offers the unique fusing of castle management and turn based rogue-like combat. Fight against humanity, the undisputed masters of this world in your absence. Choose between eight different Vampire Lords, each with their own ambition and history. Find your trinkets, skills and perks along your way. Design your very own castle by placing the right rooms, adding decors that directly contribute to your army and your Vampire Lord. Conquer more castles so your influence and power grow, until you claim your birthright.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Ferocity3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Core Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Design your castle by adding new Rooms, Traps and Minions. Stack up on some buffs with shiny decors to get ready for the invasion screen to defend it to the end of every night!<br/> <br/></li><li> Choose among 7 different Vampire Lords with unique History, Gameplay and Abilities.<br/> <br/></li><li> Master 1 out of 3 Disciplines each time you play, each with 60 unique skills.<br/> <br/></li><li> Acquire new random skills, perks and trinkets to survive the nights.<br/> <br/></li><li> Excel in either being a Prestigious Vampire, a Seductive one, or master a Terrifying presence against your enemies.<br/><br/></li><li> Test the builds you made against a variety of Hunters, Veterans and Unique Bosses in an action packed turn based combat system.<br/> <br/></li><li> Endure three acts across 12 difficulty levels, striving to survive and progress. Accumulate Heritage Points to enhance your lord's starting stats, skills, and unlock new castles and talents unique to each lord.<br/><br/></li><li> Engage in the boundless challenge of Infinity Mode, where you can continuously test your limits without relying on a castle. Each night, you will be presented with three options to advance, growing stronger as you push yourself to see how far you can go.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703259090"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703259090"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703259090"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703259090"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703259090"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703259090"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1702674942"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grimhook</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667430/Grimhook/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667430/extras/Logo_Text_Small.png?t=1702093226"><br/>Embark on a harrowing journey beneath the ruins of the once-vibrant city of Miletos. <br/><br/>Grimhook, a fast-paced, first-person action-adventure game, thrusts you into the heart of a flooded wasteland where robotic minions reign supreme and an ancient deity lies dormant beneath the city's surface. As Dart, you'll harness powerful abilities to navigate through cavernous depths; grapple, bounce, dash, and slash your way through relentless automata in intense combat arenas while you experience a grim world and a somber narrative.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667430/extras/HighresScreenshot001182.png?t=1702093226"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <i>Fast-paced First-Person Platforming:</i> Unleash a myriad of Lovecraftian abilities as you navigate the caverns of Miletos. Time and combine your powers to swiftly traverse the game's terrain and outmaneuver your enemies.<br/></li><li> <i>Tightly Tuned Combat:</i> Engage in intense battles in multiple combat arenas, utilizing your powers to dodge bullets and decimate robotic foes. Watch as fully destructible adversaries explode, leaving a chaotic aftermath on the battlefield.<br/></li><li> <i>Explore a Cavernous World:</i> Traverse dilapidated skyscrapers, rushing rapids, and forgotten excavations in a sprawling subterranean world. Encounter diverse biomes that add depth and variety to your adventure.<br/></li><li> <i>Hand-Painted Art Style:</i> Immerse yourself in a somber environment brought to life by a carefully hand-painted art style, capturing the melancholic beauty of a city on the brink of ruin.<br/></li><li> <i>Immersive Audio Experience:</i> Immerse yourself in the tragic journey with over 10 electronic tracks in the musical score, composed by BelowCloudNine.<br/></li><li> <i>Voiced Characters:</i> Two fully voiced characters bring intimacy to the narrative and characterize the unlikely camaraderie between Dart and the dormant deity beneath the city.<br/></li><li> <i>Dynamic Animations and Cutscenes:</i> Dynamic first-person animations strike a vivid contrast with the desaturated world. Multiple fully authored first-person cutscenes enhance the immersive storytelling experience.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1702562956"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1702562956"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1703493452"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1703493452"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1703186631"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1703318086"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1703318086"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 5 Tactica</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2254740/Persona_5_Tactica/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join the Phantom Thieves as they lead an uprising of the heart! Assemble a team of beloved heroes in a brand-new story in this thrilling combat adventure set in Persona’s iconic universe. The Persona 5 Tactica: Digital Deluxe Edition includes the following content:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Repaint Your Heart Challenge Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Weapon Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Picaro Summoning Pack + Raoul Persona</li></ul><br/><strong>Ignite your heart— An emotional uprising begins!</strong><br/><br/>After a strange incident, the Phantom Thieves wander into a bizarre realm where its citizens are living under tyrannical oppression. Surrounded by a military group named Legionnaires, they find themselves in grave danger until a mysterious revolutionary named Erina rescues them and offers an enticing deal in exchange for their help. What truth lies behind Erina and the deal she offers to the Phantom Thieves?<br/><br/>Persona 5 Tactica features an all-new story, the return of fan-favorite characters, and brand-new allies and foes. Join the group as they lead an emotional revolution in this thrilling combat adventure!<br/><br/><strong>An Emotional Revolution</strong><br/>Lead an uprising of the heart in a brand-new storyline that takes place in Persona’s iconic universe.<br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Squad</strong><br/>Assemble a team of beloved heroes to fight oppressive armies in thrilling turn-based combat.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Combat</strong><br/>Overthrow your enemies with powerful Personas, an assortment of weapons, and wipe them out with style!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 5 Tactica</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2254740/Persona_5_Tactica/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join the Phantom Thieves as they lead an uprising of the heart! Assemble a team of beloved heroes in a brand-new story in this thrilling combat adventure set in Persona’s iconic universe. The Persona 5 Tactica: Digital Deluxe Edition includes the following content:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Repaint Your Heart Challenge Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Weapon Pack<br/></li><li>Persona 5 Tactica: Picaro Summoning Pack + Raoul Persona</li></ul><br/><strong>Ignite your heart— An emotional uprising begins!</strong><br/><br/>After a strange incident, the Phantom Thieves wander into a bizarre realm where its citizens are living under tyrannical oppression. Surrounded by a military group named Legionnaires, they find themselves in grave danger until a mysterious revolutionary named Erina rescues them and offers an enticing deal in exchange for their help. What truth lies behind Erina and the deal she offers to the Phantom Thieves?<br/><br/>Persona 5 Tactica features an all-new story, the return of fan-favorite characters, and brand-new allies and foes. Join the group as they lead an emotional revolution in this thrilling combat adventure!<br/><br/><strong>An Emotional Revolution</strong><br/>Lead an uprising of the heart in a brand-new storyline that takes place in Persona’s iconic universe.<br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Squad</strong><br/>Assemble a team of beloved heroes to fight oppressive armies in thrilling turn-based combat.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Combat</strong><br/>Overthrow your enemies with powerful Personas, an assortment of weapons, and wipe them out with style!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teardown</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1167630/Teardown/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1167630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Plan the perfect heist using creative problem solving, brute force, and everything around you. Teardown features a fully destructible and truly interactive environment where player freedom and emergent gameplay are the driving mechanics.<br/><br/>Tear down walls with explosives or vehicles to create shortcuts no one thought was possible. Stack objects, build structures, or use floating objects to your advantage. Take your time to create an efficient path through the level, plan the heist and get ready to execute it.<br/><br/>Run, jump, drive, slingshot. Do whatever you need to collect targets, avoid robots or steal whatever your clients ask for. But make sure not to get caught!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1167630/extras/campaign.gif?t=1700055440"><br/><br/><strong>Campaign</strong><br/>With your company pressured by increasing debt, you start accepting work from some more or less shady individuals. Soon you are knee-deep in a murky soup of revenge, betrayal, and insurance fraud. Beginning with some more or less legitimate assignments, you soon find yourself stealing cars, demolishing buildings, blowing up safes, avoiding trigger-happy robots and more. Upgrade your expanding arsenal of tools by searching for hidden valuables scattered around the environments.<br/><br/><strong>Sandbox</strong><br/>Play around in the various environments with the tools you have unlocked. In this mode you have unlimited resources and an abundance of vehicles. No pressure, just pleasure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1167630/extras/sandbox.gif?t=1700055440"><br/><br/><strong>Challenges</strong><br/>Test your skills in experimental game modes. New challenges unlock as you progress through the campaign.<br/><br/><strong>Modding</strong><br/>Teardown has extensive mod support with built-in level editor, Lua scripting and a Steam Workshop integration. Build your own sandbox maps, mini games, tools, vehicles or try out existing mods from the community. <br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fully destructible voxel environments<br/></li><li>Realistic physical simulation of objects, debris, vehicles, water, fire, and smoke<br/></li><li>17 different tools ranging from sledgehammer, blow torch and fire extinguisher to guns and explosives <br/></li><li>Campaign with 40 missions in an escalating storyline<br/></li><li>Sandbox mode for you to roam around in the various environments<br/></li><li>Extensive mod support and Steam Workshop integration</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1702747783"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons 4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1643310/Dungeons_4/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Once upon a time in a realm far, far away, everything was lush and green. The unicorns mingled among the trees and the elves and humans lived peacefully in harmony with their surroundings. Yet somewhere at the edge of a clearing half-hidden among the trees, obscured by a rising veil of fog in the hazy half-darkness of a weather-beaten hut, a shape huddles over a large and ominously glowing crystal ball. A mumbling voice sings ancient formulae, urging the swirling glowing mists inside the crystal to part and give an insight into the future.<br/><br/>“All is in flux, nothing seems certain. Come, oh vagaries of space and time, separate the veil and show us what is yet to come”, the voice grumbles with the hint of an eye faintly reflecting the glow in front of its hood. The shape’s audience, only barely visible in the dim light, leans in closer and listens intently. “Time ebbs and flows, forming pools and wrinkles… but when the mists part only vague images rise from beyond the veil. Shhhh—don’t come too close, you don’t want to disturb my delicate magical weavings do you?” The shape, still bent over the orb, mutters and shoos the other back a bit more into the shadows. “Ah, now it seems to be clearing a little. I can see… something… several somethings, hints of voices echoing in the haze. A baby, something happening on Hill Doom and the coming together of the Council of Snots – what could all this mean?”<br/><br/>In a flash, the light reflected in the eye turns red and a distant evil laughter echoes through the woods. Stay tuned for the return of the Soothsaying Evil!</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/dungeons-4.gif?t=1703077208"><br/><br/>The Absolute Evil and its trusted *cough* servant, the Dark Elf Thalya, return in <strong>Dungeons 4</strong> after the events of its fabulous predecessor to bring about their triumph over the forces of good once more.<br/><br/><strong>Build a cozy and comfortable Dungeon</strong> to suit your creatures’ needs and rule over them, then send them out into the Overworld to kindly remind the good people living there that the Absolute Evil rules over their lands. <strong>Gather your Evilness</strong> in new and dynamic ways <strong>and unleash it upon</strong> the lush green forests and plains of <strong>the Overworld</strong> to turn them over to the dark side. But make sure that <strong>your Dungeon is well-secured</strong> by traps and defended by your creatures, for those pesky Overworlders won’t just twiddle their thumbs while you <strong>turn their land into the Absolute Evil’s most pleasurable holiday paradise</strong>.<br/><br/>But what is that noise? <i>“Gold, gold, gold and gems, gold and gems and gold!”</i> The ancient song echoes throughout the underworld, accompanied by the clanging steel of hammers and axes. <strong>The Dwarves have arrived</strong> to claim their share of the abundant resources and together with the Elves and Humans of the Overworld, they send out their raiding parties to find the Dungeon’s heart.<br/><br/>Dungeons 4 keeps the spirit of its predecessor, but everything is now <strong>bigger, better, and with even more dynamic Evilness™</strong>.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-1_EN.png?t=1703077208"><br/><strong>Everything is better with Dwarves™:</strong> The Dwarves have arrived to build their underground strongholds and the hardy little fellows (although they don’t like being called that) compete with the Ever-Expanding Evil for space and resources.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-2_EN.png?t=1703077208"><br/><strong>It makes your Dungeon great again:</strong> Dungeons are up to four times larger than before and there are many more creatures who wait for the All-Commanding Evil’s orders to conquer the Overworld. Now the time has come for massive armies and truly sprawling dungeons!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-3_EN.png?t=1703077208"><br/><strong>Ripe for the taking:</strong> The Overworld is bigger than ever before. Gain Evilness by beating Mini Bosses like the obsessively harmonious Unicorn and use it to transform the Overworld into stunning biomes of pure evil.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-4_EN.png?t=1703077208"><br/><strong>New and shiny:</strong> An ability-based Perk system for Thalya, the Absolute Evil’s trusted *cough* and most loyal subordinate, grants her impressive new powers. The Absolute Evil can now enjoy taking over the world, governing the creatures and slapping subordinates even more with the customizable Evil Hand.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-5_EN.png?t=1703077208"><br/><strong>Minions, everywhere:</strong> The Horde, the Undead and the Demons wait to do the Absolute Evil’s bidding, with more creatures than ever eagerly following the gesturing Evil’s orders, and Snots will play a much more prominent role this time.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-6_EN.png?t=1703077208"><br/><strong>Many ways to tell the story:</strong> A long campaign, narrated by the beloved English Narrator from previous titles, as well as several skirmish maps all to challenge your rule as the Absolute Evil.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-7_EN.png?t=1703077208"><br/><strong>Change the world:</strong> Spread your Evilness across the Overworld to bring lush and green environments over to the dark side, now shining even more vibrantly and beautifully evil as you spread your evilness across many new biomes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1643310/extras/feature-8_EN.png?t=1703077208"><br/><strong>Work together, slay together:</strong> 2-player co-op multiplayer with both players managing one Dungeon together. All maps from the skirmish mode and the campaign are playable in co-op.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>phantom unit 999</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2689490/phantom_unit_999/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2689490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Welcome to the World of Phantoms Unit 999</h2>You are about to dive into the depths of a new mission called Storm Phantoms<br/>The unit's monitoring team noticed something strange that had begun to happen in the previous days<br/>Some places in the world have come to life and we do not know why<br/>The goal of the mission is to find the reason why life began in other creatures and eliminate this reason. Are you ready to undertake this mission? It is a <br/>mission for the brave only.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2689490/extras/1.gif?t=1703510083"><h2 class="bb_tag">important Instructions</h2>Each level consists of two stages. Each stage consists of a group of guards who protect the road leading to the Boss <br/>You have to eliminate them all, and then you can kill the Boss. If you kill the Boss on the first try, you will get three stars. If you kill him on the second try, you will get two stars, and if you kill him on the third try, you will get only one star.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2689490/extras/2023-11-24_11-11-03.gif?t=1703510083"><br/>The map consists of more than ten worlds, more than 20 stages, and more than 20 bosses, in addition to the final battle<br/>And many, many enemies too<br/>- Soldiers who betrayed humans<br/>- Mushroom<br/>- Transformed trees<br/>- Mice<br/>- Mutant pirates<br/>- Snowmen<br/>- Snow monsters<br/>- Zombie<br/>- Squash<br/>- Pumpkin man<br/>- The Minotaur<br/>- Dogman<br/>- Little monsters<br/>- Rotary bombs<br/>- Flying bombs<br/>- Defender<br/>- Soldiers' cars<br/>- Bats<br/>- Snowballs<br/>And so much more awaits you						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mushroom Age</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2683110/Mushroom_Age/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2683110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Vera track down her lost love!<br>
<br>
Battle the forces of evil through challenging Hidden Object's search, Puzzles and time-twisting Mini-Games!<br>
Explore world history first-hand and interact with ancient sages and fearsome, prehistoric predators. Save your fiance Tom, the world, and time itself in this expansive quest game!<br>
<br>
The Mushroom Age is a classic love tale of girl finds boy, girl loses boy, girl chases boy... in a crazy adventure that spans several historic eras! Our heroine, Vera, is desperately searching for her fiance, Tom, who has disappeared a few days before their wedding. She stops by the TimeLab where Tom works to see if they don't have him working on some super top-secret project. When she doesn't believe the staff, she searches the lab for her fiance and accidentally activates a time machine.<br>
And thus she embarks on a race against time and through history to find her fiance and save the world from futuristic evil powers that want to change history and destroy the world.  <br/>
<br/>
A "classic" game that stands up well against current games: well thought out story line, fun characters &amp; challenging mini-games.<br/>
"Mushroom Age" is a gripping hidden object puzzle adventure game with an original and humorous story line, sharp bright graphics, and unimaginable characters. Solve interesting puzzles and play mesmerizing mini-games with prehistoric characters like a dinosaur and a caveman, historic personages like Socrates and Nostradamus, robots and bad guys from the future, not to mention characters not bound by the confines of time!<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Main game-features:<br/>
<br/>
- a lot of Puzzles, Hidden Object games and different mini-games with great historical figures<br/>
- Breathtaking story line with spectacular characters<br/>
- Unbelievable locations from the Jurassic period to the year 100,000,000 A.D.<br/>
- Colorful Hi-Resolution graphics						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Melt the Snowman</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2717250/Dont_Melt_the_Snowman/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							​A festive hangman type word game which is fun to play.<br>
<br>
Don't Melt the Snowman is a word game that is often played by one or more people. The game is a simple yet engaging way to test one's vocabulary and guessing skills. Here's how the game typically works:<br>
<br>
Setup: Don't Melt the Snowman will generate a word, based on a festive time of year, and keeps it a secret in its memory bank. The chosen word is usually related to a specific category, such as Christmas or other celebration.<br>
<br>
Melting the snowman: The original game traditionally involves drawing a gallows (a structure used for hangings) and an empty space for each letter of the chosen word. The number of spaces represents the number of letters in the word.  In Don't Melt the Snowman, the gallows are replaced by a Snowman figure that will slowly melt if your guess at a letter in the word is not successful.<br/>
<br/>
Guessing Letters: For each correct guess, the letter is revealed in its correct position(s) in the word, and the Snowman figure remains unchanged. For incorrect guesses, a different image of the Snowman is presented signifying a melting Snowman character.<br/>
<br/>
Limited Incorrect Guesses: As a player you will only have a limited number of incorrect guesses. If you exceed this limit before guessing the word correctly, you will lose the game and the Snowman will be completely melted - poor Snowman!<br/>
<br/>
Winning or Losing: The game continues until the word is guessed correctly, or the Snowman has melted. If the word is guessed successfully, you win that round and the choice to play again will be displayed.<br/>
<br/>
The original Hangman game, from which Don't Melt the Snowman is based upon, is a popular game for its simplicity and adaptability. It can be played with pen and paper, on a whiteboard, or through various online platforms. Additionally, it is often used as an educational tool to reinforce vocabulary and spelling skills.  Don't Melt the Snowman is an online platform with very much of a fun way of using word play!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect the Planet</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2425160/Protect_the_Planet/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2425160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a simple typing game. In the game, the alien from the UFO is very evil, he will shoot many missiles to attack the planet. You need to type and type, to destroy the missiles, to protect the planet.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zodiac Landing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2716870/Zodiac_Landing/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game consist of 12 levels, one of which is a zodiac constellation. Every constellation has several stars, you need use keyboard or gamepad controll the rocket, avoiding any obstacle, to land rocket on target platform and so light up a star. Completing all stars of a constellation will unlock its image. <br>
<br>
Operation: <br>
press F key or push left joystick to ignite left engine<br>
press J key or push right joystick to ignite right engine<br>
press Esc key or Circle/B button (on gamepad) to pause/resume<br>
press R key or Square/X button (on gamepad) to restart level						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rock 'N Racing Off Road DX</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2505940/Rock_N_Racing_Off_Road_DX/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Rock'N Racing Off Road DX offers the most entertaining and exciting races, with loads of skids, crashes and amazing jumps. You will have several modes of play, such as Cup mode, time trial and multi-player with the option of up to 4 Players at a time.<br>
<br>
Online ranking table where you can compare your best times with friends and players from around the world.<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
<br>
- Wide variety of tracks.<br>
- Multi-player with 4 players!<br/>
- Realistic physics for driving, jumps and crashes.<br/>
- Loads of Rock'N Roll music.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EndlessCar</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2371510/EndlessCar/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2371510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							EndlessCar is a casual mini-game that allows you to earn unlimited points to control cars, and the controls are simple and easy to play.<br>
<br>
The screen you see is all about the game, no upgrades, no levels, and the way you control it is A/D to dodge obstacles left and right while gaining oil drums to gain points and power-ups.<br>
<br>
The makers thoughtfully added the function of switching backgrounds for players to make it less monotonous, using the keyboard :W. This will not affect the progress of the game.<br>
<br>
If you want to take a break from a stressful game, you can also press ESC to pause the game.<br/>
<br/>
Conditions of Death:<br/>
1. The energy bar state disappears, that is, it loses power, so collect as many oil barrels as possible to keep energy.<br/>
2. Avoid crashing into obstacles!<br/>
<br/>
Points Requirements:<br/>
One point is awarded for successfully obtaining the oil drum.<br/>
<br/>
Please note: there is no upper limit to the maximum score!<br/>
<br/>
Have fun!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EndlessEx</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2371330/EndlessEx/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2371330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							EndlessEx is a jumping/flying/casual mini-game with unlimited credits that will make our boring lives even more boring!<br>
<br>
The screen you see is the whole game, with no upgrades or levels, and the way you do it is by tapping the keyboard in a continuous rhythmic manner: W.<br>
<br>
Of course, the makers also thoughtfully added the ability to switch backgrounds for players to make it less monotonous, using keyboard :D. Of course, this will not affect the progress of the game.<br>
<br>
Conditions of Death:<br/>
1. The energy bar state disappears, i.e. loses power, so collect as many batteries as possible to maintain energy.<br/>
2. Avoid hitting the exclamation mark! (very obvious hint).<br/>
<br/>
Points Requirements:<br/>
A successful crossing between exclamation points earns one point (even if you don't get an energy battery).<br/>
<br/>
Please note: there is no upper limit to the maximum score!<br/>
<br/>
Have fun!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Randy Blaster 3D</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1591960/Randy_Blaster_3D/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1591960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Randy Blaster 3D</strong> is a satirical retro-style FPS featuring Deep Twitch Integration and fully customizable gameplay configuration.<br/><br/>Featuring two game modes: Solo Survival and Twitch Survival. Battle endless waves of enemies and collect money to unlock new map regions or purchase weapons and power-ups from Dandy Randy’s Handy Pantry.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> <strong>Solo Survival</strong><br/>        — Face Randy’s dark forces alone in Solo Survival. The longer you survive, the more difficult and numerous the enemies become. Oh, and did we mention the steadily rising lava? Test your resolve and skill against Randy’s hordes and an increasingly hostile environment and see how long you can last in this classic FPS experience.<br/> </li><li> <strong>Twitch Survival</strong><br/>        — Twitch Survival mode has all the excitement of Solo Survival mode, plus extra features created specially for streamers.<br/>        — Engage your community in a new and exciting way using Deep Twitch Integration. Allow your audience to affect gameplay in real time using Twitch events such as cheering, subscribing, chat commands, and more. Chat can choose to either support or hinder the streamer by affecting the environment, deploying AI support bots, or gifting power-ups to the player or the enemies. No matter your play style, the sky’s the limit when it comes to customizing your gameplay and your audience’s control. Simply connect your Twitch account in the Randy Blaster 3D settings menu to get started.</li></ul><br/>Custom gameplay configurations<br/>    — Sandbox-style customization with dozens of options for triggers and events. You can easily export and share your favorite configurations with friends.<br/><br/>Compete in global leaderboards, unlock Steam achievements, find Easter eggs, and enjoy this fast-paced wave-based shooter as a solo hero or alongside your audience.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Lore</h2><br/>After eons of peace in the Vaporverse, the hellish entity Randy has brought chaos and death to the world, with the help of his legions of darkness. It’s up to you, our daring beefcake hero, to bring justice to his doorstep, vanquish Randy’s diabolical forces, and cancel him… for good.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Story of Randy Blaster</h2><br/>Randy Blaster 3D’s chaotic development journey began in 2021 as a silly inside joke amongst friends. My buddy Randy (aka 3D BLAST), a popular figure in the vaporwave music scene, was hosting the #3DBLASTisOverParty, a roast-style Twitch stream where viewers would submit tongue-in-cheek videos or songs to “cancel” Randy once and for all.<br/><br/>At the time I was looking to experiment further with Unreal Engine and saw Randy’s stream as the perfect opportunity for some mischief. With only two weeks until the submission deadline, I had the idea to create a parody of a first person shooter game. . I found a basic UE4 template with simple mechanics and crude sprites that were perfect for some silly photoshopping! My initial photoshops weren’t too great, so I commissioned a talented sprite artist named Atina to create custom Randy enemy designs and environment sprites that set the tone. My concept: “Canceling Randy isn’t enough. He has to die!”<br/><br/>The date of Randy’s stream ended up getting pushed back significantly. Originally, I planned only to submit a brief video capture of the gameplay, but I saw the extended timeframe as a challenge and pushed myself to make Randy Blaster 3D fully playable.<br/><br/>In this early version, the player objective was to fight through Randy’s evil minions and gather his “vinyl records of power” to unlock new areas, eventually leading to the final boss: Randy himself. The platforming grew more intense in later levels as larger swarms of enemies pursued the player. The climax was a showdown with Randy himself! Easter egg cameos from vaporwave artists added surprise and flair. There was even a speedrun timer for competition with friends.<br/><br/>On stream day, it all hit me. I had created a complete, albeit short, retro FPS in just one month! To make things even more chaotic, the stream aired while I was moving from Virginia to California, and I caught the broadcast from an Oklahoma City hotel. The trailer (parodying a vintage Doom ad courtesy of our pal Discoholic) kicked things off strong. When Randy revealed the game was available for download, chat went wild! Randy played the game on stream for hours as viewers cheered on the zany carnage. This early version of Randy Blaster 3D still lives on itch.io as “The Bootleg Version.”<br/><br/>I pondered where to take things next. I adored the mechanics and wanted to bring Randy Blaster 3D to Steam, but this brief story mode didn’t seem substantial enough for a Steam release. After contemplation, I settled on creating a wave-based survival mode to add tons of replayability.<br/><br/>What followed was an explosion of new features over months of passionate work. More enemies, expanded mechanics, cunning AI, a robust progression system, elaborate level design, and the invention of what I call Deep Twitch Integration. Each step of the way I brainstormed wild ideas to make the game as fun and innovative as possible. Eventually, Randy Blaster 3D evolved into a polished, completely customizable, and novel FPS experience.<br/><br/>I was assisted by many incredible collaborators. <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Atina, the skilled sprite artist whose visual creativity can be seen throughout the entire project.<br/></li><li>Prominent Quake mapper Kayne crafted the elaborate level design in the main castle level. <br/></li><li>I licensed renowned texture artist Makkon’s eyecatching environmental palettes. <br/></li><li>Christtt helped rework UI/UX and design concepts. His visage even made it into the game. See if you can find it! <br/></li><li>David Lamb for game testing and breaking things. <br/></li><li>Justin Higgs for assisting with website updates and validating UX. <br/></li><li>Randy himself voiced all the enemies and shopkeeper, Dandy Randy. He suggested the iconic air dash.<br/></li><li>The skilled musician Dial-up for Murder composed the perfect doom midi-inspired DJENT soundtrack. <br/></li><li>My talented girlfriend DATAGIRL handled all sound design and Wwise implementation - filling the world with character through audio.</li></ul><br/>Nearly 4 years have vanished in this development marathon. From a joke between friends to a passion project establishing my talents as an indie developer, I can only laugh looking back on all this effort creating such an unhinged game about battling my buddy Randy.<br/><br/>This journey was filled with unexpected twists and turns, but it led to creating something far more creative than I imagined. Every wild idea and late-night coding session was fueled by a desire to build an intensely fun and replayable experience alongside an awesome, collaborative team. At the end of the day, this has been a labor of love; a passion project creating something special for my friend and for the community we are a part of.<br/><br/>The work is not done, but the time has come to unleash this creation upon the world! I can't wait for friends to team up against Randy's forces and for streamers to engage their fans in new ways. My ultimate goal is to spread as many smiles as possible by fully embracing the chaos. Hopefully Randy Blaster 3D delivers a one-of-a-kind good time!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Object Legends: Deadly Love Collector's Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2690820/Hidden_Object_Legends_Deadly_Love_Collectors_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A gripping detective series filled with mystery and riddles awaits you! You, by some unfortunate chance, have managed to get on a train full of petty criminals and scoundrels. And now you're sitting there wondering who you can trust and who you can't? Solve each passenger like a piece of a puzzle. Are you ready to embark on an unforgettable journey where you will have to play the best puzzles and brainteasers of all time, search and find objects, and get incredible fun and positive emotions! Challenge your investigator skills in this spectacular new Hidden-Object Puzzle Adventure!<br>
<br>
This Collector's Edition includes:<br>
<br>
🔎	A grand story<br>
🔎	Unique content<br>
🔎	Own solutions<br/>
🔎	Diverse achievements<br/>
🔎	Intuitive gameplay<br/>
🔎	Collectibles<br/>
🔎	Over 100 riddles and puzzles<br/>
🔎	Anytime, anywhere<br/>
🔎	For old and young						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>多边星球 Multilateral Planet</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2720980/_Multilateral_Planet/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2720980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Hey! Hello, everyone! This game I tried to incorporate different aspects of the gameplay, and then carefully improve it; Its play is relatively novel, remove the brainless plot, remove the boring construction; Yes! It is to let you experience the fun of fighting strange bosses faster and better! You can kill bosses with the city's Mechs; You can also bring bosses into opposing camps and kill them; Kill the BOSS, have the probability to drop NB equipment, and then buy Mecha, dragon mount; I love the idea of the Dyson Sphere flying in space, and I love the thrill of famine and hounds! Yes! I integrate them, you can sit on the dragon to travel in space, at night you can enjoy the excitement of the night beast chase! I hate deductions for gear sold in stores, so my store is free to buy and sell gear without deductions. Especially love the plot and build don't buy it!<br/><br/>This is a single-player game on a multi-sided planet where humans have built tall walls to survive the attacks of mutants,<br/>This is the last city of mankind; The game requires the player to control a character to pick up a sword and shield to kill these mutants and get them to drop<br/>Food and weapons, to arm themselves; Level up with experience gained through kills to gain powerful attack and defense bonuses.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Gameplay introduction</strong></h2><br/>1. Players can freely exchange food and weapons into gold through the store, and then use the gold to buy more powerful swords and shields, and follow the battle Mech warrior, can accelerate the flying dragon mount, the dragon can fly to other planets; Shop items are bought and sold equally.<br/><br/>2. The planet has 4 camps, human, beast, demon, plant, they are opposed to each other, the player belongs to the human camp; Players in the early days<br/>Limited power, you can use the opposing camp to kill the mutants by luring them to the opposing camp; There's something special about the plant camp. They<br/>The other camp will attack them only if they attack the other camp first.<br/><br/>3. Can spin silk control spider, it seems that you can always control the player to death, but as long as you carefully avoid the spin silk, come to its body, it will<br/>Switch melee attack; The raging Gigantopithecus has attack slowdowns like every big mutant, and maybe tumbling and galloping can carry it around!<br/>If there are no opposing sides of the beasts in sight, the raptors better not disturb them, because their speed will cause you to roll over!<br/><br/>4. Both humans and mutants on the planet have an upgrade system that distributes experience equally to the last individual (up to 5) to attack after their death.<br/>Therefore, in most melee, the player needs to capture one of the last five players to attack in order to gain experience points. <br/><br/>5. Players and mutants upgrade levels in the basic health, attack, defense will be increased, rise 1 level plus 10%, rise 10 levels<br/>Add 100%, 100 level is equal to 10 times on the original basis. The player is equipped with swords and shields by eating food with a life cap<br/>The base value is increased, and there is also a level bonus.<br/><br/>6. The buildings, mountains and lakes in the planet are just scenery, which can be worn, and some powerful weapons are put into some buildings and mountains accordingly Waiting for the player to discover, get them players will be faster to get more powerful weapons, follow the combat Mech fighters, flying mount dragon.<br/><br/>7. The multi-planet world will have 15 minutes of the real world day and 5 minutes of the night, and the city's buildings, street lights, and vehicle lights will be lit at night, if you Already have a dragon mount, flying over the city to see these scenery, will have a different flavor!<br/><br/>8. Night comes, there will be a night beast refresh next to you, they only attack the player and the human camp, if they do not find the target,<br/>It will run towards the player no matter how far away, and fast; Even if you already have a dragon, as long as you're still within the gravitational sphere of the planet,They'll be forced to land, banned from the skies; So be strong to survive.<h2 class="bb_tag">Comments and feedback</h2>Email address: <a href="mailto:yueleilei.st@qq.com">yueleilei.st@qq.com</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merry XMerge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2717080/Merry_XMerge/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Merry XMerge </strong> is a good board game for <strong>all ages</strong> this Christmas. Put together Christmas cakes and candies to make them more attractive. The better your strategy, the higher your score will be. Join and play with your friends to see who is the winner and enjoy a fun moment together. <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717080/extras/ezgif.com-resize__2_.gif?t=1703491945"> Merry Christmas.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>:::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::: - <u>GAME FEATURES</u> - ::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>2d Startegy Board Game</strong><br/>You can rotate objects by clicking on them and dragging them onto the board.<br/></li><li> <strong>Support Tools</strong><br/>There are two boosters at the right corner to correct your mistakes - use diamonds to buy them.<br/></li><li> <strong>Seven Levels Of Cake and Candy</strong><br/>Match 3-5 pieces of your cakes and candies to increase into new forms and get 6 diamonds at the highest level. <br/></li><li> <strong>Themes</strong><br/>There are two themes added. You can optionally choose the Bear Cake Chef or Christmas Candy theme in the store.<br/><i>Please write a review to let us know which themes you'd like to see added in the future.</i><br/></li><li> <strong>Upcoming Feature</strong><br/>You can pick the song you like from the list to increase your enjoyment when combining cakes and candies.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717080/extras/ezgif.com-resize__1_.gif?t=1703491945"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuro Hacker : Intrusion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2644540/Neuro_Hacker__Intrusion/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2644540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2644540/extras/超脑侦探_主宣传图.jpg?t=1703487894"><h2 class="bb_tag">-Introduction-</h2>Brain Hackers is a deduction and puzzle VR game. You take on the role of a “brain hacker” detective who is skilled at hacking into the human brain to solve complex crimes. You are about to hack into an airship crash survivor's brain and probe into his memories in order to uncover the horrible truth behind the incident.<h2 class="bb_tag">-About this game-</h2>–– Hello, detective. I'm your assistant Kate.<br/>To solve the case, we need you to hack into the brain of an airship crash survivor, and we will help you recreate his memories from one hour before the crash. You will act as the survivor himself, wandering through his memories. Within this hour, you must use all of your detective skills and think of every possible way to access every corner of his memories. You may listen in on discussions you believe are important, look for clues, and search for information related to suspicious persons in order to uncover the truth in a timely manner.<br/>Attention! Once the owner of the brain becomes aware of your presence, he will not only place numerous traps in his mind to stop you, but he will also create horrible illusions that trap you, and launch mind attacks to force you out of his head. It's rare for a beginner like you to last more than 10 minutes. If you feel you can't keep on, don't be a hero and notify me right away; I will cut the connection at any time and pull your consciousness out of his brain...This is entirely for your safety.<br/>Solving this case is both a commission from the Club and a rigorous test. The Club will award you with different levels of detective badges based on your performance. The highest honor is the exceedingly rare Star Detective badge, which can serve as your qualification to join the club. But, according to my research, no beginner detective has ever received this badge; will you be the lucky one?<br/>If you accept the challenge, please sign the commission agreement, and your mission will begin.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2644540/extras/hairu.jpg?t=1703487894"><h2 class="bb_tag">-How to play-</h2>Enjoying a feast of deduction in a crisis-ridden mind space<br/><br/>- An immersive crime investigation experience: We offer you a 360-degree immersive experience in an open crime scene, with dead bodies right at your feet! You may search for evidence at your will, perform hands-on autopsies, and make deductions according to the clues. You are not just playing a game; you are witnessing a bizarre murder that is part of a century-long conspiracy.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2644540/extras/shiti.jpg?t=1703487894"><br/><br/>- Hacking into the memory maze: You are trapped in the victim's brain. Each fragment of his memories represents a separate chamber full of secrets. You must be a detective as well as an escape master, as getting out of the maze is also the only way to discover the truth about the crimes.<br/><br/>- Dual cases and dual identities: You will solve the puzzles while getting to know the whole picture of the story. The clues not only lie in the physical evidence, but also in your interactions with NPCs. Pay attention to every word they say to you. Who is lying?!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2644540/extras/zhaopianqiang.jpg?t=1703487894"><br/><br/>- Submitting case reports: Submitting case reports to the Club is a difficult task that many investigators have failed at. It's now your chance to face the challenge! At each stage, you shall organize clues for the case and give your own reasoning. Are you a novice or a seasoned detective? Your performance will determine which detective badge you receive!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2644540/extras/zhiwen.jpg?t=1703487894"><h2 class="bb_tag">-Game features-</h2>- Cinematic audio-visual enjoyment<br/>You can have immersive audio-visual enjoyment, as the game contains movie-quality dubbing and performance, as well as a mysterious and unpredictable atmosphere, with monsters coming right at you. You will be like a main character in a movie!<br/>- An exclusive suspenseful puzzle-solving experience<br/>The puzzle solving process is enjoyable and interactive: extracting fingerprints from corpses, decoding gesture codes, dripping blood to unlock seals, learning about secret techniques of the Eight Diagrams, finding clues in ancient paintings...You will not want to stop the game!<br/>- A mind-bending story with several plot twists<br/>The case is bizarre and what happened in the past is a mystery. Each suspect has a secret, and the plot is full of surprises. While investigating the case, you are also drawn into a carefully planned conspiracy...<br/>- High-caliber producer<br/>The game’s producer is also the director of a spin-off of China's most popular detective variety show, delivering you a suspenseful, thrilling VR investigation experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">-Adult content description-</h2>The content in this game may not be suitable for all age groups or for access during work hours: frequent violence or bloodshed, common adult content.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frozen Friday Night: The Eve</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1870180/Frozen_Friday_Night_The_Eve/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1870180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Game with Limited Planned Content</strong><br/>Dear survivors,<br/><br/>Hi, this is FFN team. We were eager to release this scary game on Christmas Eve, so we went ahead with it, even though we haven't fully created this world just yet. We plan to continually add new content in the coming months, and it will likely look even better in three months. If you were considering giving FFN Eve a thumbs down due to the limited content, we sincerely appreciate your patience and understanding.<br/><br/>Thanks for your great interest. Merry Christmas and Happy New Year.<br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><strong>Synopsis</strong><br/>On a Friday night, deep in the Christmas season, Setsuka throws a festive party and invites her friends to join in the merriment. As the night progresses, and the drinks flow, an unexpected blackout shrouds the gathering in darkness. That's when Rose and Pandu discover their friends have vanished, and they go on a search to find them.<br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/>🪓 Players can play Rose as survivor.<br/>🪓 The Santa Mask Suit, lurks in the shadows, ready to chase and murder the young.<br/>🪓 Rose may find useful weapons to defend herself against the relentless slasher.<br/>🪓 Beware of the deadly splitting axe, its menacing swings can be your doom. Your only chance: Kill the devil before it kills you.<br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><strong>Warning</strong><br/>This horror game contains extremely brutal and violent content, including blood, murder, and dismemberment elements. Streamers should set their live streaming settings to allow only adults to watch while you're playing this game. The infirm, pregnant women, and children must not play this game. Additionally, this videogame may cause people with photosensitive epilepsy to convulse in seizures. Player discretion is advised.<br/><br/>The content of this videogame is purely fictional, is not intended to represent or depict any actual event, person, or entity, and any such similarities are purely coincidental. The makers and publishers of this game do not in any way endorse, condone or encourage engaging in any conduct depicted in this videogame.<br/><br/>All characters in this videogame do not represent any country, race, organization, gender, generation, and so on. Each of them is a unique individual.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowbreak: Containment Zone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668080/Snowbreak_Containment_Zone/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Snowbreak: Containment Zone is a 3D sci-fi RPG-shooter powered by the Unreal Engine 4 that offers a next-gen, cross-platform gaming experience, sharing your progress across all of your devices. <br/><br/>The Descent of the Titans turned a once-vibrant city into the devastated wasteland of Containment Zone Aleph. As the Adjutant of Heimdall Force, bravely undertake missions alongside Manifestations with the powers of gods and unique personalities, seeking to bring this bitter winter to an end...<br/><br/>[Enjoy Hybrid Combat]<br/>Snowbreak's weaponry injects realism into a sci-fi setting, with designs closely simulating future firearms technology. This combines with the otherworldly, RPG-like skill mechanic to create a refreshing combat experience.<br/><br/>[Take on Titans]<br/>The Descent of the Titans completely changed the world, and the battlefield. Feel the thrill of battling giants in this dystopian future!<br/><br/>[Befriend Operatives]<br/>Spend time with your Heimdall Force companions in the Base system. Decorate, chat, and give gifts to grow closer!<br/><br/>[Play Co-Op in Gigalink] <br/>Tired of exploring alone? Join up with friends and fight enemies together!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project N.E.X.T</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2693820/Project_NEXT/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2693820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to "Project N.E.X.T,"<br>
<br>
In this world, players engage in intense team battles, with the Red Team and Blue Team clashing in ever-changing settings. From quaint fictional villages to the mysterious city of Bazaar, the vibrant Dragon City, and the typical hustle and bustle of a train station, players strive for ultimate victory in environments that constantly shift in both time and space.<br>
<br>
This game offers not just traditional team deathmatch modes but also introduces innovative gameplay modes like capturing and surviving, where strategy and skill are paramount. Adding to the excitement, some modes feature zombies, bringing unexpected challenges to the battles.<br>
<br>
Good luck, as victory will only favor the bravest and smartest.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Knowledge of Hermit</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2641090/The_Knowledge_of_Hermit/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2641090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Knowledge is Power.  Break the rules of the puzzles and collect knowledge EXP in this Non-Linear Top-down exploration action-adventure-puzzle game with Power Ups Abilities &amp; Health Upgrades.<br>
-<br>
Non-linear exploration action real-time puzzle game where all of the puzzles are non-linear, solvable in various ways imagined &amp; decided by the player. <br>
A videogame where the rules of the can be broken using the Hermits various unique unlockable abilities. <br>
-<br>
100 Puzzles and Multiple Areas.<br>
-<br>
Solve non-linear puzzles while purging parasitic infestations in the Hermit's quest for knowledge.<br/>
The Knowledge of Hermit is a top-down classic 1980s inspired hybrid action-adventure-puzzle game.<br/>
-<br/>
Solve over 100 Block-Pushing Puzzles while exterminating deadly threats<br/>
Puzzles are non-linear and can be solved in various ways<br/>
10+ Unique Areas<br/>
Each area consists of specific puzzle mechanics tailored to that area<br/>
Collectable Abilities that alter gameplay in different ways <br/>
Collectable Health Upgrades <br/>
Non-Linear Path Selection and Exploration<br/>
Infestation Survival Area that focuses on threat extermination and survival time with Steam integrated leaderboards<br/>
<br/>
Pause Menu that also serves as a puzzle reset function<br/>
<br/>
3 Save Files that require manual saving from the in game pause menu *though this game does autosave on specific occasions<br/>
<br/>
60 Achievements to Collect						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VR Dinosaur Island Paradise</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2539890/VR_Dinosaur_Island_Paradise/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2539890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is an immersive VR casual game. Players will experience the fun of driving cars freely in the virgin forest. In the game, you will be in a vibrant dinosaur paradise and enjoy the beauty of nature.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2539890/extras/1.jpg?t=1703472271"> <br/> <br/>As a player, you will drive a car in this mysterious and vast forest. Along the way, you will encounter a variety of animals, from the mighty rhinos to dexterous goats, and even cute polar bears. Their existence and activities will bring vitality and vitality to the entire forest. When you drive leisurely, the animals may be curious about you, or you may also make a charming cry, as if saying hello to you. In addition to some common animals, you can also find some dinosaurs hidden in the forest. They have ruled this land and left a rich footprint.<br/>The forest itself is also a beautiful scroll, full of amazing natural landscapes. You can stop to enjoy the magnificence of the forest and enjoy the gifts of nature.<br/>This game's realistic visual effects and stereo sound effects will bring you an immersive experience, as if in a real forest. Whether it is driving, watching animals, or immersing in the beauty of nature, this game will bring you a pleasant, relaxing and exploring experience. Come and start your forest adventure!<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2539890/extras/2.jpg?t=1703472271"><br/><br/>Operation method:<br/>Throttle    Right-handle trigger<br/>Steer       Left-handle left/right<br/>Menu      Left-handle trigger						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pond Scum: A Gothic Swamp Tale</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2617030/Pond_Scum_A_Gothic_Swamp_Tale/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							At the edge of the Deep Swamp stands Snappy and his gang. <br/>Anxious to proceed, they press on as a rite of passage for all young pond dwellers.<br/>What will they find ahead? <br/>Uncover the secrets of the swamp in this Diorama-based VR Platformer.  <br/><br/>🐊<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617030/extras/Movie_034.gif?t=1703460948">🐊<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Jump, die and journey across 5 unique worlds packed with 30+ levels<br/></li><li>Solve puzzles while dodging the twisted creatures of the Deep Swamp<br/></li><li>Collect all the Golden Fangs!<br/></li><li>Enjoy our original music fresh from the Garden<br/></li><li>Delve into the dark, introspective tale of Snappy<br/></li><li>Meet new friends and eat old ones<br/></li><li>Call your mother!!!<br/></li><li>Lose yourself in the marsh</li></ul> <br/>🐊<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2617030/extras/GamePlay_1.gif?t=1703460948">🐊<br/><br/>Wishlist <strong>Pond Scum: A Gothic Swamp Tale</strong> today!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abhorrent Light</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2266700/Abhorrent_Light/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2266700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Abhorrent Light is a dark medieval, non-linear hack and slash with dynamic scaling and loot. You are a bounty hunter, hired to protect the village from certain destruction. With an arsenal of weapons and items at your disposal, you must discover the source of the monsters that plague the village and defeat them before it's too late. Explore the lush environments and mysterious locations within the village and seek out more tools to help you face your enemies. Take on fearsome foes in epic battles and uncover the secrets of this once peaceful village. Designed with co-op in mind, play solo or with friends as you seek those that abhor the light.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Emphasis on melee combat - block, dodge, parry and slash your way through the world<br/></li><li>Non-linear persistent world, dynamic enemy placement and randomized loot system enhances replay value. Approach the 3 main bosses and their respective locations in any order, it's up to you to discover advantages and disadvantages<br/></li><li>Earn gold to buy new weapons or upgrade your current ones by defeating monsters and selling weapons<br/></li><li>Play with friends for an even more intense experience</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">A torch is essential as you descend to darkness, there are many sconces to light the environment, you may even find other tools</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2266700/extras/torches_crop.gif?t=1703460709"><h2 class="bb_tag">Find or purchase the weapon with the best stats. Slower weapons generally deal more damage per attack. Sometimes a weapon is better being sold.</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2266700/extras/weapondemo.jpg?t=1703460709"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowbots and Aliens</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/517670/Cowbots_and_Aliens/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/517670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Zany interactions, fast-paced combat and challenging AI!</h2><br/><i>Drop into a colorful western “Saloon-iverse” with competitive combat and gameplay!</i><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/517670/extras/CaA_01.gif?t=1703459000"><br/><br/>Cowbots and Aliens delivers unparalleled fun with fast-paced competitive matches! <br/><br/><strong>Party up for Team Deathmatch modes, or throw down in Free-For-All chaos!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/517670/extras/CaA_02.gif?t=1703459000"><br/><br/>Unlock hilarious cosmetic accessories, juggle a variety of cool sci-western weapons, or grab mundane items like barstools and bottles to smash against opponents!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/517670/extras/CaA_03.gif?t=1703459000"><br/><br/>Compete against other players online in Free-For-All arenas, or party up for a variety of Team Deathmatch modes! Sophisticated AI offers challenging competition!<br/><br/><strong><i>Are you ready for the zanniest, cartoon brawl?!</i></strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/517670/extras/CaA_04.gif?t=1703459000"><br/><br/>Cowbots and Aliens is a furious PvP Multiplayer VR brawl set in the Saloon-iverse! Free movement, laser precise gunplay, multiple competitive modes and a custom networked physics system that lets you use EVERYTHING as a weapon makes for an immensely satisfying VR ruckus! <br/><br/>Flip a table and take cover, break a chair over your friends head, hurl a tomahawk, jump out with six-shooters blazing or just practice shooting beer bottles out of the sky. Cowbots and Aliens is a wild west brawl scene brought to life by robots, aliens, the magic of VR and you!<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle Online - Fight your friends in a variety of competitive multiplayer modes including Free For All, No Guns, Team Deathmatch and Gold Rush!<br/></li><li>Single Player Bots - Battle against or along-side clever AI bots so you're never alone!<br/></li><li>Interact with Everything - Grab whatever you can get your hands on, and use it in battle! (Pro Tip - a throwing knife deals more damage than a poker chip;)<br/></li><li>Hang Out - Hit the saloon to have a virtual drink with a fellow Cowbot, make art out of a stack of chairs or join a battle. No consequences in this social area.<br/></li><li>Customize your Avatar - Unlock cool gear to outfit your Cowbot or Alien with hats, shirts, vests or facial hair!<br/></li><li>Master Creative Weapons - The Cowbots and Aliens have retrofitted the iconic weapons of the old west for use in their ongoing feud. From guns to tomahawks to broken bottles - the Cowbots and Aliens have em all.<br/></li><li>Wreck the Place! - Don’t hesitate to make a mess - this is the Wild West, after all.</li></ul><br/><strong>Get ready for wild sci-western, shooter action that you can play alone or with your friends online!</strong><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspringboardvr.com%3Fgame_verification%3Daecc3aa0-c736-11e7-a8aa-33bf32303e37" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> Available for Arcades on SpringboardVR </a> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warlords Battlecry: The Protectors of Etheria</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420170/Warlords_Battlecry_The_Protectors_of_Etheria/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Warlords Battlecry: The Protectors of Etheria (or TPE), is a mod for Warlords Battlecry 3 and sequel to the Warlords franchise. TPE is an ambitious project which focuses on a new interactive RPG experience and a streamlined &amp; modernized RTS experience. It is stand-alone, meaning that it can be run without having the original game installed.<br>
<br>
Currently, TPE is in development (and has been since 2010), and has not reached a stable version. However, there are beta versions available for download. All users are considered beta testers and are encouraged to report bugs and make suggestions:<br>
- On the TPE forum<br>
- On the TPE Discord channel<br>
Multiplayer games are also run on the Discord channel.<br>
<br/>
Among various other features, TPE attempts to achieve the following:<br/>
- Provide new RTS and RPG elements which deliver greater strategic and role-playing depth, including greater terrain influences on battles, unit types, dialogue choices, multiple endings and psychological profiles<br/>
- Improve old, poorly designed systems or mechanics, including the resource, combat stat, damage type/armor, hero, retinue, conversion and terrain systems<br/>
- Integrate all official Warlords lore into the game, including lore from: Warlords, Warlords 2, Warlords 3 &amp; its expansion, Warlords Battlecry, Warlords Battlecry 3, Puzzle Quest &amp; its expansions, Puzzle Quest 2, Puzzle Quest 3 and unofficial TPE lore to help fill any gaps (which is based on and respects Warlords lore)<br/>
- Provide new content, including music, maps, productions, heroes, items and a new story-driven, multi-choice campaign with diplomacy, new locations, quests, characters, and videos, which also changes based on hero traits and any of their prior actions or choices<br/>
- Provide the campaigns of the previous Warlords Battlecry games, including the Tears of Dawn WBC1 campaign, the Conquest WBC2 campaign and The Fifth Horseman WBC3 campaign, all updated with TPE’s gameplay<br/>
- Improve pre-existing content, providing new graphics, audio, features and functionality<br/>
- Provide up to 16 player gameplay which can be reliably played in multiplayer<br/>
- High resolution support for up to 4K<br/>
- Improve the editor, increasing the amount of control that map-maker’s have over their designs<br/>
- Fix every single one of the series’ bugs, from the most notorious to the most insubstantial, thereby providing the most reliable and bug-free experience in Warlords Battlecry history<br/>
- In general, bring the game up to modern standards and fulfill the potential of Warlords Battlecry, a founder of the role-playing real time strategy genre						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle Of Zodiacs - Card Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2325880/Battle_Of_Zodiacs__Card_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2325880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Fully competitive 1v1 game, where the goal is to dominate your enemy's land!<br/>To fulfill their objective, each player will assemble a team with 3 heroes and a deck composed of items and spells.<br/><br/>Get ready to enter an epic battle that unites the zodiac signs with the medieval fantasy world! This competitive battle card game is the perfect game for fantasy and superstar fans.<br/><br/>Embark on a journey to become the great champion of this magical world, using the strength of the zodiac signs to defeat your enemies. Each hero represents a zodiac sign and comes with special abilities you can use to overcome your opponents.<br/>But be careful, your opponents also have their own powerful abilities! Be cunning and strategic to defeat them and become the big winner.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2325880/extras/boz_ecra_hud_baixa5.jpg?t=1703441583"><br/><br/>With a mix of fantasy and astrological elements, this game looks amazing. The card illustrations are stunning, depicting the zodiac signs as mighty medieval warriors, with legendary armor and weapons.<br/><br/>Waste no more time and join this epic adventure. Now join BoZ - Battle of Zodiacs, a competitive battle card game and get ready to fight for dominance in this fantastic world, using the power of the zodiac signs!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2325880/extras/torre.gif?t=1703441583"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Deck Building</strong></h2>Players must consider the synergy between cards to build a deck that maximizes each sign's abilities and creates powerful combos. It is also important to take into account the strength and weakness of each sign in relation to the others, to balance the deck and make it more effective.<br/><br/>Additionally, the game has a pre-battle planning phase where players can choose which cards to use each round. This allows them to adjust their strategy to deal with the opponent's strategy and create a successful plan of attack.<br/><br/>In summary, the strategic charge of building the deck in this game is crucial to success. Players must have the skill and critical thinking to choose the right cards, create a solid strategy and maximize their chances of winning the epic battles.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2325880/extras/boz_ecra_hud_baixa4.jpg?t=1703441583"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>NOT a "Pay to Win" game</strong></h2>We do not offer exclusive perks or benefits to players who invest money in the game.<br/>All players have an equal opportunity to progress and win, regardless of how much money they spend.<br/>Players will only be able to buy skins for their heroes, towers and card backs.<br/>All players will have access to all cards in the game from their first access. And they will be able to get 1 extra copy of the cards when advancing in the game levels, that is, <strong>the victory factor is in the player's skill and not in how much he invested in the game.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2325880/extras/boz_ecra_hud_baixa3.jpg?t=1703441583"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>The Heroes of Zodaics</strong></h2>In BoZ, choosing a team of heroes is crucial for success in battles. Each hero represents a zodiac sign with unique abilities and attributes that can be used to create a powerful and balanced team of heroes.<br/>The choice of heroes must take into account their abilities, synergy and the player's playstyle. Some heroes may be more attack-oriented, while others may be more defensive or strategic. Furthermore, it is important to choose heroes that can work well together to create powerful combos and synergies that can give the player an advantage during battle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2325880/extras/frixo.gif?t=1703441583"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>The game for you</strong></h2>Battle Of Zodiacs is an exciting and strategic game worth playing. With an attractive game system, strategic challenge, competitiveness and great replay value, this game is an excellent choice for players looking for a unique and exciting gaming experience.<br/>What will your team of heroes be? What will your deck look like? Which towers will you have on your battlefield?<br/><strong> Who will you be in Battle Of Zodiacs?</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Hockey VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2504390/Air_Hockey_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2504390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Obsessed with creating the best Air Hockey VR simulator in the world🥽.<br>
Play against other players online or practice against AI.<br>
The physics is designed to be as real as ever achived in any other Air Hockey simulators,you won't even notice that you are in VR.<br>
<br>
We hope that you will enjoy playing Air Hockey as much as we enjoyed working on it.If you run into any issues or if you are interested in joining our community follow the link in the addictional details section and follow on our socials!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XMas Toy Merge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2725500/XMas_Toy_Merge/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Match two Christmas ingredients of the same type to get the next one. Each time you get a match you earn points - get the highest score possible and match as many gifts as you can!<br>
<br>
*NEW* Try the challenge mode!						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Death Dungeon Darkness</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2304190/Deep_Death_Dungeon_Darkness/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2304190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"To save the one you love, rise again and again. Your unyielding spirit becomes your strongest weapon."<br>
<br>
An Arabian Nights and Ancient Egyptian civilization-themed Soulslike &amp; Roguelite Action game.<br>
<br>
Story:<br>
"In ancient times, a sun-powered priestess brought hope to the people. However, Anubis, the god of the underworld, coveting her radiant power, kidnapped her and imprisoned her in his fortress, the 'Labyrinth of Death.' His aim was to sacrifice the sun priestess to seize the power of the sun god.<br>
<br/>
You, as an assassin sworn to protect the sun priestess, embark on a quest to rescue her from Anubis's stronghold, the 'Labyrinth of Death.' The labyrinth presents various challenges and formidable foes that may defeat you.<br/>
<br/>
However, you possess a unique power—the ability to rewind time with the 'Hourglass of Time.' Even if you fail, you can return to the past and repeatedly face new challenges.<br/>
<br/>
The true enemy in this game is 'giving up.' No matter how many times you fall or fail to defeat your enemies, as long as you don't give up, new challenges await. The true game over only comes when you stop trying. With a burning resolve and belief in your own strength, save the sun priestess and find true love.<br/>
<br/>
Key Features:<br/>
<br/>
Soulslike combat system with robust magic and weapons.<br/>
Random placement of enemies, items, traps, and shops with each attempt.<br/>
Permanent death requiring you to start over upon defeat.<br/>
Dynamic combat utilizing rope actions.<br/>
Strengthen your status, purchase weapons, and items using Spirits gained from defeating enemies.<br/>
Eight levels of dungeons.<br/>
Boss rush mode included.<br/>
*Note: The game does not have a save feature for progress. The deeper you go, the greater the pain of defeat. However, those who have not experienced setbacks are those who never dared to challenge.<br/>
<br/>
As you delve deeper, the tension and suspense increase. Overcome your fear and reach true love.<br/>
<br/>
What's important in life is not to avoid failure but to rise from it, to never give up. Your relentless spirit will become your greatest weapon in overcoming any difficulty.<br/>
<br/>
Embark on a journey beyond the realm of the unreasonable."						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die For Light</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713130/Die_For_Light/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Trap yourself in a cycle that repeats itself, with countless mistakes pointing out false ways out.<br/>This  is a game about repetition and never ending failure.<br/>Firm faith, avoid distractions, return to the starting point, face the unknown road ahead, failure is inevitable, but "memory" will record this failure for you, help you to cross it next time, until "right".<br/>Before entering the level, you will first pass through a moving distraction section that tests your beliefs.<br/>In the level, you will face completely dark unknown roads and traps, only to try the risk, failure is inevitable.<br/>But you travel back in time and do it all over again, and this time, the path emerges in your "memory" and you will gracefully cross the trap.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713130/extras/化光而逝_0FqeevCwWy.gif?t=1703419491"><br/><br/><span class="bb_spoiler">You can open help options in the Settings.</span><br/><br/>The game is developed by individuals, the audio is found on the Internet, and the sprite is drawn by a coder.<br/><span class="bb_spoiler"> Dirty Tricks: One of the main inspirations for the game was one Magica. </span><br/>Part of the inspiration for the game was Shadow Mist						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orcs in the Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713910/Orcs_in_the_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Orcs in the Forest is an exciting 2D platformer where a cute bunny goes on an exciting adventure in a wonderful forest. Your main goal is to collect as many carrots as possible, and many obstacles and enemies await you along the way. The forest is filled with orcs, bees and thorns, and each of them poses its own danger. Orcs are the hare's enemies and should be avoided by jumping over platforms. The bees buzz nervously and may attack the hare if it gets too close.<br>
<br>
The game is a 2D platformer where you need to collect carrots at locations and move through the levels avoiding enemies.<br>
<br>
Collect carrots, avoid enemies and overcome all obstacles in this exciting platformer Orcs in the Forest!<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br/>
- Pixel graphics<br/>
- Various enemies<br/>
- Good soundtrack						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FADE^2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2725240/FADE2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							　Everything became ashen,<br>
　and a long lingering wish awakens.<br>
<br>
　Deep in the cemetry, bleached within vast snow blindness,<br>
　another wish, yet blue, is withering out.<br>
<br>
　… desperate for the reanimated one.<br>
<br/>
　How fated would they be?<br/>
　Shall they be allowed to be redeemed?<br/>
<br/>
　May the melody FADE to guide the way...<br/>
<br/>
* * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * <br/>
<br/>
<br/>
FADE^2 is a 2D action game that brings platformer, runner and music interactive genre all together.<br/>
A desperate journey of the reanimated one, and the storytelling of music from the world.<br/>
<br/>
Menu control : Mouse<br/>
Game control : F (jump) / J (ground)<br/>
<br/>
Single Gem : short input,<br/>
Long Gem : long input, hold until the line ends.<br/>
<br/>
Special Flower : collide to be harvested.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream Team Basketball</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2152630/Dream_Team_Basketball/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2152630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Innovative Gameplay</strong><br/>A unique take on CCG games that combines 5vs5 team battles and basketball lore. The result is a short strategically and tactically intensive match that leaves you wanting for more. While your average team battle game needs you to do damage, manage mana and health bars, Dream Team Basketball revolves around scoring points, passing, movement and management of players.<br/><br/>The game has no critical strike chance, but it has 3point shooting that will make your shots score more, there is no armor or evasion but there is stealing and blocking as defense layers. The game embraces well know tactical game systems and brings them to a sports environment format.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2152630/extras/1lineup.jpg?t=1703410527"><br/><br/><strong>Lore Driven Design</strong><br/>Play with over 360 basketball and NBA inspired cards, that allow a multitude of gameplay styles and enable crazy combos. With over 450 players, each with an unique combination for their 3 skills, up to 4 passives and other various traits, the game offers infinite possibilities for the deck building side of the game. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2152630/extras/1pp2.jpg?t=1703410527"><br/><br/><strong>Competitive Environment</strong><br/>Our intention is to develop a competitive scene around the game and have embraced a "easy to learn, hard to master" design philosophy. The starting 5 players will have an important role for the outcome of the game, while the 7 bench players will give players a multitude of option to interact with various strategies when needed. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2152630/extras/1pack.jpg?t=1703410527"><br/><br/>Dream Team Basketball is still in development. The current design is evolving every day and we’re hoping to take it to the next level with the help of our community. We plan to add a plethora of new game systems while also improving the polish for the game.<br/>​						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great Filter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2066600/Great_Filter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2066600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A 2D top-down view, strategy game, with original mechanics. The game consists of 46 levels. Each level takes approximately 30-60 seconds to clear,  but maybe 10 minutes to think or 10 times to try.<br>
You would operate two characters to collect diamonds from mines, one character moves quickly and works slowly, and the other character moves slowly and works quickly. Although each character has different moving control keys, only one character can be moved at one time.<br>
When get diamonds from mining, characters could fetch diamonds of different colors into “little universe” to generate bricks of corresponding color to pave the way to the key.<br>
Each level has strict time limit, and you need to obtain the key within the time limit.<br>
The game describes my understanding of how intelligent species encounter or avoid Great Filter. Extinction or survival.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buns: Bunny Survivor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684450/Buns_Bunny_Survivor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help the magical bunny girl to survive for 10 minutes against hordes of evil. Collect gems to get new skills, find bunnies to heal, carrots to recharge. <br>
<br>
This is tiny roguelike bullet heaven with a bunny girl made for Pico-8 fantasy console.<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
- incredibly crisp 128x128 resoltuion<br>
- an explosion of color with a massive palette of 16 whole colors!<br/>
- super hard game, can be beaten in 10 minutes but it will be impossible, some players played it for 100+ hours!<br/>
- don't need mouse to play<br/>
- cute bunny<br/>
- CARROTS						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visit From Above</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2709810/Visit_From_Above/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Visit From Above is a sit-and-survive horror game (inspired by Five Nights at Freddy's) that puts you face to face with aliens. You will have to survive 3 nights using different methods to defeat the aliens including a flashlight, turning power on/off, and closing your eyes (pretend to sleep).<br>
<br>
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------<br>
<br>
In the quiet town of Crestwood, something sinister lurked beyond the starlit sky. The Stevenson family, comprised of John, a high-ranking military officer, his wife Lisa, a scientist, and their teenage daughter, Mia, lived a seemingly ordinary life in their suburban home.<br>
<br>
One fateful night, as the family settled in for dinner, an unnatural darkness enveloped the neighborhood. The power grid failed, plunging the Stevenson household into an inky blackness. As the family groped for flashlights, a blinding flash illuminated the sky. Unbeknownst to the unsuspecting Earthlings, an alien race with nefarious intentions had set their sights on Crestwood.<br/>
<br/>
From the shadows emerged extraterrestrial beings capable of mimicking any form they encountered. These shape-shifters, driven by a malevolent agenda, had been observing humanity and plotting their infiltration for years. The power outage provided the perfect cover for their invasion.<br/>
<br/>
Silently, the alien doppelgangers assumed the appearance of the Stevenson family, mimicking every detail down to the last freckle. With their disguises in place, they infiltrated the Stevenson home, lurking in the corners like predatory phantoms.<br/>
<br/>
The real Stevenson family, armed with flashlights, cautiously navigated their darkened house. Unease hung in the air as they felt an unnatural chill. Unknown to them, their doppelgangers now sat at the dinner table, their eyes glinting with an otherworldly malevolence.<br/>
<br/>
As the power outage persisted, tensions within the household escalated. The alien clones, adept at replicating human behavior, exploited the confusion and paranoia that gripped the real Stevenson family. Whispers in the dark and eerie laughter echoed through the halls, sowing discord among the unsuspecting inhabitants.<br/>
<br/>
The turning point came when John, suspicious of his surroundings, stumbled upon the imposter version of himself. A chilling confrontation unfolded, revealing the true horror that had invaded their home. The alien doppelgangers, no longer able to maintain their facade, shed their human forms, exposing grotesque, otherworldly features.<br/>
<br/>
A desperate struggle ensued as the real Stevenson family fought to protect their home and each other. The alien invaders, relentless and ruthless, revealed their plan to conquer Earth and subjugate its inhabitants. The once peaceful Crestwood became a battleground, with the fate of humanity hanging in the balance.<br/>
<br/>
In Visit From Above, you are put in the shoes of John Stevenson, after the rest of his family has already been overtaken by their alien clones. Your job will be to keep the aliens at bay until the government broadcasts a special audio frequency harmful only to the extraterrestrials. But be warned, nothing is as it seems...						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grapple Tournament</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1384320/Grapple_Tournament/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1384320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Grapple. Shoot. Score. Master the vertical combat.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>VIRTUAL REALITY ARCADE SHOOTER</strong></h2>Built from the ground up for virtual reality, Grapple Tournament is a thrilling VR arcade shooter where you can enjoy movement freedom using your 3D maneuver abilities and your grappling hook while fighting with a wide variety of multifunctional weapons (even dual wielding) in various multiplayer game modes and co-op challenges through an alluring stylized world.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1384320/extras/gtvr_hydro_grapple_flak_grenade.gif?t=1703350710"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>3D MOVEMENT FREEDOM</strong></h2>Run, jump and double jump to get yourself into position, wall jump to evade incoming harm, pull yourself up with the grappling hook to get the high ground or grapple-swing around corners to surprise your enemies. Learn how to chain these abilities with your 3D maneuvering gear to perform untraceable movement combos and outsmart your enemies like never before in a VR game! Maps are specifically designed with vertically in mind to get the most out of it.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1384320/extras/gtvr_container2_high_ground.gif?t=1703350710"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>MULTIFUNCTIONAL WEAPONS</strong></h2>More than 12 weapons eagerly await to get into battle under your command. From the common mechanical guns through the plasma pistols to the energy rifles, single-fire or automatic, instant shot or projectile based, you can have everything.<br/><br/>Target-following laser? Shotguns and grenade launchers? You got them. Rockets? Let them rain! Your VR dream is to become a turret with massive firepower? Go with dual miniguns! Double handed weapons have both primary and secondary fire modes letting you choose the perfect reaction for any situation. By the way you always have your melee weapon - the energy blade - on your side. You know, for slicing cake.<br/><br/>Play the game any way you like, use the grappling hook with a weapon or dual wield any weapon combination. Mobility versus firepower. Your call.<br/><br/>Did we mention that you can also summon an energy bow and shoot an arrow any time?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1384320/extras/gtvr_temple_railgun_combo.gif?t=1703350710"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>MULTIPLAYER</strong></h2>Multiplayer is the heart of the Tournament. Starting individually or with your friends, matchmaking will find you worthy opponents and let you fight in various game modes on engaging, stylized maps which were created with verticality in mind. The currently available game modes are:<br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Deathmatch: Everyone against everyone, up to 6 players. It can be messy and chaotic but you just can’t stop until you win. Can you be the very best on your own?<br/></li><li>Team Deathmatch: Fast-paced, frantic 3v3 combat. Get your weapons and defeat the enemy team with pure skill or finesse. Teamwork is essential here: shield your allies, assist in attacks and if all is critical, heal your teammates.<br/></li><li>Capture Point: Strategic point capture mode to spice up 3v3 team battles. Stay in the point areas to capture them and utilize all your arsenal to keep them at all cost. The team with the most points wins.<br/></li><li>Mutant: Eliminate the mutant to become the Mutant. When being the mutant you are stronger but everyone is hunting you.</li></ul><br/>During multiplayer you will visit a plethora of carefully crafted arenas, both outdoors and closed space maps for your all-terrain grapple experience. From sci-fi factories through cave excavations to japanese temples or greek monuments and more. You'll certainly find some maps to your liking.<br/><br/>Bots: Feel free to play with bots to master your skills or have some light-hearted fun.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1384320/extras/gtvr_parthenon_grapple_plasma_double.gif?t=1703350710"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>PRACTICE RANGE</strong></h2>Yeah, we have this too for 3D training purposes. With drones... with hats. You can try all the weapons in sandbox mode here.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CUSTOMIZATIONS</strong></h2>Customize your character to your liking with crazy hats and accessories.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Nefargad</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707090/The_Nefargad/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You've been abducted completely defenseless from your home and brought to a dungeon. You have no idea who did this to you or why. You must find your way out of this dungeon, where you were forcibly brought, by solving puzzles. Luckily, there have been others before you who came into this dungeon to explore it. They have previously solved the mysteries you now have to solve, and left notes about the solutions. With these notes, you can progress more efficiently. Thanks to the left messages, you will also learn about what happened here before you, but you are determined not to trust anyone.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Tension and Horror</strong><br/>The dungeon seems to respond to your every move. Sometimes it might feel like someone is watching you. If you’re not using your torch, you should extinguish it. Staying in the darkness for too long might not be a good idea either. You must balance the dark and light well. Also, don’t forget that puzzles may sometimes have alternative solutions. Random and unpredictable events will make the experience in this dungeon unique and irreplicable!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707090/extras/1.gif?t=1703358267"><br/><br/><strong>Your Knowledge, Insight, and Patience Will Be Tested</strong><br/>As you progress, the fundamental mechanics of the puzzles in the dungeon will change. Sometimes your knowledge about a subject will be tested. Sometimes how you approach problems will be examined. When you can’t find a solution, you will test your patience through trial and error!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707090/extras/2.gif?t=1703358267"><br/><br/><strong>Multilayered Story</strong><br/>As you progress through the dungeon, you will not only write your own story but learn about the stories of the researchers who entered this dungeon before you. What happened to those researchers? Did they share the same fate as you? Were they brought here forcibly? Were they able to get out? This dungeon is ready to tell you all this and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707090/extras/3.gif?t=1703358267"><br/><br/><strong>Warnings</strong><br/>The Nefargad includes profanity and slang in its game content. <br/>The Nefargad contains flashing and/or rapidly blinking lights in both game content and promotional materials. Consult your doctor before viewing any content related to the game or playing it if you have a history of epilepsy.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sci-fi builder</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2438540/Scifi_builder/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2438540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Sci-Fi builder is a simulator and third-person sandbox game defined by creativity and fantasy, it's a game where you can do whatever you want and create anything and everything. It's like a sandbox with a lot of items where you will entertain yourself starting from landing and to the very end, but what is the end? Well, you have to come up with yourself.<h2 class="bb_tag">STORY</h2>Play as the head manager in the completely new and empty space station in the planet number 1188 in the Constellation Centurion. Your task is to make here a new thriving colony. The game play begins with the landing on the space station, you are alone here and have to make a create job to build your own world and hire other characters. A short list of tasks at the very beginning will help you to learn more about the game functions. You will find out how to go to certain room, put props, teleport NPC, like humanoids, alien races, creatures and robots, set up interaction between the NPC and main character, other NPC and props, so you can easily build your own world.<br/><br/>Please remember, that game is in Early Access, and I will add a lot of new modules into it. And it depends on you, what modules it would be. Please, go to the discussion's sections and post all of your notes and ideas there.<br/><br/>Turn on your creativity, in Sci-fi builder, you are free to do whatever you want.<br/>Arrange all elements the way you want. No placing by the grid - complete freedom of action. If you don't like where you put a piece of furniture, just move it or remove it at any time. No limits on the number of objects in the room. If you do not like the main colors of your space station or any item's color, you can easily change it in the color settings. In the light settings menu, you can change the light in the whole station and adapt it to your needs.<br/><br/>Sci-fi builder is a simulation game about building sci-fi rooms and station and create your own society. A huge selection of characters, whom you can give commands, devices which you can manage, furniture, construction elements, computers and other interior details await you.<h2 class="bb_tag">GAME PLAY</h2>Enjoy over hundreds of different characters which you may use as the main character or NPC in the game. Players can freely guide character movements and interact with the objects to influence character reactions. Every room is fully sounded and contains a variety of action options.<br/>Personalize the characters, manage their wardrobe and decide how they will behave.<br/><br/>Good luck in your new life in a space station!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
