<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Portal: Revolution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/601360/Portal_Revolution/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Portal: Revolution is a fan-made mod for Portal 2 which plays before the events of Portal 2 in the dead and decaying Aperture facility.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/ezgif-7-f507c3c464_1_.gif?t=1704560425"><br/><strong>Over 40 new puzzles</strong><br/>The campaign contains 40 brand new puzzles making use of new test elements and presents existing mechanics in a new way not seen in Portal 2.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resurrected "Pneumatic Diversity Vent" element<br/></li><li> New laser cube variant<br/></li><li> Over 15 puzzles using only the blue Portal-Gun<br/></li><li> Gel Cleansing Field</li></ul><br/><strong>Difficulty</strong><br/>Portal: Revolutions puzzle difficulty starts where Portal 2 stops, but fear not. All new mechanics and advanced portal tricks are taught to you. We have ensured through rigorous playtesting that every player can solve the puzzles. Although very few chambers require portals to be fired mid-air, no puzzles require advanced tricky movement.<br/><br/>Depending on your experience with Portal 2 mechanics, you can expect about 5 to 7 hours of playtime.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/banner_story_2.gif?t=1704560425"><br/>Set inbetween Portal and Portal 2, Portal: Revolution tells a brand new story using new characters. You play as a test subject who is awoken by a personality sphere called Stirling and join his mission to find a powerful device capable of restoring Aperture to its former glory.<h2 class="bb_tag">ENGINE</h2>Portal: Revolution uses a modified version of Portal 2: Community Edition's engine, which is a custom version of the Counter-Strike: Global Offensive Source Engine branch using licensed source code provided by Valve Software.<br/><br/>This allowed us to introduce many mechanics and improvements to the engine to create an experience which would be impossible in Portal 2.<br/><br/>-----------------------------------<br/><br/>Something you want to say? <br/>Email us: <a href="mailto:hello@secondfacesoftware.com">hello@secondfacesoftware.com</a><br/>Support: <a href="mailto:support@secondfacesoftware.com">support@secondfacesoftware.com</a> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Memories</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2495450/Winter_Memories/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1704499222"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_1-EN.png?t=1704499222"><br/>After the unforgettable summer memories you’ve made half a year ago, Yui, Rio, and Miyuki are back. With the change of seasons and the cold falling snow, a new page to your story is about to begin. <br/><br/>Revisit the peaceful, seaside town, and spend time catching up with your family and friends.<br/><br/>What new memories will you make this winter?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_3-EN.png?t=1704499222"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Miyuki_EN.png?t=1704499222"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Rio_EN.png?t=1704499222"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Yui_EN.png?t=1704499222"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_4-EN.png?t=1704499222"><br/><strong>A Relaxing, Adventure RPG<strong><br/><br/><strong>Explore the Beautiful, Seaside Town<strong><br/><br/><strong>Manage How You Spend Your TIme<strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones: NWO Wars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2487350/Alex_Jones_NWO_Wars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Play the OFFICIAL Alex Jones video game! Save the world from the evil globalists’ plot to turn everyone into bug-eating pod-dwelling libtards! STAY TUNED FOR FUTURE BONUS LEVELS AND CHARACTERS.<br/><br/><strong>Classic Run-and-Gun Gameplay</strong>: Enjoy fast-paced action, intricate animations, and detailed environments as you blast your way through waves of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>Unique Levels</strong>: Battle in various environments like secret underground bases, globalist conferences, and mind control facilities, all inspired by real events. Stay tuned for future levels.<br/><br/><strong>Challenging Boss Fights</strong>: Face off against the elite henchmen of the New World Order, including lizard overlords, secret society leaders, and genetically modified creatures.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Voice Lines</strong>: Featuring iconic and often humorous catchphrases from Alex Jones himself, adding flavor to every combat scenario. Special guest vocals by Ryan Katsu Rivera.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_06.png?t=1704518222"><h2 class="bb_tag">JOIN ALEX AND HIS ALLIES </h2><br/>Every day the deep state sues, lies, defames, and KILLS law-abiding patriots who threaten their power!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_05.png?t=1704518222"><h2 class="bb_tag">DEFEAT BIG TECH CUCKS and MORE</h2><br/>And other anti-American communist bosses throughout this adrenaline-inducing adventure!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_04.png?t=1704518222"><h2 class="bb_tag">PLAY AS ALEX!</h2><br/>For the first time in history, experience the world through Infowars leader Alex Jones’ eyes and see the WAR he fights!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/new_screenshot_03.jpg?t=1704518222"><h2 class="bb_tag">SAVE THE BABIES</h2><br/>It’s no secret the NWO REPTILES are after our children. Play NWO Wars now to help save these innocent victims from these MONSTERS!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_02.png?t=1704518222"><br/><br/>“They’re turning the friggin frogs gay!”<br/><br/>Only Alex Jones can stop this madness and restore balance in the Brain Force!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_01.png?t=1704518222"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowbreak: Containment Zone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668080/Snowbreak_Containment_Zone/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Snowbreak: Containment Zone is a 3D sci-fi RPG-shooter powered by the Unreal Engine 4 that offers a next-gen, cross-platform gaming experience, sharing your progress across all of your devices. <br/><br/>The Descent of the Titans turned a once-vibrant city into the devastated wasteland of Containment Zone Aleph. As the Adjutant of Heimdall Force, bravely undertake missions alongside Manifestations with the powers of gods and unique personalities, seeking to bring this bitter winter to an end...<br/><br/>[Enjoy Hybrid Combat]<br/>Snowbreak's weaponry injects realism into a sci-fi setting, with designs closely simulating future firearms technology. This combines with the otherworldly, RPG-like skill mechanic to create a refreshing combat experience.<br/><br/>[Take on Titans]<br/>The Descent of the Titans completely changed the world, and the battlefield. Feel the thrill of battling giants in this dystopian future!<br/><br/>[Befriend Operatives]<br/>Spend time with your Heimdall Force companions in the Base system. Decorate, chat, and give gifts to grow closer!<br/><br/>[Play Co-Op in Gigalink] <br/>Tired of exploring alone? Join up with friends and fight enemies together!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milo and the Christmas Gift</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2716140/Milo_and_the_Christmas_Gift/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							After his adventure in Milo and the Magpies, Milo is looking forward to spending a cosy Christmas at home. But a Christmas gift is about to upset his holiday celebrations, especially when said gift disappears after a little misunderstanding! Can you help Milo bring home the lost Gift and save Christmas for Marleen… and himself?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_playing_1.gif?t=1704473114"> <br/><br/>Milo and the Christmas Gift is a free-to-play short and atmospheric point-and-click adventure game created by artist Johan Scherft. The game is a spin-off story following the events in Milo and the Magpies. The game has 5 chapters and a gameplay time of around 30 minutes!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/>■ Relaxing yet stimulating game-play<br/>Join Milo in his home and revisit some of the neighbouring gardens, but this time in a wintery Christmas wonderland! Interact with the festive environment and solve small point-and-click / hidden-object puzzles.<br/><br/>■ Captivating artistic atmosphere<br/>Each hand-painted, interior and snowy garden Milo has to search through has its unique personality, reflecting that of Milo’s owners and next-door neighbours respectively.<br/><br/>■ Atmospheric soundtrack<br/>Each chapter has its own festive theme song composed by Victor Butzelaar.<br/><br/>■ Average playtime: 15-30 minutes<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_snow_1.gif?t=1704473114"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few Nights More: Genesis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713070/Few_Nights_More_Genesis/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Please note: This is a free prologue and it includes act 1, and only 1 playable character and blood school is playable, The maximum heritage gained is limited to 50, and the maximum difficulty can be set to 2. As well only one castle will be available. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Blood3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Conquer castles and claim your birthright!</strong><br/> <br/>The fight to reclaim your place in this world begins. Rebuild lost ruins, make them stronger and defend them against your enemies. After you regain your strength, move on to conquer more territories and eventually claim your birthright.<br/><br/>Few Nights More offers the unique fusing of castle management and turn based rogue-like combat. Fight against humanity, the undisputed masters of this world in your absence. Choose between eight different Vampire Lords, each with their own ambition and history. Find your trinkets, skills and perks along your way. Design your very own castle by placing the right rooms, adding decors that directly contribute to your army and your Vampire Lord. Conquer more castles so your influence and power grow, until you claim your birthright.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Ferocity3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Core Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Design your castle by adding new Rooms, Traps and Minions. Stack up on some buffs with shiny decors to get ready for the invasion screen to defend it to the end of every night!<br/> <br/></li><li> Choose among 7 different Vampire Lords with unique History, Gameplay and Abilities.<br/> <br/></li><li> Master 1 out of 3 Disciplines each time you play, each with 60 unique skills.<br/> <br/></li><li> Acquire new random skills, perks and trinkets to survive the nights.<br/> <br/></li><li> Excel in either being a Prestigious Vampire, a Seductive one, or master a Terrifying presence against your enemies.<br/><br/></li><li> Test the builds you made against a variety of Hunters, Veterans and Unique Bosses in an action packed turn based combat system.<br/> <br/></li><li> Endure three acts across 12 difficulty levels, striving to survive and progress. Accumulate Heritage Points to enhance your lord's starting stats, skills, and unlock new castles and talents unique to each lord.<br/><br/></li><li> Engage in the boundless challenge of Infinity Mode, where you can continuously test your limits without relying on a castle. Each night, you will be presented with three options to advance, growing stronger as you push yourself to see how far you can go.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703868247"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1704471185"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1704471185"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1704471185"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1704471185"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1704471185"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1704380508"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1704380508"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1703493452"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1703493452"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1703186631"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1703318086"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1703318086"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Expanse: A Telltale Series</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1708010/The_Expanse_A_Telltale_Series/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1708010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the exciting universe of The Expanse like never before in Telltale’s latest adventure, The Expanse: A Telltale Series. Take on the role of Camina Drummer and explore the dangerous and uncharted edges of the Belt aboard the Artemis. From scavenging wrecked ships in a zero-g environment, to surviving a mutiny, to combating fearsome pirates, you make the difficult choices and reveal Camina Drummer’s resolve in this latest Telltale adventure.<br/><br/><strong>A TELLTALE STORY LIKE NO OTHER</strong><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in the role of Camina Drummer, the Executive Officer aboard the Artemis, a scavenging ship hunting for a big score in the outer regions of the Belt. You must corral a crew rife with tense relationships and powerful personalities, and make tough decisions that will decide everyone’s fate.<br/><br/><strong>EXPLORE THE BELT IN ZERO-G</strong><br/><br/>Scour shipwrecks, use mag boots to walk on walls and ceilings, and utilize zero-g thrusters to float through the void. As you fly through sections of ships and the open expanse of space, interact with objects in the world and converse with members of the crew in the largest and most immersive exploration of any Telltale game to date.<br/><br/><strong>DIFFICULT CHOICES, GRAVE CONSEQUENCES</strong><br/><br/>Contend with the unforgiving brutality of space, the politics of a corrupt solar system, the animosities of your crew, and Drummer’s own conflicting responsibilities to the people she cares about and the Belt she has sworn to protect. There is no right or wrong path - only your choices and the consequences they unleash.<br/><br/><strong>INCLUDES ALL 5 EPISODES</strong><br/><br/>Episode 1: Archer's Paradox<br/>Episode 2: Hunting Grounds<br/>Episode 3: First Ones<br/>Episode 4: Impossible Objects<br/>Episode 5: Europa's Folly						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1704392583"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1704392583"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1704392583"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teardown</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1167630/Teardown/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1167630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Plan the perfect heist using creative problem solving, brute force, and everything around you. Teardown features a fully destructible and truly interactive environment where player freedom and emergent gameplay are the driving mechanics.<br/><br/>Tear down walls with explosives or vehicles to create shortcuts no one thought was possible. Stack objects, build structures, or use floating objects to your advantage. Take your time to create an efficient path through the level, plan the heist and get ready to execute it.<br/><br/>Run, jump, drive, slingshot. Do whatever you need to collect targets, avoid robots or steal whatever your clients ask for. But make sure not to get caught!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1167630/extras/campaign.gif?t=1700055440"><br/><br/><strong>Campaign</strong><br/>With your company pressured by increasing debt, you start accepting work from some more or less shady individuals. Soon you are knee-deep in a murky soup of revenge, betrayal, and insurance fraud. Beginning with some more or less legitimate assignments, you soon find yourself stealing cars, demolishing buildings, blowing up safes, avoiding trigger-happy robots and more. Upgrade your expanding arsenal of tools by searching for hidden valuables scattered around the environments.<br/><br/><strong>Sandbox</strong><br/>Play around in the various environments with the tools you have unlocked. In this mode you have unlimited resources and an abundance of vehicles. No pressure, just pleasure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1167630/extras/sandbox.gif?t=1700055440"><br/><br/><strong>Challenges</strong><br/>Test your skills in experimental game modes. New challenges unlock as you progress through the campaign.<br/><br/><strong>Modding</strong><br/>Teardown has extensive mod support with built-in level editor, Lua scripting and a Steam Workshop integration. Build your own sandbox maps, mini games, tools, vehicles or try out existing mods from the community. <br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fully destructible voxel environments<br/></li><li>Realistic physical simulation of objects, debris, vehicles, water, fire, and smoke<br/></li><li>17 different tools ranging from sledgehammer, blow torch and fire extinguisher to guns and explosives <br/></li><li>Campaign with 40 missions in an escalating storyline<br/></li><li>Sandbox mode for you to roam around in the various environments<br/></li><li>Extensive mod support and Steam Workshop integration</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1702747783"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror inside the forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2584370/Horror_inside_the_forest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2584370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark into the depths of the unknown with <strong>Horror inside the forest</strong>, a captivating gaming experience that's now available. Confront the darkness that shrouds a mysterious forest, where shadows conceal logic-defying secrets and lurk for the brave souls who venture there.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2584370/extras/fotosteam1StopM.png?t=1704592623"><br/><br/>The game immerses you in the shoes of a fearless explorer who delves into the woods, defying warnings and the curse surrounding the place. As night falls, you find yourself alone, surrounded by a palpable darkness that hides puzzles and deadly dangers.<br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/><br/>Immersive Exploration: Discover a detailed, immersive world brought to life with stunning graphics. Every corner of the forest is unique and presents distinct challenges.<br/><br/>Intense Atmosphere: Immerse yourself in an atmosphere full of tension and mystery, thanks to carefully designed visual and sound effects that will keep you on edge at all times.<br/><br/>Supernatural Challenges: Confront supernatural creatures and phenomena that will challenge your survival instincts and compel you to face your deepest fears.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2584370/extras/monstruos.png?t=1704592623"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>エスカレーター |  Escalator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2738050/___Escalator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Escalator | Escalator is a horror game in which you must find anomalies while riding an escalator and escape from an enclosed space.<br>
<br>
You are trapped by someone in an underground passageway where only the sound of the escalator flows silently.<br>
<br>
Join the game presented by someone and try to escape from this mysterious space.<br>
<br>
<br>
While riding the escalator, strange things happen.<br/>
<br/>
Identify what is happening while you are on the escalator.<br/>
<br/>
Sometimes nothing happens while you are on the escalator.<br/>
<br/>
If nothing happens, exit through the emergency exit. If something strange is happening, go down the stairs and ring the emergency bell.<br/>
<br/>
Once you make a mistake, you have to start over. If you do not make a mistake, the same anomaly will not occur.<br/>
<br/>
◆Tips<br/>
<br/>
For the "gone" achievement, if you press a certain key at a certain time, a special action will be performed.<br/>
<br/>
You may make a live video or stream without permission.<br/>
We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or stream, and a link to the Steam store page in the summary section.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunflower Pie</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2742040/Sunflower_Pie/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2742040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The worst thing about Oliver’s breakfast is that it wants to be eaten. <br>
<br>
Inspired by early RPGmaker horror games and Adult Swim bumpers, Sunflower Pie is a bite-sized visual novel with extra parasites (for flavor). Much like real life, it oscillates violently between discomfort and sincerity. Unlike real life, however, there is only one correct choice. <br>
<br>
Features:<br>
<br>
*You can beat this visual novel in 25 minutes<br/>
<br/>
*Oliver’s speech therapist is good at her job and owns a revolver <br/>
<br/>
*Learn about all the cool ways to remove ticks from your body<br/>
<br/>
*Made with love (sincerely)						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veg out Crew FPS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2085290/Veg_out_Crew_FPS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are <strong>Carro</strong>, the lone carrot on a mission to take back the Veg out World from all the moldy fruits and vegetables.<br/><br/>A throw back to the old classics of how the FPS originated. Get in and get blasting with all the weaponry you can handle and the enemies you can blast!<br/><br/>What you can expect:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 15 different weapons and more to come<br/></li><li>3 single player stages filled with enemies, weapons and some retro artwork<br/></li><li>A heap of enemies to keep the entertainment and adrenaline pumping<br/></li><li>3 different bosses to keep you on your toes and wanting more<br/></li><li>A survival mode where enemies keep on spawning</li></ul><br/>Casually rocking out the pea shooter and hotdog gun!!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085290/extras/PeaShooter_and_Hotdog.gif?t=1704571490"><br/><br/>Another epic weapon with the tomato launcher just thumping down those enemies!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085290/extras/Tomato_Launcher.gif?t=1704571490"><br/><br/>So what are you waiting for? Get in there as <strong>Carro </strong>and do some damage and blast your way through the Veg out World.<br/><br/>Also, come join in on the discord at <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FVJzWw7N8TK" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/VJzWw7N8TK</a> and help shape our game.<br/><br/>Happy Veg out Crew! :)						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Balls</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551030/The_Balls/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">The Balls: A Revolution in the World of Battle Royale FPS</h2>"The Balls" is not just another PVP FPS (Battle Royale) game. It redefines the freedom of movement in a virtual world. Breaking the boundaries of usual running and flying, we offer players complete freedom as geometric spheres, unrestricted by gravity or centrifugal forces.<h2 class="bb_tag">Unlimited Freedom of Movement</h2>Imagine a world where you can instantly reach any location without physical limitations. This dynamic changes everything you know about strategies and tactics in Battle Royale games.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551030/extras/movement.gif?t=1704570324"><h2 class="bb_tag">Community and Communication</h2>In "The Balls", community is our priority. A simple and transparent communication system allows for easy connection with other players. Create lobbies, join matches, and invite friends with the press of a single button.<h2 class="bb_tag">Family-Friendly Graphics</h2>Our game is free from blood and explicit violence. Instead, players compete by attacking abstract, geometric shapes. Perfect for players of all ages.<h2 class="bb_tag">Ranking System</h2>An advanced ranking system tracks your daily, monthly, and overall results. Get ready for the introduction of clan duels and periodic tournaments, offering a new level of competition.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>MULTIPLAYER Deathmatch and Battle Royale.<br/></li><li>The most dynamic movement mechanism.<br/></li><li>Global rankings and achievements.<br/></li><li>Vibrant, cartoon-style graphics.<br/></li><li>Simple communication system.<br/></li><li>Strategic build-and-destroy mechanics.<br/></li><li>Unique arenas for various battle strategies.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Upcoming Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Clan Creation: </strong>Organize and manage your own clan in "The Balls".<br/></li><li><strong>Monthly Tournaments: </strong>Compete for prizes in regular tournaments.<br/></li><li><strong>Map Creation Mode:</strong> Design and share your own maps, offering extraordinary creativity to players.</li></ul><br/><strong>Join the "The Balls" community today and experience unparalleled freedom of movement and exciting competition!</strong> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Present</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2690790/Christmas_Present/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Christmas Present is an adventure game based on the adventures of Santa Claus. In this game, the player controls Santa, who flies on a reindeer-drawn sled across the sky. The goal of the game is to throw gifts into chimneys and bring happiness to children.<br>
<br>
The Christmas Present game features a variety of gifts, real Christmas reindeer, Santa Claus and a variety of locations. Together with Santa, the player travels to different cities, throwing gifts and delighting children's hearts.<br>
<br>
An important feature of the game is the atmosphere of Christmas joy and kindness, which is conveyed through bright graphics and pleasant melodies. Christmas Present is the perfect game for those who love Christmas, Santa Claus and adventures in the spirit of Christmas fairy tales.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End Of Life</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2666520/End_Of_Life/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2666520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							End of Life is a third-person action shooter set in a fragmented and ever-moving city, rotating like a Rubik's Cube. The player will shoot needles to overcome enemies and obstacles, dodge deadly attacks, and navigate the changing landscape with a grappling hook, always seeking an advantageous position to eliminate rivals.<br/><br/><strong>Story</strong><br/><br/>The world is governed by two goddesses. Asdis is the creator, while Disad must balance her sister's creations to prevent chaos. When Asdis creates humans, her greatest creation, Disad decides to divide her power and personify it in the Aarendjin, an extension of herself. The mission of the Aarendjin is to kill those humans who pose a real threat to the planet.<br/><br/>Over time, a city discovered the Aarendjin's weakness and started a war to acquire the magic within them. They killed them all and stole their power cores, except for one, Nashla, whom they imprisoned. This power allowed the city to be in constant motion, rotating on itself, preventing Nashla from escaping.<br/><br/>Years later, a revolt within the city aimed to kill the Aarendjin, providing Nashla with the perfect opportunity to execute her plan: recover her core and seek revenge on humans for killing her sisters.<br/><br/><strong>What is End Of Life?</strong><br/><br/>Changing World: A world based on a Rubik's Cube that the player and enemies can manipulate to create combat situations, new paths, and challenges.<br/><br/>Multiple Gravities: Each area of the world has its gravity, with no safe spots when enemies can shoot from the sky.<br/><br/>Relentless Movement: Everything in this world is in motion—the player, enemies, and the world itself. Constantly changing, the player must strive to find their way through battles and gravities.<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/><br/>End of Life is a third-person action shooter where the player embodies a demigoddess with a broken power seeking revenge and reclaiming stolen power. The player faces decisions that define whether they remain faithful to their original mission or succumb to revenge.<br/><br/>The player must use the demigoddess's remaining powers and the world's resources. Different gravities and world modifications create new paths and allow the player to escape enemies when unable to face them.<br/><br/>During the adventure, the demigoddess will find traces of her fallen sisters, recovering part of their powers. These powers grant her new abilities to progress in the world and new tools to defeat her enemies.<br/><br/><strong>Mechanics</strong><br/><br/>Navigation<br/><br/>Gravity Shift: The game world is fragmented, and each fragment has its gravity on each face. Nashla can observe the world from different perspectives, finding paths that would be invisible otherwise.<br/><br/>World Movement: The fragmented world is constantly moving, and the civilization residing there has created mechanisms to alter the world's movement at will. Nashla will use these to turn her enemies' tools against them.<br/><br/>Grappling Hook: Nashla's main tool is a grappling hook, constantly used to reach otherwise inaccessible places and quickly approach enemies to finish them off before they can react.<br/><br/>Combat<br/><br/>Needles: Needles symbolize Nashla's power, each type providing effects to her projectiles. Each needle she carries once belonged to her fallen sisters.<br/><br/>Bullet Time: Nashla's keen senses allow her to enter a state of total concentration. In this state, the world slows around her, allowing for quick decisions and providing a devastating advantage.<br/><br/>Fury: As a vengeful demigoddess, Nashla becomes enraged at the mortals' challenge. When Nashla accumulates enough anger, she enters a Fury state, launching her projectiles more frequently and forcefully. The needles she launches in this state drain life from her enemies to heal her.<br/><br/>Barriers: Enemies, aware of their weakness, constantly try to corner and wear down Nashla. Using complex magical barrier mechanisms, they will trap the demigoddess in an inescapable battle to weaken and defeat her.<br/><br/><strong>Core Loop</strong><br/><br/>The core of End of Life is primarily divided into three parts: advancing through the level, killing all enemies in the way, and discovering how to use her powers to interact with the world.<br/><br/>This core loop represents a partnership between the player and their avatar, discovering the world and the demigoddess's powers at the same pace, fostering player immersion and empathy.<br/><br/>Throughout the adventure, the player's style will reinforce each of the three core elements, from trying to advance by avoiding unnecessary conflicts to exploring the presented world or simply ending all life like a bloodthirsty beast. The decision of which aspect to reinforce will depend on the player's gameplay style, reflecting in Nashla's adventure their own story.<br/><br/><strong>Visual Style</strong><br/><br/>End of Life features a fusion of realistic environments and stylized characters, providing greater creative freedom while maintaining realistic textures for consistency.<br/><br/>The environment represents a Middle Eastern style with warm, earthy, and luminous colors in squares where life once thrived. The warm tones contrast with Nashla's cool palette, indicating she doesn't belong to this world.<br/><br/>The world is portrayed as a Rubik's Cube mirror, with marked edges and different sizes present throughout the entire scenario. It floats disorderly due to the ongoing war, constantly rotating and repositioning as the protagonist advances in the story. The sense of enormity and frenzy is reflected in all the cubes sustaining the world, and the magnitude in each playable scenario.<br/><br/>Magic is prevalent throughout the game, playing a fundamental role. It's represented with brighter and more vivid colors in the environment, highlighting the game's mechanics.<br/><br/><strong>References</strong><br/><br/>The dynamic and changing world created in Doctor Strange inspired the game's dynamic landscape, covering both land and sky, the constant change through battles, and the extraordinary yet partially common landscapes.<br/><br/>Rollerdrome is a central reference regarding gameplay. The combination of action with constant movement is a point that End Of Life seeks to achieve.<br/><br/>The game's story draws strong influences from Hellblade, where both protagonists embark on a revenge story and face psychological issues distorting their perception of reality and objectives. The world-based puzzles served as inspiration for level design.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demons Infernalize</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2324380/Demons_Infernalize/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2324380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">demons Infernalize - Early Access</h2> A bullet hell survival game with minimalistic gameplay and roguelite mechanics .You are banished from the hell, directly to Ice Planet, and the people are not gonna let you live as a fire spirit in the snow planet. Survive as long as you can until your soul goes out. Burn those ice people and complete the levels, upgrade yourself, become the true survivor in the snow planet.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2324380/extras/steam_gif_2.gif?t=1704566159"><br/><br/><strong>Become the Demon</strong><br/>Have fun with minimalist gameplay and the following mechanics:<br/>*Burn the crowd<br/>*Upgrade yourself<br/>*Build your skill set to face the enemies<br/>*Heal by burning the objects<br/>*Find treasures in ice planet<br/>*Find the portals and face the frosty bosses<br/>*Evolve yourself, gain abilities like dash and flying<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2324380/extras/steam_gif_1.gif?t=1704566159"><br/><br/><strong>Gain the Skills</strong><br/>*Crossfire<br/>*Detonation<br/>*Magma Mine<br/>*Cage<br/>*Geo Fire<br/>*Fire Tornado<br/>*Dagger<br/>and lots of more upcoming skills<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2324380/extras/steam_gif_0.gif?t=1704566159"><br/><br/><strong>Early Access</strong><br/>Remember, this game is in the early access. The contents will developed by time.<br/> However,<strong> you can still have fun with this version</strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Laura Up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684010/Super_Laura_Up/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Super Laura Up is a platformer Inspired by retro platformers and precision platformers, this game will take you on a journey through a variety of challenging levels, where you must use your precision and timing to overcome obstacles and reach the end.<br/><br/>Experience a challenging and rewarding precision platformer that will test your skills and patience.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> A challenging level<br/></li><li> Smooth and responsive controls<br/></li><li> A retro art style</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PolyZen Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2715060/PolyZen_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							             <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715060/extras/ingiliz.gif?t=1704581425"><br/><i><strong>Welcome to PolyZen Drive, where every drive is a unique journey tailored to your mood. Immerse yourself in the beauty of open-world exploration and customize your ride to match your vibe. Your mood dictates all in here; adjust your car, visuals, music, driving style, and everything else. In PolyZen Drive, you have complete freedom, and you decide your gameplay!</strong></i><h2 class="bb_tag"><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Open-world Serenity:</strong></li></ul></h2>Embark on a serene journey through meticulously crafted open-world maps. Whether you're cruising through city lights or enjoying the calm of the countryside, PolyZen Drive offers a tranquil escape.<h2 class="bb_tag"><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Drop A Gear to Disappear:</strong></li></ul></h2>When you feel the urge to speed things up, don't hold back. Blast some music on the radio and use all that space in the accelerator pedal. Who doesn't love the sound of big engines roaring anyway?<h2 class="bb_tag"><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Drive Your Way:</strong></li></ul></h2>Tailor your driving experience to your mood. Slip into the calm with drift mode for graceful maneuvers or rev up the excitement with arcade mode for an energetic, heart-pounding adventure.<h2 class="bb_tag"><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Love-Hate Relationship with Traffic?</strong></li></ul></h2>Take control of your journey, just like you take control of your mood. In PolyZen Drive, traffic is at your command. Choose to navigate through dense traffic, skillfully maneuvering through the obstacles as a challenge, or opt for a more relaxed drive by turning it off entirely. The road is yours, and the traffic is just another element you get to customize.<h2 class="bb_tag"><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Visual Harmony:</strong></li></ul></h2>Find your visual sweet spot. Adjust speed effects for a calming experience or dial up the intensity with tons of effects. All are adjustable, and you have control.<h2 class="bb_tag"><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Melodic Exploration:</strong></li></ul></h2>Explore a melodic universe with a plethora of radio stations. From chill lofi beats to high-energy phonk vibes, find the soundtrack that resonates with your drive.<h2 class="bb_tag"><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Your Zen, Your Drive:</strong></li></ul></h2>PolyZen Drive adapts to you, offering a calm refuge or an adrenaline-fueled escapade. From the gentle purr of a slow ride to the roaring engine of a drift king, find your perfect drive with PolyZen. Make PolyZen Drive your own. Alter the mood of your drive, and experience the road like never before.<h2 class="bb_tag"><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Versatile Input Support:</strong></li></ul></h2>Play with your keyboard, joystick or even with a steering wheel, all are supported!<br/>                               <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2715060/extras/input.gif?t=1704581425"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Ready to Rediscover the Road?</strong></h2><br/><strong><u>Get Polyzen Drive Now!</u></strong> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portal: Revolution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/601360/Portal_Revolution/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Portal: Revolution is a fan-made mod for Portal 2 which plays before the events of Portal 2 in the dead and decaying Aperture facility.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/ezgif-7-f507c3c464_1_.gif?t=1704560425"><br/><strong>Over 40 new puzzles</strong><br/>The campaign contains 40 brand new puzzles making use of new test elements and presents existing mechanics in a new way not seen in Portal 2.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resurrected "Pneumatic Diversity Vent" element<br/></li><li> New laser cube variant<br/></li><li> Over 15 puzzles using only the blue Portal-Gun<br/></li><li> Gel Cleansing Field</li></ul><br/><strong>Difficulty</strong><br/>Portal: Revolutions puzzle difficulty starts where Portal 2 stops, but fear not. All new mechanics and advanced portal tricks are taught to you. We have ensured through rigorous playtesting that every player can solve the puzzles. Although very few chambers require portals to be fired mid-air, no puzzles require advanced tricky movement.<br/><br/>Depending on your experience with Portal 2 mechanics, you can expect about 5 to 7 hours of playtime.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/banner_story_2.gif?t=1704560425"><br/>Set inbetween Portal and Portal 2, Portal: Revolution tells a brand new story using new characters. You play as a test subject who is awoken by a personality sphere called Stirling and join his mission to find a powerful device capable of restoring Aperture to its former glory.<h2 class="bb_tag">ENGINE</h2>Portal: Revolution uses a modified version of Portal 2: Community Edition's engine, which is a custom version of the Counter-Strike: Global Offensive Source Engine branch using licensed source code provided by Valve Software.<br/><br/>This allowed us to introduce many mechanics and improvements to the engine to create an experience which would be impossible in Portal 2.<br/><br/>-----------------------------------<br/><br/>Something you want to say? <br/>Email us: <a href="mailto:hello@secondfacesoftware.com">hello@secondfacesoftware.com</a><br/>Support: <a href="mailto:support@secondfacesoftware.com">support@secondfacesoftware.com</a> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satori</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2730020/Satori/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Satori is a Hack &amp; Slash Roguelike game with a third-person camera where a mask allows you to choose between different passive abilities and a ghost arm gives you different special abilities that you must use to fight against yokais and Japanese gods, all with a unique aesthetic. Cell Shading in three colors.<br>
Satori consists of starting in a lobby, going through two rooms with simple enemies and finally reaching the boss room. Each enemy will give you coins that you can exchange in the lobby for new skills or character upgrades. If you die, you will always return to the lobby.						</br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outforce</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2633480/The_Outforce/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Conquer the Dark Universe!</h2><br/><br/>In the 25th century, mankind is fighting for survival far away from home. The human race has left Earth, after nearly getting wiped out due to an asteroid hit, and is now trying its best to settle down in a nearby star system, Epsilon Eridani. Once the colonists reached their destination, they found themselves in the middle of an intergalactic conflict.<br/><br/>The Outforce is a real-time strategy game taking you to the far reaches of the universe where mankind is fighting for survival. With over 120 different units and advanced AI system you must crush the alien empires and master the Universe. Peace can only be achieved by conquest.<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>3D technology, such as a free-floating camera with a variable zoom field of view perspective and rotation.<br/></li><li>Artificial intelligence with a genetic learning algorithm<br/></li><li>Extensive physics system including pressure waves, elastic collisions, gravity and push-and-pull forces.<br/></li><li>Innovative new devices and units, such as towship, phasing units and self-destructing units.<br/></li><li>Three individual races and over 120 different units.<br/></li><li>Multiplayer features up to eight players adapted for both LAN and Internet play.<br/></li><li>Warp stations allow your units and buildings to be transported anywhere on the map.<br/></li><li>Outer space battlefields include details such as asteroid fields, planets, massive space platforms, and of course, alien defensive barriers.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow Vault</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2633490/Shadow_Vault/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">"As I walk through the shadow of death, I fear no mutants" — General Draw</h2><br/><br/>Shadow Vault is a Strategy RPG that will pit you against an evil government army of mutants hell bent on world domination. Set during a violent time in Earth's alternate history, you must battle the heavily armed forces of the Contingent government and take back your planet!<br/><br/>You are out-gunned, out-manned, and their technology is one hundred years more advanced...<br/><br/>Only your skill at commanding your small band of fighters on the battlefield will help you survive. Choose the right person for the right job, discover the mystery of the Contingent government and change Earth's history forever!<br/><br/>Defend your territory from the Contingent at all costs! Customize your team and choose which one will make it to the next level. Explore the abandoned buildings and hunt down the enemy. Make sure to save civilians who have taken refuge in deserted buildings!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Nuclear war-ravaged environment. Use destroyed structures for cover, enter buildings and clear them of enemies.<br/></li><li>Interact with various pieces of mutant technology.<br/></li><li>Unique unit classes, each with its own special sets of abilities, such as medics, engineers, snipers and commandos.<br/></li><li>Units improve abilities and acquire new ones as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>Over thirty unique abilities and over forty different actions to enhance and update your units.<br/></li><li>Hours of strategic gameplay through twenty one levels.<br/></li><li>Thirty units and characters to choose from and a multitude of mutated enemies.<br/></li><li>Epic and dynamic storyline that truly immerses the player.<br/></li><li>High level Artificial Intelligence that reacts to your strategies.<br/></li><li>Intuitive gameplay and interface placing emphasis on the strategic experience rather than on complex game rules.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rails Across America</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2680190/Rails_Across_America/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2680190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Rails Across America is a game of railroad empires in North America, covering the period from 1830 to the near future. It is a real-time strategy game with a "sim" flavor. Rails allows hundreds of tracks with thousands of trains crossing the continent. Players must focus on strategic decisions: where to expand, where to compete, and when to call in favors from government officials, union leaders, and other powerful figures.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Sophisticated cargo routing system enables large-scale play enabling hundreds of routes and thousands of engines.<br/></li><li>Influences let you directly affect other players: cause a financial panic, start an investigation into the player's company, instigate a strike, petition a city for route assignment or force independents out of business.<br/></li><li>60 different engines and cars.<br/></li><li>Intelligent AI modeled after 12 real world rail barons.<br/></li><li>Up to 8 players in multiplayer over LAN.<br/></li><li>Create new worlds using the Map Editor and unleash your creativity to craft your ultimate train fantasy.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Throne: Battle of Red Cliffs</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2633500/Dragon_Throne_Battle_of_Red_Cliffs/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dragon Throne: Battle of Red Cliffs is an epic real-time strategy game that depicts a turbulent and chaotic time in Chinese history. Three individual campaigns allow you to control the kingdoms of Liu Bei, Sun Quan, or Cao Cao, warlords who played a pivotal role in Ancient China. Lead your kingdom and develop new technologies, establish strategic alliances and create a mighty army in an attempt to unify the nation.<br/><br/>This real-time strategy game features a unique period in Chinese history and is based on the classic historical novel, "Romance of the Three Kingdoms", written in the 14th Century. Play the game and experience the thrill of being a heroic conqueror in that chaotic, war-ridden time.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Warriors choose from more than 40 different skills.<br/></li><li>Multi-map system enables you to separate battlefield and city development.<br/></li><li>Use domestic policies, diplomacy, science, trade and other management factors to affect your Kingdom's overall state.<br/></li><li>Unique Profession-Transference system enables laborers to be trained as sergeants and then, if needed, revert to laborers again.<br/></li><li>Tech-Tree is composed of over 100 items extracted from the social reality of the Three Kingdoms period.<br/></li><li>Engage in 3 campaigns that allow you to change the destiny of China.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glimpse</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2683490/Glimpse/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2683490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Glimpse" takes you on a journey through the mind of a man haunted by the relentless erosion of his mind. As you traverse a labyrinth of distorted reality, you'll bear witness to the internal fears and confusion faced by those with Alzheimer's disease. Explore a nightmarish world where memories blur, and reality becomes a nightmare.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2683490/extras/Xyu7NR.gif?t=1704548994"><br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A truly confusing and unsettling experience.<br/></li><li>Each level has a distinct look and atmosphere.<br/></li><li>Dialogues and an interactable environment.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2683490/extras/YF07Ge.gif?t=1704548994"><br/><br/><strong>IMPORTANT:<br/><br/>This game doesn't save your progress and is meant to be played in one sitting.<br/>Average playtime: ~30 minutes.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2683490/extras/muczc2.gif?t=1704548994"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost in the Void - Official Soundtrack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2723780/Lost_in_the_Void__Official_Soundtrack/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723780/extras/lostinthevoid_logo_steam_new.png?t=1704548897"><br/><br/>Dive into the evocative original soundtrack of "Lost in the Void," crafted by Milchomalefic &amp; Daniel Jackson for Nightcall studio's isometric pixel art adventure. Drawing inspiration from 80s RPG elements, the music complements the game's narrative, where you, a high school senior, grapple with an unsettling voice urging you down a mysterious path. Lucien Anemos' album art sets the visual tone for this haunting musical journey. Immerse yourself in a symphony of nostalgia and suspense as the soundtrack echoes the choices and challenges of the game.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost in the Void : Chapter One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2105610/Lost_in_the_Void__Chapter_One/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2105610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2105610/extras/lost_in_the_void_logo_gif.gif?t=1704549971"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in the mesmerizing realm of Lost in the Void —an enchanting isometric pixel art adventure skillfully interwoven with captivating RPG elements. Drawing inspiration from the cherished era of the 80s, this game is meticulously crafted to rekindle the enchantment of your childhood dreams. Lost in the Void unfolds as an episodic journey, akin to your beloved TV shows, with each episode released one at a time, promising a continuous tapestry of immersive storytelling and thrilling gameplay.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Embark on a Journey as a High School Senior</strong></h2><br/>Embark on a transformative journey as a high school senior in Lost in the Void. Amidst the bustling corridors of academia and the camaraderie of your tight-knit group of friends, an eerie voice begins to resonate within your mind. It beckons you toward an enigmatic and shadowy path, compelling you to confront a pivotal decision. Will you succumb to the allure of this mysterious force, or will you resist its persuasive influence, shaping your destiny in the process?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2105610/extras/bike_steam.jpg?t=1704549971"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge Unforgettable Bonds with Your Companions</strong></h2><br/>Throughout your enthralling expedition, you'll be accompanied by Martin, Sasha, and Aaron – your steadfast friends, each with their own distinct personalities that react dynamically to your choices. Depending on your decisions, their affections for you may blossom or wither away.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2105610/extras/fixed_buddies.png?t=1704549971"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Shape Your Character through Skill Distribution</strong></h2><br/>At the onset of the game, indulge in character creation where you allocate points into three primary skills – Fight, Tech, or Comms. These skill allocations will dictate how you navigate intricate dialogues, as combat is non-existent in this enthralling adventure. All in-game situations are resolved through a robust dialogue system, putting the power of choice firmly in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2105610/extras/fixed_various_npc.png?t=1704549971"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Unleash Your Imagination in a Narrative-Driven Experience</strong></h2><br/>Lost in the Void is an episodic captivating narrative-driven game that captures the essence of classic pen-and-paper RPG games and game-books. While our pixel art style sets the stage, the game's rich narration vividly paints a detailed picture of your surroundings, allowing your imagination to breathe life into every nook and cranny of this mesmerizing universe.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2105610/extras/dragonspeak_steam.png?t=1704549971"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chompania</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2734020/Chompania/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2734020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an out-of-this-world odyssey with Eddie, a stranded explorer trying to break free from the quirky landscapes of Chompania.<br>
<br>
Unravel the planet's secrets, solve perplexing riddles, and engage in encounters with the local wildlife. Each level is a cosmic challenge, blending the classic platformer fun and head-scratching puzzles.<br>
<br>
Will you outsmart the intergalactic enigmas that block your path, or will you be swept away by the weirdness of this alien world?<br>
<br>
The universe is counting on you to guide Eddie to freedom!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad-Draw</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2183790/BadDraw/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2183790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The unloved is erased, but the cultivated remains. Here are the old ones full of hate and these hate books. A long time passes, it increases so much that they start to control and our character is born with stubborn ambition.<br/><br/>This is a 2D platform game with competitive bosses and parkour mechanics. Defeating bosses gives the character new skills or mechanics.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2183790/extras/bdBeta.png?t=1704536042"><br/><br/>please note this game is in Beta before purchasing<br/><br/><strong>Bad Draw Beta available now</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">try my other game</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2269530/HaHa/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2269530/HaHa/</a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backrooms: Eight Levels</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2738420/Backrooms_Eight_Levels/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>An atmospheric horror game based on the popular internet creepypasta.</strong><br/><br/><strong>The game offers you a journey through a confusing maze of yellow rooms, endless dark corridors, abandoned offices and other dangerous places Backrooms. You will have to explore spaces that are hard to believe exist. It's hard to say who could have built such a thing and why.  There are eight different levels available for you to explore. Each level of this otherworld is fraught with danger, and no matter what surreal place you find yourself in, you have only one goal - to survive and find a way out. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738420/extras/1.gif?t=1704531612"><br/><br/><strong>One of the few descriptions we know of this mysterious place reads - "If you're not careful and noclip out of reality in the wrong areas, you'll end up in the Backrooms, where it's nothing but the stink of old moist carpet, the madness of mono-yellow, the endless background noise of fluorescent lights at maximum hum-buzz, and approximately six hundred million square miles of randomly segmented empty rooms to be trapped in. God save you if you hear something wandering around nearby, because it sure as hell has heard you.."</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738420/extras/2.gif?t=1704531612"><br/><br/><strong>In Backrooms you do need to be careful. Remember that you're just a guest here and you definitely shouldn't disturb the inhabitants of this place. The deeper you go into the backstage, the more creepy dangers will come your way.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738420/extras/3.gif?t=1704531612"><br/><br/><strong>Graphics, sounds, post effects, as well as character and entity animations are as close as possible to the original "Backrooms Found Footage" videos. All these visual solutions create the atmosphere of a realistic journey through the backstage.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738420/extras/4.gif?t=1704531612"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost In The Shadows</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2425090/Lost_In_The_Shadows/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2425090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Become the hero who will be the first to defeat the toughest enemies of the dungeon.<br/>Develop your character to become indestructible.<br/>You can gain levels, distribute points and upgrade your abilities.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic combat</strong><br/>In the game, combat is about using the right skills at the right times.<br/>If you do dodge in wrong time you will be hit.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2425090/extras/opis_00.png?t=1704513642"><br/><br/><strong>Huge amount of upgrades</strong><br/>You can develop your character through a huge number of upgrades.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2425090/extras/opis_001.png?t=1704513642"><br/><br/><strong>Easy to understand mechanics</strong><br/>The mechanics in the game are easy to understand, so you don't have to struggle with finding solutions.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hot Beaver Camp</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2511870/Hot_Beaver_Camp/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2511870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2511870/extras/MiniBannerSteam_Story.png?t=1704513289"><br/>You will take the role of Samantha Reynolds, who accepted a job as a counselor at a quiet and remote campsite in the woods, which is suddenly enveloped by overwhelming darkness, her counselor friends and camper children are lost, left at the mercy of stalking. of some strange creatures that ferociously besiege the place and will not stop until they are eliminated.<br/><br/>Will you be able to save the camper kids, your counselor friends, survive and escape with your life?<br/><br/>Hot Beaver Camp, is an RPG Action Game, a mixture of horror and action, with a hint of mystery that generates an immersive atmosphere.<br/><br/>"There is slight content of violence and blood, some textual insinuations of an adult nature, photosensitive people should be careful, as there are moments when flashes appear on the screen, which can be removed in the game options."<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2511870/extras/MiniBannerSteam_Features.png?t=1704513289"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple endings<br/></li><li>Story reset keeping level<br/></li><li>Images in pixel art<br/></li><li>Multiples characters to play<br/></li><li>Make a party or move alone<br/></li><li>Using Keyboard or Xbox Controller</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Memories</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2495450/Winter_Memories/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1704499222"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_1-EN.png?t=1704499222"><br/>After the unforgettable summer memories you’ve made half a year ago, Yui, Rio, and Miyuki are back. With the change of seasons and the cold falling snow, a new page to your story is about to begin. <br/><br/>Revisit the peaceful, seaside town, and spend time catching up with your family and friends.<br/><br/>What new memories will you make this winter?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_3-EN.png?t=1704499222"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Miyuki_EN.png?t=1704499222"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Rio_EN.png?t=1704499222"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Yui_EN.png?t=1704499222"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_4-EN.png?t=1704499222"><br/><strong>A Relaxing, Adventure RPG<strong><br/><br/><strong>Explore the Beautiful, Seaside Town<strong><br/><br/><strong>Manage How You Spend Your TIme<strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Night Heist</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2738840/The_Night_Heist/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Meet Mariah, Maria, and Missy a group of college girls from Whitson Community College, however like most people who attend college find themselves also working a part-time job trying to pay off their student loans and other bills.<br>
<br>
For Mariah, working part time at a shop wasn’t enough.<br>
She wanted more.<br>
More money to not only pay off her loans and bills but for other things she and the girls wanted.<br>
<br>
So Mariah and the girls take things into their own hands and began robbing houses at night.<br>
Calling it. The Night Heist.<br/>
<br/>
In this Visual Novel you will follow Mariah and her friends as they try to pull off the perfect heist. But it won't be as easy as you may think.<br/>
<br/>
(FREE DLC) Content: Includes another visual novel story following a girl name Grace who has a best friend name Hector who happens to have a crush on her. But Grace has a secret she hasn't told Hector. She's a God. <br/>
<br/>
But their way more to the story your gonna have to find out with CHOICE DECISIONS which may or may not affect Grace's life while you play.<br/>
Play (Grace) to find out what happens next.<br/>
<br/>
"This game is a visual novel based off the book series which shares the same title as the game."						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before Time Runs Out</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2724520/Before_Time_Runs_Out/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this modern twist on the 2D platform game, make your way through numerous traps and obstacles such as spikes, saws, laser beams and explosives to reach the goal at the end of each level. Each level has a limited time to complete. You can collect time orbs throughout the level to increase your time. But remember, speed is the key or it's game over.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724520/extras/Gif_1.gif?t=1704498369"><br/><br/><strong>Game Components</strong><br/>- Each Level Is Physics Based.<br/>- Speed Is Key.<br/>- Each Level Has A Limited Amount Of Time To Complete.<br/>- Momentum Is Vital To Reaching The End Of Each Level.<br/>- Over 60 Unique Levels.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724520/extras/Gif_2.gif?t=1704498369"><br/><br/><strong>Obstacles</strong><br/>- Spikes<br/>- Saws<br/>- Laser Beams<br/>- Explosives<br/>- Yourself<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724520/extras/Gif_3.gif?t=1704498369"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Spyroxo Adventures: Island of Dnfoo</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2089750/Super_Spyroxo_Adventures_Island_of_Dnfoo/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2089750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Classic side scroller arcade adventure retro 2d game "Super Spyroxo Adventures: Island of Dnfoo" . This game brings back memories of old school arcade games with numerous adventure. World of this game contains well designed levels, various enemies, bosses, simple gameplay, nice pixelart graphics fun music and sounds.<br>
<br>
On beautiful sunny day our hero Spyroxo Jack and his wife Jill were eating apples together and enjoying life and suddenly bad cavemen called "DNFOO" group appeared from deep jungles of the island. These evil mosters captured Jack's wife and ran away. Jack is on adventure to rescue his wife by defeating cavemen &amp; dinosaurs and teach them a lesson.<br>
<br>
To bring Spyroxo Jack's wife back he needs your help. Run ,shoot and jump through the different island environments, avoid traps, clear all enemies in your way and defeat all bosses. This game will give you classic feel with side scrolling view, with classic gameplay, simple yet beautiful pixelart graphics, easy and intuitive controls, many weapons to unlock, each level with unique graphics and epic boss battles.<br>
<br>
The game use Steam Leaderboard to save players scores, you can see it in the game community, so the high score you will see in the game is the top score found in that leaderboard, make sure to try to defeat that score with yours, the final boss will gives you 10000 score points if you can defeat it too, and once you have finished the game you can click on new game to restart and guess what, you can keep all the weapons you have unlocked even in very first level, so you can get a better score this time.<br/>
<br/>
Tips:<br/>
-please use a controller for a better game experience to be able to fast switch between weapons while you can jump and shoot.<br/>
-in the game click Esc then show help to see the buttons config						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Pressure: Hive War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2645650/No_Pressure_Hive_War/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><h2 class="bb_tag">No Pressure: Hive War</h2></strong><br/>This title is designed to reintroduce the element of fun in gaming, transporting players to an alternate reality where the world is on the brink of collapse.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645650/extras/Armada.png?t=1704492091"><h2 class="bb_tag">Pickups</h2><br/>Pickups provide the player with some much needed assistance during each wave to aid the player in possibly attaining victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645650/extras/Pickups.png?t=1704492091"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Modes</h2><br/>choose from three exciting game modes.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645650/extras/Game_Modes.png?t=1704492091"><br/>* Story mode: play through the waves of the enemy swarm to wave 50 where you get to test your metal against the hive ship.<br/>* Music mode: play through the 50 waves of the story mode in an invulnerable state, by being indestructible you can escape reality comfortably to just fly around and shoot robots while enjoying your playlist.<br/>* Endless mode: play through an endless number of waves collecting score to rank on the leaderboard and compete globally against other players to earn your place on top and the title of Earth's Greatest Defender!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645650/extras/Leader-Board.png?t=1704492091"><br/><br/>Conquer the Hive ship to add new ships to your arsenal.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645650/extras/Ships-Render_2.png?t=1704492091"><h2 class="bb_tag">Enhancements</h2><br/>Upgrades are earned from killing mini bosses which appear every five waves, <br/>these upgrade points can enhance your firepower, <br/>unlock your reflex ability or soften enemy damage and more.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645650/extras/Upgrade.png?t=1704492091"><h2 class="bb_tag">Integrated Music player</h2><br/>the integrated music player allows you to increase or decrease the volume of your music.<br/>skip or play previous song and play or pause your music during play. <br/>opening the music player also pauses the game giving you the time you need to make sure your ambience is just perfect without worry of losing to the plentiful AI swarm.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645650/extras/Music-Player.png?t=1704492091"><h2 class="bb_tag">Top-Down Perspective</h2><br/>The Top-down perspective allows you to confront multiple foes simultaneously, all while immersing yourself in this captivating universe as you battle not only for your own life but also for the survival of humanity as a whole.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645650/extras/Shot1.png?t=1704492091"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645650/extras/Shot2.png?t=1704492091"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645650/extras/Shot3.png?t=1704492091"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645650/extras/Shot4.png?t=1704492091"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645650/extras/Shot5.png?t=1704492091"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645650/extras/Shot6.png?t=1704492091"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lacey's Wardrobe</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2654760/Laceys_Wardrobe/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654760/extras/store_tittle.png?t=1704539340"><h2 class="bb_tag">Introduction</h2><br/>Some time ago, a YouTube channel called ghosttundra uploaded a video about a game called "Lacey's Wardrobe", and its strange plot went viral on the internet. Despite looking like a classic 2000s dress-up game, its appearance was nothing but deceptive.<br/>Its viewers were astonished and scoured the internet in search of a clue that would lead them to where to find this particular game, to no avail. Over time, it was discovered that this eerie game never existed, and that video was a fake gameplay created by the owner of that YouTube channel.<br/><br/>This fangame aims to recreate that analog horror for all the fans, lost-media enthusiasts, and curious individuals who still want to experience what "Lacey's Wardrobe" could have been in a game. All the art is recreated from scratch and mostly includes new content.<br/><br/>For information on how to unlock endings or other matters, you can do so through the Twitter account veratrumgames.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654760/extras/store_line.png?t=1704539340"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Story</h2><br/>Lacey is a very sociable and active girl, so much so that her schedule is filled with beautiful places to go to (Isn't that great?)<br/>Unfortunately, each place requires the right outfit, and that's too much responsibility for Lacey, she needs help.<br/>That's where you come in! Do you think you can choose the prettiest clothes for every occasion? Dress up Lacey and have unique moments with her!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654760/extras/store_line.png?t=1704539340"><h2 class="bb_tag">Character</h2> Lacey!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654760/extras/store_character.png?t=1704539340"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654760/extras/store_line.png?t=1704539340"><h2 class="bb_tag">Characteristics</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Sensational Strategy</li></ul>       Just as love is a serious matter, choosing which type of shoes go with that skirt is a matter of life or death. Think carefully about each outfit!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple Endings</li></ul>       If there's a variety of clothing, why shouldn't there be multiple endings? Play non-stop to discover all 6 endings!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A Charming Protagonist</li></ul>       Lacey will love that you're playing with her!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Unique Art and Soundtracks</li></ul>       Eye-catching colors and spectacular ambient music.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654760/extras/store_line.png?t=1704539340"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potato Arena: Multiplayer Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2585400/Potato_Arena_Multiplayer_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Fun and challenging minigames are waiting for you and your friends. Play and compete to destroy your friends in this unique collection of minigames. You can play local and online multiplayer. Against 3 of your friends! And offline against Bots. <br/>Customize your potato! Make yourself unique and show off to your friends.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585400/extras/MENTWL_SORUN.gif?t=1704490633"><br/><br/>WATERMILL: Beat your friends off the watermill. Slap them! Kick them! Be the last one standing.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585400/extras/YETR.gif?t=1704490633"><br/><br/>WATER WRESTLE: Try to throw your friends off the platform but be careful there is a windstorm coming.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585400/extras/AAAAAA.gif?t=1704490633"><br/><br/>FUNBALL: Classic football but with random powerup drops. Team up with your friends and try to score<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585400/extras/NEFRET.gif?t=1704490633"><br/><br/>CRAZY PAINTING: Beat your friends to the score, jump around and paint the tiles.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kill Ball</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626090/Kill_Ball/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome!<br/><br/>It's 1996, and the popular game show Killball is now in its third season. This high-stakes blood sport has gained more popularity than ever before! You can now enjoy all the fun of Killball in the comfort of your own home with your friends and family.<br/><br/>Players find themselves in an Arena resembling the game PONG, <br/>Scoring the ball will grant the player <strong>one </strong>Explosive Bullet <br/><br/>Be careful, though, as players can only hold one bullet in their rifle at a time. Getting killed by the KillBall or Player results in you losing your bullet <br/>so make your shots count <br/><br/>The first player to get three Kills Wins the game <br/><br/>Control the Pong paddles and player at the same time, use the controller triggers to move the Pong paddle up and down, and <br/>the analog sticks to control the player in the arena <br/><br/><strong><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Use Steam Remote Play to play online with your friends  </li></ul></strong><br/><br/><strong>The game only supports Local multiplayer. </strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Move players freely across the arena play area. <br/><br/></li><li>top-down with 360 degrees of aiming </li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Keep track of Win/loss count at the end of each game  </li></ul> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Experiance a game that feels like rubbing your belly and patting your head at the same time   </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><strong>Controllers Required. </strong><br/><br/><strong>A mouse will be needed to navigate some menus.</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adventure Trip: Amazing World 3 Collector's Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748020/Adventure_Trip_Amazing_World_3_Collectors_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Let's continue our journey of the Amazing World, round the globe from the Big Ben of London to the vibrant windmills, Kinderdijk of Netherlands, from the exquisite Fort Amber, India to the natural habitat, Kakadu National Park, Australia. From the Heavenly Aurora lights, Greenland to the Monuments Valley of the United States.<br>
<br>
As the game unfolds, you are presented with 8 mini puzzles with lots of levels which will add to the fun and give you a little break from fact-finding. <br>
<br>
•	Collector Edition include, 14 extra locations.<br>
•	60 amazing facts to find<br>
•	Explore 20 locations of The World<br/>
•	Collect 15 unique items for your treasure<br/>
•	5 Modes – Word, Silhouette, Scrambled Word, Missing Vowels, Finding Pairs						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Skirmish</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2718210/The_Skirmish/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2718210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Play The Skirmish with your friends on LAN as one of two teams, score enough points to win.<br/><br/>In this game you will find:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Three types of weapons. <br/></li><li> First aid kits to restore health. <br/></li><li> Create a server in the local network, or connect to an already created one. <br/></li><li> Collect points to win. <br/></li><li> Fight for one of the two commands.<br/></li><li> Realistic graphics and numerous related settings to optimize graphics for your computer.<br/><br/>Plans for the future:<br/></li><li> Add FSR support.<br/></li><li> Add new levels and game modes.<br/></li><li> Add support for different languages.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivery Impossible</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2335550/Delivery_Impossible/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2335550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Delivery Impossible is an arcade truck driving simulator spiced with fun and a little bit of madness.<br/><br/>Tom's life and career were perfect: he could easily take the most expensive and interesting delivery orders. But one day everything changed: new "effective" managers fired him after 20 years of hard work. In order to stay afloat, Tom decided to start his own delivery company. Now he is forced to take on the most bizarre, ridiculous and crazy jobs: how about getting a group of tipsy tourists who can't help but fall off the bus all the way to the fair? Easy, I can do it with my eyes shut! A bunch of dynamites with a lit fuse? Without blinking an eye! A UFO? Nothing is impossible if you love your job!<br/><br/>Delivery Impossible features:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>10 different levels and cargo types;<br/></li><li>Multiple vehicle types, from a small sedan to heavy trucks;<br/></li><li>A varied soundtrack.</li></ul><br/>Immerse yourself in the world of Delivery Impossible and see for yourself what it is all about - real drive, fun and madness!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Touch My Phone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2729710/Dont_Touch_My_Phone/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729710/extras/Final_Render_1.gif?t=1704539444"><br/><br/>"Don't Touch My Phone" is not just your ordinary 2D side-scrolling platform adventure—it's a hilarious escapade that follows the misadventures of a six-year-old boy desperately trying to connect with his crush, Susan. The catch? He's phoneless! To chat with Susan, he must sneak into other people's phones, but it's anything but easy. These digital devices are fortified with guns, wires, bombs, mines, nukes, and heavy weapons, turning each level into a wacky obstacle course.<br/><br/>The game revels in its intentional silliness, throwing absurd challenges at our pint-sized hero. Your mission, should you choose to accept it, is to use your smarts to navigate this ludicrous landscape, outwit the phone defenses, and win Susan's heart. Can you help the boy overcome these comically exaggerated obstacles? Brace yourself for a laughter-filled adventure that's as funny as it is tricky! Get ready to dive into a world where the absurd meets the amusing, and where the journey to romance is anything but conventional!<br/><br/>.............................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729710/extras/Glitch_01.gif?t=1704539444"><br/>..............................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729710/extras/Heavy_Weapons.gif?t=1704539444"><br/>..............................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729710/extras/And_More.gif?t=1704539444"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/>* Discover a world worth exploring. Run, climb, dash, and glide as you immerse yourself in a virtual world. Each level is meticulously designed to transport you inside your own phone, enabling you to playfully manipulate its elements. Picture yourself navigating through a digital realm, solving brain-teasing missions, and outsmarting quirky obstacles—all while enjoying a healthy dose of laugh-out-loud humor.<br/><br/>* Speak the language of the phone, allowing you to communicate with and address everything as if it were a living entity within the device. However, be wary—your phone elements have turned into real enemies and obstacles against you, transforming each level into a challenging battleground where wit and strategy are your best allies for you to get your charge back.<br/><br/>* Susan will send text messages while you are playing that can either help you on your journey or bring it to a sudden stop. Pay attention to her messages as they can shape the outcome of your gameplay!<br/><br/>* The player's secret weapon for survival? Just their foot! They can stomp, run, avoid traps, open doors, and even destroy enemies—with the power of their feet, they kick their way through challenges and emerge victorious!<br/><br/>* An additional weapon in the player's arsenal is the umbrella, helping them glide through the air and overcome gravity's attempts to bring them down.<br/><br/>* And more .....						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
