<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Milo and the Christmas Gift</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2716140/Milo_and_the_Christmas_Gift/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							After his adventure in Milo and the Magpies, Milo is looking forward to spending a cosy Christmas at home. But a Christmas gift is about to upset his holiday celebrations, especially when said gift disappears after a little misunderstanding! Can you help Milo bring home the lost Gift and save Christmas for Marleen… and himself?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_playing_1.gif?t=1703496663"> <br/><br/>Milo and the Christmas Gift is a free-to-play short and atmospheric point-and-click adventure game created by artist Johan Scherft. The game is a spin-off story following the events in Milo and the Magpies. The game has 5 chapters and a gameplay time of around 30 minutes!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/>■ Relaxing yet stimulating game-play<br/>Join Milo in his home and revisit some of the neighbouring gardens, but this time in a wintery Christmas wonderland! Interact with the festive environment and solve small point-and-click / hidden-object puzzles.<br/><br/>■ Captivating artistic atmosphere<br/>Each hand-painted, interior and snowy garden Milo has to search through has its unique personality, reflecting that of Milo’s owners and next-door neighbours respectively.<br/><br/>■ Atmospheric soundtrack<br/>Each chapter has its own festive theme song composed by Victor Butzelaar.<br/><br/>■ Average playtime: 15-30 minutes<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_snow_1.gif?t=1703496663"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few Nights More: Genesis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713070/Few_Nights_More_Genesis/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Please note: This is a free prologue and it includes act 1, and only 1 playable character and blood school is playable, The maximum heritage gained is limited to 50, and the maximum difficulty can be set to 2. As well only one castle will be available. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Blood3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Conquer castles and claim your birthright!</strong><br/> <br/>The fight to reclaim your place in this world begins. Rebuild lost ruins, make them stronger and defend them against your enemies. After you regain your strength, move on to conquer more territories and eventually claim your birthright.<br/><br/>Few Nights More offers the unique fusing of castle management and turn based rogue-like combat. Fight against humanity, the undisputed masters of this world in your absence. Choose between eight different Vampire Lords, each with their own ambition and history. Find your trinkets, skills and perks along your way. Design your very own castle by placing the right rooms, adding decors that directly contribute to your army and your Vampire Lord. Conquer more castles so your influence and power grow, until you claim your birthright.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Ferocity3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Core Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Design your castle by adding new Rooms, Traps and Minions. Stack up on some buffs with shiny decors to get ready for the invasion screen to defend it to the end of every night!<br/> <br/></li><li> Choose among 7 different Vampire Lords with unique History, Gameplay and Abilities.<br/> <br/></li><li> Master 1 out of 3 Disciplines each time you play, each with 60 unique skills.<br/> <br/></li><li> Acquire new random skills, perks and trinkets to survive the nights.<br/> <br/></li><li> Excel in either being a Prestigious Vampire, a Seductive one, or master a Terrifying presence against your enemies.<br/><br/></li><li> Test the builds you made against a variety of Hunters, Veterans and Unique Bosses in an action packed turn based combat system.<br/> <br/></li><li> Endure three acts across 12 difficulty levels, striving to survive and progress. Accumulate Heritage Points to enhance your lord's starting stats, skills, and unlock new castles and talents unique to each lord.<br/><br/></li><li> Engage in the boundless challenge of Infinity Mode, where you can continuously test your limits without relying on a castle. Each night, you will be presented with three options to advance, growing stronger as you push yourself to see how far you can go.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703868247"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1702674942"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1702674942"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1703400171"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1703400171"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1703493452"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1703493452"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1703186631"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1703318086"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1703318086"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1702747783"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobalt Core</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2179850/Cobalt_Core/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_1.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>Cobalt Core is a sci-fi roguelike deckbuilder with a unique single-axis combat system that will throw you for a loop. Many loops! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_2.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>Give orders to your crew by playing cards: Will you <strong>raise shields</strong> to protect your ship, <strong>dodge</strong> incoming missiles and cannon fire to avoid damage outright, or <strong>strike</strong> preemptively to disable your enemy’s weapons? Outmaneuver your foes to stay just ahead of impending calamity, and reach the Cobalt Core!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/characters.png?t=1703278835"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fresh new spin on tactics –</strong>  dodge attacks and target weak points in this unique single-axis take on tactics combat. Outwit the enemy in a high stakes game of cat and mouse!<br/></li><li><strong>Customize your deck –</strong> hundreds of cards and split upgrade paths means no two runs will be the same. Find that perfect combo that brings your deck from powerful to overpowered.<br/></li><li><strong>Get to know your crew –</strong> each character comes with a completely unique playstyle and their own personal story. Bring 3 along, mix and match their decks, and see how these little goobers get along with each other.<br/></li><li><strong>Tons of replayability –</strong>  hundreds of different character+ship combinations before you even hit “start run”. Crank up the difficulty and really test your skills!<br/></li><li><strong>Get in the groove –</strong> featuring 90+ minutes of catchy and electrifying original music by <i>Minecraft</i> composer Aaron Cherof!<br/></li><li><strong>Forward momentum –</strong> untangle a narrative and unlock more playstyles as you go. Is there any escape from this time loop?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/grandma_cookies.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>By the makers of <i>Sunshine Heavy Industries</i>, recipient of IGF's <strong>Honorable Mention for Excellence in Design 2022</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1702627749"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658820/Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							10 possible fruits and one goal, reach the Watermelon.<br/>Your job is to combine matching fruits to evolve them to the next one and eventually reach the coveted Watermelon.<br/>To help you, you have 3 different abilities at your disposal. But watch out, using these will cost you some of your points. Be smart about when you use them to get the highest score!<h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLAYER</h2>Measure your fruit skills against another player.<h2 class="bb_tag">GET THE WATERMELON</h2>How many Watermelons can you combine before your basket overflows?<h2 class="bb_tag">USE YOUR ABILITIES</h2>Power, level up and destroy — These abilities will help you reach the Watermelon, using any of those will also allow you to angle your aim.<h2 class="bb_tag">GOLDEN FRUIT</h2>If luck is on your side, you might even see the mysterious Golden Fruit. Find it and witness its effect firsthand.<h2 class="bb_tag">STATISTICS</h2>Track your progress with in-depth statistics. Visit the menu to see the number of fruits you've combined, your ability usage, and much more.<h2 class="bb_tag"></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.codecks.io%2Fwatermelon-game" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/extras/Roadmap_Banner.png?t=1702238677"/></a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football Manager 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2252570/Football_Manager_2024/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2252570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a real boss and write your own football story in Football Manager 2024, the most complete edition in the series yet. <br/><br/>Whether you’re a manager who likes to build from the bottom or prefers to chase immediate glory, the perfect challenge awaits. The arrival of the new Meiji Yasuda Insurance Ltd J. League licence unlocks J1 League, J2 League, J3 League for the first time ever, giving you the opportunity to explore new horizons in Japan.<br/><br/>Wherever you manage, it's up to you to build a team capable of competing with the world's elite.<br/><br/><strong>Game Description </strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Continue your relentless journey to the top of the footballing world by using the new ability to import your existing career from Football Manager 2023.<br/></li><li>Craft a winning tactical approach, incorporating modern football’s most popular systems and cutting-edge positional innovations to deliver victories on the pitch. <br/></li><li>Master the transfer market, using new ways to shape your side to cultivate a squad capable of achieving your goals. <br/></li><li>Level up your players on the training field, developing the mentality and teamwork needed to transform contenders into champions. <br/></li><li>See your tactical vision come to life on Matchdays, with every game elevated by improvements to ball and player movements.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">NEW FOR THIS SEASON</h2><br/><br/><strong>TRUER FOOTBALL MOTION</strong><br/><br/>Enhancements to player animations, ball physics and lighting deliver the most immersive Match Engine in Football Manager history. Move to the cutting edge of football by using the new Inverted Full-Back player role, while more intelligent player rotational movements add more fluidity to every highlight. <br/><br/><strong>DOMINATE FROM SET PIECES</strong><br/><br/>Make an impact at both ends of the pitch with an overhauled Set Piece Creator. Lean on the expertise of brand-new Set Piece Coaches to develop winning routines in every scenario that will help you to outsmart your rivals. <br/><br/><strong>BRACE FOR TRANSFER BATTLES</strong><br/><br/>Showcase your squad-building skills in our most refined transfer market yet. You’ll face a trickier battle for talent as your rival opposition managers are now more strategic than ever in their recruitment decision-making. <br/><br/><strong>NEW AGENTS TO BUILD A DREAM SQUAD</strong><br/><br/>Better shape your perfect squad with the introduction of new Intermediaries that will help you offload surplus players for a cut of the final transfer fee. Additional functionality for existing Agents and the debut of TransferRoom, a football marketplace for transfers in real life, gives you more real-world powered tools than ever to build an elite team and dominate the competition.<br/><br/><strong>ELEVATE PERFORMANCES WITH TARGETS</strong><br/><br/>Motivate your team to achieve more on and off the field by setting them individual Targets. Whether you’re focusing on goals scored in a season or average training performances, challenge your star players and top prospects to maximise their ability. <br/><br/><strong>A HOST MORE ADDITIONS</strong><br/><br/>Enjoy greater variety in every career with the arrival of two new game modes. Real World mirrors when players actually joined your club. Your World sets club squads and budgets at the day your career starts, meaning that only players who joined before that date will be in your squad, giving you the opportunity to rewrite your team’s transfer window.<br/><br/>Elsewhere, you can look to dominate international management and plan for your country's future with a revamped National Pool that gives you a better overview of the talent at your disposal. Match preparation and briefing meetings deliver you winning insights before each fixture. <br/><br/>That’s not all though, with many more changes waiting for you to discover in every career.<br/><br/><i>This version contains information that is still under approval process by rights holders and may contain data that does not, at this time, accurately reflect real world data. For context, some club and player assets may be absent during this version.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EA SPORTS™ WRC</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1849250/EA_SPORTS_WRC/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1849250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build the car of your dreams in our biggest rally game ever, EA SPORTS™ WRC, the all-new official videogame of the FIA World Rally Championship, the first developed by the award-winning team behind the DiRT Rally series.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1849250/extras/WCR_GameFeatures_PostLaunch.jpg?t=1702998175"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For The King II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1676840/For_The_King_II/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/header_alt_assets_7.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_AboutThisGame_Steam_StoreBanner_2_EN.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Once beloved by her people, Queen Rosomon has turned against her subjects, casting them into servitude in the darkness of Fahrul’s mines whilst building alliances with sinister and malevolent forces.<br/><br/>Gather your party in four player co-op or adventure alone through Fahrul as you risk everything to fight the tyrannical queen and bring an end to her oppressive reign.<br/><br/>From the creators of For The King, the much-loved RPG that blends roguelite and tabletop gameplay comes a new chapter in Fahrul’s history, designed on an updated engine bringing innovation and gameplay refinement for returning heroes and new adventurers alike.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading01_Inspired_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>For The King II is easy for anyone to pick up and play, but takes skill, patience, and strategic excellence to master whilst remaining infinitely replayable with a procedurally generated map that ensures no two playthroughs will ever be the same. Unique yet familiar dice roll inspired movement, encounter and combat mechanics add even more spontaneity and variety as your fortunes rise and fall on the roll of the dice.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF01_InspiredByTabletop.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading02_Digestible2_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>For The King II provides a complete campaign with over 30 hours of gameplay, split into 5 separate adventures, each narratively linked. The journey is long and the path is treacherous but fear not, if your party fails you will start stronger and wiser on your next playthrough with better starting items to draft into your loadout.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF02_RogueliteCampaign.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading03_Muster_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Create your party from 12 unique character classes, each with their own unique perks, strengths and playstyles. From the heavy-handed hitter of The Blacksmith, to the wily potion-wielding Alchemist, you choose which characters will take on the fearsome Queensguard and the combat strategies that will ensure success. Introduce new characters to your party with mercenaries and companions that enable you to pluck wild beasts from the forest floor and recruit ruthless mercenaries from local taverns (for a price of course) to bolster your ranks in times of trouble.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF03_MusterYouMight_.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading04_Party_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Traverse Fahrul solo or with up-to three friends in four-player co-op. As a solo player you can control all characters in your party, giving you complete ownership of the campaign map and combat strategy whilst in four-player co-op you must coordinate and negotiate with your party members. Play online multiplayer with your friends controlling your own character(s) or play offline co-op on the same PC. Offline co-op supports multiple controllers; each controller will have input control on everyone’s turn.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF04_PartyofFour.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading05_Evolved_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Inspired by turn-based classics, For The King II adds strategic depth to much-loved combat mechanics with the new Battle Grid, where movement and position provide you and your enemies with strategic buffs and penalties. Defend the back row by equipping a mighty Tower Shield, push enemies into lethal pools of burning fire, or entangle melee troops with dark magic cast with weapons looted from vanquished foes. The choice is yours!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF05_EvolveTurnBased.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_StorePageHeading06_Explore_ENGLISH.png?t=1703284946"><br/><br/>Fahrul is both beautiful and deadly in equal measure. On your journey you will encounter a wealth of diverse biome environments brought to life in a breathtaking art style. From lush forests, toxic swamps and lava-filled wastelands to pirate (no scratch that!) Merling-infested tropical seas, For The King II transports you deep into the wonders of Fahrul, leading you further than ever before into this stunningly-imagined land of adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTKII_Steam_GIF06_ExploreFantastical.gif?t=1703284946"><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Ffortheking" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676840/extras/FTK_Discord_Banner_EN.gif?t=1703284946"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoboCop: Rogue City</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1681430/RoboCop_Rogue_City/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FGzNdTVQAs6" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/ROBOCOP_ROGUE_CITY_BANNER_DISCORD_615x195px_EN.jpg?t=1701074570"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif01_EN.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif02_EN.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Description_Banner01_EN.png?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif03_EN.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Description_Banner02_EN.png?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Gif04_EN_V1.gif?t=1701074570"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1681430/extras/Robocop_Rogue_City_Basegame_Steam_Description_Banner03_EN.png?t=1701074570"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitler My Friend</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674580/Hitler_My_Friend/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the absurd world of <strong>Hitler My Friend</strong> - a 3D shooter that will change your ideas about alternative history! In this game you will climb into the boots of the unforeseen Adolf Hitler and go in search of the last representative of the Ururi race.<br/><br/>Lost in an underwater laboratory surrounded by ruthless communists, Hitler must fight his way through waves of dark humor and destroy all the Gomorites in his path. Go deep under the water, where dangers await in the form of Soviet sea dolphins and various traps.<br/><br/>Immerse yourself in this absurd underwater world where humor becomes a weapon and Hitler is a failed hero in search of an exotic race. Mixing dark humor with madness, <strong>Hitler My Friend</strong> promises a unique and unpredictable experience that definitely stands out in the sea of shooters on Steam<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674580/extras/Новая_папка_2023.11.21_-_18.42.14.01.gif?t=1703935874"><br/><br/><strong>What awaits you in the game:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Lots of dangerous, funny, absurd enemies;<br/></li><li>Lots of funny and dangerous traps (Boom and you're gone)<br/></li><li>Play as the most legendary character HITLER!<br/></li><li>Lots of Easter eggs and references (with humor, of course)<br/></li><li>Communist boss, iron and dangerous with a secret weapon (good luck :D)<br/></li><li>Horror elements where you never thought</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little Nemo</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2722230/Little_Nemo/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Little Nemo is back in this new Adventure. He helps him to find the Secret Keys to another Dimension.<br/><br/>Can you help him to find the Keys on this mysterious and magical Journey to a New Magic World?<br/>Rush throught the Space before the Time runs out.<br/><br/>This game is inspired by the Little Nemo original Winsor McCay comics stripes from 1900,s New York and the modern 80,s tale written by Gilles Villeneuve, The Wicked World.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>For fans of 2D Open World and Puzzle Metroidvanias.<br/></li><li>Maze Runner like game, explore, find and talk to secret Characters to acess secret Areas.<br/></li><li>Multiple endings, cinematic, story driven and non linear.<br/></li><li>Short game, about 2 hours.<br/></li><li>Not an Action Combat, but Puzzle Exploration focused.<br/></li><li>Amazing graphics and sound.<br/></li></ul><br/>Little Nemo is a 2D Open World game inspired on the very good retro genre titles. <br/><br/>Talk, Run, Explore. Find secret passages and characters and discover a Fantasy World full of Magic and Color. <br/><br/>Little Nemo is a modern Maze Runner Adventure. <br/><br/>Can you find the Keys before your Time runs out?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wicked Wreck</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2442640/Wicked_Wreck/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2442640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Wicked Wreck meets The Dreamworld in this new Adventure. He helps the Wicked Wizard to find the Mistery Golden Key and discover the secrets fields of a Wicked World. <br/><br/>Can you find The Golden Key on this mysterious and magical Journey to the Final Gate?<br/>Rush throught the Space before the Time runs out.<br/><br/>This game is inspired by the 80,s tale written by Gilles Villeneuve, Wicked Wreck.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>For fans of 2D Open World and Puzzle Plataformers Metroidvanias.<br/></li><li>Maze Runner like game, explore, find and talk to secret Characters to acess secret Areas.<br/></li><li>Multiple endings, cinematic, story driven and non linear.<br/></li><li>Short game, about 1 hour.<br/></li><li>Not an Action Combat, but Puzzle Exploration focused.<br/></li><li>Amazing graphics and sound.<br/></li></ul><br/>Wicked Wreck  is a 2D Open World game inspired on the very good Puzzle Metroidvania genre titles. <br/><br/>Talk, Run, Fly, Dash, Explore. Find secret passages and characters and discover a Fantasy World full of Mistery. <br/><br/>Wicked Wreck is a modern Maze Runner Adventure. <br/><br/>Can you find the Key before your Time runs out?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Jump</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2704260/Tiny_Jump/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2704260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							So what is Tiny Jump all about?<br>
Tiny Jump is a first person precision platformer,<br>
The main goal of the game is to climb all the way to the top while facing difficult types of jumps &amp; challenges,<br>
Tiny Jump is for those who are looking for difficult and challenging gameplay.<br>
The Controls are easy &amp; handy to use<br>
&amp; The mechanic is simple, <br>
Tiny Jump Is a simple game that focus only on the actual gameplay,<br>
the game is difficult &amp; The higher you climb, the more difficult and challenging it becomes.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polite animals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2734340/Polite_animals/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2734340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a highly challenging casual relaxation game.<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
This is a fast dodge type game.<br>
<br>
The ball will continue to move forward, and you need to manipulate it to avoid upcoming obstacles.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Send the ball home, avoid numerous obstacles, and accumulate wealth by obtaining diamonds on the way. In the game, you will play as a brave little ball, facing various complex obstacles and traps. Through flexible finger sliding operations, you need to constantly jump, turn, and roll to avoid falling or hitting obstacles. The exquisite graphics and beautiful sound effects of the game will immerse you in it and experience new gaming fun.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Challenge yourself, push your limits, and become a king! Come and experience this challenging game.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ant secret</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2736110/Ant_secret/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2736110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a tower defense game with simple game modes, strong playability, and endless fun. <br>
It is a competition of intelligence and strategy. The ancient European style, fresh content, innovative creativity, and comprehensive store skill system all give people a refreshing feeling. <br>
In the game, you can also freely switch perspectives, making you feel like God, taking in all the details of the battlefield. It can also switch to a flat perspective, allowing you to see the enemy's attack route clearly, making it easier to adjust defense strategies. <br>
The enemy marched along a fixed route, with many platforms set up along the way, and strategies can be adjusted at each platform. You can set up guards or attack devices, depending on your strategy.<br>
 Your goal is to defeat the enemies along the way with reasonable mechanism arrangements and achieve the final victory.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raven Fighter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2699580/Raven_Fighter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2699580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Raven Fighter is a new classic shoot 'em roguelite game with endless maps, a rich weapon system, and the challenge to defeat the ultimate boss within 30 minutes.<br>
Features:<br>
- Automatic attacks and directional movement to evade enemies.<br>
- Choose from 6 characters, each with unique attribute<br>
- Play for 30 minutes to achieve the victory.<br>
- Hundreds of weapons to choose.<br>
- Defeat numerous enemies to gain experience and acquire weapons.<br/>
- Endless map system, allowing free flight, and unexpected rewards for destroying asteroids.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>妖变速递Mutant Express</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2561330/Mutant_Express/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2561330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> What kind of work is this? </strong><br/><br/>Retro Pixel Platform Jump Game<br/><br/>It tells the story of a pair of good friends who, in order to survive in the plagued city, unfortunately become orcs due to illness. They search for an antidote to save themselves and their friends.<br/><br/>Receive clues for delivering goods. Each delivery has a different level or encounters a boss. After completing the task on time, you will receive rewards.<br/><br/><strong> What should I do if I encounter a problem? </strong><br/><br/>You can provide feedback on the issues you have encountered, either in the Steam comments section or by joining the trial QQ group, and provide your valuable feedback. Thank you, this is crucial for us.<br/><br/>QQ group number: 874292403<br/><br/>Welcome to try it out<br/><br/>Developers<br/>BGM/bgs:乌鸦Producer<br/>art：ninety-nine<br/>programmer：绝命面包						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Molly the Werezompire</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2677800/Molly_the_Werezompire/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Finding a magical portal to another world? Cool! Being killed soon upon arrival? Not cool. Turning into a Werezompire (Werewolf + Zombie + Vampire) and gaining amazing power? Very cool! Embarking on an interactive story with many different paths &amp; endings? Totally awesome!<br>
<br>
Molly the Werezompire is back! Originally released on Xbox Live Indie Games, this classic text-based interactive novel from 2009 is now available on Steam! Experience Molly's original story, before she made cameos in other Zeboyd RPGs.<br>
<br>
This game also includes the sci-fi parody, Epiphany in Spaaace! Both games have been lovingly ported, with new backgrounds, editing, music, and more.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100% Orange Juice - Character Song Pack: Star Baker Breaker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2727920/100_Orange_Juice__Character_Song_Pack_Star_Baker_Breaker/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2727920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							It's time to burn it all up! The third official Character Song Pack for 100% Orange Juice contains the Star Breaker character song "Star Baker Breaker" in 5 different versions!<br>
<br>
Tracks are included in both .mp3 and .WAV versions.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Leave</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2737320/Dont_Leave/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2737320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><u>Don't Leave Story</u></strong><br/><br/>Once upon a time, in a small town nestled between mist-covered mountains, there lived a wise and just judge named Justice Harlan. He was renowned for his fair decisions and unwavering commitment to justice. However, his life took a bizarre turn when he found himself at the center of an otherworldly mystery that would shake the foundations of his beliefs.<br/><br/>One gloomy evening, after a particularly long day in the courtroom, Judge Harlan retired to his quaint cottage on the outskirts of town. Unbeknownst to him, a group of paranormal beings had been observing him from the shadows. These beings, ethereal and mysterious, were fascinated by the concept of human justice and intrigued by the power wielded by the judge.<br/><br/>As the clock struck midnight, the paranormal beings decided to make their presence known. The room filled with an eerie glow as they materialized before Judge Harlan. They were beings of light and shadow, with eyes that sparkled like stars. The judge, initially startled, quickly composed himself and demanded an explanation for their intrusion.<br/><br/>The leader of the paranormal beings, a being with a voice like a gentle breeze, spoke to Judge Harlan. "We have been watching your pursuit of justice, and we are both curious and impressed. We have decided to challenge your understanding of justice and morality."<br/><br/>Judge Harlan, ever the rationalist, was skeptical but intrigued. The paranormal beings presented him with a series of perplexing cases that transcended the boundaries of human understanding. These cases involved supernatural elements, moral quandaries, and cosmic dilemmas that pushed the judge's intellect to its limits.<br/><br/>As the days turned into weeks, Judge Harlan found himself engrossed in these otherworldly trials. The paranormal beings, pleased with his thoughtful deliberations, continued to present increasingly complex scenarios. The judge's reputation in the human realm suffered as he spent more time with the paranormal beings, neglecting his duties and responsibilities.<br/><br/>Word of the judge's strange behavior spread throughout the town, and the once-admired figure became an object of suspicion and fear. The townspeople, unable to comprehend the supernatural nature of his trials, believed he had made a pact with dark forces.<br/><br/>One fateful day, the paranormal beings, satisfied with the judge's growth and wisdom, vanished as mysteriously as they had appeared. Left alone and abandoned, Judge Harlan returned to his duties in the human realm, but the damage was done. The townspeople, unable to understand the cosmic trials he had faced, continued to view him with distrust and disdain.<br/><br/>And so, Justice Harlan lived out his days haunted by the memories of the paranormal trials, forever marked by an otherworldly encounter that had cost him the respect of his community. The story of the judge's abandonment by paranormal beings became a cautionary tale in the town, a reminder that the pursuit of justice could sometimes lead one down a path that transcends the boundaries of the known and the unknown.<br/><br/><strong><u>Features:</u></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2737320/extras/1.gif?t=1703878559"><br/>- You can eliminate your fear, at least a little, with interactive household items.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2737320/extras/2.gif?t=1703878559"><br/>- It's completely up to you to get out of this place. Solve all the locked codes and find a way out of the house.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2737320/extras/3.gif?t=1703878559"><br/>- Solving passwords will not be as easy as you think. You will need to find clues hidden inside the house and the passwords needed to exit.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2737320/extras/4.gif?t=1703878559"><br/>- Use the equipment you have with caution. At least they need some energy. You will need to extend the time you stay lit by finding the batteries hidden inside the house. The only way out of this house is light.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2737320/extras/5.gif?t=1703878559"><br/>- Not all doors will open easily. Therefore, you will need to open the doors by trying different methods.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2737320/extras/6.gif?t=1703878559"><br/>- Leaving the house will not be easy for you. There will be a secret room behind the visible and clues to complete your password.<br/><br/><br/><strong><u>Summary of the Game;</u></strong><br/>In this game, in which you play the role of the kidnapped judge, many psychological difficulties await you, and despite all this, you try to solve the puzzles and escape from this magical house.<br/><br/><br/><strong><u>Warning:</u></strong><br/><br/>Any mistake you make may cause you to restart the game. You need to search all the rooms one by one to solve all the passwords and escape from this cursed house.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elfin Around</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2723900/Elfin_Around/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this immersive game, you get to play as one of Santa's elves.<br>
<br>
You are in charge of the production line, so it is in your hands to produce the prettiest, most unique toys for children all over the world!<br>
<br>
Grab a core, put some limbs to it however you like, and choose a box to fit it in! Once you have your box, you can choose its color too!<br>
<br>
Don't forget to place it in Santa's sledge!<br/>
<br/>
Put on your VR headset and step in this immersive experience, where you get to use your hands to grab and place all sorts of arms and legs to your toy, even wings! <br/>
<br/>
Once you are happy with your creation, it'll be analyzed so you can choose the best box to wrap it in, but be careful, a wrong kind of box will result in a piece of coal!<br/>
<br/>
As your gift is ready to be delivered, you will have to throw it onto Santa's sledge yourself! (Just don't forget to customize the colors of your box).						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spellbound Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2602450/Spellbound_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602450/extras/1.png?t=1703874885"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself deeply in a pixelated realm where each map unfolds before your eyes as pages of an epic tale, facing off against the formidable Overlord Wizard, who commands vast hordes of soul reapers.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602450/extras/2.png?t=1703874885"><br/><br/>With every map you conquer, unlock a treasure trove of new abilities and powers, enabling you to unleash devastating attacks. As you continue to grow in strength and skill, transform into an indomitable force of nature, capable of bending the very elements to your will.<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay Tips</strong><br/><br/>1. Collect experience and items; they serve as your strategic cards.<br/>2. Strengthen and level up your weapons for increased effectiveness.<br/>3. Customize weapons through diverse upgrade paths for tactical advantage.<br/>4. Upgrade and refund power-ups to optimize your combat strategy.<br/>5. Experience thrilling animated <strong>super attacks</strong> that deliver goosebumps in the heat of battle.<br/><br/><br/>The excitement doesn't end there!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602450/extras/BannerGif2.gif?t=1703874885"><br/><br/>Spellbound Survivors promises more than just thrilling battles; it represents a system called the <strong>Legend Bar</strong> meter, a decisive factor in overcoming the Overlord Wizard. Choose your moves wisely, fill the meter strategically, and ascend as the ultimate survivor in the magical realms.<br/><br/><strong>Are you ready to turn the pages of destiny?</strong><br/><br/>The time has come to answer its call and embrace the spellbinding battle that awaits!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Station 5</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735060/Station_5/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an underground subway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully and take the correct trains to reach the 'Station 5' and exit the subway.<h2 class="bb_tag">GAME LOOP</h2><br/><strong>You start at Station 0, waiting for trains.<br/>When each train arrives, get on that train and inspect it to see if you can find any anomalies inside.<br/><br/>If you find any anomalies, leave that train and wait on the station for the next train.<br/>If you don't find any anomalies, take that train to the next station.<br/><br/>If you take the train with anomaly, that train will take you back to Station 0.<br/>If you take the train without any anomaly, that train will take you to the next station.<br/><br/>Take the correct trains to reach 'Station 5', where you will have the exit available.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">ANOMALIES</h2><br/>Inspect each arriving train to identify any anomalies by observing the specific order of items inside. If anything appears odd or strange, consider it as an anomaly.<br/>Examples of anomalies include things like objects that have moved, the sudden appearance of extra items, or the unexplained disappearance of something on the train at the station.<h2 class="bb_tag">SPOT THE DIFFERENCE</h2><br/>The Station 5 is a short walking simulator inspired by the 'spot the difference' games and liminal spaces (backrooms).<h2 class="bb_tag">PLAY TIME</h2><br/>Play time is 15-60 minutes.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unknown Soul With Me</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2734790/Unknown_Soul_With_Me/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2734790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>About Game</strong></h2>You are a young girl who wakes up in a dark and mysterious dungeon. You don’t know how you got there or why you are there. You only know that you want to escape.<br/><br/>As you explore the dungeon, you encounter a friendly spirit who claims to have been trapped there for a long time. He says he can’t leave the dungeon but can help you find a way out. He also tells you that he has a secret that he can’t reveal to you yet.<br/><br/>You decide to trust the spirit and work with him to solve the puzzles and challenges the dungeon presents. Along the way, you learn more about the spirit’s past and his connection to the dungeon. You also discover that the dungeon is not what it seems and that there is a hidden truth behind your imprisonment.<br/><br/>Will you be able to free the spirit and yourself from the dungeon? What will you do when you find out the spirit’s secret? How will you deal with the consequences of your actions?<br/><br/>This is a game of adventure, mystery, and friendship. It is a game where your choices matter and affect the story's outcome. It is a game where you will face danger, betrayal, and sacrifice. It is a game where you will find hope, courage, and love.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Game Feature</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Character Switching</strong>: You can control both the girl and the spirit and switch between them at any time. Each character has different abilities and perspectives that can help you overcome obstacles and discover secrets in the dungeon.<br/><br/></li><li> <strong>Puzzle Solving</strong>: You will encounter various puzzles and challenges that require logic, creativity, and teamwork. You will need to use the girl's and the spirit's skills in combination to find solutions and progress through the dungeon.<br/><br/></li><li> <strong>Storytelling</strong>: You will experience a rich and immersive story that unfolds as you explore the dungeon. You will learn more about the girl's and the spirit's backgrounds, motivations, and personalities. You will also face choices that will affect the outcome of the story and the fate of the characters.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>About the Developer</strong></h2>We are a small team of indie game developers who are passionate about creating immersive and engaging games. This is our first game project, and we are excited to share it with you.<br/><br/>However, as this game is still in Early Access, it may contain some bugs and errors that we are working hard to fix. We appreciate your feedback and support, and we apologize for any inconvenience caused by the game's issues.<br/><br/>We hope you enjoy playing our game and exploring the dungeon with the girl and the spirit.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient Sprits: Columbus' Legacy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2723470/Ancient_Sprits_Columbus_Legacy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A mysterious ghost story, a gripping thriller, a historical adventure:<br>
Virginia and Professor MacNara, a famous archaeologist, come upon a 500 year-old galleon on the beach of a deserted village. The ship, laden with a mysterious artefact, belonged to Christopher Columbus, discoverer of America, and was thought to have simply vanished. Strange, everything on board looks as though the mighty ship was abandoned only yesterday. The ravages of time do not appear to have left a trace…<br>
When Professor MacNara inexplicably dies, Virginia begins to pierce the veil of these mysteries in her search for the murderer. It seems the ship is only one piece in a mystical puzzle about a time long ago.<br>
<br>
•	Adventure-style hidden object gameplay<br>
•	Hundreds of clues and search objects<br>
•	Thrilling mini games<br/>
•	Amazing soundtrack						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peasant Royale</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2677640/Peasant_Royale/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Peasant Royale is what all fans of the battle royale genre have been waiting for for so long.<br/>Medieval battle royale with up to 50 players on one huge map.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> More than a hundred items. <br/></li><li> Smooth and realistic melee combat. <br/></li><li> Exciting ranged combat.<br/></li><li> Resource management.</li></ul><br/>Peasant Royale masterfully combines both ranged and melee combat systems.<br/><br/>Early in the game, while players are not yet heavily armored, use a variety of throwing weapons<br/>in order to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677640/extras/Ranged_opt.gif?t=1703845817">]<br/><br/><br/>Then, approaching the later stage of the game, having acquired a set of armor, shields, and melee weapons, enter into exciting duels<br/>with other players and finally become the last one standing!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677640/extras/melee1_opt.gif?t=1703845817"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Box VR: Hidden Secrets</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2738770/Mystery_Box_VR_Hidden_Secrets/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738770/extras/h1.png?t=1703838576"><br/>Interact with objects, handles, buttons, and wheels on each side. Crack enigmas and collect hidden puzzle tiles on a random side of the boxes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738770/extras/1.gif?t=1703838576"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738770/extras/h2.png?t=1703838576"><br/>You won't be able to compare reality with fiction.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738770/extras/h3.png?t=1703838576"><br/>Once you unlock all 8 boxes of a Level Pack, you can compose a puzzle and discover a brief history of an invention.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738770/extras/h4.png?t=1703838576"><br/>It's not always easy to escape the room, so use all your IQ to crack the riddles. There's a logic behind all of them, even where it seems it's not!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738770/extras/2.gif?t=1703838576"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738770/extras/h5.png?t=1703838576"><br/>Play the game with your headphones to get immersed in this amazing adventure.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738770/extras/h6.png?t=1703838576"><br/>Got stuck on some enigma? No worries, you can still get a helpful hint! You can also get in touch with me in case you really can't make it through a riddle, I'll be glad to help ;)<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738770/extras/h7.png?t=1703838576"><br/>Available in English, French, Italian, German, Spanish, Russian, and Japanese.<br/><br/>The game language will change automatically based on the language settings of your device<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738770/extras/xslogo.png?t=1703838576"><br/><strong>XSGames</strong> is an indie game startup from Italy. Since the first <strong>Mystery Box</strong> chapter (released on the mobile App Stores in 2021), the series had amazing success with the community of puzzle and escape room gamers.<br/>I hope you'll enjoy playing the <strong>Mystery Box</strong> adventures as much as I love creating them!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timeline 存档守护者 -Manage your game save</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2603950/Timeline__Manage_your_game_save/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2603950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							Timeline is a game utility tool designed primarily for managing save files.<br>
In games, we often encounter the following types of issues:<br>
1. Save file corruption/loss<br>
2. Excessive death penalties in the game<br>
3. The game offers multiple choices.<br>
<br>
Timeline can backup your game save, and roll back to the moment you desire.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barely Racing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1351480/Barely_Racing/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1351480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Barely Racing is an isometric view racing game, inspired strongly by Death Rally and other old-school racing games. However, we spiced it up a bit with online play and weapon choice. <br/><br/><strong>FEATURES</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>7 cars, with color customization.<br/></li><li>9 tracks, with reverse variant, across 3 biomes.<br/></li><li>Machine guns, rockets, and mines are your weapon of choice.<br/></li><li>Game is primarily made to be played in split screen, but there is a story mode too.<br/></li><li>Online multiplayer is supported, but it is peer to peer, which means your online match quality highly depends on the person who created the server.<br/></li><li>Single player story where you race to win the cups?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1351480/extras/BR_Garage.gif?t=1703835102"><br/><br/><strong>LOCAL AND ONLINE MULTIPLAYER</strong><br/>This game is meant to be played with your friends. Don't hesitate to challenge them. It is not a surprise that games like these are best enjoyed in multiplayer.<br/><br/><strong>MULTIPLAYER MODES</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Race - just a regular race like any other. Addition of mines, rockets and machine guns, might change that experience a bit.<br/></li><li>Mine Tag - good old tag game, but this time you carry a mine that has a timeout. Better hurry up to touch (tag) someone before it explodes. <br/></li><li>Flag Chase - take the flag and hold it as much as possible. <br/></li><li>Football - soccer + cars. <br/></li><li>Deathmatch - wreckfest, just destroy every car you see</li></ul><br/><strong>HOW TO WIN A RACE?</strong><br/>Well, you need to be the first one to cross the finish line. If you have anyone in front of you, use dem rockets and machine gun. If you have someone behind, just drop a mine, they'll do the rest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1351480/extras/BR_Weapons.gif?t=1703835102"><br/><br/><strong>DRIFTY DRIVING MODEL</strong><br/>We don't drive trams here, so expect some drift. It's post apocalypse anyways. No new tires have been produced.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1351480/extras/BR_Drift.gif?t=1703835102"><br/><br/><strong>THAT IS ALL YOU NEED TO KNOW. POUR THE GASOLINE AND START RAMMING!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1351480/extras/BR_Race.gif?t=1703835102"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost in Nowhere</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2296740/Lost_in_Nowhere/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2296740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2296740/extras/Headerkapsel.jpg?t=1703826886"><br/>Dive into the oppressive atmosphere of Lost in Nowhere, an intense blend of Action, Adventure, and Horror. Your mission: Solve three puzzles to escape a complex labyrinth. But beware, dangers lurk in the darkness... Creatures prowl in the shadows and will chase after you. Collect weapons and ammunition, and use them wisely. If you run out of ammunition, solving the puzzles and surviving become nearly impossible.<h2 class="bb_tag">Relentless Pursuit</h2>In the gloomy corridors of the labyrinth, terrible creatures lurk, waiting for a chance to drag you into the abyss. With only a limited amount of ammunition, you must carefully decide when to fight and when to flee.<h2 class="bb_tag">Complex Puzzles</h2>Three challenging puzzles stand between you and your freedom. Solve them and find the exit before time runs out and new threats are unleashed.<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore Various Locations</h2>The labyrinth leads to various eerie places. Discover an abandoned small town, wander through a creepy graveyard, climb a dilapidated tower, and explore a dark forest with a silent lake. Each location has its own challenges and secrets waiting to be uncovered.<h2 class="bb_tag">Time is the Enemy</h2>A merciless countdown puts you under pressure as you navigate through the labyrinth. Every second counts as you solve the puzzles and aim to find the exit before new creatures are unleashed.<h2 class="bb_tag">Fight for Survival</h2>Find weapons and ammunition to defend yourself against the darkness, but be warned: Ammunition is scarce, and without it, the puzzles become nearly unsolvable.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658620/Snake_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>This is a very cool role-playing Snake game. Our design focuses on the combat experience of each character, spending a lot of time adjusting scene effects, skill effects, sound effects, and game difficulty. Now each greedy snake has 8 different skills. Their skills will have certain characteristics, and each character will bring you a different experience. We are committed to the transformation of the casual attributes of the game, the simplest interaction and the simplest character development system (as the time of using the character increases, the character will become stronger and stronger). Unlocking characters mainly depends on clearing the game and defeating enemies. The game provides unlimited levels, and the difficulty of all levels will gradually increase. In the constant game challenges, you will obtain Stean achievements and challenge rankings. The game provides local single-player mode and two-player mode. You are welcome to play with your friends.</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bread around bread around bread around bread</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2730890/Bread_around_bread_around_bread_around_bread/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Help grandpa Go Get Some Bread! </h2>He can't do it without you. But please, no bag with milk inside the bag for milk. <br/>Grandpa has an upset stomach from milk<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>An almost psychedelic novella with a philosophical plot, but...<br/></li><li>Three endings, none of which you will like.<br/></li><li>A princess whose lines must be read not with the eyes.</li></ul><br/><br/>And please, don't die. The princess will be disappointed.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Albatross</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2528400/Albatross/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2528400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Albatross is a FPS/TPS designed with 7 gamemodes for users to play with and includes a singleplayer and multiplayer option. You can play any of the gamemodes with friends and try them all.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ore Quest: Digger's Delve</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731710/Ore_Quest_Diggers_Delve/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an exhilarating subterranean adventure, where you take on the role of a skilled miner operating a state-of-the-art mining machine. Your mission: to dig deep into the earth, unearth precious ores, and amass a fortune to upgrade your machine for even greater mining feats.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmic Resistance</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2541580/Cosmic_Resistance/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2541580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Cosmic Resistance</strong> is an engaging 2D pixel art casual game with strategy elements that puts you in the role of a skilled fleet commander. Tasked with leading the charge against an alien invasion, your objective is to liberate humanity from their tyrannical rule.<br/><br/>Planets hold the key to victory! Conquer these celestial bodies and harness their abundant resources to fuel your epic fight against the relentless alien invasion. Your strategic prowess will determine the fate of the universe in this thrilling cosmic adventure!<br/><br/>Build shipyards, Build Defense Stations and of course ships. The universe awaits your command!<br/><br/><strong>Key Elements:</strong><br/>- Immersive story<br/>- Quality pixel art<br/>- Planets with unique materials<br/>- 3, I repeat, 3 ship types<br/>- A lot of fun						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONSTER GRINDER ULTRA</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731610/MONSTER_GRINDER_ULTRA/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>KILL THE MONSTERS. LEVEL UP AND COLLECT ITEMS THAT UPGRADE YOUR CHARACTER. UNLOCK NEW CHARACTERS. BRING 3 FRIENDS SO YOU CAN ALL KILL EACHOTHER WITH THE POWDER KEG. COMPLAIN THAT THE POWDER KEG DOES TOO MUCH TEAM DAMAGE. I'M NOT GOING TO CHANGE THAT.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Things in the game</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Over 50+ items that uniquely upgrade your character<br/></li><li> Over 10+ Characters with unique weapons and stats that can be unlocked<br/></li><li> Explore many areas, seek out secrets and items<br/></li><li> Survive as long as you can against the increasingly powerful horde of monsters<br/></li><li> Collect coins to spend on permanent upgrades that persist between runs<br/></li><li> Listen to the <i>electric</i> soundtrack featuring tracks from doopdee</li></ul><br/>Controllers are recommended for playing local multiplayer on one machine, unless you and your friends can fit four hands on one keyboard.<br/><br/>For online remote play, I tested with my friends and we were able to comfortably play all 4 players with inputs into the hosts keyboard. But controllers also work too.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731610/extras/masterItemSheet1.png?t=1703796495"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boo's There?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2686930/Boos_There/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In the world of Boo's There, play as a monster hunter given a life-or-death mission by a monster hunting guild: Monsters are hiding amongst regular trick or treaters on Halloween night, catch as many monsters as you can, fail to catch them all before the hour ends and there will be dire consequences… The guild has supplied you with inspection tools that can make your job easier, but be warned, using them takes up valuable chunks of time!<br>
<br>
Interrogate visitors based on suspicious quirks of their appearance. Appease the kids by giving them candy, and make sure not to anger their parents! Pick through the hordes of sugar-high children and identify the monsters using their weaknesses. See right through ghosts with a flashlight and make vampires gag with unappetizing garlic candy before trapping them in your patented monster-proof cage. Keep your block safe and make your guild proud! Are you ready to find out Boo's There?						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen's Garden Christmas</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2639620/Queens_Garden_Christmas/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639620/extras/qg5_logo.png?t=1703877684"><br/><br/>It’s that time of the year again! Christmas is here and the Queen has decided to celebrate it in style. In this merry match-3 game, you can help Jack, her loyal advisor, decorate the garden for a magical Christmas season. With over 119 levels to play, you can collect coins and special jewels to purchase plants and decorations to design the most beautiful garden this Christmas.<br/><br/>Here are some of the key features of the game:<br/><br/>120 challenging Match-3 levels: The game offers a wide range of levels that will keep you engaged and entertained for hours on end.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639620/extras/match.gif?t=1703877684"><br/><br/><br/>Individual garden cells for full customization: You can customize each cell of the garden to your liking, making it unique and personal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639620/extras/garden.gif?t=1703877684"><br/><br/>Lots of items to make the garden your own!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2639620/extras/store.gif?t=1703877684"><br/><br/>Thematic Power ups!: The game offers thematic power-ups that will help you progress through the levels with ease.<br/><br/>Santa Claus!: Who doesn’t love Santa Claus? The game features Santa Claus as one of the characters, adding to the festive spirit.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maskonauts: Chat'Attack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2139730/Maskonauts_ChatAttack/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Turn your Twitch channel into a game level!<br/><br/>Get in your Maskopod and play in real time with Twitch chats activities! Survive waves of texts, Emoticodes and enemies. <br/>Collect bonuses and try to defeat the Blockbossters and save the Maskotios!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139730/extras/APropos_01.jpg?t=1703785635"><br/><br/>Everything you type in the chat appear in the game!<br/><br/>🎲 Each channel generates a game level and its content with a unique boss, enemies combination, musics and environment colors.<br/><br/>💪 The number of spectators and the intensity of the exchanges on the chat change the difficulty of the levels. High activity means more obstacles and enemies, but also more bonuses to collect!<br/><br/>🎁 Specific characters and emojis bring up bonuses: a red heart emoji brings up a ❤️ which restores energy, the "!" and "?" make random bonuses appear... And there are plenty of others to discover!<br/><br/>💎 Collect Emogems, reach high scores and beat bosses quickly to earn more Maskoins.<br/><br/>🛠️ Use your Maskoins to unlock upgrades and new Maskopods with special weapons and statistics.<br/><br/>👾 Survive all 10 waves on a channel and beat it's Blockbosster to get a boss badge, the ultimate Maskonauts reward.<br/><br/>💬 Interact in the chat to influence the games of other players just as they influence yours!<br/><br/>⭐ Connect to your Twitch account to play with your favorite channels and unlock more features!<br/><br/>🖥️ The game behaves like a PC widget, making it easier to interact with Twitch chats during games.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Menu languages: English, French<br/></li><li> Supported Twitch text message characters and symbols: Latin, Cyrillic, Bengali, Arabic, Japanese, Korean, Thai, Simplified Chinese and Mandarin.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Maskonauts: Chat'Attack does not require a Twitch account to play.<br/></li><li>Maskonauts: Chat'Attack is a game that allows you to read and interact with Twitch channels using official Twitch API.<br/></li><li>We don't share any personal data.<br/></li><li>An internet connexion is required to use Maskonauts: Chat'Attack. Any costs relating to this connexion are at your expense.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasty Platformer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2729890/Nasty_Platformer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Do you know what madness is? Repeating the same action over and over again in the hope of results. This fun frog game may change the way you think about indie platformers.<br>
<br>
Nasty Platformer is a small adventure in a world of endless traps awaiting you at any moment of the game. With only one life, your character will end the game at the most unexpected moments. And the goal of the game is simple - reach the end of the level, avoiding all obstacles.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
- One life and many dangers<br>
- Calm soundtrack						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain Urge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2714690/Brain_Urge/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2714690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are playing on the side of evil. You have a squad of wandering dead at your disposal, and the main goal is to capture a human military base and eat their brains.<br>
Your army of darkness consists of used ordinary farmers, police officers and city dwellers.<br>
The human base is reliably defended by military equipment, and at the sight of zombies, shelling begins with all guns.<br>
Plan your attack carefully, use the capabilities of several types of zombies and strive to defeat all of humanity.<br>
<br>
Brain Urge is a real-time strategy game where you attack a human base on the side of zombies.						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead Garden Zero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2708180/Dead_Garden_Zero/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this score attack mini game, navigate through the dark garden carefully and search for your friends. Save as many friends as you can before the evil entity kills you! The amount of friends saved is your highest score. How many of your friends can you save?<br/><br/>Features include a saved high score! Yeah I know, another one of these on here. Not much to say about gameplay, but its dark so navigate carefully before running into friends.<br/><br/>Anyways...<br/><br/>Hello netizens, just a worried mom here that made a mini game for my ten year old daughter and sharing it with the world. She loves video games and loves being in the garden. This mini game I made for her is what she describes as what happens in our garden when friends visit. My daughter always talks about how this monster is always chasing them around. Our garden is openly attached to a forest, so a lot of her neighborhood friends run through it to get home from school.<br/><br/>My daughter has been upset and extremely sad as of recently due to three people in the area that have gone missing. A mother, the mother's cousin, and the mother's daughter who was my daughter's friend. The main reason why I made this was to keep us distracted from the glooming news. She wanted me to make something where she was the main character that saved everyone from this monster. Vain selfie below, just wanted to show you all who I am and if there are any other moms out there to relate and communicate with.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708180/extras/Steam_DGZ.png?t=1703777461"><br/><br/>Once again my daughter recently just stood in our garden staring at the forest for hours. She would always scream, telling me the monster was there eating her friend, albeit there was absolutely nothing there. I don't understand, I can't see what she sees nor do I believe her, although I want to. It's all just eerie to me even if I'm playing along. Her behavior is also due to a lack of certain medication which keeps her calm. My job doesn't provide health insurance for us, so I've been buying her meds normally using savings and donations.<br/><br/>This time I want to give something in return to those who help us. This mini game project was a great bonding experience with my daughter. She illustrated concepts and cemented ideas for me to program. Now that development is complete, she's lost interest in wanting to try it out. She tells me she's too afraid to play it. Although I'm a bit frustrated about her not wanting to, I understand. This project will always be here for her whenever she's ready. Thank you everyone for reading and whatever you can give is appreciated!<br/><br/>Update: On 10/20/2023 two more people have gone missing in the area. Local detectives have reported difficulty finding any evidence of their location. The fear is infecting my head and my daughter's behavior has gotten uncontrollable. Something horrific is going on that is completely beyond my understanding.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign Fortress</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2722960/Foreign_Fortress/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Greg, decorated American military veteran, was tasked by the United States military to solve the alien epidemic because of his brave actions in the last World War on earth.<br>
He has been in a coma in a forgotten hospital trapped by a foreign non-terrestrial being for decades. Dreams of his past life and family has awakened him.<br>
Greg awakes from his coma and realizes he's not the only one in the dark, lifeless, and forgotten building and that he must vanish the alien. He remembers he had a gun on him before the alien captured him.<br>
Find and use your weapon and/or radar and hide behind walls, under tables, and closed doors to escape the alien. Be careful when you explore the hospital as the alien can hear you walk when you least expect it.<br>
Greg is confident he can use his gun and/or stealth tactics to escape the alien, gather items that can be used to expel alien life on earth, and return to his glory and family and live life like before his coma and the last World War that happened.<br>
There is a radar and/or a gun that you can use to complete your mission and track the alien's location and make sure he is out of your way and also a lighter to light your way in dark areas in the abandoned hospital because the lights have gotten dimmer each year you have been asleep, will Greg persevere and have some normality after being asleep in this foreign fortress for decades?						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underground Waifus TCG</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2602510/Underground_Waifus_TCG/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Underground Waifus: Dive into the Future of TCG multiplayer with PVP Battles. Play for free this CCG and battler card game and compete, achieve quests and earn free rewards!<br/><br/>The universe of Underground Waifus takes place in the future, corrupted by the scarcity of materials, money: stardust, and the desire for power. An eternal war between different races and more than 9 factions. The gameplay merges several themes: cyberpunk and manga, anime waifus cards based in a post-apocalyptic future.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602510/extras/gifTitle.gif?t=1703760151"><br/>Underground Waifus is more than just a TCG, CCG, or JJC. It's the dawn of a new era of TCG  gaming. If you are tired of traditional Card PVP games, enjoy battling in a vast Battle Arena CCG with players worldwide.<br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602510/extras/gifPacks.gif?t=1703760151"><br/>One of the main sources of innovation is that it proposes a circular economy model that combines F2P (Free to Play) in that TCG (Trading Card Game), we’re shifting gears to warp speed!<br/><br/>Can you create a top deck building strategy? There are several combat modes in this card F2P collecting action game:<br/><br/>PVE CCG training available in the F2P mobile and PC version. <br/><br/>PVP Battler Card version with a game pass, winning player gets all. <br/><br/>PVP Player Battle Card Battler version of winning ELO will determine who is the winner of each SEASON.<br/><br/>That JJC trading card game is focused on a competitive side, with an easy PVP (player vs player) battles game with no barriers to entry and hybrid F2P for all players!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602510/extras/gifCards.gif?t=1703760151"><br/>FEATURES of an awesome CCG game based on a TCG game:<br/><br/>TCG and CCG Fusion: Enjoy the flavor of the card battles both Trading Card Games and Collectible Card Games with an awesome deck builder.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602510/extras/gifCombat1.gif?t=1703760151"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602510/extras/gifKill.gif?t=1703760151"><br/>Deck building Dynamics: Conquer all factions, strategy and deck builder here is that fun but with cards!<br/><br/>Join us in crafting a tale of strategy, card battles, trading and prosperity in the ever expanding cosmos of Underground Waifus TCG (Trading Card Game).<br/><br/>2023 and 2024 Underground Waifus TCG it is a trademark or registered Jurval Corp (Warlands Corp and Nexxyo company)						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel Heldritch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2726310/Hotel_Heldritch/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							“Hotel Heldritch” is a first-person horror adventure that transports you to an old abandoned hotel, steeped in dark mysteries and deadly dangers. Your goal is to survive and escape the hotel within an hour and a half gameplay limit, cracking codes, collecting keys, and evading monstrous creatures that roam the dark corridors.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
