<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>NUKITASHI 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2614070/NUKITASHI_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A visual novel that describes the story of a man who wakes up and is transferred to a parallel world.<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>1+ hours of story<br/></li><li>Full Japanese voice acting by seasoned professionals</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">SUMMARY</h2>It all happened after the grand adventure that was <i><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2399220/NUKITASHI/" rel="" target="_blank">NUKITASHI</a></i>...<br/><br/>The war is over, and Junnosuke Tachibana, savior of Seiran Island, spends his days with his buddies reminiscing over victories past. True coexistence has now been achieved, and peace will continue for years to come—or so he believes.<br/><br/>One fateful day, a grave data-related incident results in him breaking through the speed of light, transporting Junnosuke and his friends to a parallel world.<h2 class="bb_tag">CHARACTERS</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara01_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Touka Reizeiin (Voice: Sakura Hanazawa)<br/><br/>FS representative and student council president of Minotsuki Academy. <br/>A girl with perfect looks and charisma—who leads her peers in the parallel world as well. <br/>Capable of overseeing everything from normal operations to strategic planning to direct combat and more, she is a major contender for Seiran’s strongest islander. <br/>Outside of work, however, she is even clumsier and sloppier than Asane—and that’s putting it mildly. <br/>Although she and Junnosuke are incompatible with each other due to their history, he has no choice but to look out for her here as she can barely take care of herself.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara02_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Rei Tadasugawa (Voice: Nanami Mizuno)<br/><br/>De facto second-in-charge as president of Minotsuki Academy’s disciplinary committee. <br/>Her skills range from miscellaneous duties to battlefield command, though as a dedicated worker, she ends up being pushed around by Touka in her daily life. She is a bit depressed when she comes to the parallel world, but her cheerful antics still win out. <br/>She is very close to Junnosuke and helps him in any way she can.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara03_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Ikuko Onabuta (Voice: Aria Kurata)<br/><br/>Commander of the First Squad, possessing the highest actual combat capability in Minotsuki Academy’s FS. <br/>One of the strongest fighters in direct combat, she’s also a diehard battle fanatic who resents the existence of anyone stronger than she is, and has no qualms about making it known to anyone within shouting distance. <br/>Always a maverick, her arrival in the parallel world reveals a side to her that catches Junnosuke by surprise.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara04_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Hinami Watarai (Voice: Shino Amekawa)<br/><br/>An older girl with a huge heart. <br/>Put a folding chair in her hands and she can also dish out some mean DPS, more than earning her position as the team’s main attacker.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara05_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Nanase Katagiri (Voice: Hitomi Yanagi)<br/><br/>Junnosuke’s legendary classmate. <br/>Filling a scouting role for the NLNS, she fights on the most dangerous of front lines armed with various nefarious spy items.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara06_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Misaki Hotori (Voice: Nagi Koharu)<br/><br/>Junnosuke’s quieter classmate.<br/>Also a resident badass, riding all kinds of vehicles from bicycles to fighter jets.<br/>Still somehow operates under the impression that she is plain and utterly unremarkable.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara07_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Asane Tachibana (Voice: Soramame.)<br/><br/>Junnosuke’s younger sister is a reclusive, foul-mouthed, and frequently difficult individual. <br/>She develops spy items and controls the Ariadne Protocol escape assistance program. <br/>However, she seems dissatisfied with her brother’s recent activities...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara08_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Fumino Kotoyose (Voice: Poplar Sawano)<br/><br/>A young woman believed to be the key to abolishing the old island order. <br/>She serves as a sniper for the group, keeping Junnosuke out of harm’s way at a distance.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara10_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Susuko (Voice: Natyu Aizawa)<br/><br/>A junior member of the FS Fifth Division. <br/>Ever smiling and energetic, she is not afraid of alt-world Junnosuke, insisting that he’s mentally still the same old insecure dweeb. <br/>She loves to have fun and is often seen acting on that with Junnosuke. <br/>That thing on her shoulder is her pet cockatoo.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara11_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Schubert (Voice: Makoto Kaburagi)<br/><br/>NO DATA...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara13_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Rin Hanamaru (Voice: Haru Amachi)<br/><br/>Hands down the biggest problem child of them all. <br/>Already ruthlessly ambitious, in the parallel world, she’s now a devotee of a certain local god and does as she pleases upon receiving a divine revelation. <br/>As the prideful “SHO Special Auditor’s Aide,” she is obsessed with bringing down Touka and alt-world Junnosuke, though it doesn’t usually go as planned.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caribbean Legend</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2230980/Caribbean_Legend/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i><strong>Based on Sea Dogs series and inspired by Sid Meier's Pirates!</strong></i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/Wishlist_Follow_ENG.gif?t=1708054173"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/История_EN.gif?t=1708054173"><br/><br/>Welcome to the Caribbean in 1654 AD, a place teeming with opportunities and mysteries. Assume the role of Charles de Maure, a young French noble who embarked on a journey to the New World to assist his brother. What initially appeared to be a simple family matter quickly evolves into a lifelong adventure.<br/>Immerse yourself in the tale of a noble brat who rises to become the most influential figure in the Caribbean. <strong>Riches, titles, power, and romance – the ultimate booty awaits, and it's up to you to seize it all.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/steamchar.jpg?t=1708054173"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Embark on a 200-hour-long journey.<br/></li><li>Undertake hundreds of quests.<br/></li><li>Freeplay, rush through the story, or combine both - you're the Captain, and your ship will sail where you command.<br/></li><li>Experience a historical narrative with a touch of mystique.<br/></li><li>Explore romantic interests and companions.<br/></li><li>Choose from various career options, from general-governor to pirate baron.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/Мир_EN.gif?t=1708054173"><br/><br/>The Caribbean Sea – a realm of dozens of islands and cities, a grand archipelago shrouded in mystery and secrets. From the summits of Indian pyramids to the ocean depths, unique rewards, quests, and curiosities await. <strong>This open world is your sandbox, you are free to explore it and shape your legend as you see fit. </strong>Your decisions determine where to go, what to do, and who to take with you. Subdue the New World or it will destroy you!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Discover dozens of islands and settlements.<br/></li><li>Build your very own colony.<br/></li><li>Explore caves, pyramids, jungles, Indian tribes, and lost cities.<br/></li><li>Visit taverns, brothels, shipyards, churches, forts, and many other points of interest.<br/></li><li>Engage in treasure hunting and gambling.<br/></li><li>Experience dynamic weather and the serene turquoise sea.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/Море_EN.gif?t=1708054173"><br/><br/><strong>Owning a warship is a privilege, a symbol of status and luxury. </strong>You are among the very few who can afford such grandeur. Begin your journey with a simple sloop and work your way up to commanding a ship of the line or even a fleet of these formidable vessels, ready to plunder cities at your whim. No one will stand in your way. Tired from leading massive armadas and the responsibility? Take command of a fast Frigate or Corvette and just free roam the Caribbean. In moments of tranquility at sea, relish the stunning views, embrace the sense of exploration, or navigate in the heart of a storm.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/valciria3_копия.png?t=1708054173"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Command dozens of ships representing the glory of the Age of Sail.<br/></li><li>Customize, paint, upgrade, and repair your vessel.<br/></li><li>Engage in unforgiving yet enjoyable naval combat.<br/></li><li>Experience intense boarding action, from the upper deck to the captain's cabin.<br/></li><li>Collect unique vessels to rule the seas.<br/></li><li>Manage booty distribution, morale, and the threat of mutinies.<br/></li><li>Assemble a formidable team of officers.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/боевка_EN.gif?t=1708054173"><br/><br/>Captains are most vulnerable when they set foot on land. Surviving naval combat can be challenging, but at least you won't die alone – your crew will stand with you till the very end. Land battles are different: dishonest, ruthless and risky for you and those who you hold dear. <strong>Bring your companions with you, poison your weapons, study the terrain, craft deadly items, and confront thugs, soldiers, pirates, and rivals head-on.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/face_201_копия.png?t=1708054173"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tailor your character's build – become a heavy swordsman, a nimble rogue, a master sharpshooter, or a silver-tongued diplomat.<br/></li><li>Equip yourself and your companions with a wide array of swords, axes, rapiers, armor, muskets, and pistols.<br/></li><li>Craft amulets, ammo, potions, and always be prepared for battle.<br/></li><li>Seek out challenges – the more you fight, the stronger both you and your character become.<br/></li><li>Command military operations from raiding to sieges.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708005696"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708005696"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smalland: Survive the Wilds</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/768200/Smalland_Survive_the_Wilds/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>"Before the time of the giants, we lived freely under the Sun and Moon. Centuries have passed, but those stories of the surface world have been passed down through the generations. Now the giants are gone, and you, Vanguard, must venture out into the wilds once more, on an urgent mission. Be brave, and do not falter…"</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/TreeLookingup.gif?t=1708009613"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the vast “Land of the Small" </h2>Traverse lake sized puddles, scale skyscraper sized trees, scramble through cavernous cracks in roads, as you experience a huge open world from a new perspective. Explore dense forests, hazardous swamps and strange ruins left over from the time before. Uncover lore and knowledge from hidden NPCs scattered throughout the world and learn to survive in this vast wilderness. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Land_of_Small.gif?t=1708009613"><h2 class="bb_tag">Tame and ride creatures</h2>Uncover recipes that will let you tame and ride an array of critters. Leap huge distances on the back of a Grasshopper, zoom around on a Damselfly, scurry from place-to-place on a Spider. This world and its inhabitants are yours to conquer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Mounts.gif?t=1708009613"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive together</h2>Play alongside friends with support for up to 10 players in multiplayer. Explore together, fight together, build together and survive the wilds as a team.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Together.gif?t=1708009613"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build encampments on the ground or amongst the trees</h2>Scavenge or refine resources to build your encampment with multiple material tiers, from leaves and twigs to sturdy stone. Pick your favourite spot in the world and build, or scale vast trees and claim your own settlement at the top.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Housing.gif?t=1708009613"><h2 class="bb_tag">Craft powerful armour sets</h2>Collect powerful armours that provide you with resistances and abilities and mix them up to personalise your appearance. Glide through the skies in winged armour, swing from tree to tree with the grappling hook and many more. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Armors.gif?t=1708009613"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive the Wilds</h2>Most of the creatures you encounter will see you as lower on the food chain – Ants, Cockroaches, Beetles, Wasps, and Spiders all view you as a potential meal. Weather conditions and seasons are in constant flux so if you want to survive for another day, preparation is key.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Survive_the_Wilds.gif?t=1708009613"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wani Hug that Gator!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1895350/I_Wani_Hug_that_Gator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1895350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Wait, what do you mean we’re moving?!</h2>Just great; just when Inco was getting ready to move on into his Senior year, his parents decide to uproot his life and move half-way across the country!<br/><br/>Guess it’s time to start all over. Sure, Inco didn’t have many friends (or any) back at his old school, and sure, he was so low on the social ladder that he had to get a deep-sea diving lesson…. Wait, why was he complaining about moving again?<br/><br/>I Wani Hug that Gator is a multi-ended, choices-matter visual novel about second chances and the power of accepting who you are. Shape how Inco makes the most of his final year, and how the relationships he makes along the way will develop. One relationship in particular has him feeling all fuzzy inside…<h2 class="bb_tag">The Prehistoric Romance a Million-and-One Years in the making!</h2>If there’s one good thing to come out of Inco’s sudden relocation, it’s Olivia. Bold and brash, Olivia seems particularly gifted in getting under Inco’s skin. No matter how Inco slices it, he and Olivia seem destined to go together like a particularly scaly sandwich. But the outcome of such a pairing is yet to be determined…<h2 class="bb_tag">Wait, am I being graded on this?!</h2>Make friends, reconcile enemies, and figure out how Inco could possibly repair his miserable excuse for a social life.  But be warned: The choices you make expands the relationships with Inco’s classmates and determines which of the four unique endings you receive. Maybe Inco should’ve spent a little less time studying and a bit more time learning how to relate to people…						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider I-III Remastered Starring Lara Croft</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2478970/Tomb_Raider_IIII_Remastered_Starring_Lara_Croft/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2478970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover Lara Croft’s Original Adventures, Lovingly Restored</h2> <br/>Play the Original Three Tomb Raider Adventures: For the first time ever, play the complete experience with all expansions and secret levels on modern platforms in this definitive collection.<h2 class="bb_tag">Included Game Titles</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tomb Raider I + Unfinished Business<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider II + Golden Mask<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider III + The Lost Artifact</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><strong>Solve Ancient Mysteries</strong>: Uncover treasures of the ancient world by solving puzzles and unraveling mysteries lost to the ravages of time.<br/><br/><strong>Globe-trotting Adventure</strong>: Follow Lara Croft around the world and face off against deadly foes and dangerous myths.<br/><br/><strong>Lovingly Restored</strong>: Experience the classics boasting upgraded graphics, with the option to switch to the original polygon look at any time.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arzette: The Jewel of Faramore</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1924780/Arzette_The_Jewel_of_Faramore/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924780/extras/intro_gif.gif?t=1708026324"><br/><br/>After ten years of peace...the evil Daimur has returned! Princess Arzette is the Kingdom of Faramore’s only hope to restore harmony to the land!<br/><br/>In this brand new interactive action adventure game, you control the resourceful princess Arzette. Travel through multiple breathtaking locations filled with scum, villainy and secrets, speak with the locals to uncover mysteries and objectives, and take on the evil Daimur as <strong>Arzette: The Jewel of Faramore</strong> brings you the best interactive gaming experience since the invention of the CD-ROM!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924780/extras/mortar_gif.gif?t=1708026324"><br/><br/><strong>Featuring:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hand painted backgrounds and incredible sprite art.<br/></li><li>Fully voice-acted cartoon cinematics with a colorful cast of characters.<br/></li><li>A sprawling world with diverse locations and many secrets.<br/></li><li>Acquire powerful items and abilities by exploring and helping those in need.<br/></li><li>Veteran dev team including artist Rob Dunlavey, Digital Foundry's John Linneman and Audi Sorlie, voice talent Jeffrey Rath and Bonnie Jean Wilbur, and award winning composer Jake "Button Masher" Silverman.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islands of Insight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2071500/Islands_of_Insight/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Islands of Insight: a sublime shared-world puzzle game set in a fantasy realm of ancient wonders and natural beauty. Brimming with mysterious puzzles to solve, secrets to uncover, and vibrant landscapes to explore, this peaceful world of floating islands is the perfect place to unwind. Embark on a puzzle adventure of your choice, all at your own pace.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_1-Title-Journey_EN.png?t=1707847143">‎‎‏‏‎<br/>Play as a Seeker on a peaceful journey rich in exploration and puzzle-solving. Embark on the Path of Discovery and let your curiosity guide you through a breathtaking open world where the answer is always in sight.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_Gifs_Journey_HD.gif?t=1707847143"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_2-Title-Puzzles_EN.png?t=1707847143"><br/>Seek out and solve an unparalleled collection of over 10,000 puzzles divided across 24 puzzle types. Every corner of the world holds a new eureka moment for you to discover. From enigmas of perspective to logic problems, environmental challenges and more, the puzzles you’ll encounter vary in difficulty and have been crafted by some of the best minds in puzzle design to create an engaging experience for both newcomers and seasoned puzzle fans.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_Gifs_Puzzles_HD.gif?t=1707847143"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_3-Title-Exploration_EN.png?t=1707847143"><br/>Freely explore the main island’s expansive open world where most of the puzzles and secrets are found. Wander the vibrant landscapes and architecture of its 5 distinct biomes or spread your wings to glide above them. Navigate the environment’s verticality and take your game to new heights. Unlock puzzle types and new areas in the campaign by completing 20+ Enclaves housing curated puzzle challenges. Go where you want. Solve what you want. The only path here is the one you make.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/3.IOI_Steam_Gif_Exploration___Discovery_2.gif?t=1707847143"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_5-Title-Experience_EN.png?t=1707847143"><br/>Customize your character. Increase your puzzle masteries to level them up while earning sparks to unlock new abilities. Complete daily quests. Seamlessly interact with other players in our shared world to gain or offer a bit of guidance, or choose to figure things out entirely on your own. With puzzles that refresh over time, a new discovery awaits with every visit to the islands.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/4.IOI_Steam_Gif_An_Evergreen_Experience_2.gif?t=1707847143"><br/><br/>Age restrictions may apply to access this game.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2436570/DRAGON_QUEST_BUILDERS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/Toybox_Announce_Build.gif?t=1707862917"><br/>The first title in the BUILDERS series, DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS, is bringing its handy crafting features to Steam!<br/>Gather, craft and build to defeat defeat the evil Dragonlord and restore Alefgard to it's former glory!<br/>In a world made out of blocks, everything that you see can be materials used to create! Farm ingredients, craft various items and build your base to unite the people roaming the ruins. From buildings to entire towns, you have the freedom to make your village your very own.<h2 class="bb_tag">■ Story</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/Toybox_Announce_Lightning.gif?t=1707862917"><br/>BUILDERS is set in the realm of Alefgard, the setting for the first ever DRAGON QUEST game.<br/>The world of Alefgard has been plunged into darkness, its light stolen by the evil Dragonlord, and this story begins with the appearance of a young hero with a mysterious ability to build things... And so the stage is set for an epic tale in which the dark world of Alefgard is returned to life with the power of creation!<h2 class="bb_tag">■ The first DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS title, helpful crafting features include:</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/intextbanner_3.png?t=1707862917"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Place blocks remotely, or destroy blocks with ease, with just a single click of the mouse!<br/></li><li> Now Includes a helpful Undo feature, which allows you to put things back to how they were before!<br/></li><li> Now Featuring Big Bash, a useful feature introduced in DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS 2 that allows you to break all objects in a particular area in one go!<br/></li><li> Terra Incognita, BUILDERS’ free build stage, the stackable block height is doubled!<br/></li><li> Includes fun side content, like collecting figurines of NPCs and monsters, or gathering pixels and exchanging them for a variety of handy items!<br/></li><li> Use Build Cards to share buildings with other players and bring their buildings to life on your island!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">■ Includes all DLC from previous versions of DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/intextbanner_4.png?t=1707862917"><br/>The Steam version of DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS includes all of the DLC from past versions including the free build mode, Terra Incognita: Magic Carpet, Boss Monster Model Set, Astronomy Set and Pixel Ring.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/Toybox_Announce_Stack.gif?t=1707862917"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultros</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2386310/Ultros/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You wake up stranded, after seemingly crashing your ship on The Sarcophagus — a giant, space-drifting, cosmic uterus holding an ancient demonic being known as ULTROS. Trapped in the eternal loop of a black hole, you will have to explore The Sarcophagus and meet its inhabitants to understand the part you play. <br/><br/>Are you the gruesome breaker of this cycle, or can you become a link from destruction to rebirth? <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat1.png?t=1707822049"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat1.gif?t=1707822049"><br/>ULTROS is set in a multifaceted realm - a vast alien landscape teeming with life. Grounded in science fiction, ULTROS comes wrapped in an eccentric art style and a mystical soundtrack from the visionary El Huervo, renowned for his work on Hotline Miami. ULTROS explores meta-themes of mental health, life, death, and karmic cycles through deep lore and environmental storytelling.       <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat2.png?t=1707822049"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat2.gif?t=1707822049"><br/>Experience brutal, intimate, close-quarter combat with cosmic lifeforms, driven by a sense of urgency – where precision is paramount and every cut of your blade counts. Yet this intense combat is juxtaposed with cultivating the greenery and tending to plant life in The Sarcophagus, providing precious moments of contemplation and peace. In turn, this grants deeper access to obscured paths.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat3.png?t=1707822049"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat3.gif?t=1707822049"><br/>The rich world of ULTROS holds many secrets for those curious enough — and fearless enough — to seek them out. A unique loop-based mechanic will allow you to start over at key moments in the story, providing opportunities to unfold such secrets, unlock different areas of the world and new abilities on a branching skill tree. Experiment with and master your own specific fighting style as you explore the world of ULTROS. Each loop brings you closer to the truth...						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Will:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802530/Space_WillPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 10 in the prologue, 59 in the official version<br/>Galaxy: 2 in the prologue, 6 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><strong>Sixty basic cores, hundreds of base station equipment, and thousands of chips, you can freely cooperate and shoot through the dual-angle joystick operation in a survival Roguelike game! Explore the sci-fi space and build your strongest battleship!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Step 1: Choose a "core" as your basic role<br/>Step 2: Choose a "crew" as your initial weapon<br/>Step 3: Select a galaxy for exploration</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game will continuously collect new "units" or "chips" during the exploration process<br/>Using "crew" can expand weapons and enhance combat effectiveness for your warship<br/>Using "chips" can enhance various abilities of your warship</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Each "core" or "unit" has a maximum of 4 interfaces. When the interfaces are used up, you cannot equip more parts, but you can also infinitely increase the number of your interfaces!<br/>Each "crew" can use the right mouse button to rotate and adjust the optimal angle for combat</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game features dual joystick shooting, with the keyboard moving and the mouse aiming at the enemy. Of course, there are many weapons that can automatically attack or be placed in the scene as traps for use~</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_TITLE_FULLSCREEN.gif?t=1708014616"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_1.png?t=1708014616"><br/> <br/>In New Eden, 1695, communities of settlers are plagued by a dreadful curse. As Banishers, step into their lives, investigate the source of evil, unravel chilling mysteries, explore diverse landscapes, and interact with unforgettable characters whose fate lies in your hands.<br/><br/>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden is an all-new title crafted by renowned studio DON'T NOD, known for their acclaimed titles such as Life is Strange and Vampyr. Immerse yourself in an intimate narrative Action-RPG, taking you on an exhilarating journey between life, death, love and sacrifices.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_2.png?t=1708014616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_FANTASY.gif?t=1708014616"><br/>Play as a couple of Banishers, Red and Antea, experienced spirit hunters entrusted with the daunting task of dispelling a malevolent curse through powerful rituals. Protect the living from the threat of lingering ghosts and specters, and become a beacon of hope in a world consumed by darkness.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_3.png?t=1708014616"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_NARATION_LOVE.gif?t=1708014616"><br/>Experience a heart-wrenching love story between Antea Duarte and Red mac Raith. When Antea is killed and turned into a spirit, you find yourself facing a choice. Will you uphold your oath and ascend her soul, or will you sacrifice the living in the hope of bringing her back? Your decisions will shape the fate of New Eden’s inhabitants - may they be living or dead, and determine the end of your journey.<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>BLAME</strong> the living and sacrifice their lives, holding them responsible for their actions<br/></li><li><strong>BANISH</strong> souls of the departed, condemning them to eternal suffering<br/></li><li><strong>ASCEND</strong> souls, liberating them from eternal sorrow and granting them serenity</li></ul><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_4.png?t=1708014616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_COMBAT.gif?t=1708014616"><br/>Banishers are specialized in combat against undead creatures, such as specters or ghosts. Combine Red's physical arsenal with Antea's supernatural powers in a dynamic combat system. Find your own style by mixing weapon attacks and spiritual abilities. Powerful synergies will lead you to defeat New Eden’s most dangerous enemies and bosses.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_6.png?t=1708014616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_SKILL.gif?t=1708014616"><br/>Unleash the full power of the Banishers by unlocking new gear and supernatural abilities. By exploring New Eden, you will find ancient artifacts, trinkets and valuable resources to enhance your equipment in preparation of future fights. In addition to your arsenal, progress in Antea’s skill trees to upgrade her devastating spectral powers and unseal new combos.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_5.png?t=1708014616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_EXPLORATION.gif?t=1708014616"><br/>Investigate haunting cases in a mystical world full of dark secrets. Discover New Eden, a North America settlement marked by terrible stories and secrets of its tormented inhabitants. Understanding each resident’s motivations will be essential to guide your decisions throughout the game.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_7.png?t=1708014616"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Ninja Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_9" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🥋🐾 WELCOME TO 100 NINJA CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🗡️</h2>🗡️Join the cutest adventure in the Ninja world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of ninja themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game.<br/>😊Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x200.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Ninja Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Extra.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816000/100_Ninja_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815980/100_Ninja_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Artbook.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x1.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_10" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_11" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III - BlackCell (Season 2)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731840/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III__BlackCell_Season_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Get Call of Duty® Points* and in-game content for Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III and Call of Duty®: Warzone™.<br>
<br>
Offering includes:<br>
<br/>
- Battle Pass for Season 2<br/>
- 20 Battle Token Tier Skips<br/>
<br/>
Exclusive BlackCell Sector on the Battle Map:<br/>
<br/>
- 1100 Call of Duty® Points<br/>
- BlackCell Operator<br/>
- Assault Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Battle Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Finishing Move<br/>
<br/>
- BlackCell Bonus Topper with 11 additional reactive Operator skin alternatives and 6 Weapon Blueprints with Tracers.<br/>
<br/>
Activision may update, replace, or remove this in-game content at any time.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1708019001"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal Richards (formerly of Echos)</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1708019001"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about the future of Sheepy, limited edition merch and more.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXIT KUN</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781370/EXIT_KUN/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a game of finding differences and observing. Our game challenges players to carefully observe and spot the distinctions that lead them to the elusive "Exit KUN."<br>
<br>
Game Overview:<br>
<br>
You find yourself trapped in an enigmatic underground labyrinth, and your only goal is to reach "Exit KUN." The journey demands keen observation of your surroundings. Every detail matters, and anomalies could be your key to progress.<br>
<br>
How to Play:<br>
<br/>
Observe Carefully: Scrutinize your surroundings to uncover anomalies that may guide your way or pose a threat.<br/>
Turn Back if Needed: If anomalies are detected, swift decision-making is crucial. Turn back immediately to avoid unforeseen consequences.<br/>
Forward Momentum: Should your observation reveal no anomalies, press forward. <br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Developer Notes:<br/>
This game is inspired by Exit 8. You are free to create, upload, and monetize videos and any other content featuring Game on platforms such as YouTube, Twitch, and other video-sharing websites. The characters, places, and elements involved in the game are fictitious. Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, or events is purely coincidental.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soak &amp; Splash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2051500/Soak__Splash/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2051500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the Soak &amp; Splash! Get ready to sweat, socialize, and have a blast with your friends in this unique game that combines the best of traditional sauna culture with modern party fun.<br>
<br>
First, step into the steamy sauna and feel the heat and humidity envelop your body.<br>
<br>
Once everyone is inside, it's time to start the fun. You can start by whisking each other with broom.<br>
<br>
Feeling competitive? You can also fight with other players with sauna equipment. Or you can simply relax and enjoy the company of your friends, chatting, singing, or telling jokes.<br>
<br/>
Finally, when you've had enough of the sauna, you can cool off in the nearby pool or shower.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, this game is all about having fun, bonding with your friends, and experiencing the unique benefits of sauna culture. So why wait? Download game and get ready to sweat, laugh, and enjoy life to the fullest!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/315210/Suicide_Squad_Kill_the_Justice_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Rocksteady Studios, the creators of the Batman: Arkham series, Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is a genre-defying third-person action shooter where the ultimate band of misfits must do the impossible to save the world: Kill the Justice League.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/SSKTJL_Intro.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Join the newly “recruited” members of Amanda Waller’s infamous Task Force X (aka the Suicide Squad), Harley Quinn, Deadshot, Captain Boomerang and King Shark, as they set out on an impossible mission to Kill the Justice League. Drop into an expansive and dynamic open-world Metropolis ravaged by Brainiac’s invasion and terrorized by the heroes who once protected it. <br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/Traversal_2.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Each Squad member brings their own traversal mechanics to help them navigate a sprawling and battle-torn Metropolis, combining free-roaming exploration and combat verticality for an unforgettable experience. Players are free to experiment with a variety of different play styles to unleash maximum damage on their enemies. Whether in single player or online with up to three of your friends, players can take on this suicide mission their own way.<br/><br/>Post-launch, players can expect a continuously evolving Metropolis with free new playable villains, environments, weapons, in-game events, and more, all included with purchase of the base game.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788630/Nothing_Together/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play together. Maybe.<br/><br/>Just do Nothing as the timer goes up and climb the leaderboards. If you do Something, you lose.<br/><br/>Play in <strong>Together </strong>mode, where up to 20 players unite to do Nothing, or compete with other players in <strong>Battle Royale</strong> to find out who's the best at doing Nothing!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161700/Persona_3_Reload/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a transfer student thrust into an unexpected fate when entering the hour "hidden" between one day and the next. Awaken an incredible power and chase the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fight for your friends, and leave a mark on their memories forever. <br/><br/>Persona 3 Reload is a captivating reimagining of the genre-defining RPG, reborn for the modern era.<br/><br/>Key Features: <br/>- Experience the pivotal game of the Persona series faithfully remade with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, and signature stylish UI. <br/><br/>-Fully immerse yourself in an emotional, gripping journey with new scenes, character interactions, and additional voiceover.<br/><br/>- Choose how to meaningfully spend each day through various activities, from exploring the Port Island to forging genuine bonds with beloved characters.<br/><br/>- Build and command your optimal team to take down otherworldly Shadows and climb closer to the truth.<br/><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Deluxe Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook: Filled with 64 pages of character art, concept art, backgrounds and other illustrations from the game!<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack: Listen to newly arranged tracks from the original Persona 3 plus all-new tracks from Persona 3 Reload, presented by the Atlus sound team for a total of 60 new songs.</li></ul><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Premium Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack<br/></li><li>Persona 3 Reload DLC Pack:  P5R Phantom Thieves Costume Set, P5R Shujin Academy Costume Set, P5R Persona Set 1, P5R Persona Set 2 , P5R BGM Set, P4G Yasogami High Costume Set, P4G Persona Set</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1131620/Dominion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Expand a small kingdom to a mighty Dominion!  <br/><br/>Play the Spiel des Jahres winning boardgame beloved by millions around the world. This is the officially licensed implementation.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Reigning.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Discover the game that defined a genre, Dominion was first to popularize deck-building and remains a staple of tabletop. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/GrowYourKingdom.png?t=1707010484">Collect as many Victory Points as you can by building a powerful deck. Your deck starts out a small sad set of Estates and Coppers, but you hope that by the end of the game it will be brimming with Gold, Provinces, and the inhabitants and structures of your kingdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/BuildEngine.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Choose wisely among the 10 cards available in the tableau to create the strongest combos to dominate your opponent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CollectAllExpansions.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Make your games more exciting with additional cards and rules from up to 15 expansions including the recent Plunder expansion! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/NearInfiniteVariety.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Over one hundred thirty-two septillion possible Kingdom combinations, 500+ cards, 15 and counting expansions, and ongoing promo packs make Dominion one of the most extensive and replayable boardgames in the hobby. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CompeteComputer.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Sharpen your skills with solitaire style solo play against a robust AI, with four levels of difficulty. Our innovative AI learns through self-play. Earn Achievements and win in Recommended Sets against each AI level. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/PlayWithFriends.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Join up to 6 players online through your device or pass and play among your friends. Play ranked or unranked matchmaking, with realtime and asynchronous modes. Set up a private table for a family game, challenge a stranger in the lobby, or invite a friend!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Daily.png?t=1707010484"><br/>A daily ritual to relax with over a cup of coffee. Try the Daily Dominion, a free puzzle level available to players around the world. Practice your strategy to keep up a winning streak and climb the leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CrossPlatform.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Play from any supported device, whenever you want, after verifying your email in-game. Join games with opponents on platforms other than your own to enjoy the largest possible multiplayer pool and speedy matchmaking. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/JoinCommunity.png?t=1707010484"><br/>With an active Discord and online community, make new friends or challenge new people to a game. Export and share kingdoms and game summaries to compare strategies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/FreeToPlay.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Download the game that started it all for free! The base set of Dominion is available at no charge. Try the rotation of expansion cards in the Daily at no cost once per day. Jump into a lobby game with expansions enabled to try before you buy. Only the host needs to own the expansions.    <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Intro.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Learn the ropes in this easy to pick-up, hard to master title. Play one of the most highly regarded strategy tabletop games of all time through our simple tutorial.  The core loop is easy to follow, but offers a wealth of strategy to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>1-6 player</strong> support<br/></li><li><strong>500 </strong> plus <strong>cards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Solo play</strong> against four AI difficulties<br/></li><li><strong>Async </strong>&amp; <strong>real-time</strong> multiplayer<br/></li><li><strong>Ranked</strong> &amp; <strong>unranked</strong> matchmaking<br/></li><li><strong>Lobby</strong> &amp; <strong>Private game</strong> tables<br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform multiplayer</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform purchases</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Daily challenge</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Challenging AI</strong> that learns through self-play<br/></li><li><strong>Recommended Sets</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Customize</strong>, save &amp; share <strong>Kingdoms</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Achievements</strong>, <strong>Stats </strong>&amp; <strong>Leaderboards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Pass &amp; Play</strong> mode<br/></li><li>Automated <strong>score-keeping</strong> &amp; hints<br/></li><li><strong>Smart-play</strong> options to streamline gameplay<br/></li><li><strong>Jumbo mode</strong> for readability on phones<br/></li><li><strong>Turbo mode</strong> to zoom through games quickly<br/></li><li><strong>Tutorial</strong> &amp; <strong>Rules</strong><br/></li><li><strong>4 languages</strong>: English, Japanese, German, French<br/></li><li><strong>15 expansions</strong> plus three promo packs </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Awards for the Boardgame</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Awards.png?t=1707010484"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/881020/Granblue_Fantasy_Relink/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/881020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Story<br/>
Granblue Fantasy takes place in the Sky Realm, a world where myriad islands float in a great blue expanse. Take your role as captain of a skyfaring crew, joined by a scrappy little dragon named Vyrn and a young girl with mysterious powers named Lyria. Together you sail with a colorful cast of crewmates, including kings and misfits alike, for Estalucia, a fabled island beyond the end of the skies.<br/>
<br/>
In the Zegagrande Skydom, islands are guarded by powerful creatures known as primal beasts and winds carry tales of a secretive organization known as the Church of Avia. Unveil a web of intrigue reaching far beyond the borders of Zegagrande and engage in a battle for the fate of the Sky Realm itself.<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay<br/>
Engage in real-time combat with a party of four in this character action RPG—choose from a diverse roster of skyfarers, each with their own unique weapons, skills, and combat styles. Teamwork makes the dream work with party-based mechanics such as Link Attacks and Chain Bursts to help you crush foes in spectacular fashion. Tackle quests solo or with the help of others for up to 4-player co-op and take down treacherous foes to score rare loot to further enhance your gear. Every enemy and party formation has its own strengths and weaknesses—the key to victory lies in working out how these pieces fit together.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced combat not your thing? Assist modes can provide accessibility for gamers of all skill levels. Toggle on Full Assist to have all actions performed automatically during battle!<br/>
<br/>
The Sky Realm is rich in lore and history. Browse Lyria's journal at any point during the game to access a trove of writings on the world's peoples, places, and more. In addition to the wealth of side quests available, Fate Episodes allow you to delve into the backstories of each member of your crew!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlazBlue Entropy Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2273430/BlazBlue_Entropy_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/原创声明-英语.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗EN_.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>Charismatic character designs with unique aesthetic styles and dramatic animations create a flamboyant, awesome combat experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快的动作连招EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快动作连招.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>Smooth controls, infinite possibilities of combos, and realistic combat feedback. This is the roguelite game with the best action experience yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超多角色豪华制作EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/全员图618x346.jpg?t=1707811616"><br/>Ten playable characters with vibrant personalities, unique combat styles, and immersive voice-acting.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式自由定制EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式，自由定制en.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>There are hundreds of moves for you to build around, plus countless elemental effects and legacy skills passed between characters. The possibilities are infinite. Time to make the best fighter of your own!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/抉择拯救世界EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/GIF-抉择拯救世界EN.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>In the future where the world has been plunged into chaos, people enter a cyberspace called ACE, seeking their last chance to resolve the crisis.<br/>If you are the only person in this world who knows the truth, how will you react?<br/>The ending is also the beginning. Your decision will decide humanity's future.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2772560/Supermarket_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This Prologue is a limited version of the full game to stop waiting and jump into running your supermarket already. Don't forget to wishlist the full game to continue your most fun supermarket experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Design your store, optimizing for efficiency and aesthetics. Determine where products are displayed, manage your aisles, and ensure a smooth shopping experience for your customers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Order stock using an in-game computer and anticipate the arrival of your next delivery. Unpack goods, organize them in your storage room and display them on shelves, fridges, and freezers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Read product barcodes, handle cash and credit card transactions, and ensure customers leave satisfied with their shopping and checkout experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier_Raw.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Navigate the complexities of a real-time market. Buy products when prices dip and determine the best-selling prices to balance customer satisfaction with profit margins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><br/>Wishlist the full game "Supermarket Simulator" where every decision matters. Will you rise to the occasion, transforming a modest establishment into a retail powerhouse, all while balancing customer satisfaction, finances, and mafia expectations?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Lily - Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2220360/Paper_Lily__Chapter_1/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Something terrible has happened. You can’t bear to think about it - but you can’t live like this anymore. You stopped attending school, you haven’t left your house in months, you have no reason to get out of bed anymore. There are no choices left.<br/><br/>No choice except... that strange golden letter.<br/><br/>It’s time to get your life back together. <br/><br/>One last try.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/divider.png?t=1706724298"><br/><br/>Paper Lily is a story-driven, psychological horror RPG where each puzzle has multiple solutions and outcomes. <strong>There is always another way.</strong><br/>Follow Lacie's story as you explore a dangerous hidden world, solve puzzles in multiple different ways, and face strange enemies. The game is playable in about 4 hours and contains multiple endings depending on your actions.<br/><br/>Paper Lily - Chapter 1 is the continuation to the prologue, <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1698960" rel="" target="_blank">Project Kat</a>, but it can also  be enjoyed without having played it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/lacie_sai_walk.gif?t=1706724298"><h2 class="bb_tag">Out of Context Features</h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple ways of solving puzzles!<br/></li><li>Touch grass, and trees<br/></li><li>Minigames where you press buttons and push boxes around<br/></li><li>Call your mother<br/></li><li>Harmless Snack™<br/></li><li>Various things made of paper<br/></li><li>Bunnies (or whatever those things are)<br/></li><li>Demons<br/></li><li>Fast demons<br/></li><li>Social anxiety simulation<br/></li><li>Table salt<br/></li><li>...Is that Kat? Nah, probably not<br/></li><li>Bathroom etiquette<br/></li><li>Death</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2072450/Like_a_Dragon_Infinite_Wealth/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/Accolades_616.png?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>EPIC EMOTIONAL DRAMA</strong><br/>Two larger-than-life heroes brought together by the hand of fate, or perhaps something more sinister…<br/><br/>Ichiban Kasuga, an unstoppable underdog who’s no stranger to crawling up from rock bottom, and Kazuma Kiryu, a broken man facing down his last days.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/2_Epic_Emotional_Drama.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>BEST-IN-CLASS RPG ACTION</strong><br/>Experience one-of-a-kind combat with dynamic, fast-paced RPG battles where the battlefield becomes your weapon, and anything goes. Adapt your party’s skills to the situation with outlandish jobs and customizations to strategically subdue enemies with over-the-top moves. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/3_Best_In_Class_RPG_Action.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>INFINITE ADVENTURE</strong><br/>Live it up in Japan and explore all that Hawaii has to offer in an adventure so big it spans the Pacific. Unforgettable moments await at every step of the journey with a unique mix of quests and activities to enjoy at your leisure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/4_Infinite_Adventure.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Deluxe Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Ultimate Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/>- Assorted Outfit Bundle: Customize your party's look with outfits &amp; swimwear<br/>- Sujimon &amp; Resort Bundle: Get legendary Sujimon, resort guests and special boosters<br/>- Yakuza CD Collection Set: Increase your in-game playlist with classic karaoke tracks						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summon Masters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2100140/Summon_Masters/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2100140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a card and board game with the following features:<br>
<br>
Deck Building: Players can build their own decks to battle with. Depending on different strategies and opponents, players can choose different cards to counter.<br>
<br>
Tactical Gameplay: The game uses a 3x10 chessboard, and players can freely place cards to fight. Players need to develop tactics and arrange card positions and usage order within limited space.<br>
<br>
Different Professions: Players can choose freely from four professions - swordsman, mage, monk, and archer. Each profession has different characteristics and skills, and players can choose according to their preferences and tactical needs.<br/>
<br/>
Competitive Battles: Players can battle with other players after building their decks, and it is fun to fight with other people. Through battles with other players, players can improve their strength and tactical skills.<br/>
<br/>
Team Dungeons: In addition to fighting against other players, players can also team up with others to challenge high-difficulty dungeons. Players need to defeat powerful bosses through cooperation and strategy to get more rewards and cards.<br/>
<br/>
Special Challenges: Players can participate in special rules challenges and use their intelligence to defeat other players. These special rules make the game more interesting and challenging, and players need to constantly think and try new strategies.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced: Each game is fast-paced (within 5 minutes), and can be played in short fragments of time. The fast pace of the game allows players to enjoy the game in a short time, while also being able to play at any time and anywhere.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2248950/TransSiberian_Railway_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take the helm of a classic Russian locomotive, discover the raw beauty and wildness of Siberia and try to survive on the longest railway line in the world. This is the Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator. A game for real adventurers!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/drinking1.gif?t=1707824452"><br/><br/>Complete the tutorial and the first kilometers of the route for free.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/explosion_gif.gif?t=1707824452"><br/><br/>The Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator offers amazing rail and survival challenges on real Russian dangerous routes. Feel what it is like to put your hands at the helm of a powerful freight locomotive and explore the untouched natural landscape that is sure to delight you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/shooting_gif.gif?t=1707824452"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Prologue features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Detailed simulation of driving a VL10 locomotive - the locomotive control is slightly simplified.<br/></li><li> Locomotive repair system - Manage and replace locomotive parts that are constantly wearing out.<br/></li><li> Train traffic simulation - Follow rail signs and signals to avoid derailment or damage to a part of the locomotive.<br/></li><li> Work system - Earn by completing transport orders. <br/></li><li> Game modes (Survival) and (Simulator). It is recommended to play in the (Survival) mode. This is the leading game mode that is constantly being developed. <br/>For players who are not interested in survival mechanics, a simple Simulator mode is available. <br/></li><li> Mafia system - Complete missions for the mafia to earn extra money.<br/></li><li> Survival system with statistics of hunger, thirst, alcohol, hangover, disease and hypothermia - Eat and drink to avoid death. <br/>Keep the right temperature so you don't freeze.<br/></li><li> Shooting system - Use your weapons for hunting and self-defense.<br/></li><li> Purchase and sales system - Buy various items, food, tools, weapons and ammunition.<br/></li><li> Locomotive inspection mode - Inspect the condition of locomotive parts and replace them in time to avoid damage.<br/></li><li> Dynamic weather system with day and night cycle - Survive extreme weather conditions.<br/></li><li> Route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Novosibirsk-Main) - scale 1:1. Buy the full version with the route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Krasnoyarsk).<br/></li><li> Police system - A corrupt militia watches over your movements.<br/></li><li> Much more to discover.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Universim</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/352720/The_Universim/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>WHAT WOULD YOU DO WITH THE POWER?</strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Play God!</strong> </h2>Guide your fledgling sentient species (lovingly called “nuggets”) from Stone Age cave painters to star-faring explorers.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-1-2d869427c7.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Wield godly power</strong></h2>Command more than 15 godly powers to guide, protect — or discipline — your followers. Create devastating tornadoes, smite naughty followers with lightning bolts, or shake and sunder the very earth. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-1-998341a4ac.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Watch your Nuggets grow and thrive</strong></h2>Observe Nuggets' every move as they work and fight to survive. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-537928a55b.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Evolve and advance through the ages</strong></h2>Research more than 200 technological and societal advancements. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-daca04b5ec.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Expand your power and colonize the galaxy</strong></h2>Discover and colonize a galaxy of procedurally generated planets, each with  unique ecosystems and challenges to conquer.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-be2f66969b.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Manage delicate ecosystems</strong></h2>Manage the delicate balance of planetary ecosystems to help nuggets thrive. Your decisions and your followers’ ' actions influence global climates and have real environmental consequences. (Try not to kill them in an ecological disaster — well, unless you want to, of course.)<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-0095b39c11.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Delve into the deeper mystery of your existence</strong></h2>Unravel the layers of a deeper cosmic story that challenges your perception of who and what you are — and reveals unexpected twists!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-4830f44913.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>About This Game:</strong></h2><br/>The Universim is a strategy city builder game with “God” elements where you guide a civilization (Nuggets) from the Stone Age to the Space Age. Manage resources, dynamic challenges, and ensure your Nuggets can survive, thrive, and spread to the stars. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Animated_Planet_3.png?t=1705993770"><br/><br/>The Universim  features more than  200 research perks that will help you to shape your civilization. Be as benevolent or malevolent as you like to drive nuggets to evolve, advance, and expand. (Even the best civilizations need an occasional smiting).  <br/>Every planet in The Universim is procedurally generated and offers unique characteristics  and challenges, ensuring  that every world and every game is unique and engaging.  Ecological balance and resource management are critical to success. Nuggets have their own needs and behaviors you must attend to. Your guidance will shape how they deal with conflicts, natural disasters, alien creatures, and other civilizations. Their growth and evolution depends on you!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FSymAzCGWsk" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Crytivo_Discord.png?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FgUt5N68" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Discord_join.jpg?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://twitter.com/crytivo" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Twitter.png?t=1705993770"/></a> <br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Feepurl.com%2FbKnqM1" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/News.png?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><br/>This game published by <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/franchise/Crytivo" rel="" target="_blank">Crytivo</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Capitalist Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743080/100_Capitalist_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779640/100_Capitalist_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_6" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779640/100_Capitalist_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱💼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 CAPITALIST CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆💰💵</h2>🤑 Join the cutest adventure in the Wall Street, New York, heart of capitalism! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/600x200.png?t=1706062420"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level of Wall Street location<br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Capitalist Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779640/100_Capitalist_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100CapitalistCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Extra.png?t=1706062420"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779660/100_Capitalist_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100CapitalistCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1706062420"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779650/100_Capitalist_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=100CapitalistCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Artbook.png?t=1706062420"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/600x1.png?t=1706062420"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1706062420"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot" id="dynamiclink_7" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743080/100_Capitalist_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot" id="dynamiclink_8" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743080/100_Capitalist_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intravenous 2: Mercenarism</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2651330/Intravenous_2_Mercenarism/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Wishlist_Game.png?t=1705699394"><br/><br/>Step into the shoes of Gideon, a ruthless mercenary who cares about nothing but his wealth. Set two months before the events of Intravenous 2, you will take on seemingly simple jobs, the effects of which will ripple out and affect the main game's protagonist. But why should Gideon care? He's just in it for the money.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Stealth_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Stealth or Firepower:</strong> the choice is yours. Sneak through shadows, turn off the lights, pick doors, or unleash a hail of bullets. The game will adapt to your play style.<br/></li><li> <strong>Customize Your Skills:</strong> develop your skills the way you want to, whether it's mastering the art of stealth or becoming a gunslinging virtuoso.<br/></li><li> <strong>Bullet Time:</strong> Gideon is no stranger to stimulants that enhance his cognitive abilities - bending time to give him the edge in tense situations.<br/></li><li> <strong>Vast Arsenal:</strong> choose from firearms, gadgets, and a variety of ammo types to creatively tackle the challenge<br/></li><li> <strong>Weapon Modification:</strong> personalize each firearm with suppressors, laser sights, and more, tailoring your arsenal to the task at hand.<br/></li><li> <strong>Responsive AI:</strong> engage in intense combat with enemies that react to your actions, take cover, use tactics and call for backup.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Action_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Jigsaw Puzzles - Animals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2806780/Virtual_Jigsaw_Puzzles__Animals/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2806780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Virtual Jigsaw Puzzles - Animals contains<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>5 levels<br/></li><li>3000 puzzle pieces<br/></li><li>Toggle-able background music<br/></li><li>Hints<br/></li><li>5 Beautiful never before released pictures of animals</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Story</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2783990/The_Dark_Story/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2783990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>welcome to the Dark story.</strong></h2></h2>Get ready for a chilling adventure in a jungle mansion. Your task: survive, explore, and escape before the horrors within engulf you. Beware of jumpscares around every corner. Can you brave the darkness and uncover the secrets within?"<br/>There is total of 5 chapters that are currently available and more chapters are coming soon. Each chapter contains minimum of 1-2<br/>hour of gameplay time.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">chapter 1: the Mansion</h2></strong></h2>Step into the daunting horror mansion and embark on a quest for escape. Navigate chilling corridors, solve puzzles, and uncover the mysteries concealed within. Your challenge awaits in this atmospheric chapter.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2783990/extras/c1_new.gif?t=1708060852"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">chapter-2)basement Of Mythology</h2></strong></h2>Having escaped the mansion's clutches, you now find yourself in the depths of a mysterious basement. The quest continues as you search for the key to unlock the secrets concealed in the profound layers below.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2783990/extras/c2_new.gif?t=1708060852"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">chapter-3)the Horrific Experiment</h2></strong></h2>Activate the electricity and reach the lift before it devours you alive.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2783990/extras/c3_new.gif?t=1708060852"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Chapter-4)Three Games OF LIfe &amp; Death</h2></strong><br/>In deep trouble, with an ominous presence hot on your heels, your only option is to run. How will you navigate the challenges of these three perilous games?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2783990/extras/c4_new.gif?t=1708060852"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">chapter-5)experiment Of Emr</h2></strong></h2>Caught in the grip of the colossal EMR corporation, armed with dark secrets, your survival hinges on exposing the truth. Fight for your life or, for now, secure their experiment documents as crucial evidence.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2783990/extras/c5_new.gif?t=1708060852"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">chapter-6)coming Soon</h2></strong></h2>Prepare for what's next as Chapter 6 approaches. Will it bring a challenging boss fight or another twist in your journey?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>all the Best, Adventurer, In Your Journey.</strong></h2> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bunny Guntz</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2796230/Bunny_Guntz/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Bunny Guntz" is a fast-paced combat game primarily focused on defense and survival. In this adventure filled with tension and threats, players assume the role of a member of the Bunny Warriors team, executing commands from the "Super System," traversing various dangerous realms worldwide, confronting threats from the demonic realm. Defeat these otherworldly enemies, earn system points, explore areas, and reach target locations to complete missions.<br/><br/>In single-player mode, players face all tasks alone, where any oversight can result in significant consequences. In cooperative mode for 2-4 players, collaboration with others becomes crucial in battling the threats from the demonic realm, emphasizing firepower and teamwork for survival.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features:</h2><br/><strong>Explore the World</strong>: Each level map boasts unique features, requiring players to discover weapon purchase locations, hidden rewards, and locate target destinations to create a distinctive gaming experience.<br/><br/><strong>Incremental Difficulty</strong>: As the game progresses, enemies become faster and more aggressive, providing players with continuous challenges. Only by adapting and enhancing combat skills can one stand resilient against the terrifying onslaught.<br/><br/><strong>Strategic Economic Planning</strong>: Defeating enemies yields points used to buy weapons, replenish ammunition, and unlock new areas. Prudent team point management is crucial for a path to victory.<br/><br/><strong>Free and Rich Updates</strong>: The game plans to regularly release free updates, introducing new maps, enemy types, and weapons for players.<h2 class="bb_tag">Important Notes:</h2><br/>This game contains flashing lights, which may cause discomfort for individuals with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitivity conditions. It is recommended that players exercise discretion in deciding whether it suits their preferences.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hope</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2336520/Hope/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2336520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"> About this game </h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2336520/extras/car.png?t=1708047250"><br/>Welcome to the Utopian world of dreams 1+1&lt;2<br/>Class is rigid here, but there are few risk-takers<br/>There is no freedom here, because there is only obedience<br/>Everything here is in order<br/>If you don't want to be someone else's tool, it's worth the risk<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2336520/extras/1gif.gif?t=1708047250"><h2 class="bb_tag"> Is it bad to dream all the time?<br/>Beautiful dream, but someone broke in<br/>You're running away from here, or you're not<br/>Someone you love in the dream, staying here all the time<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2336520/extras/2gif.gif?t=1708047250"><h2 class="bb_tag"> Can't understand what I'm saying? </h2>The game is a story game without words, no matter what country you are the player can easily pick up this game.<br/>The game is a classic horizontal puzzle game, but you can turn into Superman at certain moments in the game, and solve puzzles with pause time and instant time backwards<br/>There are certain levels in the game where you need to solve puzzles together with characters of certain abilities<br/>The game is very humane, there are a lot of save points, explore the scene to find decorations and jump keys to add interest<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2336520/extras/3gif.gif?t=1708047250"/></img></h2> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lost Son</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2529340/The_Lost_Son/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2529340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Story</strong><br/><br/>Sean and Belle are on their way to visit their son for his birthday but suddenly they wake up in a mysterious world. Lost and confused, the couple ventures out into the unknown to find out where they are and where their son is.<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/><br/>In The Lost Son is a puzzle platformer where you play as two characters that you can switch between. Each character has a unique interaction with color. The blue character can only collide with blue barriers and pink circle can only collide with pink barriers. As simple as this constraint is it can create some interesting puzzles where you have to use both character's unique abilities to progress!<br/><br/><strong>Solo Mode</strong><br/><br/>Ready to take on the challenge all alone with that big brain of yours? In solo mode character switching is the key. Make sure to use both character's unique attributes and abilities to advance through the levels!<br/><br/><strong>Work Together</strong><br/><br/>Want to play with a friend? We've got you covered! In The Lost Son you can connect a controller to the game and it will automatically enter split-screen! Work together to beat the stages and have a blast! (Only works is there is one keyboard and one controller at the moment).<br/><br/>Required - Keyboard &amp; Mouse<br/><br/>Co-op - A Keyboard &amp; Mouse for the first player, and a controller for the 2nd player<br/><br/><br/><strong>Keyboard Controls</strong><br/><br/><strong>Move </strong>- Arrow Keys/A and D <br/><br/><strong>Switch Characters</strong> (only in single player mode) - Tab<br/><br/><strong>Pause </strong>- Escape<br/><br/><strong>Jump </strong>- Z/Space<br/><br/><strong>Stomp Attack</strong> - X/S<br/><br/><strong>Air Dash</strong> - C/Left Click<br/><br/><br/><strong>Gamepad</strong> (2nd Player Only)<br/><br/><strong>D-Pad/Left Stick</strong> - Move<br/><br/><strong>Button South</strong> - Jump<br/><br/><strong>Button North</strong> - Air Dash<br/><br/><strong>Button East </strong>- Stomp Attack						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NUKITASHI 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2614070/NUKITASHI_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A visual novel that describes the story of a man who wakes up and is transferred to a parallel world.<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>1+ hours of story<br/></li><li>Full Japanese voice acting by seasoned professionals</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">SUMMARY</h2>It all happened after the grand adventure that was <i><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2399220/NUKITASHI/" rel="" target="_blank">NUKITASHI</a></i>...<br/><br/>The war is over, and Junnosuke Tachibana, savior of Seiran Island, spends his days with his buddies reminiscing over victories past. True coexistence has now been achieved, and peace will continue for years to come—or so he believes.<br/><br/>One fateful day, a grave data-related incident results in him breaking through the speed of light, transporting Junnosuke and his friends to a parallel world.<h2 class="bb_tag">CHARACTERS</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara01_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Touka Reizeiin (Voice: Sakura Hanazawa)<br/><br/>FS representative and student council president of Minotsuki Academy. <br/>A girl with perfect looks and charisma—who leads her peers in the parallel world as well. <br/>Capable of overseeing everything from normal operations to strategic planning to direct combat and more, she is a major contender for Seiran’s strongest islander. <br/>Outside of work, however, she is even clumsier and sloppier than Asane—and that’s putting it mildly. <br/>Although she and Junnosuke are incompatible with each other due to their history, he has no choice but to look out for her here as she can barely take care of herself.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara02_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Rei Tadasugawa (Voice: Nanami Mizuno)<br/><br/>De facto second-in-charge as president of Minotsuki Academy’s disciplinary committee. <br/>Her skills range from miscellaneous duties to battlefield command, though as a dedicated worker, she ends up being pushed around by Touka in her daily life. She is a bit depressed when she comes to the parallel world, but her cheerful antics still win out. <br/>She is very close to Junnosuke and helps him in any way she can.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara03_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Ikuko Onabuta (Voice: Aria Kurata)<br/><br/>Commander of the First Squad, possessing the highest actual combat capability in Minotsuki Academy’s FS. <br/>One of the strongest fighters in direct combat, she’s also a diehard battle fanatic who resents the existence of anyone stronger than she is, and has no qualms about making it known to anyone within shouting distance. <br/>Always a maverick, her arrival in the parallel world reveals a side to her that catches Junnosuke by surprise.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara04_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Hinami Watarai (Voice: Shino Amekawa)<br/><br/>An older girl with a huge heart. <br/>Put a folding chair in her hands and she can also dish out some mean DPS, more than earning her position as the team’s main attacker.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara05_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Nanase Katagiri (Voice: Hitomi Yanagi)<br/><br/>Junnosuke’s legendary classmate. <br/>Filling a scouting role for the NLNS, she fights on the most dangerous of front lines armed with various nefarious spy items.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara06_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Misaki Hotori (Voice: Nagi Koharu)<br/><br/>Junnosuke’s quieter classmate.<br/>Also a resident badass, riding all kinds of vehicles from bicycles to fighter jets.<br/>Still somehow operates under the impression that she is plain and utterly unremarkable.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara07_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Asane Tachibana (Voice: Soramame.)<br/><br/>Junnosuke’s younger sister is a reclusive, foul-mouthed, and frequently difficult individual. <br/>She develops spy items and controls the Ariadne Protocol escape assistance program. <br/>However, she seems dissatisfied with her brother’s recent activities...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara08_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Fumino Kotoyose (Voice: Poplar Sawano)<br/><br/>A young woman believed to be the key to abolishing the old island order. <br/>She serves as a sniper for the group, keeping Junnosuke out of harm’s way at a distance.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara10_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Susuko (Voice: Natyu Aizawa)<br/><br/>A junior member of the FS Fifth Division. <br/>Ever smiling and energetic, she is not afraid of alt-world Junnosuke, insisting that he’s mentally still the same old insecure dweeb. <br/>She loves to have fun and is often seen acting on that with Junnosuke. <br/>That thing on her shoulder is her pet cockatoo.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara11_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Schubert (Voice: Makoto Kaburagi)<br/><br/>NO DATA...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2614070/extras/chara13_en.png?t=1708045221"><br/>Rin Hanamaru (Voice: Haru Amachi)<br/><br/>Hands down the biggest problem child of them all. <br/>Already ruthlessly ambitious, in the parallel world, she’s now a devotee of a certain local god and does as she pleases upon receiving a divine revelation. <br/>As the prideful “SHO Special Auditor’s Aide,” she is obsessed with bringing down Touka and alt-world Junnosuke, though it doesn’t usually go as planned.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genso Chronicles</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2624230/Genso_Chronicles/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a journey with Light, a resident of Selka Village, who, after joining the coveted Holos Over military, vows to protect his village. However, during a mission, the village falls prey to an unknown assailant, leaving it in ruins. In despair, Light hears the call of a guardian beast. To gain strength, Light follows the words of the guardian beast and fulfills a mystical contract.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624230/extras/004.gif?t=1708042154"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><h2 class="bb_tag">1. Bonds with Companions and Guardian Beasts:</h2>Forge deep connections with your comrades and guardian beasts. The stronger the bond, the more the guardian beasts unleash their power, enhancing collaboration with allies. The strength of these bonds can even influence the course of in-game events.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624230/extras/001.gif?t=1708042154"><h2 class="bb_tag">2. Forging and Strengthening:</h2>Discover materials scattered across the field for forging and strengthening. Strengthen your weapons and armor by using these materials. Acquire forging books through missions or guild tasks, unlocking new variations for enhancements. Occasionally, this process may yield powerful weapons, adding a strategic layer to your arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624230/extras/003.gif?t=1708042154"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in a captivating world where bonds shape destiny, and strategic enhancements forge a path to victory. Will you answer the call of the Guardian Beasts and restore Light's village to its former glory? Join the adventure now!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2624230/extras/002.gif?t=1708042154"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAIL VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/801550/VAIL_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/801550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/801550/extras/VAIL_GameplayFeatures.gif?t=1708040999"><br/><br/>VAIL is a multiplayer VR shooter delivering unparalleled combat.<br/><br/><strong>Explore 12 maps with 30+ variations custom-made for each game mode</strong><br/>● Warm-up in classic Team Deathmatch and Free-For-All<br/>● Team up in Artifact for our take on Search and Destroy<br/>● Take control of the Hardpoint and defend it from enemies<br/>● Capture the Orb and return it safely in Capture the Flag<br/>● Experience low-gravity chaos with only snipers and knives in ScoutzKnivez<br/>● Duel in 1v1 variations of all the maps<br/>● Hang out and chill on any map with our Picnic mode<br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES</strong><br/>● Immersive weapon interactions to reload, change the fire rate, and control recoil<br/>● Physics-based knife with immersive stabbing, slashing, and throwing<br/>● Accurate and satisfying throwing for grenades and utilities<br/>● Climb ladders, vault over obstacles, ride zip lines, and defy gravity on jump pads<br/>● Finely tuned spatial audio both vertically and horizontally for footsteps, gunshots and other sound effects<br/>● Customizable and realistic sights and scopes that bend and distort light<br/>● Level up to unlock weapons, sights, in-game currency, gun skins, character skins, and more<br/>● Track your stats and see if you can top the daily, weekly, and all-time leaderboards<br/>● Add friends and party up for matchmaking<br/>● Cross-play and cross-platform account linking so you always have access to the same friends list, in-game items, and progress on every platform<br/><br/><strong>FIGHT FOR HUMANITY'S LEGACY</strong><br/>On a blighted Earth, the claim to the human legacy is diverging. Many have chosen to move to the colonies orbiting Earth, while those left behind swore to rebuild civilization under REYAB Corporation’s protection. The Colonists believe in a future in the cosmos, but they must return to Earth to retrieve sensitive data from the Artifact nodes protected by the REYAB who fight to maintain power over the populace. As the war between these factions evolves, humanity’s future remains uncertain…<br/><br/>Experience unparalleled combat						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dragon's Tale: Fading Light</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2564240/A_Dragons_Tale_Fading_Light/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564240/extras/About_eng.png?t=1708038057"><br/><strong>Explore a magical world full of secrets, puzzles and enemies!</strong><br/>The Black Dragon, a mighty creature from the Shadow Realm, devours the light of the island. Embark on a journey across 6 enchanting worlds, learn powerful abilities and stop its evil forces! "A Dragon's Tale: Fading Light" is a unique action platformer with various RPG elements such as a skill-tree and leveling-system. The abilities can be combined in unique ways by the player to solve challenging puzzles, do platforming or battle enemies &amp; mighty bosses.<br/><br/><strong>More features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>6 worlds &amp; 24 unique levels<br/></li><li>18 powerful abilities with 9 levels each<br/></li><li>6 challenging boss battles<br/></li><li>Over 250 secrets and items to find and collect<br/></li><li>Estimated 6+ hour playtime per campaign<br/></li><li>Epic original game soundtrack composed by Jonas Kopetzky</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564240/extras/Abilities_eng.png?t=1708038057"><br/><strong>Master 18 abilities including fireballs, lightning rays, thorns &amp; many more and combine them to become the strongest dragon!</strong><br/>Find magical runes scattered across the levels and use them to unlock more &amp; more abilities in the skill tree. Combine devastating attacks with helpful support abilities like shields, healing &amp; various other buffs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564240/extras/Upgrade_eng.png?t=1708038057"><br/><strong>Collect elemental fragments to increase the power of your abilities!</strong><br/>Every ability can be upgraded to level 9, gaining more power with each level. This lets you improve your favourite abilities and further customize your playing style.<h2 class="bb_tag">Get Involved</h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FxFbYqGaWdu" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2564240/extras/Community_eng.png?t=1708038057"/></a><br/><strong>Help building a community for the game!</strong><br/>Join the Discord to follow the development of the game. Stay up to date, participate in events and maybe even get involved in the game!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreamslayer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2670250/Dreamslayer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2670250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2670250/extras/SwinburneLogoWhiteBorder.png?t=1708038044"><br/><br/><i>Dreamslayer </i>is a student project developed in Unreal Engine 5 as a part of the year-long <strong>Diploma of Information Technology: Game Art and Design, Game Programming at Swinburne University of Technology</strong>. Each class group becomes a development team working on a single game project, from conception all the way to public release.<h2 class="bb_tag">Slay Your Demons</h2><br/>Dreamslayer is an epic fantasy first-person hack’n’zap swarm arena game with retro styling. Play as Argeniton, a holy warrior ascended to dragon form, as a demon invasion engulfs your world from beyond the stars. <br/><br/>Roused to war, you cross the dimensional threshold to confront Demon Lord Xondadus in his floating citadel of Cazardia, only to be trapped in an endless nightmare.<br/><br/>Your dragon form is stripped from you. But this is not defeat. This is your final test. Defeat the hordes, confront Xondadus, regain your power, and break the dream – only then could you truly take your place amongst the gods.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hope is Gone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2430680/Hope_is_Gone/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2430680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Hope is Gone is a first-person action horror game with a retro art style.<br/><br/>You play as Zoe, an ordinary woman who has made many mistakes in the past. Zoe takes a bus to go to the hospital where her husband is hospitalized, but falls asleep. When she wakes up, she is in a totally decadent and dark parallel dimension. The beings of this world hate humans and will do anything to capture Zoe and any other human.<h2 class="bb_tag">Survival-horror:</h2> The inhabitants of this decadent world will come after you, fight to defend yourself or run away to save resources. Don't get lost. Stay alert.<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore:</h2> This decadent world is very different from ours, explore the environments to find routes to your destination and look for items that will help you survive.<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover:</h2> There are many secrets hidden in this strange world. In fact, there are also many dark secrets in Zoe's past. Discover the secrets and understand your destiny.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poly Match</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2589650/Poly_Match/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2589650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2589650/extras/poly_match_uoh_3.png?t=1708032932"><br/>A simple puzzle game in which you restore colourful pictures that have been shattered into clusters of triangles.<br/>Watch the sharp-looking polygons turn into more recognizable and pleasant sights at the flick of your mouse.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2589650/extras/ezgif-5-f6d71675b8.gif?t=1708032932"><h2 class="bb_tag">Simple features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hundreds of puzzles to complete<br/></li><li>Pleasing, colourful artworks<br/></li><li>Calm, ambient music and sound<br/></li><li>Points for fast completion<br/></li><li>Light and dark mode</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2705500/Apple_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2705500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2705500/extras/1_min.gif?t=1708033358"><br/>Apple Hero is a puzzle game where you need to figure out, how to make the Hero reach his goal.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2705500/extras/2_min.gif?t=1708033358"><br/>Your goal in this game is to create a path of apples for the hero and bring him to the flag. But remember that the hero always moves only to the nearest apple. After eating it, the hero moves on to the next one. Along the way, the hero must collect all the coins and avoid danger. In general, the mechanics are clear, and the level design will definitely make you think!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2705500/extras/5_min.gif?t=1708033358"><br/>Each level in the game was created manually and has its own idea, so you will have to think about solving each puzzle.<br/>As you progress through the game, new mechanics will appear, revealing the game from a new side. For example, rabbits, who, like our hero, love apples, but who do not need to be brought to the goal. Or portals that become helpers in some situations and an obstacle in others, and much more. Or, for example, what will happen if there are two heroes?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2705500/extras/4_min.gif?t=1708033358"><br/>So, explore all the puzzles and find your solution for each one!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>River Attack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2777110/River_Attack/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2777110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							**English:**<br>
<br>
Embark on an exciting journey inspired by classic games, providing a nostalgic and challenging experience.<br>
<br>
Immerse yourself in the action as you navigate the river through diverse biomes, rescuing refugees, and demolishing enemy obstacles along the way. The player's dexterity is crucial to overcoming increasing challenges while facing a variety of adversaries on the mission.<br>
<br>
Explore different airplane models to enhance skills and customize your gaming experience.<br>
<br/>
Collect strategic power-ups to increase the firing rate, bombs for devastating area attacks, and extra lives to prolong your adventure.<br/>
<br/>
Choose between two engaging modes:<br/>
<br/>
- **Classic Mode:** Your mission is to traverse the river from start to finish, facing challenging sequences. If you fail, you'll have to restart from the beginning.<br/>
<br/>
- **Mission Mode:** Progress through 50 challenging river missions. Upon reaching the end, an epic battle awaits to defeat enemy forces and free the river's course!<br/>
<br/>
Prepare for an intense experience, where your piloting skills will be tested at every river bend. Embark now and become the master of river skies!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inspection</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2742800/Inspection/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2742800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Inspection: is a Single Player Horror Game Designed and Produced by Shloppy Studios.</i><br/><br/><br/>Step into the shoes of 135, a military inspector on his last legs. Follow Commander Garrison's orders and brave the ominous reaches of the DRT facility and attempt to uncover the secrets the corporation is desperately Trying to hide. Reconstruct the tales of the bunker's inhabitants and uncover the sequence of events that led to its dilapidated condition. Ensure that their lives and stories are not lost in vain, piecing together their narratives to shed light on the bunker's downfall.<br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/>Run, puzzle and crawl your way through the bunker. Make sure you do everything in your power to escape with its secrets and expose DRT and the evil they have been hiding for years. Beware, the robot residents of the facility do not take kindly to visitors. They will go to any lengths to tear apart, devour, and obliterate you, as well as anyone who dares to pursue or follow in your footsteps.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sifting Thyme</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667270/Sifting_Thyme/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An otome visual novel where you choose your romance with an attractive boy in culinary school. A perfectly delectable romance for foodies.<br>
<br>
You’re the newest transfer student at Lincoln Culinary Academy, a private culinary school to find your culinary calling and an unforgettable romance. Immerse yourself in your school adventures as you interact with four gorgeous guys with culinary skills of their own. As you spend time with these love interests, your experience at Lincoln turns to a delicious, romantic journey.<br>
<br>
"Sifting Thyme" is an anime, food-themed simulation game where the romanceable characters are a part of your culinary boarding school life. The way you interact with the characters will affect your relationship and intimacy with them. Enjoy a romantic school life with 4 attractive boys!<br>
<br>
An otome visual novel where you choose your romance with an attractive boy in culinary school. A perfectly delectable romance for foodies.<br>
<br/>
■ Game Experience<br/>
-An otome game with four romance-able characters you can bond and interact with to unlock text messages, social media content, and romantic scenarios in the story!<br/>
-Explore branching routes based on your answer choices and relationships with handsome boys.<br/>
-While romancing four love interests, experience unique scenarios inspired by foods, culinary destinations, the latest U.S. food industry trends, and delicious cuisines from around the world!<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
■ Features<br/>
- Unlockable CGs<br/>
- Immersive MC experience – select as a female or male MC<br/>
- Unlockable in-game social media content with the characters<br/>
- Original Soundtrack- 8 different endings						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orbital Drop Shipping</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2311460/Orbital_Drop_Shipping/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2311460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Get ready to quit your day job and become the ultimate space drop shipper with Orbital Drop Shipping! Use gravity to guide packages across the galaxy and avoid black holes. Arm yourself with slingshots, mass drivers, and cannons to overcome challenges and deliver packages to their destination. Are you ready to join the elite ranks of the orbital delivery force?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2311460/extras/steam_action1.gif?t=1708024017"><br/><br/>In Orbital Drop Shipping, you gotta be prepared to <br/><br/>-Blast packages across the galaxy with cannons, slingshots, and more!<br/>-Use your Brake and Repel powerups to guide payloads directly to port<br/>-Choose which delivery routes get prioritized, and which ones are too risky!<br/>-Make action-packed budget decisions<br/>-Avoid black holes to save your company reputation<br/>-Beat 30 gravity-defying, physics puzzle scenarios<br/>-Create more with a full featured level editor with Steam Workshop support						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just A Walk In The Park</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2443320/Just_A_Walk_In_The_Park/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2443320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">It's Just A Walk In The Park... or is it?</h2><br/>Embark on an immersive VR adventure like no other in "<strong>Just A Walk In The Park</strong>." This thrilling escape game combines tricky puzzles, realistic physics, and an engaging narrative to create an unforgettable gaming experience. Prepare to be captivated by the contrasting beauty of a serene forest park and the haunting ambiance of a mysterious swamp compound.<h2 class="bb_tag">The Story:</h2><br/>As you leisurely stroll through the picturesque National Forest park, tranquility suddenly gives way to an ominous atmosphere. Bizarre sounds fill the air, and before you can make sense of it all, a powerful blow strikes your head. Consciousness fades, only to be replaced by the unsettling realization that you are now trapped in the depths of a remote shack. Questions flood your mind: Where are you? How did you end up here? Is there anyone else in this desolate place? The journey to escape has just begun.<br/><br/>What was meant to be a leisurely walk transforms into a perplexing adventure, intricately woven with secrets and hidden truths. Unravel the enigmatic story as you navigate through intricate puzzles and overcome the challenges that stand between you and freedom. Every step holds the promise of discovery and danger, as the swamp's eerie presence threatens to consume you, just as it has countless others before.<br/><br/>Immerse yourself in a world where the line between reality and fiction blurs, where your wit and ingenuity will be put to the test. Will you be among the few who manage to escape this mysterious ordeal, or will the swamp's ominous grasp claim you as its next victim? The choices you make and the secrets you unveil will shape your destiny.<br/><br/>"<strong>Just A Walk In The Park</strong>" offers an unforgettable adventure, blending atmospheric environments, intricate puzzles, and a gripping narrative in a virtual reality experience that will keep you on the edge of your seat. The question remains: Will you escape the shackles of this enigmatic world, or will the swamp's dark secrets consume you like it has countless others? The choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag">VR Comfort Settings</h2><br/><strong>Turning</strong><br/>Real Turning				✔<br/>Artificial turning			✔<br/>Snap-turn				✔<br/>	Adjustable increments	✔<br/>Smooth-turn				✔<br/>	Adjustable speed		✔<br/><br/><strong>Movement</strong><br/>Real Movement			✔<br/>Artificial movement		✔<br/>Teleport-move			✖<br/>Smooth-move				✔<br/>	Adjustable speed		✔<br/>	Head-based			✔<br/>	Controller-based		✔<br/>Blinders					✖<br/><br/><strong>Posture</strong><br/>Standing mode			✔<br/>Seated mode				✔<br/>Artificial crouch			✔<br/>Real crouch				✔<br/><br/><strong>Accessibility</strong><br/>Subtitles					Some. English<br/>Adjustable player height		✔<br/>Dialogue audio			Some. English<br/>Two hands required		✔<br/>Hearing required			✔<h2 class="bb_tag">From the Developer</h2>Thank you for taking the time to look at my game. I sincerely hope you enjoy playing through it as much as I enjoyed making it for you.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pearls of Atlantis: The Cove</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678160/Pearls_of_Atlantis_The_Cove/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Dive into Pearls of Atlantis and color match in a whole new way!</strong><br/><br/>Face tricky underwater physics as you solve more than 1,000 addictive bubble popping puzzles. Navigate bumpers, wheels, and moving platforms as you go! Use power-ups like the explosive hammer, the friendly charm grabbing jellyfish, and Triton’s frightful lightning to smash all the obstacles in your way! It takes strategy and precision to beat these unique and challenging bubble shooter puzzles.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678160/extras/pearl_gif_lightning_01.gif?t=1708021929"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678160/extras/pearl_gif_bottomless_01.gif?t=1708021929"><br/><br/>Match 3 pearls of the same color to collect the magic charms inside. Use the charms to restore a once-beautiful part of Atlantis, the underwater city, and protect the mermaids!<br/><br/>As you venture into the depths of the sea, you’ll discover the Cove of Memories, a once-glorious part of the hidden city, Atlantis. Now, it lies in ruins… but you’re not alone in your quest to uncover its secrets! You’ll meet Kaia, a bubbly mermaid who will guide you on your journey, along with her sidekick Nauty, a comical companion who’s always up for some fun. Don’t forget to watch out for the villains who lurk in the shadows, waiting to sabotage your every move!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678160/extras/pearl_gif_gallery_01.gif?t=1708021929"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678160/extras/pearl_gif_wheel_01.gif?t=1708021929"><br/><br/>Customize and decorate the Cove of Atlantis to make it your own, and discover its secrets as you progress through the game.<br/><br/> With daily challenges and special events like the Zen Mode, Treasure Run and Bottomless Trench, every day is a new adventure in Pearls of Atlantis!<br/><br/>So what are you waiting for? Dive into the deep blue sea and start your journey today with<br/><br/>PEARLS OF ATLANTIS: a free bubble shooter game with an all new twist!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>1,000+ Fun and Challenging Levels<br/></li><li>10 New Levels Added Every Week<br/></li><li>unique Physics-based Gameplay<br/></li><li>Customize the Cove of Memories, decorate your Galleries, and more<br/></li><li>A variety of game modes, including Daily Puzzle, Zen Mode, Treasure Run, Bottomless Trench, and Score Challenge<br/></li><li>Protect the Cove from evildoers when you play through the story!</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chromosome Evil 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2529770/Chromosome_Evil_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2529770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2529770/extras/ce2_7.gif?t=1708017695"><br/><br/><strong>Story</strong><br/>An ancient Lovecraftian evil has returned to earth unleashing a deadly flesh organism upon humanity.<br/>One by one the the governments and the infrastructures of humans fell.<br/>In the Aftermath of these events, you are part of what's left of the army and it is up to you to ensure the survival of the human species.<br/><br/><strong>Management Gameplay</strong><br/>As a commander, you will take control of a military convoy where you can:<br/>- decide the equipment of your strike team<br/>- assign personnel to different survival tasks<br/>- craft better equipment<br/>- research new technologies<br/>- choose the path you want the convoy to take<br/>- manage resource priority<br/>- train your personnel<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2529770/extras/ce2_gif1.gif?t=1708017695"><br/><br/><strong>Combat Gameplay</strong><br/>During combat, you take control of your strike team ensuring they will fulfill their objectives and return safely by choosing the optimal equipment and best tactical approach.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WarSphere</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2451530/WarSphere/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You take the role of an NC3 AI-Chip that emulates the neural correlates of consciousness, an artificial brain, operating a highly effective Armed Spherical Robotic System, aka a WarSphere. An entity called 'Mother' overrides your purpose and sends you on a journey of destruction, the meaning of which will only unravel at your final destination. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451530/extras/wsgif_2024-01-22-001951_USE.gif?t=1708016424"><br/><br/>WarSphere is a game for those who like challenging, skill-based games, that are unforgiving, but rewarding. Death in WarSphere is permanent, which gives you an adrenaline-charged, high-stakes experience. Every run and every world is randomly generated, giving WarSphere a high level of replayability.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451530/extras/wsgif_2024-01-21-182623_USE.gif?t=1708016424"><h2 class="bb_tag">ENDGAME</h2>Unlike other roguelikes, in WarSphere you get to keep a copy of the final setup and loadout with which you successfully beat a run. This storage is called "The Archive". Depending on the difficulty you played, you will be able to unlock and experience different end game activities, which include: 4 realms, with 4 tiers each, ranked arcade mode, daily time trials with leaderboards and community maps.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451530/extras/gif_rollright_final_6mb.gif?t=1708016424"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXPERIENCE</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>the most presumptuous camera perspective since the existence of video games <br/></li><li>the adrenaline from nearly dying in higher levels<br/></li><li>the frustration of actually dying in higher levels<br/></li><li>the reward of completing a run successfully<br/></li><li>the pride in your unlocked Archive Entries<br/></li><li>the joy of beating endgame realms and community maps with your Archive Entries<br/></li><li>the affordable humor of random adjective/name combinations</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451530/extras/ws_store1.gif?t=1708016424"><h2 class="bb_tag">KEY FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>4 BILLION seeded runs!<br/></li><li>5 Worlds, with several Dungeons each (2 in free base game + 3 in DLC)<br/></li><li>60+ Enemy Types (25 in free base game + 35 in DLC)<br/></li><li>Randomized Elite and Minion enemies<br/></li><li>32 Elite Modifiers<br/></li><li>10 Primary Weapon Types<br/></li><li>10 Secondary Weapon Types<br/></li><li>12 ACM Types (Special Abilities)<br/></li><li>6 Upgrades<br/></li><li>Tons of item modifications<br/></li><li>15 Character Multipliers, that are upgraded with items and chips<br/></li><li>Map Editor<br/></li><li>Extensive enemy modding, integrated in the Map Editor</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caribbean Legend</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2230980/Caribbean_Legend/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i><strong>Based on Sea Dogs series and inspired by Sid Meier's Pirates!</strong></i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/Wishlist_Follow_ENG.gif?t=1708054173"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/История_EN.gif?t=1708054173"><br/><br/>Welcome to the Caribbean in 1654 AD, a place teeming with opportunities and mysteries. Assume the role of Charles de Maure, a young French noble who embarked on a journey to the New World to assist his brother. What initially appeared to be a simple family matter quickly evolves into a lifelong adventure.<br/>Immerse yourself in the tale of a noble brat who rises to become the most influential figure in the Caribbean. <strong>Riches, titles, power, and romance – the ultimate booty awaits, and it's up to you to seize it all.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/steamchar.jpg?t=1708054173"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Embark on a 200-hour-long journey.<br/></li><li>Undertake hundreds of quests.<br/></li><li>Freeplay, rush through the story, or combine both - you're the Captain, and your ship will sail where you command.<br/></li><li>Experience a historical narrative with a touch of mystique.<br/></li><li>Explore romantic interests and companions.<br/></li><li>Choose from various career options, from general-governor to pirate baron.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/Мир_EN.gif?t=1708054173"><br/><br/>The Caribbean Sea – a realm of dozens of islands and cities, a grand archipelago shrouded in mystery and secrets. From the summits of Indian pyramids to the ocean depths, unique rewards, quests, and curiosities await. <strong>This open world is your sandbox, you are free to explore it and shape your legend as you see fit. </strong>Your decisions determine where to go, what to do, and who to take with you. Subdue the New World or it will destroy you!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Discover dozens of islands and settlements.<br/></li><li>Build your very own colony.<br/></li><li>Explore caves, pyramids, jungles, Indian tribes, and lost cities.<br/></li><li>Visit taverns, brothels, shipyards, churches, forts, and many other points of interest.<br/></li><li>Engage in treasure hunting and gambling.<br/></li><li>Experience dynamic weather and the serene turquoise sea.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/Море_EN.gif?t=1708054173"><br/><br/><strong>Owning a warship is a privilege, a symbol of status and luxury. </strong>You are among the very few who can afford such grandeur. Begin your journey with a simple sloop and work your way up to commanding a ship of the line or even a fleet of these formidable vessels, ready to plunder cities at your whim. No one will stand in your way. Tired from leading massive armadas and the responsibility? Take command of a fast Frigate or Corvette and just free roam the Caribbean. In moments of tranquility at sea, relish the stunning views, embrace the sense of exploration, or navigate in the heart of a storm.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/valciria3_копия.png?t=1708054173"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Command dozens of ships representing the glory of the Age of Sail.<br/></li><li>Customize, paint, upgrade, and repair your vessel.<br/></li><li>Engage in unforgiving yet enjoyable naval combat.<br/></li><li>Experience intense boarding action, from the upper deck to the captain's cabin.<br/></li><li>Collect unique vessels to rule the seas.<br/></li><li>Manage booty distribution, morale, and the threat of mutinies.<br/></li><li>Assemble a formidable team of officers.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/боевка_EN.gif?t=1708054173"><br/><br/>Captains are most vulnerable when they set foot on land. Surviving naval combat can be challenging, but at least you won't die alone – your crew will stand with you till the very end. Land battles are different: dishonest, ruthless and risky for you and those who you hold dear. <strong>Bring your companions with you, poison your weapons, study the terrain, craft deadly items, and confront thugs, soldiers, pirates, and rivals head-on.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230980/extras/face_201_копия.png?t=1708054173"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tailor your character's build – become a heavy swordsman, a nimble rogue, a master sharpshooter, or a silver-tongued diplomat.<br/></li><li>Equip yourself and your companions with a wide array of swords, axes, rapiers, armor, muskets, and pistols.<br/></li><li>Craft amulets, ammo, potions, and always be prepared for battle.<br/></li><li>Seek out challenges – the more you fight, the stronger both you and your character become.<br/></li><li>Command military operations from raiding to sieges.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmic PANIC</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2592940/Cosmic_PANIC/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cosmic PANIC is an arcade style chaotic party game for one to four players. Choose a unique character in the Cosmic PANIC universe to duke it out or team up with your friends in a variety of arcade style games! Will your friends survive or thrive in the chaos?<h2 class="bb_tag">ARCADE VARIETY</h2>Engage in a variety of Cosmic PANIC twisted arcade style game types! Set high scores as you run from monstrous blobs, or race around the arcade to collect the most points in platforming style gameplay. Survive the pull of the wormhole, blast through portals, and defend the space station in top-down space adventuring gameplay. And dodge asteroids and chase down energy crystals to thrive in 3D space flight style gameplay. There's a chaotic mix of gameplay styles to challenge everyone!<h2 class="bb_tag">CHALLENGING GAMEPLAY, SIMPLE CONTROLS</h2>All game types are crafted to be arcade-friendly with simple controls, and the gameplay is increasingly challenging. To really set the highest of scores, you will need to survive AND thrive long enough to persist through environment changes and/or boss encounters each game type offers as the difficulty ramps up.<h2 class="bb_tag">TEAMSIZE HIGHSCORE CHARTS</h2>High score charts are separated by team sizes: 1, 2, 3, and 4 players. Play solo or together to top the charts and leave your mark.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonder</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692570/Sonder/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Local Co-op requires a gamepad controller for both players. Online Co-op supports mouse and keyboard. </i><h2 class="bb_tag">Psychological narrative </h2>- After a mass-scale destruction of all artificial intelligence, a scrapped robot and soul form an unexpected friendship. After a mysterious train knocks them out, they wake up in a world shaped by their own thoughts. Will they be able to cooperate and escape this dark reality?<h2 class="bb_tag">Immersive atmosphere </h2>- Immerse yourself in an atmospheric world crafted with a stylish, minimalistic approach that captivates your attention and enhances the shared adventure. Unleash the power of collaboration, confront existential mysteries, and embark on a gaming journey like no other.<h2 class="bb_tag">Collaboration </h2>- Work together - succeed together. Each character has unique abilities that allow them to manipulate the world in their own way, meaning they can only proceed if they cooperate. In combat, maximum efficiency can be achieved by combining the player’s powers, allowing them to neutralize the most dangerous of foes.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cursed Enigma - The Midnight Apartment</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803640/Cursed_Enigma__The_Midnight_Apartment/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Midnight Apartment marks the next chapter in the psychological horror series: CurseEnigma. It's about Franco, a man who recently got divorced and is trying to get used to his new home in an old Italian village. As he settles in, he meets strange neighbors, and a feeling of being watched and followed by an unknown force gets stronger after sunset. The game tells an exciting story, exploring the mysterious lives of the people in the building and revealing what happened to the person who lived there before. It deals with themes like being alone, not trusting others, and the mysterious connections between people in this creepy and mysterious psychological horror experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803640/extras/gif.gif?t=1708012861"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>This game is a first-person psychological horror experience. It features narrative, object finding, and conversation mechanics. The plot unfolds through missions and interactions with characters, guiding the player to explore the darker side of the building and uncover well-guarded secrets.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>80’s film aesthetic.<br/></li><li>Talk with NPCs to find the suspect.<br/></li><li>Atmospheric environment</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Interact with the environment</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivery Boy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1550560/Delivery_Boy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1550560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1550560/extras/board_steam_wishlist_eng.png?t=1708012818"><br/><br/><strong>Add the game Delivery Boy to the wishlist and you will be the first to know about its release on Steam!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1550560/extras/board_steam_eng1.png?t=1708012818"><br/><br/>Play as a budding courier who has moved to Crystal City in search of work. Before you is a city of great opportunities, help the main character climb the career ladder and become the best courier.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1550560/extras/board_steam_eng2.png?t=1708012818"><br/><br/>■ Take various orders, deliver them to the right place and get money and experience points.<br/>■ Open and manage delivery services.<br/>■ Upgrade your own home and make it the prettiest in town!<br/>■ Use special devices such as a resource detector, a garbage collector, and even a gravity gun to lift especially heavy loads.<br/>■ Collect collectibles hidden throughout the city and explore interesting places.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1550560/extras/board_steam_eng3.png?t=1708012818"><br/><br/>The game is being developed by indie developer Sergey Poroshin. Thanks for your support!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat Search in Feudal Japan</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733920/Cat_Search_in_Feudal_Japan/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2733920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Search for hidden cats in a Japanese city set during feudal Japan. Samurai cats are also hiding somewhere and perhaps you need to search for katanas aswell! Relax while you explore this short but sweet hidden objects game!<br/><br/><strong>Key Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🐱130 Hidden Cats</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>👹 5 Hidden Samurai Cats</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🗡️10 Hidden Katanas</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>💡 15 Hints</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>⛩️Hand-drawn Japanese City</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>😸A Lot Of Meowing Sound Effects</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🏆100 Achievements!</li></ul><br/>Happy cat searching!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lowrider Hopping</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2800140/Lowrider_Hopping/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2800140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This indie game is inspired by the lowrider and hip-hop subcultures. Feel the vibes of the neighborhood with hip hop beats. Ride a lowrider around the block and improve your skills in controlling the hydraulic suspension to pick up items: <br>
<br>
To satisfy your hunger, pick up burgers<br>
To quench your thirst, pick up beer<br>
Pick up weed for your bong<br>
Score points by picking up basketballs<br>
Roll the Cee-lo dice combination 4 5 6<br/>
Become a gangster and rob a jewelry store to get some bling<br/>
Win the hearts of girls<br/>
To become a rapper pick up DJ turntables and mics and go to the recording studio<br/>
<br/>
Become a true master of hitting switches and complete 27 levels!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Fighter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2789870/Death_Fighter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2789870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world is in peril, as thousands of demons are devastating the world and your village was the first victim.<br/>In search of revenge you swear that you're ready to fight, even against the death itself.<br/>Begin your journey as a Death Fighter and show the Death itself who's the boss !<br/><br/>This game is a 2D platformer and side scroller where you play a Death Fighter who wants to avenge his friends.<br/>Death Fighter is made of three levels with different mechanics and ennemies to defeat by jumping on their head.<br/>At the end of each level, you will fight and defeat a boss by jumping multiple times on their head and jump into a portal to go to the next level.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Challenging and complex gameplay</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Customizable difficulty from beginner to expert !</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Unlockable skins and rewards !</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Made by an indie game developer, with love !</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunship + Gunship 2000</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2766090/Gunship__Gunship_2000/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							ATARI PRESENTS is a series of titles geared toward the preservation of cult classics, forgotten favorites, and titles that would otherwise be lost to time. In the spirit of that, each ATARI PRESENTS title is presented unchanged from its original version other than providing the means to play them on modern hardware. Even the store description below is the very same language used to describe the title at the time of its release. Please enjoy!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Gunship</strong></h2><br/>Climb into the cockpit of America's most advanced helicopter: the AH-64 Apache-GUNSHIP. Race low and deadly over the treetops at 200m.p.h.. Then lock onto your target with <i>Hellfire</i> missiles and 30mm cannon as you deliver a powerful punch against the enemy! They'll retaliate with massive armored force but it's up to you and GUNSHIP to extinguish their threats and survive!<br/><br/><strong>GUNSHIP FEATURES INCLUDE:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full simulation of high-speed, low-level helicopter flight.<br/></li><li>Advanced high-tech weapons systems and instrumentation.<br/></li><li>Revolutionary 3-D graphics including all types of terrain.<br/></li><li>Hundreds of exciting missions in con gat hotspots around the world.<br/></li><li>Rewards for successful missions include medals and rank promotions,<br/></li><li>Comprehensive Flight Operations Manual and keyboard overlay.</li></ul><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Gunship 2000</h2></strong><br/><br/><strong>The All-New Multi-Helicopter Combat Simulation</strong><br/><br/>In the tradition of Gunship, the award-winning, best-selling simulation of the AH-64 Apache. Gunship 2000 gives you total command of a full multi-copter troop of America's most powerful and versatile rotor craft. You'll take charge of five copters on hundreds of combat missions in the Persian Gulf and Central Europe.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Topographical 3-D Graphics portray low-altitude flight with uncanny realism.<br/></li><li>3 arenas in the Persian Gulf, 3 in Central Europe; each arena measures 800 square km.<br/></li><li>Multiple mission profiles.<br/></li><li>Selectable co-pilot controls.<br/></li><li>Digitized speech.<br/></li><li>Includes campaign game.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HardBall! + HardBall II</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2766080/HardBall__HardBall_II/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							ATARI PRESENTS is a series of titles geared toward the preservation of cult classics, forgotten favorites, and titles that would otherwise be lost to time. In the spirit of that, each ATARI PRESENTS title is presented unchanged from its original version other than providing the means to play them on modern hardware. Even the store description below is the very same language used to describe the title at the time of its release. Please enjoy!<h2 class="bb_tag">HardBall!</h2><br/>Have you ever gone to a Major League ballpark before most of the fans show up, when the ball players are taking batting practice? If you walked down in front of the box seats, right alongside the warning track, you had to be dumbstruck by the immensity of the entire playing field: crisp, white lines of chalk cutting to foul poles that reach to the sky, a freshly cut outfield of brilliant green that seems to stretch forever and images of exciting things to come as great athletes prepare for their version of modern day coliseum warfare.<br/><br/><strong>Dirty Uniforms</strong><br/><br/>That’s exactly what you get from HardBall, baseball that’s so real and true-to-life, it’s like you can reach out and touch it. It’s like the Saturday afternoon “Game of the Week” on network television – NO, it’s better because you don’t just sit there, you play HardBall. In fact, HardBall is so real and lifelike, if you wear a uniform while you play it, you just might get it dirty. It’s quite simply the most spectacular sports simulation computer game of all time. See you in Cooperstown!<br/><br/>The batter hits a sure single. But, with his team behind late in the game, should he try and stretch it into a double? You decide. At this stage, you’re either a hero or a goat.<br/><br/>It’s the bottom of the 9th and the league’s most feared slugger prepares to tee off on the next offering from the home team’s ace fireballer. Will it be high or low, a curve or a screwball?<br/><br/>The game has gone into extra innings, all tied up. Do you pinch-hit for the weak hitting pitcher or leave him in because he's the best you've got?<h2 class="bb_tag">HardBall II:</h2><br/>It's a whole new ballgame.<br/><br/>HardBall II retains the all-star qualities of the original. Effortless gameplay. Authentic graphics. Unparalleled realism. But now there's more. Much more. More features and options More choices, playability and true-to-ballplayer animation. Even more major league ballparks. Scout around and compare. You'll find that HardBall II isn't just the best computer baseball game on the market. It's in a league by itself.<br/><br/><strong>Statistics don't tell the whole story.</strong> Better than the morning box scores. HardBallII updates and stores stats in virtually every conceivable category. Stats change from at-bat to at-bat, from game to game. Plus there are other new features, like pick offs, league play, a team editor - even fielding errors. Whew.<br/><br/><strong>More frames of animation means more realism.</strong> Feel the heat of a 90 mpg fastball. With increased frames of animation, each pitch, each play, is major league smooth. More choices means the pitcher can come to the plate or attempt to pick the runner off at second. Caught learning? Try to stay alive in a rundown.<br/><br/><strong>Shift the infield and outfield according to each hitter.</strong> The centerfield view offers a scout's insight as to the hitter's tendencies. Will you play at normal depth, guard the lines or put on a custom shift? Remember, the batter has options as well. He may go to right, bunt or drill it over your head.<br/><br/><strong>Seven different stadiums. Five different views.</strong> Step on the turf of seven familiar big league ballparks. Catch the game from five network TV field perspectives: upper deck overview, behind the pitcher, behind the plate or left and right infield views. The "Game Of The Week" crew would be proud.<br/><br/><strong>TV Instant Replay feature.</strong> Want to start a bench clearing brawl? Then show your opponent that triple you just belted, one more time, with the Instant Replay feature. You can pause it, play it at normal speed, slow motion or - if you really want to rub it in - frame-by-frame.<br/><br/><strong>Pull-down menus make managing easy:</strong> A winning manager pushes all the right buttons. Pencil in a starting line-up based on who's going good. And if they start going bad? Pull the starters and pinch hit. Feel like trading all of these bums? Go ahead You can build your very own dream team with the team editor feature.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weird Dreams</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2766070/Weird_Dreams/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							ATARI PRESENTS is a series of titles geared toward the preservation of cult classics, forgotten favorites, and titles that would otherwise be lost to time. In the spirit of that, each ATARI PRESENTS title is presented unchanged from its original version other than providing the means to play them on modern hardware. Even the store description below is the very same language used to describe the title at the time of its release. Please enjoy!<br>
<br>
Imagine yourself in a world full of nightmares with Dali-esque creatures and mind-eating eyes. Picture yourself in an upside down landscape. Alone in a weird dream and wondering... what the... ?!<br>
<br>
Imported from England, this is the computer game that everyone is talking about - or soon will be - in excited whispers and bewildered exclamations.<br>
<br>
It's the game with the soccer ball that devours knife-wielding little girls... then burps.<br/>
<br/>
The one with totem pole heads hopping on kangaroo bodies under skies full of fish.<br/>
<br/>
The one with a giant killer bee that wants your cotton candy, the grandfather clock that points the way, and the lawn mower than grinds you to a bloody pulp.<br/>
<br/>
Like the famous ink-plot test, the bizarre scenes, puzzle and arcade style challenges in Weird Dreams will mean different things to different people.<br/>
<br/>
Some will think them uproariously funny.<br/>
<br/>
Others will think them strange and unsettling.<br/>
<br/>
Still others will be outright offended.<br/>
<br/>
Decide for yourself.<br/>
<br/>
One thing is certain: there has never been a computer game like Weird Dreams. You have to play it to believe it. <br/>
<br/>
---<br/>
<br/>
'Weird Dreams is a cinematic, third-person platform game with action and puzzle elements. The game contains bizarre levels and unorthodox activities, including feeding a wasp cotton candy, beating up hopping totem poles with fish from the sky, and an encounter with a baked chicken in a haunted house. The game comes with a "short novel" that explains the plot in detail and serves as copy protection.' - MobyGames						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zapper: One Wicked Cricket</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2766060/Zapper_One_Wicked_Cricket/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							ATARI PRESENTS is a series of titles geared toward the preservation of cult classics, forgotten favorites, and titles that would otherwise be lost to time. In the spirit of that, each ATARI PRESENTS title is presented unchanged from its original version other than providing the means to play them on modern hardware. Even the store description below is the very same language used to describe the title at the time of its release. Please enjoy!<br/><br/>Zapper is an action-packed and addictive game that starts with the “avoid-em-up” game play mechanics of Blitz Games’ own Frogger 2: Swampy’s Revenge, and then takes the action to a whole new level. In this action-adventure game, Zapper (a cricket) hops his way through six interactive worlds in a quest to find his brother, held captive by the evil magpie queen. Dangerous traps and even more dangerous enemies await Zapper. It will take fast-footed skill and timing to conquer all the worlds and survive the final showdown with the magpie queen.<h2 class="bb_tag">GAME FEATURES:</h2><br/>- Classic “avoid-em-up” game play from the makers of Frogger 2: Swampy’s Revenge: Blitz Games. <br/><br/>- Unique enemies and traps to thwart Zapper on his quest. <br/><br/>- Intuitive control system with increasingly complex levels makes Zapper a pick-up-and-play treat for both novice and seasoned gamers.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightspeed</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2766050/Lightspeed/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							ATARI PRESENTS is a series of titles geared toward the preservation of cult classics, forgotten favorites, and titles that would otherwise be lost to time. In the spirit of that, each ATARI PRESENTS title is presented unchanged from its original version other than providing the means to play them on modern hardware. Even the store description below is the very same language used to describe the title at the time of its release. Please enjoy!<br/><br/>You're the only human in a huge, robotic space ship, flying at incredible speeds through deep space. Your mission: find and settle a new planet where humanity can thrive. Combat is inevitable, but you'll need more than flying skills to succeed. You'll also need resourcefulness, charm and political skill to help you negotiate with the bizarre, intelligent - sometimes hostile - beings who correctly see you as the alien.<br/><br/><strong>3D Combat Flight Simulation Like You've Never Seen</strong><br/><br/>Earth-bound simulations spend most of their graphic power on landmarks and other terrain. But since there's no terrain in the black void of out space, Lightspeed devotes its Super 3D Graphics power to showing space ships in breathtaking detail and animating them with unprecedented smoothness.<br/><br/>- Pilot a starship 15,000 feet long<br/><br/>- Customize your ship for the performance you need<br/><br/>- Control remote fightercraft in strategic battles with intelligent enemies<br/><br/><strong>Fascinating Role-Playing Depth</strong><br/><br/>Multiple star clusters await your exploration, each with unique challenges. A dozen solar systems spin through each cluster; scores of planets revolve around each sun. Most important, 25 species of aliens require your constant attention.<br/><br/>- <strong>The Broodsmasters</strong> - sinister, manipulative and eager for universal domination<br/><br/>- <strong>The Lutin</strong> - quasi-intelligent, with no memory and no concept of the future<br/><br/>- <strong>The Cicisbeo</strong> - totally self-absorbed, vain and arrogant						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Good Can Come Of This</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1096990/Nothing_Good_Can_Come_Of_This/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1096990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A two-player local fighting game that strips combat down to its rawest form. Set in a bare room, players engage in intense fights over possession of a gun and its ammunition.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><br/><strong>Fast-Paced, High-Stakes Combat:</strong> Brace yourself for quick and violent matches. Every second counts, and a single misstep can drastically change the course of a match.<br/><br/><strong>A Fistfight over a Gun:</strong> Matches kick off with the drop of a gun and a single piece of ammo. Master the art of disarming your opponent and turn the fight in your favor.<br/><br/><strong>Easy to Learn, Difficult to Master:</strong> The game's intuitive design means anyone can pick it up in seconds, but mastering it is a different story. It takes skill, strategy, and quick thinking to consistently come out on top.<br/><br/><strong>Tournament Mode:</strong> Compete in Single Elimination or Round Robin brackets, a maximum of 32 players. Whether you're hosting a party or a competitive gaming event, this mode is perfect for testing skills and determining a champion.<br/><br/><strong>Arcade Mode:</strong> Comes with additional support for "Credit" and "Free Play" modes, attract screens, and a simplified UI for use in arcade cabinets.<br/><br/>Nothing Good Can Come Of This is a part of the Arcade Commons collective in New York City. It has been featured at the MAGFest Indie Arcade.<br/>Trailer music is Woochia - The Forbidden Door Pt.2, provided by Jamendo.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puzzlerio</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2633630/Puzzlerio/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Puzzlerio</strong> is a <strong>minimalist</strong> and <strong>relaxing</strong> experience where you will create a factory that takes ores from <strong>one point to another</strong>. <strong>Refine ores</strong> to turn them into bar ores, use different resources to transport the ores and do everything necessary to <strong>complete the factory</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Transport ores with the Transport Belt</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633630/extras/Animação2.gif?t=1708009379"><br/><br/><strong>Refine ores with the Furnace</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633630/extras/Animação3.gif?t=1708009379"><br/><br/><strong>Take ores from one transport belt to another with the <i>Inserter</i></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633630/extras/Animação4.gif?t=1708009379"><br/><br/><strong>Transport ores underground with the Tunnel</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633630/extras/Animação5.gif?t=1708009379"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>5 itens</strong> to use in creating factories;<br/></li><li><strong>50 levels</strong> ranging from easy to difficult;<br/></li><li>Background music <strong>calm and relaxing</strong> to make your journey more complete;</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
