<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Quilts and Cats of Calico</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1993180/Quilts_and_Cats_of_Calico/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1993180?utm_source=calico&amp;utm_medium=in_steam" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1993180?utm_source=calico&amp;utm_medium=in_steam</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Arrow.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/>Quilts and Cats of Calico is a cozy board game in which the player's main task is to make a quilt from patterned fabric scraps. By smartly combining the colors and patterns of the scraps, the player can not only score points for the completed design but also sew on buttons and attract adorable cats, who have their own preferences for bedding patterns.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Cats_running.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/><strong>Stepping beyond adaptation</strong><br/>In Quilts and Cats of Calico, based on the board game Calico, you will be immersed in a warm, cozy world full of cuddly cats. Here the quilt bends under the weight of their paws and loud purring can be heard. It's a world full of patterns and designs awaiting the master quilt maker.<br/><br/>We also have a few surprises for the Calico fans like variations of the rules and mechanics in the campaign play. In addition to the well-known gameplay scenarios, new ones await to be discovered.<br/><br/><br/><strong>Quilt solo, with friends, or with strangers</strong><br/>Whether you want to quilt solo or prefer to compete with other players, Quilts and Cats of Calico will provide you with the corresponding gameplay mode. You will have cross-platform multiplayer at your disposal, during which you can invite friends or play ranked matches against random players. The more peaceful solo mode allows you to face AI of varying difficulty levels and is the perfect tool to hone your skills in a relaxed atmosphere.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Game_modes.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/><strong>Sew your adventures in the city of cat worshippers</strong><br/>In the game, you can also enjoy the story mode campaign. An extraordinary world inspired by the works of Studio Ghibli awaits you. Here cats have great power and influence over people's lives. Take on the role of an itinerant quilter who decides to succeed in a city of cat-worshippers. Climb to the top of the city hierarchy and face the opponent who wants to dominate the world of humans and cats. Create quilts, perfect your craft, and help those you meet on your journey. Don't worry, you won't be alone - along the way, you'll meet friends and, most importantly, cats whose help can prove invaluable…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Calico_minigry_dialog_steampage_gif.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/><strong>Spend quality time with your cats</strong><br/>In Quilts and Cats of Calico, cats are active during your games. Sometimes minding their own business, and other times coming to you and your quilt. They will lazily observe the board, romp and run around, and sometimes fall into a blissful nap. They are cats, you never know. You can interact with them during the game, pet them, and shoo them away when they get in the way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Calico_glaskanie_v2.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/><strong>Extended customization options</strong><br/>The game is full of cats, but there could always be more! In Quilts and Cats of Calico, you can create your own, making your game even more wholesome! You can give it a name, choose the color of its fur, and put on different outfits. If you wish, it will appear on the board during your gameplay. It will also be possible to choose a different player's portrait and background for the game. Pick what you like best!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Calico_CatEditor_SteamPage_Gif_v2.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/><strong>Beautiful, relaxing music</strong><br/>We asked Pawel Górniak, the composer responsible for the soundtrack to the digital version of Wingspan, to create the music for Quilts and Cats of Calico. Thanks to it, you will not only be able to deeply feel the atmosphere of the game but let yourself be carried away by blissful relaxation.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expeditions: A MudRunner Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2477340/Expeditions_A_MudRunner_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fsnowrunner" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/extras/STEAM_DISCORD_BANNER_EXPEDITIONS.jpg?t=1709660925"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/extras/EXP_MAIN_EN.gif?t=1709660925"><br/><br/>From Arizona to the Carpathians, chart through expansive open worlds in search of hidden treasures and forgotten ruins. Expeditions: A MudRunner Game is a groundbreaking off-road simulation crafted by Saber Interactive, creators of the critically acclaimed SnowRunner. <br/><br/>Lead research missions as you drive a variety of all-terrain vehicles, using high-tech tools and managing your camp and crew to ensure your success in the wild. Embark on ever-rewarding scientific expeditions as you adapt to nature's challenges, and unravel the mysteries of uncharted lands. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/extras/EXP_OFFROAD_EN.gif?t=1709660925"><br/><br/>Expeditions: A MudRunner Game builds on the legacy of Saber Interactive’s off-road simulations with its advanced physics-based gameplay systems, perfectly encapsulating the feel of driving through the wilderness. Whether you’re a long-time player of MudRunner games or a newcomer, you are in for a thrilling scientific adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/extras/EXP_PLANYOUREXPEDITIONS_EN.gif?t=1709660925"><br/><br/>Success depends on preparation. Plan your missions carefully and hire a team of Specialists to improve your skills in the field. With the drone and metal detector, scout your itinerary and locate points of interest. Invest the profits from each expedition to expand your home bases by building support structures to gain useful supplies and summon new vehicles. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/extras/EXP_TOOLS_EN.gif?t=1709660925"><br/><br/>Equip your vehicles with state-of-the-art technologies and cutting-edge gadgets to ensure success in the wild. Use the winch and portable anchors to perform intricate maneuvers, and traverse treacherous rivers with the echo sounder. Choose strategically, as the tools at your disposal can make or break an expedition. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Winch:</strong> Get your vehicle unstuck from the mud or rappel down steep cliffs <br/></li><li><strong>Jackscrew:</strong> Turn your vehicle back on its wheels after accidental flips <br/></li><li><strong>Echo sounder:</strong> Avoid sinking by probing the depth of the water around your vehicle <br/></li><li>And much more… </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/extras/EXP_CUSTO_EN.gif?t=1709660925"><br/><br/>Customize your vehicles in the garage, choosing between nimbler scout vehicles, off-road machines or large trucks. Tailor your approach for light and fast exploration or slower, equipment-heavy trucking. Successful expeditions allow you to invest in new accessories, such as storage extensions, spare parts, and measuring tools. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/extras/EXP_EXPLO_EN.gif?t=1709660925"><br/><br/>From arid deserts to rugged forests and steep mountains, explore vast, uncharted lands brimming with hidden wonders and forgotten ruins. Archaeological sites, dinosaur fossils and natural curiosities can be found in numbers across Arizona and the Carpathians, and each discovery can be the key to groundbreaking scientific breakthroughs. <br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2477340/Expeditions_A_MudRunner_Game/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2477340/Expeditions_A_MudRunner_Game/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials - Reagent Starter Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2328320/The_Outlast_Trials__Reagent_Starter_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2328320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Prepare to face the Trials with the Reagent Starter Pack, which includes an exclusive set of 4 legendary outfits, cell items, cell posters and player icons to help you customize what is sure to be a horrifying experience.<br>
Includes the following:<br>
•    Space Oddity Vapor Suit<br>
•    Hazard Ignorance Suit<br>
•    Bidendum Glut Suit<br>
•    Chemistry Teacher Suit<br>
•    Futterman Doll cell item<br/>
•    Stun Rod cell item<br/>
•    Mannequin Skinned cell item<br/>
•    Teeth Bowl cell item<br/>
•    Police Badge cell item<br/>
•    Pistachios cell item<br/>
•    3 exclusive The Outlast Trials cell posters<br/>
•    3 exclusive The Outlast Trials player icons						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709650058"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sixty Four</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2659900/Sixty_Four/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Sixty Four is a clicker game which becomes slightly more idle and less clicker with the every machine you unlock. Upgrade a factory in an extraordinary world. Progress to unlock new resources and machines, leading to new ways to expand and grow.<br/><br/><strong>❒ From Foundation to Complexity</strong><br/><br/>Begin your journey with a simple machine generating distinct cubes. Use combinations of cubes to unlock advanced machinery and new gameplay elements.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_3a_smaller.gif?t=1709667369"><br/><br/><strong>❒ An Evolving Factory Adventure</strong><br/><br/>Your factory is not just a collection of simple machines; it's a dynamic environment of challenges and strategy. Face new situations and discover opportunities with every innovative and abstract machine you encounter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_4a_smaller.gif?t=1709667369"><br/><strong>❒ A Fresh Mix of Gaming Mechanics</strong><br/><br/>Sixty Four combines simple yet engaging elements from idle, incremental, and strategy games. Pursue constant improvement and unravel the secrets behind messages from an unknown entity.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_5a_smaller.gif?t=1709667369"><br/><br/>Music by Jake Chudnow						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Thaumaturge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1684350/The_Thaumaturge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Thaumaturge_accolade_616x320_steam.png?t=1709657037"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/TT_claim_EN_small.png?t=1709657037"><br/><strong>The Thaumaturge is an isometric, story-rich RPG with a unique take on turn-based combat, character development features, and investigation mechanics</strong>, facing you with morally ambiguous choices – set in a world teeming with mysterious powers and strange ethereal beings called <strong>salutors</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/City_3-01.gif?t=1709657037"><br/><br/>The year is 1905. Warsaw lives under the yoke of imperial Russian tsardom. Its inhabitants constitute a diverse group of different ancestries, views, and beliefs with often conflicting interests: Russian soldiers, Jewish merchants, Polish townspeople, and more. Despite the circumstances, the city is a buzzing metropolis, where one can attend a breathtaking party with the high society, and later get robbed in one of the dark alleys of the Praga district. A city of great hopes and dreams on one hand and dark desires on the other.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Buka_2.gif?t=1709657037"><br/><br/>A <strong>thaumaturge</strong> bears both a gift and a burden at the same time. This parallel holds true for <strong>Wiktor Szulski</strong>, the game’s titular protagonist, who is drawn back to the tumultuous streets of 20th-century Warsaw by family matters. The gift of thaumaturgy is intertwined with family legacy, passed down through one's ancestors. This mystical inheritance significantly shapes Wiktor’s life journey tied around a pursuit of unearthly entities and their hosts. As only a thaumaturge can tame these ethereal entities - known to a select few as <strong>salutors</strong> - utilizing their mystical abilities to discover secrets hidden within the human soul and speak to the Darkness, no one understands quite like Wiktor how everyone suffers their own demons.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Wiktor_3-01.gif?t=1709657037"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Shape your story</strong> – as a full-fledged RPG, it allows you to alternate your choices and make you deal with the aftermath. <br/></li><li><strong>Develop your character</strong> – creating your own version of the thaumaturge will allow you to approach situations in different ways. <br/></li><li><strong>Experience unique turn-based combat</strong> and defeat your foes using human attacks and skills as well as psychic strikes delivered by salutors.<br/></li><li><strong>Influence and manipulate</strong> the temperaments of other characters to bend their will to your liking. <br/></li><li><strong>Tame the power of salutors</strong> – use the unique set of their skills to gain an advantage while exploring the world and when bringing your adversaries to their knees. <br/></li><li><strong>See the world that’s inevitably gone</strong> – explore the uncommon, heavily researched historic period of the early XX century Warsaw, where crime and luxury are often two sides of the same coin. Meet historical figures and learn about their involvement in the story. <br/></li><li><strong>Created in Unreal Engine 5</strong> to deliver a detailed &amp; beautifully crafted world.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crusader Kings III: Legends of the Dead</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2671060/Crusader_Kings_III_Legends_of_the_Dead/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							What good are grand accomplishments and heroic deeds if no one sings of them after you have gone? A royal legacy is only useful, after all, if it can provide cover and legitimacy for those who come after you. Live on in the memory of your subjects and rivals in <i>Legends of the Dead</i>, a Core Expansion for <i>Crusader Kings III</i>.<br/><br/><strong><i>Crusader Kings III: Legends of the Dead</i></strong> adds new heroic gameplay, as you stoke the flames of your fame into a towering bonfire.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671060/extras/legends-v4-opt.gif?t=1709571372"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Legends:</strong> Commission an epic retelling of your family history or build your own heroic reputation through great deeds. Promote this legend, far and wide, and see how the stories of the past reverberate through the centuries, and add more glory to legendary dynasties.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Legendary Playstyle:</strong> Leverage your living legend status through new Decisions and actions, keeping the stories of your family in the minds of a continent, strengthening the legitimacy of your rule and allowing further choices. <br/><br/></li><li><strong>Legendary Buildings:</strong> Your legendary reputation gives you access to new elite buildings, cementing your legacy for future generations.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Legendary Feasts: </strong>Poets and bards can ornament your celebrations with songs and odes to your greatness, inspiring your guests to spread the tale of your legendary generosity.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Court Chroniclers:</strong> Hire an official historian to spread the story of your dynasty’s great accomplishments, or use your poets and musicians to turn your actions into art.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Two New Legacies:</strong> A new Heroic dynastic Legacy for the heirs of legendary characters, even using the great deeds of ancestors to justify claims from the distant past, as well as a Legitimacy Legacy that promotes your dynasty as the true rulers of the realm.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671060/extras/blackplague-opt.gif?t=1709571372"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Illness and Mourning:</strong> New diseases like the Bloody Flux, Measles and Holy Fire may ravage your court, but you can honor your deceased loved ones with dignified Funeral rites, according to your faith.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>The Black Death:</strong> The greatest scourge of the Middle Ages strikes down noble and commoner alike, radically transforming the political and social environment. Prepare your realm and prepare your soul, because a rampaging plague may be the strongest enemy facing your rule.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>New Art:</strong> Both life and death are given new energy with the celebrated art style that Crusader Kings III fans have come to appreciate. A new exclusive Map Table, new varieties of clothing, unit models and holding designs for extra flavor.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mortal Glory 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2216660/Mortal_Glory_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif1.gif?t=1709651463"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en1.png?t=1709651463"><br/>Roll an explosive barrel at your enemy, throw them into a pit or take out two enemies by knocking them into each other. With a wide variety of tools available to you, your creativity will determine how you deal with the competition. Unique arenas, randomized environments and occasional special rules ensure that each fight offers new tactical opportunities.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif2.gif?t=1709651463"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en2.png?t=1709651463"><br/>A wide variety of fantasy races are seeking glory, each with their own unique racial strengths. Whatever your tactics are, finding the best recruits is essential!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif3.gif?t=1709651463"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en3.png?t=1709651463"><br/>There is a vast collection of unique relics, character perks and more to discover. Finding clever combos and deadly synergies will unlock new strategies and occasionally turn your gladiators into unfairly strong demons.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif5.gif?t=1709651463"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en6.png?t=1709651463"><br/>Various difficulty settings will accommodate your preferred playstyle and there are increasingly harder challenges to master. But beware... The AI is brutally talented at the highest levels.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif6.gif?t=1709651463"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en4.png?t=1709651463"><br/>With every step comes a new challenge or perhaps... an opportunity? It is up to you to guide where your team should travel next... and suffer the consequences.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif4.gif?t=1709651463"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en5.png?t=1709651463"><br/>Each playthrough is different! With various tactics to try and additional increasingly harder challenges to master, the arena will keep welcoming you back again and again. Thanks to conveniently paced combat, Mortal Glory 2 is also great to play if you only have a moment to spare.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/EndHead.png?t=1709651463"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spell Disk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2292060/Spell_Disk/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Spell Disk is a rogue-lite action game with a unique synergy building mechanic so that your runs can never be the same. Strategize and create your own spell combo synergies to blast through enemies on your way! Each run is unique, so you must plan out how to build your power.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/extras/combo_paper.gif?t=1709316039"><br/>Discover combos and synergies that no one’s seen before! Maximize your power to better your chance of escaping the dungeon of Spell Disk.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/extras/Items_Updated.gif?t=1709316039"><br/>Craft spells, disks, and artifacts during your run that synergies with each other in their own ways.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/extras/Lobby_Updated.gif?t=1709316039"><br/>Unlock new weapons and powers to hack and slash through the enemies blocking your way.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vivaland: Dream House</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2606170/Vivaland_Dream_House/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2606170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1976830" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1976830</a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2606170/extras/ezgif-3-474fd0310c.gif?t=1709314012"><h2 class="bb_tag">Introducing the Vivaland Prologue: Dream House</h2><strong>Build Mode: Craft Your Dreams</strong><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in one of the core game modes of Vivaland: the Build Mode. It's a sandbox where you have control over architectural and design elements, enabling you to construct and decorate a house from the ground up!<br/><br/><strong>Get to Know the First Town of Vivaland</strong><br/><br/>The town of Vivaland offers 8 residential lots, each awaiting your personal touch. Claim your slice of the town, visit your friends' properties, and collaborate on grand projects that will redefine the neighborhood.<br/><br/><strong>Seamless Single and Co-op Experience</strong><br/><br/>Begin your Vivaland adventure either as a lone explorer or with your friends by your side – the choice is yours. You can build together with up to 8 players<br/><strong>Content</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Walls Toolkit:</strong> Build with single wall, curved wall and the room tool!<br/></li><li><strong>Doors &amp; Windows:</strong> Choose entrances and views that reflect your taste.<br/></li><li><strong>Foundations, Multiple Floors, and Stairs: </strong>Build structures that rise to new heights.<br/></li><li><strong>Furniture:</strong> Design with a vast selection of interior items.<br/></li><li><strong>Roofing:</strong> Choose from 10 distinct styles and an array of roof patterns.<br/></li><li><strong>Different styles of items:</strong>  Bohemian, Retro, Victorian, Antique, Cottagecore, Gothic, Modern, Minimalist, Industrial.</li></ul><br/><strong>Functional Freedom</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Resizable Objects:</strong> Adjusting the size of decorative objects.<br/></li><li><strong>Recolorable Furniture and Decor: </strong> Fine-tune your interior design with your color palettes. Save favorite shades and match your items.<br/></li><li><strong>Room Dimension Flexibility: </strong>Tweak the height and width of your rooms.<br/></li><li><strong>Grid Function: </strong>Precise item placement is a breeze with toggleable grid support.<br/></li><li><strong>Intuitive Controls and Snapping: </strong>Seamlessly move and arrange objects.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Brew Barons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1636710/The_Brew_Barons/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1636710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A tranquil world becomes ever more corrupt by the day, spoiled by a strong-armed pirate organization that forcefully impose their brewing monopoly over the lands. Armed with your own brewery and seaplane, it's up to you to explore, forage, craft, sell and deliver your handcrafted brews with aid from fellow pilots who've joined your cause to overthrow the corrupt pirate organization and restore peace.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1636710/extras/steamgif1a.gif?t=1709308740"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Assemble your plane from a variety of parts, each with their own traits.<br/></li><li>Chose your pilot and copilot of whom have strengths and weaknesses.<br/></li><li>Explore the world in search of ingredients to bring back to your brewery. </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1636710/extras/steamgif2.gif?t=1709308740"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Pick and choose which foraged ingredients to blend. <br/></li><li>Distill and/or Ferment, each producing a different outcome. <br/></li><li>Design and name your bottle to your liking.<br/></li><li>Design your very own bar to sell your brews and bring fame to your establishment!<br/></li><li>With fame comes special delivery orders from other bars to stock your brew </li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeeperRL</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/329970/KeeperRL/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/Peek-2018-11-28-09-43.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL is an ambitious dungeon simulator with roguelike and RPG elements. Take the role of an evil wizard and study the methods of black magic. Equip your minions and explore the world, murder innocent villagers and burn their homes. Build your dungeon, lay traps and prepare for an assault of angry heroes. <br/><br/>When you control your minions the game changes into a classic roguelike, with turn-based and very tactical combat. You can also play as an adventurer and assault dungeons made by you or other players.<h2 class="bb_tag">Dungeon management </h2>You will dig deep into the mountain and build dozens of rooms, corridors and traps. Your minions will train and produce weapons and armor. Prisoners will be tortured. You will research new technologies like alchemy, beast mutation and sorcery.<h2 class="bb_tag">Z-levels</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341">Develop your base across multiple floors by digging down into the earth or building up. Build fantastic dungeon designs or elaborate castles and towers.<h2 class="bb_tag">Roguelike mechanics </h2>The world is simulated on a very detailed level. Creatures use equipment and consumable items. There are dozens of special items, spells, attributes and special attacks. You can cut off heads and limbs and blind or poison your enemies. If you're not careful with fire, you can burn an entire forest or even your own dungeon.<h2 class="bb_tag">Large, procedurally generated maps </h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-animated-gif-maker__2_.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL features a large, procedurally generated world. Explore dozens of locations, from small cottages and shops to major enemies dwelling in castles and dungeons. Uncover secrets, bring back great loot and prisoners back to your base in order to grow in power.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple playable factions</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/gif_keepers-ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>Play as a:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dark wizard researching black magic.<br/></li><li>White knight specialized in horses and angelic beings.<br/></li><li>Necromancer who crafts undead from the body parts of fallen enemies.<br/></li><li>Fragile colony of twelve dwarves.<br/></li><li>Goblin king searching for his lost wives.<br/></li><li>Collective of gnomes with a mechanized army.<br/></li><li>Lone adventurer focused on exploration.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Online map sharing </h2>KeeperRL offers the ability to download dungeons made by other players from Steam Workshop, and places them on your world map as enemies. See how others design their fortresses, fight with their minions, and steal their loot! After winning the game, you'll have the option to share your dungeon online as well.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Grindea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/269770/Secrets_of_Grindea/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/269770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Secrets of Grindea</i> is an old-school Action RPG with co-op support for up to 4 players. It is a tribute to and sometimes a parody of the old SNES games so many of us grew up with and loved! Journey through fantastical lands, and battle tons of different enemies and bosses in your quest for truth, friendship and, above all, finding the world's rarest treasures!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A rich world filled with 300+ unique, colorful characters and an engaging story to drive your journey forward.<br/></li><li>Co-op support for up to four players! Enjoy the entire storyline with your friends or call someone in to help with the more difficult challenges.<br/></li><li>Customization, customization, customization - design a character that represents you, then mix and match any of the 31 spells and skills across 9 different categories.<br/></li><li>30+ epic boss fights! Overgrown slimes, giant robots, mimics - we have it all!<br/></li><li>Side content - design your own home, fish, craft items, tame pets, partake in mini-games, grow plants - there’s plenty to keep you entertained when you want a break from the main story.</li></ul><br/>And last but not least:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Arcade Mode - Separate from Story Mode, the game includes a <strong>full roguelite</strong> version where you need to battle your way to the top on a single life, building a town of your own as you progress.  How far can you get?</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON BALL FighterZ</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/678950/DRAGON_BALL_FighterZ/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/extras/GIF_DBFZ_STEAM.png?t=1709230702"><br/><br/>DRAGON BALL FighterZ is born from what makes the DRAGON BALL series so loved and famous: endless spectacular fights with its all-powerful fighters.<br/><br/>Partnering with Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ maximizes high end Anime graphics and brings easy to learn but difficult to master fighting gameplay.<br/><br/>High-end Anime Graphics<br/>Using the power of the Unreal engine and the talented team at Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ is a visual tour-de-force.<br/><br/>3vs3 Tag/Support<br/>Build your dream team and sharpen your skills to master high-speed tag combinations.<br/><br/>Thrilling Online Features<br/>Ranked matches, interactive lobby, crazy 6-player Party Match... There is something for every taste!<br/><br/>Exclusive Story Mode<br/>Discover a never-seen-before scenario featuring Android 21, a brand new character whose creation was supervised by Akira Toriyama himself.<br/><br/>Spectacular Fights<br/>Experience aerial combos, destructible stages and famous scenes from the DRAGON BALL anime in 60FPS and 1080p resolution!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robin Hood - Sherwood Builders</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1159420/Robin_Hood__Sherwood_Builders/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fk2N3rpRuB3" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/fc521c8bf21bff775962df4f130bb74eb5577a46.png?t=1709562813"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif01.gif?t=1709562813"><br/><br/>Robin Hood - Sherwood Builders is an action-adventure RPG with base-building elements, where you take on the role of a classic hero who stands up to the tyranny and injustice that haunts Sherwood. As Robin, you’ll fight, hunt, craft, steal, and of course help the local people thrive to spite the Sheriff of Nottingham and his ruthless regime – all within an open-world environment that can be freely explored.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif02.gif?t=1709562813"><br/><br/>Robin Hood is a famous hero of medieval English folk tales, believed to have during that time roamed the forests of Sherwood with his band of loyal outlaw companions. In the game you’re going to meet those legendary characters as well, such as Lady Marian, Little John, Friar Tuck, Allan-a-Dale, and Will Scarlet. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif05.gif?t=1709562813"><br/><br/>Robin's main goal is to help a fledgling community of refugees and rebels advance and expand. Starting with what could be described as a small forest settlement, with a bit of care, hard work, and good luck, it can end up as a town full of people. Recruit local peasants, rebels on the run from the law, and even the citizens and guards of Nottingham themselves as your new outlaw settlers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif04.gif?t=1709562813"><br/><br/>You start your adventure with building a forest camp, which can soon be expanded following the arrival of new residents. You will be responsible for properly managing the space you secured for yourself within Sherwood Forest to build up the village.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif03.gif?t=1709562813"><br/><br/>Another important part of taking care of the settlement will be to manage the community members’ professions and tasks, training them to become craftsmen, hunters, or guards, and to manage the settlement’s resources, either gathering them yourself or stealing them from convoys and noble estates.<br/><br/>As Robin's people grow large in number and strong in sword arm, an uprising in Nottingham may just become a reality, ending the Sheriff's tyranny once and for all.<br/>Can Robin Hood and his Merry Men survive and put an end to injustice? Their fate is up to you!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Godrop:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802550/GodropPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Prologue and the official version of the difference between<br/>Levels: one in the prologue, four in the official version<br/>Follow-up Program:<br/>The game will continue to update content after release, which includes:<br/>More bosses: different fighting styles and types of boss fights.<br/>More tech: weird and wacky tech combinations.<br/>More weapons: more basic weapons and weapon variants.<br/>More game modes: In addition to the basic level mode there will also be a survivor mode and parkour mode. </strong><br/><br/><strong>A special roguelike game that focuses entirely on ramming, piercing, and spraying as the core gameplay. You will play as Gotrop, a powerful unknown alien invasion weapon, facing the layers of barriers set up by the arrogant and ignorant humans in the solar system, using good movement and killing to steal the energy of human warships, driving our strong interaction force outer armor for invincible transformation, and destroying all the enemies in our way with incredible maneuverability and invulnerable ramming ability! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/y1.png?t=1709446521"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/1.gif?t=1709446521"><br/><strong>A combat system focused on energy. Just by being in motion you can generate a constant stream of energy, and mysterious alien technology also allows Gotrop to steal energy directly from his enemies. There is energy can be transformed into an invincible droplet state, invulnerable and unbreakable, our enemies can not cause any damage to us, but we can directly puncture the inside of their battleships havoc! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/y2.png?t=1709446521"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/2.gif?t=1709446521"><br/><strong>A large number of tech components have been beamed into the solar system, and Gotrop can access tech for morphing upgrades simply by cleaning up the battlefield! Whether it's a drill that can drill into enemy ships faster, outer armor that can reflect all attacks, or a spout that spews bullets, they can be acquired after sweeping through the enemy! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/y3.png?t=1709446521"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/3.gif?t=1709446521"><br/><strong>The solar system has been fortified by humans and is in crisis. Gotrop will break through layers of asteroids, energy stands and turret arrays until he completely destroys the human space fleet and takes over Earth! </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1709568697"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1709568697"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709568697"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1709568697"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1709568697"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1709568697"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1709568697"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1709568697"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1709568697"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709568697"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1709568697"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiritfall</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1835240/Spiritfall/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/PlatformFighterRoguelike.png?t=1709641776"><br/><strong>Spiritfall</strong> combines tight Platform Fighter combat, smooth movement, and Roguelite mechanics into one! Trek across dangerous lands, string together deadly combos to fend off swarms of enemies, and harness an ever-changing set of powers through a randomly generated map. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/SynergiesAwait.png?t=1709641776"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/GIFDivineSynergiesQuality.gif?t=1709641776"><br/>The divine spirits offer powerful blessings that enhance your abilities in combat. Discover your favorite abilities, and experiment with different builds. With over 150+ blessings to choose from, these gifts allow for a range of tactical approaches that encourage you to find synergies that fit your playstyle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/StrongerFromDefeat.png?t=1709641776"><br/>Death is but a temporary setback. Reawaken stronger than before at the Sanctum and continue your adventure. Use the resources you gathered to upgrade your skills, unlock unique powers, and awaken mighty weapons with unique movesets.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/Community.png?t=1709641776"><br/>A heartfelt thank you to our Early Access community! Your feedback has been invaluable during Spiritfall's development, helping make the game what it is today. We invite you to keep shaping our world together. Connect with fellow players on Discord and get the latest news by joining our newsletter.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minami Lane</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678990/Minami_Lane/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Minami Lane is a small, wholesome management game set on a Japanese-inspired street. Create and manage your own street, make sure everyone is happy, and watch the villagers live their lives! Enjoy 2 to 4 hours of playtime, cute tanukis and lots of cats!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/Gameplay.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/><i><strong>Build your street</strong></i><br/>Build homes to add villagers to your street, then improve their happiness by beautifying every inch and building a variety of shops &amp; attractions! These include ramen shops, boba cafes, bookstores and more, each with unique inventories and effects.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Building.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/><i><strong>Manage your shops</strong></i><br/>Attract customers with everything from floral bouquets to karaoke! Shops you create will need your careful guidance to offer the right products at the right prices. Lead them to success and make your neighborhood thrive.<br/><br/><i><strong>Watch your villagers live their lives</strong></i><br/>Once you start the day, you'll get to see each villager react to your street and offer helpful feedback on how to improve! Memorize their preferences and refine your street the following day.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Review.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/><i><strong>Reach your objectives</strong></i><br/>Complete missions to unlock new levels with more buildings, villager types, and other surprises.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/Features.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>What Minami Lane offers:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>2-4 hours of play time<br/></li><li>Create and customize your own adorable street<br/></li><li>Manage shops by adjusting their inventory, recipes, and prices<br/></li><li>Play strategically to complete each level's mission objectives<br/></li><li>Keep the streets clean by picking up trash<br/></li><li>Tanukis and cats!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Ramen.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>What Minami Lane does not offer:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hardcore strategy<br/></li><li>Multiplayer<br/></li><li>Tons of missions<br/></li><li>New levels after release</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/GameModes.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>In Minami Lane's missions, you'll need to strategically plan each day and use random events to your advantage to complete multiple objectives. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Bike.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>The sandbox mode focuses on creativity and relaxation, allowing you to immerse yourself in the peaceful, cozy world without the stress of objectives.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/DevTeam.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>Minami Lane is the collaborative effort of Dorian (Doot), Doriane (Blibloop) and Antoine (Zakku). Doot, a former data scientist turned game developer, brings light strategy and management gameplay, while Blibloop breathes life into the isometric world with her Studio Ghibli-inspired, hand-drawn designs. Zakku adds the finishing touches with joyful, wholesome music compositions and soundscape. We really hope you will enjoy this tiny game we made with love 💕<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678990/Minami_Lane/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678990/Minami_Lane/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR WARS™: Dark Forces Remaster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2292260/STAR_WARS_Dark_Forces_Remaster/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_8.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/><i>Star Wars</i>™: Dark Forces Remaster has been brought to life by the team at <strong>Nightdive Studios</strong>, fully remastered through its proprietary KEX engine, allowing the game to run on modern gaming devices at up to 4K resolution at 120FPS. New and returning players will enjoy <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces Remaster’s upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<br/><br/>The original 1995 <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces raised the bar for FPS games, offering players a significant degree of movement and interactivity, a large selection of items and power-ups, and engaging environments. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_10.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/>In the first <i>Star Wars</i> FPS video game, players assume the role of Kyle Katarn, a defector of the Galactic Empire turned mercenary for hire. Katarn joins the Rebel Alliance’s covert operations division tasked with infiltrating the Galactic Empire, where he discovers the secret Dark Trooper Project. The development of this powerful new series of Imperial battle droids and power-armored stormtroopers stands to strengthen the Empire’s grip on the galaxy unless Katarn and the Rebel Alliance intervene.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>All fourteen original levels, featuring <i>Star Wars</i>™ worlds and capital ships<br/></li><li>Use your ability to jump, duck, and crawl to solve puzzles and defeat enemies<br/></li><li>Your Personal Digital Assistant provides you with in game information such including map, inventory, and mission briefing<br/></li><li>Engaging first-person ground combat featuring ten weapons and twenty types of enemies<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS visuals<br/></li><li>Advanced 3D rendering enables updated lighting and atmospheric effects<br/></li><li>Modern gamepad support adds a new weapon wheel, and rumble<br/></li><li>Controller Support - vibration and gyro controls <br/></li><li>A variety of power-ups are made available to the player, including health, shields, weapons and ammunition<br/></li><li>For combat, the player may use fists, explosive landmines and thermal detonators, as well as blasters and other ranged weapons<br/></li><li>Includes immersive environmental puzzles and mazes </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_1.gif?t=1709278523"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shashingo: Learn Japanese with Photography</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1632490/Shashingo_Learn_Japanese_with_Photography/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Explore bright, fictional Japanese streets filled with details and interesting objects to capture with your camera. Each photograph you take will translate the name of the content into Japanese and English so you can learn with your surroundings.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/extras/Shashingo_Take_Photo.gif?t=1709246737"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A stylised, approachable 3D environment<br/></li><li>In-game photography system<br/></li><li>Japanese audio<br/></li><li>Photo album to store your flash cards<br/></li><li>A game mode that tests your memory<br/></li><li>Beginner phrases and grammar lessons<br/></li><li>Day/Night and weather cycle<br/></li><li>Display romaji, kana, furigana <i>(recommended)</i> or kanji</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/extras/Shashingo_Flash_Cards.png?t=1709246737"><h2 class="bb_tag">Create Stunning Photography Based Flashcards</h2>Every photo flash-card you take will be unique to you. The idea behind this is to strengthen the relationship between a word and how you see its physical appearance. In the real world, you can then see such objects and make connections to the Japanese words you've already learned while playing Shashingo.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/extras/Shashingo_Photo_Album.png?t=1709246737"><h2 class="bb_tag">Track Your Progress in the Photo Album</h2>Your photo album is where you keep your collection of Photo Flash-Cards. If you remember them well in Find Mode, they'll be separated into the 'mastered' tab and shown with a gold star sticker. However, if you're struggling to remember a word in Find Mode, they'll be marked with a purple exclamation mark sticker, so you know which words you need to practice more.<br/>You can also mark your favourite words &amp; images with a cute little heart sticker to add them to your favourites page.<br/><br/>At the back of your in-game photo album, there are numerous pages of Japanese lessons designed for beginners that will teach you how to speak Japanese and use the vocabulary that you learn in Shashingo. Also included are some key words and important phrases that can help you in your future conversations.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dicefolk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1996430/Dicefolk/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FtN3yxBv4tq" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Join_Our_Discord_600x224.png?t=1709379465"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Dicefolk is a tactical roguelite game based on customizable dice and monster-catching mechanics. On your adventure as a Chimera Summoner, you'll meet dozens of unique and powerful creatures that you can recruit to create the perfect team.<br/><br/>Play as Alea, a young Dicefolk hero who discovers her ability to befriend Chimera and fight back against evil forces threatening humanity’s extinction.</strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Battle_Start.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H2.png?t=1709379465"><br/>Embark on a thrilling quest to save humanity from the grasp of an evil sorcerer. Build a team from over 100 unique, hand-drawn Chimera to suit your playstyle. Unlock all the talismans to uncover the mystical secrets behind the Chimeras’ existence.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Map.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H3.png?t=1709379465"><br/>With a large variety of Chimeras to befriend and command, you'll need to strategize and adapt your playstyle to suit each battle. From tough tanks to speedy attackers, each Chimera brings a unique set of abilities to the table. Your tactical choices will determine your success in battle!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Recruiting.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H4.png?t=1709379465"><br/>It’s all up to you! Customize your dice for maximum influence over your Chimeras’ attacks and abilities. Control the order in which battles play out and choose when parties take action. Dicefolk defies RNG and gives you unprecedented influence on the roll of the dice! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Battle.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H5.png?t=1709379465"><br/>Each playthrough offers its own rewards, and the Chimeras you encounter in one run can be entirely different than those you find in another. With different Chimeras comes different strategies to assemble your team for the perfect run!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Anim_H5.gif?t=1709379465"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Dino Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_12" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🦖🐾 WELCOME TO 100 DINO CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🦕🐈</h2>🦎 Join the cutest adventure in the Dino park with Cats and Dinos! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of dinosaurs location and dino-cats as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/600x200.png?t=1709146681"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Dino Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815640/100_Dino_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=DinoCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Extra.png?t=1709146681"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816050/100_Dino_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=DinoCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709146681"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815630/100_Dino_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=DinoCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709146681"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/600x1.png?t=1709146681"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709146681"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803010/100_Robo_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803010/100_Robo_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815640/100_Dino_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815640/100_Dino_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709485776"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709485776"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709485776"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709485776"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709485776"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solium Infernum</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1893810/Solium_Infernum/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare yourself for Solium Infernum, the grand strategy game of politics, intrigue and betrayal, set in the ultimate arena of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingDarkSide2.gif?t=1709622129"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_IndulgeYourDarkSide_eng.png?t=1709622129"><br/>Satan's mysteriously vanished and Hell is in an uproar. Play as one of eight all-powerful and menacing Archfiends and indulge your Machiavellian dark side. Command legions, enlist champions, cast sinister rituals, and trick, rob, and insult your rivals to be crowned Hell’s new Dark Majesty.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingStrategy2.gif?t=1709622129"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_StrategyFromHell_eng.png?t=1709622129"><br/>Experience Solium Infernum's legendary devilish political machinations. Requiring nerves of steel and a true heart of darkness, every order you give will have lasting consequences. Get into the minds of your rivals, second-guessing their every move both on the map and on the floor of Hell’s parliament as you sling insults and demands in the only truly political strategy game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Eight playable Archfiends<br/></li><li>Eight single-player Chronicles<br/></li><li>Single-player Skirmish mode<br/></li><li>Revelations Tutorial Scenario<br/></li><li>Sessional and Asynchronous 2-6 player Multiplayer<br/></li><li>Dozens of Infernal Legions, including unique enormous Titans. <br/></li><li>Champion Praetors and dark Artifacts fit for any Archfiend!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingMulitplayer.gif?t=1709622129"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_InfernalMultiplayer_eng.png?t=1709622129"><br/>Play 2-6 player multiplayer games with your soon-to-be ex-friends in a single session of deceit and politics, or put your friendships to the test in quick daily bursts with Solium Infernum’s infamous asynchronous multiplayer for a truly harrowing scheme-in-your-sleep experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/Heading_DarkArt2.gif?t=1709622129"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_DivineMadness_eng.png?t=1709622129"><br/>If you love dark art, you’re in the right place. Brimming with striking visions of Hell unlike anything you’ve seen before, Solium Infernum is an infernal feast for the eyes with multitudes of individual dark paintings to enjoy. Every item of the game is accompanied by mind-blasting artwork, a feat declaring Solium Infernum a winner of the 2022 Game Makers Sketchbook.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingRessurect.gif?t=1709622129"><br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_CultClassic_eng.png?t=1709622129"><br/>Originally inspired by Milton’s epic poem, Paradise Lost, League of Geeks’ (known for seminal digital board game Armello) sophomore title is a re-imagining and modernisation of Vic Davis’ critically acclaimed cult-classic of the same name, hailed as a masterpiece of strategy game design. <br/><br/>Once again, prepare to lose yourself within ‘the cold glory of a difficult decision’ as we resurrect Solium Infernum from the depths of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/label_praise.png?t=1709622129"><br/>Note: The following quotes refer to the original Solium Infernum (2009) by Vic Davis.<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum is a political wargame set in hell… The game is now finished, and none of the friends survived. By which I mean, we all hate each other now.”</i> <br/>- Rock Paper Shotgun<br/><br/><i>“It’s a game about playing other people, in both senses of the word…. This is game design based on psychology as much as rules.” </i><br/>- Quarter to Three<br/><br/><i>“More than any game I've played in years, Solium Infernum nails the sensation of staring at a screen and losing yourself in the cold glory of a difficult decision.”</i><br/>- Game Developer (formerly Gamasutra)<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum kicked my knees out from under me ... this game took my past experience with strategy games and threw it, like a pro basketball player, into a bin eighty feet away.”</i><br/>- Eurogamer<br/><br/><i>“One of the best games of the year.”</i><br/>— Three Moves Ahead<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_toReign.png?t=1709622129"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kneedle Knight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2491720/Kneedle_Knight/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Kneedle Knight</i> is a third-person, puzzle platformer game developed by students at SMU Guildhall Cohort 32. In <i>Kneedle Knight</i>, the player controls a mouse knight that uses his magical needle to sew fabric which he can merge into, moving back and forth between 3D and 2D. <br/><br/>Sir Lukoss the Small was a noble knight sent on a quest to defeat the evil Witch of Fabric. The Witch, using her enchanted fabric, imprisoned and transformed many citizens and knights into malicious fabrications. Sir Lukoss climbed up through her fortress to put an end to her tyranny, only to be hexed by her magic and transformed into a mouse. In the dark dungeon of the Witch’s lair, the mouse finds a magic needle, granting him special powers to sew fabric of his own and merge in and out of the enchanted threadwork. <br/><br/>Now Sir Lukoss must use his newfound weapon to sew his path forward and up through the evil stronghold. The mouse knight can use his needle to solve puzzles, overcome challenging obstacles, and defeat the animated candle minions of the Witch. All with the hopes of returning to face the Witch of Fabric yet again to finish his noble quest.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Single-player, puzzle platformer game<br/></li><li>Playtime (main story): 1-2 hours<br/></li><li>Playtime (100% achievements): 2 hours<br/></li><li>Steam leaderboard support for level speed running<br/></li><li>Made in Unreal Engine 5<br/></li><li>Original soundtrack</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myth of Empires</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1371580/Myth_of_Empires/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple Civilizations</h2>We are developing tech trees for multiple civilizations, which will include armor, weapons, buildings, crafting stations, and more. Greece, Persia, Rome, and Egypt will be added, with Greece and Persia scheduled to make their debut in 2024.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/多文明时代，即将来临！.gif?t=1709605830"><h2 class="bb_tag">Embark Upon a Thrilling Journey</h2>Explore a land with diverse landscapes, ecologies, and weather, as well as a realistic day/night cycle. The v1.0 release of Myth of Empires also features a new map – Dongzhou Island, offering new adventures and challenges.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/11111探索之旅，发现新世界的惊险旅程.gif?t=1709605830"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Own Empire From the Ground Up</h2>Myth of Empires features sandbox gameplay with a high degree of freedom; the game has 1300+ different crafting recipe, allowing you to build your own empire. The v1.0 release adds new recipes, including mechanical tools and base defenses, as well as a new planting system. The possibilities are endless.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/2【替换Gif】自由创造，打造你的帝国.gif?t=1709605830"><h2 class="bb_tag">Recruit NPCs, Tame Wildlife</h2>In-depth taming and training systems allow players to recruit or subdue additional forces to aid them in combat and production. The v1.0 release adds new boss NPCs and powerful beasts. In addition, smaller types of animals can be used to help power your base’s defenses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/333333驯服万物，NPC、马匹与野生动物.gif?t=1709605830"><h2 class="bb_tag">Wage Epic Wars on Ancient Battlefields</h2> Myth of Empires features hundreds of different weapons, armor, and large-scale engineering equipment. Pick the weapons that best suit your playstyle, or utilize your strategic capabilities to build an army. The v1.0 release introduces powerful mechanical base defenses, wooden oxen, and other new combat equipment to further enrich the game’s deep war experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/4【替换Gif】史诗战争体验，挑战百变的古代战场.gif?t=1709605830"><h2 class="bb_tag">Engage in Cross-server Battles </h2>Establish administrative regions, fight for the position of county magistrate, and compete to expand your territory through Fortress Battles. Craft the perfect guild and utilize your diplomatic prowess to ensure its long-term stability.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/555555跨服征战，共同创造历史.gif?t=1709605830"><h2 class="bb_tag">Write Your Own Legend </h2>With 25 different development paths, a 16-level title system, and more than 100 achievements, you have complete freedom in growing your character. Become a legendary military commander, or content yourself with the life of a simple farmer – the choice is yours.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/6【替换Gif】传奇生涯，定制独特的人生.gif?t=1709605830"><h2 class="bb_tag">Play Multiple Gameplay Modes Offering Endless Possibilities </h2>Myth of Empires supports official servers, custom servers, as well as solo and hosted modes. Creative players are also able to use the game’s robust mod editor to tailor the game to their dream experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/no7多样玩法.gif?t=1709605830"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Epoch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/899770/Last_Epoch/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Epoch combines time travel, exciting dungeon crawling, engrossing character customization and endless replayability to create an Action RPG for veterans and newcomers alike. Travel through the world of Eterra’s past and face dark empires, wrathful gods and untouched wilds – to find a way to save time itself from The Void.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Gameplay.gif?t=1709060046"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>15 Mastery Classes</strong><br/>Embark on your adventure as one of five powerful classes and, through your journey, ascend into a unique Mastery Class that unlocks more specialized abilities and build-options. <br/></li><li><strong>120+ Skill Trees</strong><br/>Every skill has its own augment tree that will allow you to control, alter, and empower your playstyle. Transform your skeletons into archers, your lightning blast into chain lightning, or make your serpent strike summon snakes to fight alongside you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Nodes.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Hunt Rare &amp; Powerful Loot</strong><br/>Fill your arsenal with magic items that you may craft to perfection, change the rules of your build with powerful unique and set items, and always have that next upgrade just on the horizon with Last Epoch's deep and randomized loot system.<br/></li><li><strong>Rewarding Crafting System</strong><br/>The items you wield are yours to forge! Last Epoch’s community-revered crafting system allows you to control your character's power progression, featuring robust and deterministic upgrade mechanics.<br/></li><li><strong>Uncover the Past, Reforge the Future</strong><br/>Travel to different moments of time where you will discover the many factions and secrets that exist within the world of Eterra and fight to set the timeline onto a new path.<br/></li><li><strong>Endless replayability</strong><br/>With a wealth of classes and skills to customize, deep game systems, randomized loot, and continuing development, Last Epoch is a game that will keep you coming back for years to come.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Monolith.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Easy to Learn, Hard to Master</strong><br/>We’re committed to making gameplay approachable for new and veteran players alike by allowing you to jump into the fray quickly and providing many in-game resources. Though don’t be fooled, Eterra has many dangers waiting for you that require a mastery of combat and build-crafting.<br/></li><li><strong>Zero Pay-To-Win</strong><br/>Last Epoch will never offer gameplay advantages by being able to spend real money. We believe in creating a fair environment for all players. </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminator: Dark Fate - Defiance</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1839950/Terminator_Dark_Fate__Defiance/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif1.gif?t=1709216510"><br/><strong>Terminator: Dark Fate – Defiance</strong> is a <strong>real-time strategy game</strong> based on the Terminator: Dark Fate universe that follows the war between humanity and Legion's synthetic intelligent machine network.<br/><br/>In the<strong> single-player campaign</strong>, you take the role of a commander in the Founders, a force made up of the remnants of the US military and guide your army in an attempt to foil Legion's plan to exterminate the last remnants of humanity. In skirmish and multiplayer modes, play as three very diverse factions: Founders, Movement and Legion.<br/><br/>Take control of an army carried over from mission to mission on a series of large strategic maps. Make decisions about unit placement, battle tactics and abilities so that you don’t just survive but can become the leader of the resistance against the machines. Hone your skills and military expertise by replaying and achieving the best possible outcomes.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic battlefields: realistic tactics and consequences</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif2.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>Engage in complex, realistic battles where your <strong>tactical decisions</strong> are vital to your survival and ultimate victory. Use a variety of military equipment, vehicles and ammunition types in your battles against the enemy. Recruit and train new units, assign new skills and acquire new weapons and equipment to continue the resistance.<br/><br/>Encounter tense battles. Your battlefield tactics and choices have deep consequences that will impact through the campaign, with other factions and characters either joining you or fighting against you, and with certain missions being available or not depending on your actions. <br/><br/><strong>Your resources are limited</strong> and you must protect your army. Weapons of war receive damage through a modular component damage system where armour characteristics, component malfunctions and hull structure all affect if your troops survive.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Lead the survival of mankind</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif3.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>Recruit others to your cause and <strong>grow your army</strong>. Mix and match the composition of your troops to fit your preferred battle tactics. Use infantry units, heavy armoured military vehicles, plasma cannon technology, drones and other flying units and even human skirmishers to achieve victory.<br/><br/>Use the battlefield to your advantage! <strong>Physics-based building demolition</strong> lets you generate a realistic set of tactical consequences, especially in urban areas.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer Mayhem: Skirmish and Online Battles</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif4.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>The excitement amplifies in <strong>skirmish and multiplayer modes</strong>, where <strong>you can play as three distinct factions</strong>: Founders, Movement, and Legion. <br/><br/>Engage in epic battles across vast strategic landscapes, testing your skills and military expertise. Every decision matters, impacting alliances, missions, and the overall survival of mankind.<br/><br/>Challenge your skills in skirmish and online multiplayer matches, facing off against AI or real-life human opponents in intense 1v1 and 2v2 battles.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2379780/Balatro/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Balatro is a poker-inspired roguelike deck builder all about creating powerful synergies and winning big.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Endless_Possibility.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/>Combine valid poker hands with unique Joker cards in order to create varied synergies and builds. Earn enough chips to beat devious blinds, all while uncovering hidden bonus hands and decks as you progress. You’re going to need every edge you can get in order to reach the boss blind, beat the final ante and secure victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Jokers_Clean_Thin.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The definitive poker roguelike experience.<br/></li><li>Endless possibilities - every pick-up, discard and joker can dramatically alter the course of your run.<br/></li><li>In-depth campaign mode complete with 8 difficulties, as well as challenge, daily and seeded runs. </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Break_The_Game.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/>Deftly deploy an array of potent tools: different Decks, Jokers, Tarot cards, Planet cards, Spectral cards, and Vouchers. Use these versatile instruments to ignite a combo frenzy and turbocharge your poker hands, crafting electrifying, adrenaline-fueled synergies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro_5_Aces_GIF__HQ_.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 Jokers, each with their own unique abilities<br/></li><li>15 Decks with distinct modifiers to choose from for each run<br/></li><li>5 potential variants of each Joker which add further abilities<br/></li><li>22 Tarot cards variants that can enhance your regular playing cards<br/></li><li>11 Planet cards that help level up your possible poker hands<br/></li><li>32 Voucher cards to help provide permanent buffs for your current run</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Find_Your_Flow.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in Balatro’s distinctive psychedelic world. Let the synthwave soundtrack wash over you -  wind down, escape the daily grind and prepare to enter the ultimate roguelike flow state.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improve your collection and discover new cards and secrets with every single run.<br/></li><li>Make use of the in-depth stats screen to study your best hands, most used Jokers, and more!<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the CRT fuzz and enjoy detailed, hand-crafted pixel art.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Spectral_Pack.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F5mH3dNhjx2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro-join_the_discord.png?t=1709312324"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please, Touch The Artwork 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2600140/Please_Touch_The_Artwork_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Disclaimer:</strong><i> This is a short game made in</i> <strong>6 months</strong><i>. It's</i> <strong>100% FREE</strong><i>(no ads, no dlc's), made by a </i><strong>solo dev</strong><i> in honour of James Ensor’s 75 year remembrance.</i> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/extras/Steam3DRoomGIF_Wide.gif?t=1708975190"><br/><br/>Touch the artwork and help a lost skeleton artist find its way home in a surreal, hand-painted universe. <br/><br/>Collect hidden objects for its quirky inhabitants, solve casual puzzles, and restore cracks in the fabric of the paintings. <br/><br/>This slow paced relaxing adventure was carefully crafted from works by James Ensor, a Belgian pioneer in the world of Modern Art.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Hidden object adventure<br/></li><li>5 unique worlds<br/></li><li>Hints when stuck<br/></li><li>Casual point &amp; click gameplay<br/></li><li>Zoom-in for extra details<br/></li><li>Real hand-painted art<br/></li><li>Atmospheric relaxing sound<br/></li><li>Silly and quirky<br/></li><li>Slow-paced &amp; relaxing<br/></li><li>Fit for ages 12-99</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Small Mazes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2570630/20_Small_Mazes/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2570630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a puzzle game with twenty small mazes. If you solve the mazes, you beat the game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>It's about 1-2 hours long, maybe.<br/></li><li>You need a keyboard and mouse to play it. One person played through the whole game on the Steam Deck, but I tried it and think it's better on PC.<br/></li><li> A few puzzles require knowledge of English. No puzzle requires sound or audio to solve it. No puzzle requires being able to recognize different colors.</li></ul> <br/>I hope you enjoy it. <br/> 						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonder</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692570/Sonder/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Local Co-op requires a gamepad controller for both players. Online Co-op supports mouse and keyboard. </i><h2 class="bb_tag">Psychological narrative </h2>- After a mass-scale destruction of all artificial intelligence, a scrapped robot and soul form an unexpected friendship. After a mysterious train knocks them out, they wake up in a world shaped by their own thoughts. Will they be able to cooperate and escape this dark reality?<h2 class="bb_tag">Immersive atmosphere </h2>- Immerse yourself in an atmospheric world crafted with a stylish, minimalistic approach that captivates your attention and enhances the shared adventure. Unleash the power of collaboration, confront existential mysteries, and embark on a gaming journey like no other.<h2 class="bb_tag">Collaboration </h2>- Work together - succeed together. Each character has unique abilities that allow them to manipulate the world in their own way, meaning they can only proceed if they cooperate. In combat, maximum efficiency can be achieved by combining the player’s powers, allowing them to neutralize the most dangerous of foes.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do U Copy?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1806420/Do_U_Copy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1806420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i>Do U Copy?</i> requires a minimum of 2 players to be played.  Get the Hacker App on our website</strong><br/><br/>Gear up for <i>Do U Copy?</i>, not your average VR co-op game - it's a party in a headset! Ideal for friends who argue over pizza toppings, families who can't assemble IKEA furniture without a feud, and couples who think they've mastered the art of 'unspoken communication'.<br/><br/><i>Do U Copy?</i> is the perfect blend of chaos, strategy, and teamwork to put your communication skills to the test! <br/><br/>Play as the <strong>Thief </strong>and make your way through one of the (least) secured banks in the country. Avoid traps, guards and camera using your VR legs and the guidance of your « guy-in-the-chair ».<br/><br/>OR<br/><br/>Play as the <strong>Hacker</strong>, become the eyes and ears of the operations through your phone, tablet or laptop! Using your (un)realistic skills, hack through the bank securities, guide your ally and solve engaging puzzles with unexpected turns!<br/><br/>Together, you'll fumble, bumble, and stumble your way through the heist of the century. Will you pull off the ultimate heist or just end up virtually 'breaking' a window? <br/>Dive into <i>Do U Copy?</i> and find out! <br/><br/><i>Do U Copy?</i> requires a minimum of 2 players to be played.  <strong>Get the Hacker App on our website</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeepUp Survival</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1524630/KeepUp_Survival/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1524630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							KeepUp Survival is a base building and adventure sandbox game. Players explore and shape their survival strategies in a world based on their own preferences.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">KeepUp Survival:</h2></strong><br/><br/>Welcome to a world of survival on a deserted island, characterized by an incredible wildlife and abandoned structures. Immerse yourself in a game set in a natural and post-apocalyptic environment where your primary task is to survive in KeepUp Survival.<br/><br/>The design of your survival is entirely in your hands. There are no predefined tasks – you set your own goals to secure your survival.<br/><br/>In this world, you have numerous options available, ranging from crafting and building shelters to farming. You can even have some loyal companions by your side.<br/><br/>A stunningly detailed and immersive world awaits you, one that will captivate you and continually surprise you.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Background Story:</h2></strong><br/><br/>You have crashed on an island by plane and must now make your life on this island. It seems that this island was abandoned a long time ago, as time stood still here. Diseases have seemingly rendered the island uninhabitable, and the wildlife behaves strangely and often aggressively.<br/><br/>Soon, you'll realize that this island is full of secrets and puzzles, and not everything is as it seems at first glance.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2></strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Third and first-person perspective.<br/></li><li>Your character suffers from thirst, hunger, and exhaustion.<br/></li><li>Various means of transportation, such as vehicles, horses, and boats.<br/></li><li>Ability to farm and create your own garden.<br/></li><li>Generate your own electricity using wind and solar energy.<br/></li><li>The ability to tame and keep animals as pets.<br/></li><li>Construction of buildings from various materials like wood, stone, straw, and glass.<br/></li><li>Workbenches for crafting weapons, tools, and furniture.<br/></li><li>Hunting and harvesting opportunities.<br/></li><li>Cooking and smelting of resources.<br/></li><li>Gathering a variety of resources.<br/></li><li>Mining and ore extraction.<br/></li><li>A dynamic weather system.<br/></li><li>A constantly changing day and night cycle.<br/></li><li>A powerful admin tool available to you after reaching a certain gameplay time, allowing you to customize the player experience individually, such as simplifying item acquisition or controlling the day-night cycle.</li></ul><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Development:</h2></strong><br/>In Discord you have the possibility to follow the development and ask questions. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1524630/extras/discord.png?t=1709661769"><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F8zyKXj9SDr" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/8zyKXj9SDr</a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CastingPlz</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2831910/CastingPlz/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							CastingPlz is a 2-player cooperative roguelike game where players take on the roles of two characters with distinct responsibilities: one for attacking and the other for movement.<br/><br/>[Background]<br/>In the past, a Grand Wizard sealed away the monsters that roamed the world and restored peace by imprisoning them in a massive labyrinth.<br/><br/>During this time of peace, a rumor began to circulate worldwide: "In the deepest part of the labyrinth, the Grand Wizard grants any wish."<br/><br/>The source of this rumor is uncertain, but people from all walks of life are heading to the Grand Wizard's labyrinth, each with their own dreams.<br/><br/>[Labyrinth]<br/>The labyrinth is inhabited by sealed monsters that have formed their own ecosystems over a long period, establishing rules to live by.<br/><br/>As you conquer the ever-changing labyrinth one step at a time, delve deeper, uncover its secrets, and progress to lower, more profound levels.<br/><br/>[Monsters]<br/>The monsters trapped by the Grand Wizard are determined to eliminate newcomers who intrude into their ecosystems.<br/><br/>Defeat the advancing monsters to conquer the labyrinth, but don't get too comfortable. As you venture deeper into the labyrinth, more powerful monsters await you.<br/><br/>[Soldier &amp; Wizard]<br/>You must choose to play as either a Soldier or a wizard, with the game roles divided to the extreme. You will need to cooperate with each other to embark on your adventure.<br/><br/>Soldier:<br/><br/>High mobility<br/>Low combat power<br/><br/>Wizard:<br/><br/>Powerful magic<br/>Limited mobility<br/>To achieve your dreams, you must save your partner and approach your own aspirations.<br/><br/>[Magic and Items]<br/>As you progress through the labyrinth, defeat monsters using various spells and acquire diverse items to grow and potentially expedite the conquest of the labyrinth.<br/><br/>...<br/>Maybe?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quilts and Cats of Calico</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1993180/Quilts_and_Cats_of_Calico/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1993180?utm_source=calico&amp;utm_medium=in_steam" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1993180?utm_source=calico&amp;utm_medium=in_steam</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Arrow.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/>Quilts and Cats of Calico is a cozy board game in which the player's main task is to make a quilt from patterned fabric scraps. By smartly combining the colors and patterns of the scraps, the player can not only score points for the completed design but also sew on buttons and attract adorable cats, who have their own preferences for bedding patterns.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Cats_running.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/><strong>Stepping beyond adaptation</strong><br/>In Quilts and Cats of Calico, based on the board game Calico, you will be immersed in a warm, cozy world full of cuddly cats. Here the quilt bends under the weight of their paws and loud purring can be heard. It's a world full of patterns and designs awaiting the master quilt maker.<br/><br/>We also have a few surprises for the Calico fans like variations of the rules and mechanics in the campaign play. In addition to the well-known gameplay scenarios, new ones await to be discovered.<br/><br/><br/><strong>Quilt solo, with friends, or with strangers</strong><br/>Whether you want to quilt solo or prefer to compete with other players, Quilts and Cats of Calico will provide you with the corresponding gameplay mode. You will have cross-platform multiplayer at your disposal, during which you can invite friends or play ranked matches against random players. The more peaceful solo mode allows you to face AI of varying difficulty levels and is the perfect tool to hone your skills in a relaxed atmosphere.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Game_modes.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/><strong>Sew your adventures in the city of cat worshippers</strong><br/>In the game, you can also enjoy the story mode campaign. An extraordinary world inspired by the works of Studio Ghibli awaits you. Here cats have great power and influence over people's lives. Take on the role of an itinerant quilter who decides to succeed in a city of cat-worshippers. Climb to the top of the city hierarchy and face the opponent who wants to dominate the world of humans and cats. Create quilts, perfect your craft, and help those you meet on your journey. Don't worry, you won't be alone - along the way, you'll meet friends and, most importantly, cats whose help can prove invaluable…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Calico_minigry_dialog_steampage_gif.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/><strong>Spend quality time with your cats</strong><br/>In Quilts and Cats of Calico, cats are active during your games. Sometimes minding their own business, and other times coming to you and your quilt. They will lazily observe the board, romp and run around, and sometimes fall into a blissful nap. They are cats, you never know. You can interact with them during the game, pet them, and shoo them away when they get in the way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Calico_glaskanie_v2.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/><strong>Extended customization options</strong><br/>The game is full of cats, but there could always be more! In Quilts and Cats of Calico, you can create your own, making your game even more wholesome! You can give it a name, choose the color of its fur, and put on different outfits. If you wish, it will appear on the board during your gameplay. It will also be possible to choose a different player's portrait and background for the game. Pick what you like best!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1993180/extras/Calico_CatEditor_SteamPage_Gif_v2.gif?t=1709663584"><br/><br/><strong>Beautiful, relaxing music</strong><br/>We asked Pawel Górniak, the composer responsible for the soundtrack to the digital version of Wingspan, to create the music for Quilts and Cats of Calico. Thanks to it, you will not only be able to deeply feel the atmosphere of the game but let yourself be carried away by blissful relaxation.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unbearable</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1990060/Unbearable/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1990060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Claudia, a woman who has lost her job as a reporter, decides to go to investigate the psychiatric hospital "Milagros" which keeps a story as secret as it is macabre. During this journey she meets people who have the same intentions and others who will get in the way.<br/>With the help of her new companions, she must face the secrets of the psychiatric hospital, but the biggest fight is against her own mind.<br/><br/>Narrative Story: Delve into a dark and gritty story with mechanics inspired by survival horror games from the ps2 era.<br/><br/>Cooperative Campaign: Play the story alone or with a friend in split screen.<br/><br/>Transversality: Climb through the scenarios to reach objectives and solve puzzles.<br/><br/>Hide or Fight: Go unnoticed without alerting enemies or use the different melee and fire weapons to finish them off.<br/><br/>Inventory System: Collect items, manage your resources and combine them to solve puzzles.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1990060/extras/PArry_unbearable-3.gif?t=1709660072"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classified: France '44</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2085370/Classified_France_44/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Classified: France ‘44 is a new turn-based strategy game, set in World War II during the desperate months leading up to the Allied invasion of France in June 1944.</strong><br/> <br/>Take charge of a special-ops team of Allied commandos and French resistance fighters. Recruit elite operatives to build your squad, then engage in a sweeping campaign of sabotage and destruction. Deal with competing factions to build the resistance network and strike at German targets deep in occupied territory. However, the more chaos you cause, the more you’ll draw the merciless attention of the Gestapo secret police.<br/> <br/>In exciting missions inspired by the exploits of the Allies and French, the game expands on turn-based tactical concepts, bringing authentic World War 2 combat to life. The campaign allows for multiple playthroughs that are different each time. For those who really want to test their skills, our rich Mission Creator tool allows players to create, share and download custom missions.<h2 class="bb_tag">Every Shot Counts.</h2> In Classified: France ‘44’s unique morale system, every shot taken affects you or your enemies. Suppress and break your opposition, giving you a brief window to flank your cowering targets and finish them off.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085370/extras/1._Every_Shot_Counts_v2.gif?t=1709667542"><h2 class="bb_tag">Shape the Battle.</h2> Use stealth tactics to eliminate key targets and start the fight on your terms. However, the more kills you make, the more enemies will begin to suspect that something's wrong, so be ready to unleash your ambush before they sniff you out!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085370/extras/2._Shape_the_Battle_v2.gif?t=1709667542"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build your Team. </h2>An authentic and characterful mix of heroes will be yours to choose from, each with their own story to tell. Train, customise and equip them with your growing arsenal of skills and weapons.  Raise the morale of your team by spending time around the campfire, and learning about their lives as they fight across the war-ravaged fields of occupied France.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085370/extras/3._Build_Your_Team_v2.gif?t=1709667542"><h2 class="bb_tag">Experience History. </h2>Complete challenging objectives in over 45 missions supplied to your team by the French forces. Choose which missions suit your strategy to grow the resistance and support your ultimate goals. Manage your team by sending them on strategic operations.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085370/extras/4._Experience_History_v4.gif?t=1709667542"><h2 class="bb_tag">Built to Last. </h2>Updates and expansions will grow the world of Classified: France ‘44, bringing new and exciting elements to your freedom fight. Our Classified Mission Creator and the modding tools ensure there will always be player-created content to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085370/extras/5._Built_to_Last_v2.gif?t=1709667542"><h2 class="bb_tag">On to Victory.</h2> Classified: France ‘44 is full of challenge. Work out the optimum grand strategy while deploying the best tactical play and discover the game's multiple endings. What will your D-Day look like?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2085370/extras/6._On_To_Victory_v2.gif?t=1709667542"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expeditions: A MudRunner Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2477340/Expeditions_A_MudRunner_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fsnowrunner" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/extras/STEAM_DISCORD_BANNER_EXPEDITIONS.jpg?t=1709660925"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/extras/EXP_MAIN_EN.gif?t=1709660925"><br/><br/>From Arizona to the Carpathians, chart through expansive open worlds in search of hidden treasures and forgotten ruins. Expeditions: A MudRunner Game is a groundbreaking off-road simulation crafted by Saber Interactive, creators of the critically acclaimed SnowRunner. <br/><br/>Lead research missions as you drive a variety of all-terrain vehicles, using high-tech tools and managing your camp and crew to ensure your success in the wild. Embark on ever-rewarding scientific expeditions as you adapt to nature's challenges, and unravel the mysteries of uncharted lands. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/extras/EXP_OFFROAD_EN.gif?t=1709660925"><br/><br/>Expeditions: A MudRunner Game builds on the legacy of Saber Interactive’s off-road simulations with its advanced physics-based gameplay systems, perfectly encapsulating the feel of driving through the wilderness. Whether you’re a long-time player of MudRunner games or a newcomer, you are in for a thrilling scientific adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/extras/EXP_PLANYOUREXPEDITIONS_EN.gif?t=1709660925"><br/><br/>Success depends on preparation. Plan your missions carefully and hire a team of Specialists to improve your skills in the field. With the drone and metal detector, scout your itinerary and locate points of interest. Invest the profits from each expedition to expand your home bases by building support structures to gain useful supplies and summon new vehicles. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/extras/EXP_TOOLS_EN.gif?t=1709660925"><br/><br/>Equip your vehicles with state-of-the-art technologies and cutting-edge gadgets to ensure success in the wild. Use the winch and portable anchors to perform intricate maneuvers, and traverse treacherous rivers with the echo sounder. Choose strategically, as the tools at your disposal can make or break an expedition. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Winch:</strong> Get your vehicle unstuck from the mud or rappel down steep cliffs <br/></li><li><strong>Jackscrew:</strong> Turn your vehicle back on its wheels after accidental flips <br/></li><li><strong>Echo sounder:</strong> Avoid sinking by probing the depth of the water around your vehicle <br/></li><li>And much more… </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/extras/EXP_CUSTO_EN.gif?t=1709660925"><br/><br/>Customize your vehicles in the garage, choosing between nimbler scout vehicles, off-road machines or large trucks. Tailor your approach for light and fast exploration or slower, equipment-heavy trucking. Successful expeditions allow you to invest in new accessories, such as storage extensions, spare parts, and measuring tools. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477340/extras/EXP_EXPLO_EN.gif?t=1709660925"><br/><br/>From arid deserts to rugged forests and steep mountains, explore vast, uncharted lands brimming with hidden wonders and forgotten ruins. Archaeological sites, dinosaur fossils and natural curiosities can be found in numbers across Arizona and the Carpathians, and each discovery can be the key to groundbreaking scientific breakthroughs. <br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2477340/Expeditions_A_MudRunner_Game/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2477340/Expeditions_A_MudRunner_Game/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Ball</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2804620/Community_Ball/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2804620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a indie runner game based on geometry dash, in the game are 7 levels, Feel good, Firefly, My heart and more. The most of the levels have ncs songs so if you are a youtuber you wont have any probrem wirh the songs. In the game you have to collect coins in all levels.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DREAMIO: AI-Powered Adventures</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2795060/DREAMIO_AIPowered_Adventures/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795060/extras/StoreHeader.png?t=1709650810"><br/><strong>DREAMIO: AI-Powered Adventures</strong> is an innovative "choose your own adventure" game powered by the latest advancements in generative AI. Your decisions shape the narrative in real-time, offering a unique, personalized adventure with every playthrough.<h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic AI-Generated Content</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795060/extras/Content.gif?t=1709650810"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Story:</strong> Your journey unfolds dynamically in response to the choices you make.<br/></li><li> <strong>Illustrations:</strong> Auto-generated illustrations bring your journey to life.<br/></li><li> <strong>Narration:</strong> Thanks to speech synthesis, a narrator accompanies you throughout your journey.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple Interaction Modes</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795060/extras/Interaction.gif?t=1709650810"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Type manually.<br/></li><li> Speak into your microphone.<br/></li><li> Pick from suggested choices.</li></ul><br/>Stories are told in the second-person point of view. This lets you interact with the narrator directly. You can ask him about your character or environment, or engage in a debate.<h2 class="bb_tag">Customizable Gameplay</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795060/extras/Instructions.gif?t=1709650810"><br/>By default, the narrator will trigger a game over screen if you die and will reject impossible actions. But with simple natural language instructions, you can modify how the narrator operates, adjusting the challenges and freedoms within your story as you see fit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Save System</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795060/extras/Saves.gif?t=1709650810"><br/>Thanks to the save system, you can explore different story branches and outcomes freely. Your every decision leads to a unique adventure!<h2 class="bb_tag">Endless Exploration</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795060/extras/Explore.gif?t=1709650810"><br/>Choose from preinstalled starting prompts or create your own! Share and download prompts via <strong>Steam Workshop</strong>. Whether you're surviving a zombie apocalypse or exploring an alien planet, the possibilities are limitless.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2795060/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2795060/</a><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FZmWvM49cd6" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795060/extras/StoreDiscord.png?t=1709650810"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709650058"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709650058"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARCH ALL - DOGS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2846740/SEARCH_ALL__DOGS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">SEARCH ALL - DOGS</h2> - This is a game in the "search for objects" genre, in which you need to find all the dogs in a large location. The dogs will be located in a variety of places, from the most visible to barely noticeable places. The entire game location looks animated due to the animation elements. Find all the dogs! Don't let them go unnoticed :)<br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/>  - Animation elements on the location;<br/>  - 100 dogs to find;<br/>  - Pleasant soundtrack;<br/>  - The gameplay can be interrupted at any time, and the game will automatically save the result;<br/>  - Hints implemented! If you have trouble finding an item, use the hint!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disco Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1226970/Disco_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1226970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2822370/Chocolate_Factory_Simulator/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2822370/Chocolate_Factory_Simulator/</a><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FbcUDsvbZMy" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1226970/extras/Disco-Simulator-Discord-button.png?t=1709646933"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Select a manager</strong></h2>At the beginning of the game, you will be able to choose your manager. Each of them has their own unique skills to manage different aspects of the club. Decide in which direction you want to develop your club. The skills of the manager you choose will bear fruit in further gameplay, for example: bonuses for bartenders, organizing concerts, or taking care of customer satisfaction. The choice is yours!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1226970/extras/01-Disco-Simulator-_Select_a_manager-01.png?t=1709646933"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Choose your club</strong></h2>There is a wide selection of clubs waiting for you in the game and each of them poses different challenges and has unique victory conditions. Clubs are located in various places: a village, a small town, the center of a big city. Choose wisely and enter the club legend scene!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1226970/extras/02-Disco-Simulator-Choose_your_club-02.png?t=1709646933"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Care for your customers</strong></h2>Your success depends on customer satisfaction. Every guest has their own individual needs, which you must meet in order to keep them in the club. Do they prefer elegant drinks in stylish cocktail glasses? Or maybe they want to dance to the best hits until dawn? Your job will be to make sure that the music, atmosphere and service meet their expectations. Take care of your customers and thanks to this they will recommend your club to others, thus increasing your reputation. React to unexpected events - spilled alcohol, a clogged toilet or a drunk customer, you will have your hands full!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1226970/extras/03-Disco-Simulator-Care_for_your_customers-03.png?t=1709646933"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Organize events</strong></h2>We already have the club ready, the best staff, so it's time to party! Organizing spectacular concerts of bands and DJs is the key to increasing the recognition of your club. Invite stars to the stage, who will not only attract crowds of fans, but also allow you to earn a lot of money. Experience the thrill of making your parties the talk of the town!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1226970/extras/04-Disco-Simulator-Organize_events-04.gif?t=1709646933"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Develop your club</strong></h2>In Disco Simulator, the development of your club is a key element that will allow you to reach the peak level of club glory. Spend your money on a variety of upgrades that will make your club a real paradise for music and dance lovers. In the game, you will be able to improve every aspect of the club - furniture, decorations, music equipment, lighting or sound system. Also, do not forget about hiring employees, choose from among the available and create the best event that will be talked about for years!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1226970/extras/05-Disco-Simulator-Develop_your_club-05.gif?t=1709646933"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESD: Into the Vortex</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2840180/TESD_Into_the_Vortex/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2840180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							TESD: Into The Vortex is an old school 2D pixel art style RPG game where players control a party consisting of Bryan Johnson, Walt Flanagan, and Brian Quinn. Players will fight enemies, complete quests, upgrade gear, and solve riddles. This game was developed as a solo project and total playtime should run a couple hours max.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genopanic: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2787590/Genopanic_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1984190?utm_source=prologue&amp;utm_campaign=description&amp;utm_medium=banner" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787590/extras/link_capsule_genopanic_4_.png?t=1709639201"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Step into the World of Genopanic: Prologue</h2><strong>Embark on an Intergalactic Adventure!</strong><br/>Dive into the thrilling universe of Genopanic with this Prologue, offering a taste of the epic journey ahead. Perfect for newcomers and veterans alike, immerse yourself in a world where you can master the game's style and controls, all while getting a tantalizing preview of the adventures that await.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787590/extras/Description_alpha.gif?t=1709639201"><br/><strong>A Compact, Rich Experience</strong><br/>Designed to be completed in under an hour, the Prologue introduces you to the very beginning of our expansive story. Battle a formidable boss and get a glimpse of the challenges and triumphs that lie ahead in the full game.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787590/extras/Description_1.gif?t=1709639201"><br/><strong>Discover the Gameplay Mechanics</strong><br/>Experience a selection of the gameplay mechanics that make Genopanic unique. Although just a part of what the full game offers, the Prologue provides a solid foundation of what to expect in terms of gameplay and strategy.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787590/extras/Description_2.gif?t=1709639201"><br/><strong>Stunning Visuals and Atmosphere</strong><br/>The Prologue shares the same striking graphics and visual style as the main game. Every frame is a piece of art, setting the stage for the incredible journey that unfolds in Genopanic.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787590/extras/Description_3.gif?t=1709639201"><br/><strong>A Sneak Peek into the Genopanic Universe</strong><br/>Perfect for players new to the series or those eagerly awaiting the full release, the Prologue serves as an introductory chapter to the vast, mysterious world of Genopanic. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787590/extras/Description_4.gif?t=1709639201"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Introductory Story</strong> - Experience the beginning of an epic tale that seamlessly leads into the main game's rich narrative.<br/></li><li><strong>Sample of Combat</strong> - Engage in a thrilling boss battle that showcases the dynamic combat system.<br/></li><li><strong>Familiarization</strong> - Get comfortable with the game's controls and mechanics, setting you up for success in the full game.<br/></li><li><strong>Visual and Audio Treat</strong> - Enjoy the same high-quality graphics and atmospheric soundtrack as the main game.</li></ul><br/>Prepare yourself for an unforgettable journey with Genopanic: Prologue - your gateway to a grander cosmic adventure!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiveMeat活肉</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2825640/LiveMeat/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a first person single player horror adventure game. You need to sneak or run in the scene to avoid monsters, search for resources to survive, and find a way to leave.<br/><br/><br/>Gameplay Introduction:<br/>1.There are three areas available for exploration.<br/><br/>2.There are three different types of monsters.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825640/extras/GIF1.gif?t=1709638779"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825640/extras/GIF2.gif?t=1709638779"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825640/extras/GIF3.gif?t=1709638779"><br/><br/>3. You can avoid monsters by running or stealth, but cannot attack them.<br/><br/>4. Resources are limited, and lighting and running will continue to consume resources.There are three areas available for exploration.<br/><br/>5. Props will emit a light once you approach, so don't worry about not being able to find them.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825640/extras/GIF4.gif?t=1709638779"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRUX</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2293200/CRUX/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2293200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							CRUX is a fast-paced single player arena shooter roguelike inspired by the refined mechanics and the drive to mastery of old school boomer shooter of the 90s and the replayability and powerful abilities of roguelike action games.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2293200/extras/rjgrapple.gif?t=1709636570"><br/><br/>In CRUX you play as a cultist warrior of the blood gods, trained from childhood to undertake the trials of the CRUX. The trials consist of 13 arenas across 5 worlds, where you'll face hordes of demons native to that world. Survive the hordes to earn the right to face the Guardian of the Arena, boss fights unique to each arena that will test your skills with movement, weapons, controlling the arena.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2293200/extras/plasmaclimb.gif?t=1709636570"><br/><br/>The blood gods watch your step, and for every arena they will bless you with a selection of magic abilities to increase your power. With a selection of over 100 abilities you will have the opportunity to customize your gameplay to suit your playstyle. Whether you want to bust your foes' skulls with the Skullcrusher, chain lightning magic, steal their lifeforce (or much more!), the choice is yours!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2293200/extras/perkbook.gif?t=1709636570"><br/><br/>Successfully beating all the arenas will land you a spot in the leaderboards. But the true champion is the fastest one, so customize your build and go again to try and get to the top spot!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital 666</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2774380/Hospital_666/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2774380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You wake up in an endless hospital.<br/>You can only use the front or rear elevator to escape.<br/><br/><strong> Turn around if you see something strange.<br/>Turn around if you see something strange.<br/>Turn around if you see something strange. </strong><br/><br/>What will you find on floor 666?<br/><br/>----------------------------------------------------<br/><br/><strong>Hospital 666</strong> is a horror game inspired by Exit 8, Escape the Backrooms, SCP Foundation and many horror movies.<br/>You need to escape this abnormal hospital.<br/>Choose the forward or backward elevator according to whether there is an abnormaly or not.<br/>You will walk into different rooms and encounter different anomalies.<br/>Some monsters may chasing you along the way, and you need to find a suitable way to escape from them.<br/><br/><strong>Warning!!!</strong> This version of the game may crash.<br/><br/>----------------------------------------------------<br/><br/><strong><u>Average Play time</u></strong><br/><strong>666 minutes</strong><br/><br/><strong><u>Game content</u></strong><br/><strong>More than 100 floors, 85 unique anomalies, and 5 bosses</strong><br/><br/><strong><u>Game Difficulty</u></strong><br/><strong>Easy, Normal, and Hell modes</strong><br/><br/><strong><u>Game mode</u></strong><br/><strong>Single player or 2-4 people online cooperation</strong><br/><br/><strong><u>Save function</u></strong><br/><strong>Each floor will be automatically saved</strong><br/><br/><strong><u>Checkpoint</u></strong><br/><strong>Some floors are checkpoints</strong><br/><br/><strong><u>Game engine</u></strong><br/><strong>Unreal Engine 5.3</strong><br/><br/><strong><u>Control</u></strong><br/><strong>Mouse and keyboard</strong><br/><br/><strong><u>Stab your friend in the back</u></strong><br/><strong>Immoral but interesting</strong><br/><br/><strong><u>NFT</u></strong><br/><strong>Does not exist</strong><br/><br/><strong><u>In-game purchases</u></strong><br/><strong>Not so greedy</strong><br/><br/><strong><u>Error</u></strong><br/><strong>Not mech</strong><br/><br/><strong><u>Typo</u></strong><br/><strong>Not much</strong><br/><br/><strong><u>Real anomaly</u></strong><br/><strong>Not ������</strong><br/><br/>-------------------------------------------------- --						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Area 19</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2792510/Area_19/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2792510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							AREA 19 is a psychological first person horror game. Find yourself In a top-secret underground facility where you will have to discover the horrifying aftermath of an operation gone wrong... Horribly Wrong<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2792510/extras/Trailtext.png?t=1709632913"><br/>Discover horrifying Alien hybrid experiments as you traverse the Facility. Who created these monsters? Why?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2792510/extras/Topsecret.png?t=1709632913"><br/>Unravel the complex web of secrecy and conspiracy that shrouds each corner. What hidden agendas are at play, and what consequences await those who dare to expose the truth?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2792510/extras/LinearStory.png?t=1709632913"><br/>Area 19 is told through a Linear Story Mode. Travel through the Six levels and uncover the mysteries that shroud this forgotten place...						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legend Of Apophyxis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2224550/Legend_Of_Apophyxis/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2224550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2224550/extras/storeApo.png?t=1709629914"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Splash: Predators</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2846340/Color_Splash_Predators/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Color Splash: Predators is a charming and relaxing puzzle game that will lift your spirits and take You into the world of cool predators and art. Venture into the gallery, where you will find many extraordinary and colorful predators paintings.<br/><br/>You need to skillfully move puzzle pieces, find their corresponding places, and harmoniously connect the colored details. Paying great attention to detail and applying a creative approach will help you become a true master at assembling predators pictures.<br/><br/>Start gathering your collection of predators pictures right now!<br/><br/>In Color Splash: Predators:<br/><br/>•50 levels<br/>•Colorful art<br/>•Simple controls (mouse)<br/>•Achievements<br/>•Relaxing music<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846340/extras/640х360.png?t=1709629683"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egg RTX</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2838510/Egg_RTX/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2838510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">About</h2>Egg RTX is a clicker game that uses the most modern day technology to bring you the greatest egg experience of all time. Click the egg to obtain more eggs until your hearts content (One million Eggs).<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>High-Resolution Models<br/>RTX Raytracing<br/>Detailed Textures<br/>Up to 1 Player!<br/>Egg						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>十字防守(X Defense: Timing TD)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2767040/X_Defense_Timing_TD/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							If you are a big fan of strategy or tower defense games, you won't want to miss this novel strategy tower defense game. This game will bring you something new that you will never experience in other tower defense games.<br/>"X Defense: Timing TD" is built upon randomness, and you need to find the right strategy to defeat this randomness. You will have a lot of fun with this process.<h2 class="bb_tag">Novel tower defense experience.</h2><br/>Turret building and merging are random.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767040/extras/build.gif?t=1709627320"><br/><br/>You can upgrade your turrets by race.<br/><br/>Unleash bosses to get more game resources. You are in control of when and which boss to unleash.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767040/extras/releash_boss.gif?t=1709627320"><br/><br/>Upgrade turrets need energy balls. You can activate and upgrade Energy ball generators to collect energy balls.<h2 class="bb_tag">Powerful special skills</h2><br/>Top-tier turrets (SS) may have powerful special skills, which can help you defend more waves. You can obtain and combine the usage of different skills, and there are infinite possibilities.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767040/extras/skill.gif?t=1709627320"><br/><br/>Give this game a try, and you will have a novel gaming experience! Download the game now and start your game adventure!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Night Vigil：守夜人</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2784290/Night_Vigil/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2784290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Game Features:<br>
1.Strategic synthesis and upgrade methods that immerse you in mental calculations.<br>
2.Combine three identical patterns to synthesize and collect resources.<br>
3.Sandbox-style free play, creating unlimited possibilities.<br>
<br>
Gameplay:<br>
1.Synthesis rules: Combine three or more of the same type and level to construct advanced buildings.<br/>
2.Synthesizing more than three towers for upgrades yields stronger attack rewards.<br/>
3.Monsters invade at night; players should synthesize and eliminate them as much as possible, acquiring weapons and items to strengthen defenses.<br/>
<br/>
Game Items:<br/>
1.Treasure: Acquire a weapon.<br/>
2.Bomb: Deals direct damage to enemies.<br/>
3.Health Potion: Restores health points.<br/>
<br/>
Enemy Introduction:<br/>
1.Melee Monster: Balanced in health and speed.<br/>
2.Ranged Monster: Long attack distance but low health.<br/>
3.Mage Monster: Magic attacks with significant damage.<br/>
<br/>
Boss: Terrifying health. A nightmare for new players.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maze of Realities: Symphony of Invention Collector's Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815460/Maze_of_Realities_Symphony_of_Invention_Collectors_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2815460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A gripping detective series filled with mystery and riddles awaits you! So you’ve opened the door to other worlds! And turns out that means so many new discoveries! For example, your friend Dr. Charles Michaelson got an invitation from the world of Innovatrix to exchange knowledge and meet the most advanced AI in the universe – Omnira. And since he invites you to come along, you become a witness to its superior intellect. But is it you or Omnira’s creator, Conrad, who has some dangerous plans on his mind? The more you get to know him and the tragic circumstances of his past, the more you suspect that a catastrophe of galactic proportions is imminent… But can you stop it? Or the worlds around you will cease to exist? Thankfully you don’t have to carry all that heroic weight alone: you’ll have Leah, Conrad’s daughter with her own personal mystery, and Fabian, a scholar from the world of Chronologists, who will be a trove of knowledge and helpful advice. Challenge your investigator skills in this spectacular new Hidden-Object Puzzle Adventure!<br>
<br>
This Collector's Edition includes:<br>
<br>
🌌	Your own choices!<br>
You have the ability to choose the characters' phrases for one action or another and influence the plot of the mystery story. Don't forget that only your choice determines the course of these complex investigations and can affect the lives of the characters! <br>
<br>
🌌	A variety of achievements!<br/>
Conduct your own investigation by solving intricate puzzles, solving complex riddles and playing various mini-games. You need to solve the most important mystery by searching various places, collecting things and interviewing passers-by. Unlock all the achievements to highlight your success!<br/>
<br/>
🌌	Bonus materials!<br/>
Collect all the clues and save the residents, successfully solve the mystery to gain access to bonus locations, where you'll discover some interesting details about the characters. You might think that some mysteries are not meant to be solved, but you can do it, can't you?<br/>
<br/>
🌌	Collectible items!<br/>
This exciting new edition of the mystery story is filled with various clues and mysterious items that you need to find in order to advance your investigation! Find the collectibles at each crime scene and find the hidden objects. You'll have to be a very careful detective to collect the entire collection!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spellbound FPS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776560/Spellbound_FPS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this first-person role-playing game, you play as Damitri (the lead character of the Spellbound book series). He shoots snowballs and icicles from his hand representing his ice magic abilities. The player has a companion, Laura. She has abilities relating to sound. She can scream to destroy enemies or sing to heal the player. Eventually, two more characters join the party. The pause menu is a 2D still image of the characters frozen in time. A character with abilities relating to time and space assists the player by pausing time, reversing time either back to the beginning of the level, or the entire game.<br>
In first person mode, the player will run as Damitri shooting as many snowballs and icicles at enemies such as zombies, mummies and possessed New Heat Guards. A character bio exists within the main menu. This gives is where most of the lore and backstories of the characters exist. <br>
There are two other game play modes. The player will have a third person view of a rock creature that the player can control. A second racing/chase level exists with the player controlling a vehicle powered by fire magic in third person mode.<br>
Occasional cutscenes show the player's location and any bosses or obstacles that may exist in the scene.<br>
Some levels prevent you from pausing. This is due to the person with time and space magic being incapable of assisting in these locations.<br>
The player can heal infinitely with the help of their companion. Although, a Game Over is very possible in areas of highly littered enemies.						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arena Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2844300/Arena_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2844300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Destroy horde of enemies, use secrets, survive all arena in this rogue like RPG.<br>
<br>
Introducing Arena Survivors: Unleash your inner hero and conquer the arena like never before!<br>
<br>
Are you ready to embark on an epic adventure filled with fierce battles, cunning strategies, and endless excitement? Look no further than Arena Survivors - the ultimate rogue-like RPG game that will keep you on the edge of your seat!<br>
<br>
Destroy Horde of Enemies: Brace yourself for adrenaline-pumping action as you face off against hordes of enemies from skeletons and mythological creatures to farm chickens and daemons from hell. With each battle, the stakes get higher, and only the bravest will survive.<br/>
<br/>
Custom Crafted Maps: Explore captivating and meticulously designed maps that will take you from haunting castle cemeteries to faraway farms filled with secrets waiting to be unraveled. Immerse yourself in the atmospheric environments and prepare for a sensory feast like no other.<br/>
<br/>
Complex Bosses and Events: Get ready to put your skills to the test as you come face to face with complex bosses and encounter thrilling events along the way. Each boss will challenge you in unique ways, pushing you to adapt your tactics and unleash your full potential. Can you rise to the challenge and emerge victorious?<br/>
<br/>
Choose Your Hero: With Arena Survivors, you have the power to choose from 6 legendary heroes, each with their own distinctive abilities and weapons. Whether you prefer the deadly precision of Wild Bill and his twin Colts or the sheer brute force of Nitros and his mighty Big Axe, there's a hero to suit every play style.<br/>
<br/>
Unleash Powerful Enhancements: Enhance your hero's strengths with powerful enhancements that can turn the tide of battle in your favor. From increasing critical damage and adding AOE effects to boosting the number of projectiles and reducing cooldowns, these enhancements allow you to unleash devastating combos that will leave your enemies trembling.<br/>
<br/>
Rogue-like RPG Experience: Experience the thrill of rogue-like gameplay that offers a fresh challenge with every playthrough. No two runs will ever be the same, thanks to procedurally generated levels and dynamically changing events. Prepare to journey into the unknown, forge your own path, and face the consequences of your choices.<br/>
<br/>
Join the ranks of Arena Survivors and prove your worth in the ultimate battle against evil. Can you survive the treacherous arenas and emerge as a true champion? The fate of the world rests in your hands. Get ready for an unforgettable adventure that will test your courage, strategy, and determination. Step into the arena, and let the chaos begin!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solo Flight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2659730/Solo_Flight/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You're a pilot who is the first member of the Advanced Aviation Force and are ready to start flying. However, a giant alien worm boss rudely destroys your home town. Now it's up to you only to take on the challenge of completing missions to restore your civilization before facing off with the beast itself.<br>
<br>
Try out three unique game modes including shooter, ring flight and rescue mission that increase in difficulty and rewards. Use this to upgrade and unlock new aircraft that will help you on your journey.<br>
<br>
Highly recommended to be played using the Xbox controller (more controller support coming soon), or using the keyboard.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>希望之城 The City Of Hope</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2424740/_The_City_Of_Hope/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2424740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Your kingdom has only one piece of land left, and the enemies seem determined not to spare you. How you rebuild a city in a limited time and defeat the powerful invaders depends on your choices.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build a defense system</h2>Construct several different types of defense towers or deploy your army to resist the enemy's attacks.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2424740/extras/1.gif?t=1709614854"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cards</h2>Every day, use randomly generated cards from a pool of over 100 different cards to construct the city, build defenses, establish barracks, and more.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2424740/extras/2.gif?t=1709614854"><h2 class="bb_tag">Rich equipment system</h2>Choose from dozens of different equipment options that suit your game strategy to make the game more enjoyable and entertaining.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2424740/extras/3.gif?t=1709614854"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Somniata</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2740060/Somniata/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2740060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Somniata is a short, linear, first-person horror game with a light puzzle element. Set in rural Massachusetts, Detective Robert Moore is sent to investigate the disappearance of the Dyer family. Find keys, notes, and other items as you try and survive the waking nightmare that has been unleashed upon a family of four.<br/><br/><strong>Content Warning:</strong> <span class="bb_spoiler">Violence, Suicide</span> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOKO</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2664050/YOKO/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2664050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2664050/extras/11.png?t=1709601754"><br/><strong>YOKO</strong> :Between life and death, "YOKO" offers a unique paranormal experience. As a newcomer to a mysterious house, Yoko finds herself immersed in a haunting journey filled with intriguing riddles. Explore the intimate areas of Saikominami, at the foot of majestic Mount Fuji, and uncover the dark secrets that permeate this peaceful town. When you acquire your new home, prepare to uncover the inexplicable that waits in the shadows, challenging your courage and instigating your curiosity.<br/><br/><strong>Main Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Innovative approach to Yoko's world returning to the origins of old-school first-person survival horror</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Most confusing and complex story ever seen in a horror game</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Own soundtrack created by renowned international musician Lucaskyioshi</li></ul><br/><strong>Intriguing Narrative</strong><br/>Immerse yourself in an engaging story, where Yoko, in search of her first home, finds herself confronted by supernatural mysteries. Uncover dark secrets, explore notes left by longtime residents, and uncover the truth behind the region's mysterious disappearances.<br/><br/><strong>Supernatural Challenges</strong><br/>Face the unknown as you break local evils and defy supernatural forces. Utilize your instincts to overcome unique challenges, each designed to test your courage and determination as you uncover hidden secrets.<br/><br/><strong>Realistic Environment</strong><br/>Explore detailed and realistic environments in the intimate areas of Saikominami, with stunning graphics that immerse players in a tense and mysterious atmosphere. Feel the supernatural presence as you navigate places marked by the past and the spirits that roam between life and death.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2664050/extras/2.png?t=1709601754"><br/><strong>Redemption Mission</strong><br/>Take on the role of Yoko, whose mission goes beyond simply acquiring a home. Lead lost souls to eternal peace by unlocking mysteries that connect the worlds of the living and the dead. Your choices shape the destiny of not only Yoko, but also the souls seeking redemption.<br/><br/><strong>Tense and Immersive Atmosphere:</strong><br/>Feel the tension build as the plot unfolds, with an immersive soundtrack and sound effects that create a unique atmosphere of suspense and mystery. Yoko's every step brings with it the promise of unsettling discoveries and otherworldly challenges.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom: The Blood</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2258870/Kingdom_The_Blood/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2258870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Kingdom: The Blood</strong> is an Action RPG based on the popular Netflix miniseries "Kingdom." Fight hoards of zombies, defeat diverse bosses with intense attack patterns, and strengthen your character to rise above other players.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Beauty of Traditional Korea</strong></h2><br/>The traditional Korean clothing and unique architectural styles made with high-quality graphics can be seen throughout the gameplay. The way the clothes flutter during an action skill, various traditional clothing like the ‘gat,’ and the realistic reproduction of the traditional building’s minute details like the curvature of the roof tiles can all be seen as you venture through the game. You can relive the beauty of Korea that captured the world.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fun in control-based action</strong></h2><br/>You can create your own action by combining different skills. Enjoy a strategic action sequence that gives satisfaction with each hit.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2258870/extras/기술_연계공격_615.gif?t=1709599260"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Threatening and terrifying zombie battles</strong></h2><br/>You will face hordes of zombies with melee weapons. Zombies appear suddenly, run fast, and attack menacingly. Experience a grueling zombie battle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2258870/extras/아신_좀비전투615.gif?t=1709599260"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong> Monsters and bosses with unique attack patterns</strong></h2><br/>In addition to the zombies, human-form enemies and bosses appear as the difficulty level increases. The unique movements and appearances will captivate the players. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2258870/extras/보스_계비조씨_615.gif?t=1709599260"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Various battle modes </strong></h2><br/>Fight challenging bosses with your friends.<br/>Enjoy 1 on 1 battles with other players.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2258870/extras/다양한전투모드_PVP_615.gif?t=1709599260"><br/>When you clear the single-player mode with a particular difficulty, a new mode with a completely different gameplay will be opened.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go Bananas</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2613730/Go_Bananas/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2613730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Go Bananas is a fast paced arcade platformer where you play as Blue the monkey and race to collect as many bananas as you can before the timer runs out!<br/><br/>Explore hand crafted levels, racing through each level to collect bananas. When you collect all the bananas you move on to the next level, chosen at random from over 100 designed and balanced challenges.<br/><br/>Try to beat your best Banana Total with each go! Keep an eye on the clock and watch out for juicy Super Fruits to extend the time limit and maximise the banana collecting action.<br/><br/>Play in short bursts or sink in for an extended banana chasing session and enjoy the happy vibes all day!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>100+ Banana filled Levels<br/></li><li>Addictive arcade gameplay<br/></li><li>Challenging obstacles to avoid<br/></li><li>Play in quick bursts<br/></li><li>Hilarious post game Monkey Puns<br/></li><li>Simple, straight forward fun! </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vertical Velocity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2505630/Vertical_Velocity/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this game the sun has fallen to the earth and the moon has taken over. You the player have to get the sun back into the sky by finishing courses and getting through their obstacles. You will however be forces to master the controls in order to succeed. The moon hasn't made it easy for you and plans to cause an ice age. By staying determined and focused you will take your place back in the sky. This game features a simple look with fun arcade music. It is a 2d platformer that features simple obstacles but be warned this game is not for the faint of heart. Inspired by many of the rage platformers on the market. There are plans for more content in the future, and thank you for reading have a good rest of your day/night.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alian</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2683560/Alian/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2683560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is an ordinary shooting game.<br>
In these days of overflowing original games, it is hard to know which one to choose even if there is a game you want to play, or you want to enjoy a normal game system but the extra features get in the way, don't you think so?<br>
This game consists of four stages with different difficulty levels.<br>
The objective of the game is to clear each stage.<br>
This game operates with only the minimum system necessary to make the game work, and you can fulfill your desire to conquer the game with simple rules that aim to clear the stages by moving left and right and shooting only.<br>
There should be no loss if you have it for now.						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracking the Stone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2818560/Cracking_the_Stone/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2818560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cracking the Stone is an interactive comic about following the life of a boy who is learning what it's like to struggle with grief.<br>
<br>
As tragedy overwhelms the boy, take control of his early life and help him learn what it's like to follow his own path, all the while blocking out the negative emotions that fly toward him as a consequence of his journey through life.<br>
<br>
What is it like to juggle the complexities of childhood &amp; adolescence with the struggle to keep one's emotions at bay and stave off existential dread and depression? Cracking the Stone aims to answer that question via an emotional journey through an interactive medium!<br>
<br>
Note: This free demo is an incomplete version of the story ends on a cliffhanger! It contains only portions of the first 2 of 5 planned chapters in the story.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DrawBall</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2822910/DrawBall/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2822910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Draw ink to guide each ball into its appropriately coloured hole! Can you beat all 30+ levels? DrawBall is a fun puzzle game where the aim of the game is to complete levels by drawing ink to guide coloured balls into a correctly coloured hole. DrawBall includes over 30 in built levels and a level editor so you can create and export your own levels and even import levels made by others! You can also share your levels and download other users' levels on our DrawBall Level Portal!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
