<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>The Inquisitor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1880470/The_Inquisitor/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/the-inquisitor-intro.gif?t=1707415647"><br/><br/><strong>The Inquisitor</strong> is a story-driven, dark fantasy adventure game with action elements, that compels you to face difficult moral choices. The game is set in an alternative version of (religious) reality. Inspired by bestselling Inquisitor book series by Jacek Piekara. Once nailed to the cross and near death, Jesus becomes consumed by utter rage. He breaks free and unleashes violent vengeance on all the non-believers. Centuries pass and now an army of zealot Inquisitors brutally enforce the faith in this blood-soaked Church.<br/><br/>You are Mordimer Madderdin, an Inquisitor in God's service, sent to the town of Koenigstein which is plagued by a series of mysteries and sin. Solve the various cases and crimes of those who have transgressed against the faith, all while uncovering the truth of a darker evil from another realm that is trying to enter the world of the living.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/BeTheUltimate_EN.png?t=1707415647"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/be-the-ultimate-holy-judge-and-jury.gif?t=1707415647"><br/><br/>Be the ultimate Holy Judge and Jury: Your role as an Inquisitor is to maintain order and enforce the faith in God. But the world is full of sinners who have lost their way. Decide the fates of those you judge in multiple story-driven cases and missions. This is a world where morality and what is right have long strayed from each other. So, will you show mercy or undying belief in The Holy Law?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/MorallyTainted_EN.png?t=1707415647"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/morally-tainted-non-linear-tale.gif?t=1707415647"><br/><br/>A morally tainted, non-linear tale: This is a dark and gritty story centered around a religion preaching revenge and violence. Multiple branching story choices will test your morality. Choose your path and decide what kind of Inquisitor you will be - one of pity or one of retribution - and ultimately what mark you will leave on this world.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/EnlightenedSleuthing_EN.png?t=1707415647"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/enlightened-sleuthing.gif?t=1707415647"><br/><br/>Enlightened sleuthing: Mordimer has unique skills and abilities that allow him to solve the various crimes and mysteries that have befallen Koenigstein. Track down and interrogate suspects. Discover the hidden truths of the city and its inhabitants. Piece together the evidence and make your final judgments.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/DelveInto_EN.png?t=1707415647"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/delve-into-the-unworld.gif?t=1707415647"><br/><br/>Delve into the Unworld: Unbeknownst to those around him, Mordimer has the ability to enter the mysterious Unworld. There he can discover the deeper secrets that suspects have tried to hide in their souls. But there is a grave risk when venturing into this world and the dark force which reigns supreme here will do everything it can to destroy you for stepping foot into its realm.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/Persuasive_EN.png?t=1707415647"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/persuasive-interrogations.gif?t=1707415647"><br/><br/>Persuasive interrogations: The 1500’s remain a cruel era of justice. As an Inquisitor, you have free rein to use whatever methods and tools deemed necessary to persuade suspects to reveal ‘the truth’. These optional interrogations date back to the times of the real Inquisition and it’s up to you to decide if and how much force to apply to those under your investigation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/LetYourSword_EN.png?t=1707415647"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/let-your-sword-do-the-talking.gif?t=1707415647"><br/><br/>Let your sword do the talking: Sometimes a tongue just needs to be cut right out in order to loosen it. A full sword-based combat system means various cases will let or even require you to use brute force. Master your blade, find your openings, and use your enemy’s weak points against them.<h2 class="bb_tag">Other recommended games from Kalypso Media</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1287840/Disciples_Liberation/" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1287840/Disciples_Liberation/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Noir</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/754320/Pixel_Noir/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/754320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>There was something rotten in that old hospital. You were just following your instincts that night. But, it was your pride that killed those people, including your partner on the force. With nothing to exonerate you, on a temporary insanity defense, they threw the book at you.<h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/754320/extras/bookatyou.png?t=1707404050"/></h2><br/>For ten years, you were haunted by unanswered questions, frightened by what you saw, and what you did. Now you’re scraping by as a private eye, operating out of a crummy apartment. One day, a strange case comes along, giving you an opportunity to clear your name once and for all. With your sanity at stake and rent to pay, how can you refuse?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/754320/extras/stepintoshoes2.gif?t=1707404050"><br/>Solve a wide variety of mysteries as Pinnacle City's cheapest Private Eye! From missing pets to murder investigations, your detective skills will either earn you fortune or face punches. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/754320/extras/explorepc2.gif?t=1707404050"><br/>Home to a wretched hive of scum and villainy, Pinnacle City is littered with black market trade, grafters, and players of all kinds. From the shadowy alleys of The Sprawl to the sleek skyscrapers of Uptown, each district holds its own charm and mysteries to uncover! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/754320/extras/castchars2.gif?t=1707404050"><br/>Each member of your entourage has their own distinctive personality and skill set. Some will follow you into battle. Others will try and undermine you. Who will you choose for your lineup and will they be with you until the bitter end?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/754320/extras/epiccombos2.gif?t=1707404050"><br/>Bad guys can jump out at you from anywhere and each gang in Pinnacle City has its own devastating attacks! But you can beat 'em back in turn-based combat using timed hits and blocks to increase or reduce damage. You can also partner with your entourage members to unleash devastating combo attacks!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/754320/extras/readsomething2.png?t=1707404050"><br/>Manuscripts teach entourage members a wide variety of skills. Learned skills can then be upgraded by skill points you get from solving major cases. With each upgrade, skills become more powerful, and your entourage can take on even more powerful enemies. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/754320/extras/gearup2.png?t=1707404050"><br/>Tune up your gear with modifications to fit your play style. Experiment with different mods and ammo types to deal varying types of damage and inflict status effects on enemies. Whether you prefer a technical approach or go in guns blazing, modifying your gear is key as you battle your way through the city.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FRUtWc3RFJs" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/754320/extras/Copy_of_Join_the_discord!__1080_×_1000_px___3_.gif?t=1707404050"/></a></img></img></img></img></img></img></strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2 - Upgrade to Super Citizen Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2514130/HELLDIVERS_2__Upgrade_to_Super_Citizen_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Edition includes:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>‘DP-53 Savior of the Free’ Armor Set.<br/></li><li>‘Will of the People’ Cape.<br/></li><li>‘MP-98 Knight’ Weapon.<br/></li><li>Super Citizen Status.<br/></li><li>Stratagem Hero Ship Game.<br/></li><li>‘Steeled Veterans’ Premium Warbond.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1707382807"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1707382807"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1707382807"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1707382807"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1707382807"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION </h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1707382807"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514130/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1707382807"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort.<br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KONOSUBA - God's Blessing on this Wonderful World! Love For These Clothes Of Desire!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2349140/KONOSUBA__Gods_Blessing_on_this_Wonderful_World_Love_For_These_Clothes_Of_Desire/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/KonoSuba_KeyArt_Landscape_WithLogo.png?t=1707479148"><br/>Follow Kazuma and company, as they discover a mysterious "Black Slab" which curses them with desires contrary to their personality. The gang must now find and feed ingredients to the slab to create outfits which match and fulfil their new desires, and thus break their curse. Are you ready to meet Darkness as a ruthless dominatrix? How about Aqua as a prim and proper goddess? Or Megumin as the proud leader of the Lolita League?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/new-narrative-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/01._Black_slab!_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Witness a new story in visual novel form! Featuring a full cast of fan-favourite characters from the series, this wild adventure gives you the chance to build up affection with up to seven heroines!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/get-to-work-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/02._Schedule_overview!_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Fill out a weekly planner for each character based on their strengths to earn funds and resources which can be used for making outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/make-decisions-orange-1.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/decision_making_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Each of them has her own story endings and special dress-up CGs, so pick your words wisely and avoid invoking their wrath! Your choices matter! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/Manage-resources-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/04._Resources_schedule_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Collect resources to create outfits by completing tasks and quests. Manage your finances carefully to afford the materials you are missing, and prioritise gathering the outfit-specific ingredients you will need.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/play-dress-up-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/05._Make_more_clothes!_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Once the mystical outfits have been made it’s time to play dress-up! Be ready for twists and turns as your favourite characters’ personalities change with each curse and desire-fulfilling piece of clothing.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/DANCE-smaller-no-boaarder.gif?t=1707479148"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III - BlackCell (Season 2)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731840/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III__BlackCell_Season_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Get Call of Duty® Points* and in-game content for Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III and Call of Duty®: Warzone™.<br>
<br>
Offering includes:<br>
<br/>
- Battle Pass for Season 2<br/>
- 20 Battle Token Tier Skips<br/>
<br/>
Exclusive BlackCell Sector on the Battle Map:<br/>
<br/>
- 1100 Call of Duty® Points<br/>
- BlackCell Operator<br/>
- Assault Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Battle Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Finishing Move<br/>
<br/>
- BlackCell Bonus Topper with 11 additional reactive Operator skin alternatives and 6 Weapon Blueprints with Tracers.<br/>
<br/>
Activision may update, replace, or remove this in-game content at any time.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Touhou Danmaku Kagura Phantasia Lost</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2190220/Touhou_Danmaku_Kagura_Phantasia_Lost/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							『Touhou Danmaku Kagura Phantasia Lost』is a rebuild of Touhou Project's first officially approved smartphone rhythm game "Touhou Danmaku Kagura" as a standalone version.<br/><br/>Play Danmaku Kagura and collect the Mitama Cards, the Fragments of Memories to find the key to rebuild the now barren Phantasia.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Two different rhythm game experiences</h2></strong><br/>■Kagura Stage<br/>- In this mode you hit the notes at the right moment!<br/>- You can stack up combos and get a high score by hitting the notes consecutively, coming through the 6 lanes.<br/>- Over 160* arranged Touhou music will be playable with 4 different difficulties!<br/>*Includes music from paid DLCs<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/extras/kagura.gif?t=1707395141"><br/><br/>■Danmaku Stage<br/>- A totally new game experience that combines Danmaku shoot 'em up &amp; Rhythm games!<br/>- Hit the notes on the sides rhythmically and deal great damage to the boss!<br/>- Complete missions set for each stages and beat the stage!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/extras/danmaku.gif?t=1707395141"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Wide Variety of Music</h2></strong><br/>Contains 68 songs including the original Touhou music.<br/>Scheduled to release 4 Music Pack DLCs (A total of 102 scores)!!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/extras/songsEN1.png?t=1707395141"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/extras/songsEN2.png?t=1707395141"><br/><br/>Additionally, free DLCs also planned for release. The first will include Toby Fox &amp; ZUN’s collaboration song ‘U.N. Owen Was Hero?’, releasing February 8th!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/extras/FlanUndyne_21.png?t=1707395141"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2></strong><br/>To rebuild Phantasia, Reimu journeys to find the Fragments of Memories.<br/>The key to rebuilding is Danmaku Kagura.<br/>To rebuild the Phantasia and unveil the truth of its destruction, Reimu have to gather Mitama cards, the Fragments of Memories.<br/>Reimu's unending journey, begins.<br/><br/>Marisa begins her own journey to find Reimu<br/>Will the two, ever meet eye to eye?						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jigsaw Puzzles Infinite</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1946140/Jigsaw_Puzzles_Infinite/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1946140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							If you like jigsaw puzzles - this is your game.<br/>Sit back, relax and build puzzles to your heart's content.<h2 class="bb_tag">What you get with Jigsaw Puzzle Infinite:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Infinite possibilities</strong>- Choose from one of the dozens of included puzzles or add your own images without any limits<br/></li><li><strong>Classic mode</strong> - Jigsaw puzzles you know and love. Take your time and build the puzzle with the help of useful sorting features<br/></li><li><strong>Sorting</strong> - Sort pieces by section, sort out edges, or just spread them out neatly <br/></li><li><strong>Zen Mode</strong> - Enter the flow and assemble the puzzle piece by piece<br/></li><li><strong>Pieces snap to each other </strong>and are not placed on a preset grid - just like real puzzles<br/></li><li><strong>Adjust difficulty </strong>- Freely choose number of pieces and snapping distance<br/></li><li><strong>Different piece shapes </strong>- Choose from multiple possible shapes of the pieces<br/></li><li><strong>Free camera movement </strong>- Zoom in and out, and move around the board freely <br/></li><li><strong>Every puzzle unique </strong>- Pieces are randomized each time new puzzle is generated<br/></li><li><strong>Never lose any progress </strong>- Don't worry about losing data, autosaving will keep it safe<br/></li><li><strong>No microtransactions </strong>- Enjoy the puzzles up to 200 pieces or unlock all current and future content with a single purchase</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jigsaw Puzzles Infinite</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1946140/Jigsaw_Puzzles_Infinite/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1946140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							If you like jigsaw puzzles - this is your game.<br/>Sit back, relax and build puzzles to your heart's content.<h2 class="bb_tag">What you get with Jigsaw Puzzle Infinite:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Infinite possibilities</strong>- Choose from one of the dozens of included puzzles or add your own images without any limits<br/></li><li><strong>Classic mode</strong> - Jigsaw puzzles you know and love. Take your time and build the puzzle with the help of useful sorting features<br/></li><li><strong>Sorting</strong> - Sort pieces by section, sort out edges, or just spread them out neatly <br/></li><li><strong>Zen Mode</strong> - Enter the flow and assemble the puzzle piece by piece<br/></li><li><strong>Pieces snap to each other </strong>and are not placed on a preset grid - just like real puzzles<br/></li><li><strong>Adjust difficulty </strong>- Freely choose number of pieces and snapping distance<br/></li><li><strong>Different piece shapes </strong>- Choose from multiple possible shapes of the pieces<br/></li><li><strong>Free camera movement </strong>- Zoom in and out, and move around the board freely <br/></li><li><strong>Every puzzle unique </strong>- Pieces are randomized each time new puzzle is generated<br/></li><li><strong>Never lose any progress </strong>- Don't worry about losing data, autosaving will keep it safe<br/></li><li><strong>No microtransactions </strong>- Enjoy the puzzles up to 200 pieces or unlock all current and future content with a single purchase</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WitchHand</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420880/WitchHand/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/store-gif-01.gif?t=1707460594"><br/><br/>In <strong>WitchHand</strong>, you use cards to build your empire of witches. Maximize the production of your villages and use your resources strategically to upgrade and expand. Focus on trade, alchemy research, or war in order to secure your coven's place amongst the Council of Fates, influencing the destiny of all. Work with your neighbors to secure a better future or crush them and use their bones to fuel your spells. When the witching hour comes each night, your witch's powers are at their strongest, while unseen forces work against you. You must expand and manage your coven to new heights if you are to withstand the coming darkness. No rest for the wicked.<h2 class="bb_tag">A CIVILIZATION OF WITCHES</h2>WitchHand folds the 4X strategy formula into card-based gameplay. You'll perform strategic actions like exploring, expanding, and exterminating through real-time card placement. Manage worker placement, village production, and research in order to advance the strength and reach of your coven.<h2 class="bb_tag">WIELD THE POWERS OF THE WITCHES OF THE REALMS</h2>Each witch has a unique selection of spells, buildings, and units that defines them. Empower your villages and production with the Celestial Witch. Overpower your enemies with the might of the Chaos Witch. Cook delicious, stat-boosting meals with the Chef Witch. Choose the witch that best suits your playstyle and have full control over your research paths to further personalize your playthrough.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/spellbook_and_wonder_crop.gif?t=1707460594"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXPLORE THE MYSTERIES OF THE NINTH</h2>The Council of Fates does not have faith in your expedition to the Ninth. Make alliances with rival factions or declare war and take their resources for your own. Manage your relationships through trade and gifts or with a well-placed fireball spell. Grow your coven to new heights and prove the Council wrong.<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES:</h2>🧭 <strong>Explore</strong> the Ninth Realm to discover new sites for your villages, necessary reagents to fuel your spells, and clues to the mystery of the Ninth's sudden appearance.<br/><br/>🏘️ <strong>Expand</strong> your coven by building new villages, perfecting production, and trading with the local factions.<br/><br/>🔥 <strong>Exterminate</strong> the beasts of the void, whose relentless assaults on your coven jeopardize your mission.<br/><br/>🧙‍♀️ <strong>Choose</strong> the witch to lead your coven, each with unique spells and playstyles.<br/><br/>⌛ <strong>Impress</strong> the Council of Fates and benefit from their powerful boons.<br/><br/>🕊️ <strong>Peaceful Mode</strong> - The option to play without the constant threat of extinction.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/combat-crop.gif?t=1707460594"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/store-gif-04.gif?t=1707460594"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1707227820"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal from ECHOS</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1707227820"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about playtesting opportunities, dev news, limited edition merch and more.<h2 class="bb_tag">Wishlist &amp; Follow on Steam</h2>Make sure to wishlist and follow the game for the latest updates. Due for Release early Q2-Q3 2023.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vampire: The Masquerade - Justice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2431700/Vampire_The_Masquerade__Justice/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_Venice.gif?t=1707339642"><br/><br/>Become a vampire. Strike from the darkness and drink the blood of your prey. Use stealth, persuasion, and an arsenal of upgradable abilities to sneak past enemies undetected or punish the guilty in the seedy backstreets of nighttime Venice.<br/><br/><strong>Vampire: The Masquerade - Justice</strong> is an open-ended, narrative Adventure RPG set in the World of Darkness universe. You have the power to strike fear into the hearts of a criminal underworld as an untraceable shadow, picking off targets one-by-one.<h2 class="bb_tag">STEALTH IS YOUR WEAPON</h2>Shadows are your ally. Take to the rooftops and seek new paths away from enemy eyes. Use Shadow Traps to snatch up unsuspecting prey and drag them into Oblivion. Activate Cloak of Shadows and slip unseen through enemy defenses. In Vampire: The Masquerade - Justice, stealth is your weapon.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_BloodDrinking.gif?t=1707339642"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_sneaky.gif?t=1707339642"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A POWERFUL VAMPIRE</h2>Punish the guilty with brutal abilities. Launch yourself towards opponents with immense force or boil their insides with Cauldron of Blood. Approach from behind and sink in your fangs to stock up on blood. Load your crossbow with special bolts to kill, distract or knock out guards from afar. Dish out Justice with a vengeance.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_BloodDrinking_2.gif?t=1707339642"><h2 class="bb_tag">LEVEL UP AND EXPLORE</h2>The dark skies of Venice provide ample opportunity to level up powers and build a character suited to your playstyle. Tackle side-missions away from the campaign to earn more experience. Convince NPCs to aid your quest, solve puzzles, uncover collectibles and test yourself with optional tasks in each mission.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_update.gif?t=1707339642"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_enviornement.gif?t=1707339642"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXIT KUN</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781370/EXIT_KUN/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a game of finding differences and observing. Our game challenges players to carefully observe and spot the distinctions that lead them to the elusive "Exit KUN."<br>
<br>
Game Overview:<br>
<br>
You find yourself trapped in an enigmatic underground labyrinth, and your only goal is to reach "Exit KUN." The journey demands keen observation of your surroundings. Every detail matters, and anomalies could be your key to progress.<br>
<br>
How to Play:<br>
<br/>
Observe Carefully: Scrutinize your surroundings to uncover anomalies that may guide your way or pose a threat.<br/>
Turn Back if Needed: If anomalies are detected, swift decision-making is crucial. Turn back immediately to avoid unforeseen consequences.<br/>
Forward Momentum: Should your observation reveal no anomalies, press forward. <br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Developer Notes:<br/>
This game is inspired by Exit 8. You are free to create, upload, and monetize videos and any other content featuring Game on platforms such as YouTube, Twitch, and other video-sharing websites. The characters, places, and elements involved in the game are fictitious. Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, or events is purely coincidental.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soak &amp; Splash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2051500/Soak__Splash/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2051500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the Soak &amp; Splash! Get ready to sweat, socialize, and have a blast with your friends in this unique game that combines the best of traditional sauna culture with modern party fun.<br>
<br>
First, step into the steamy sauna and feel the heat and humidity envelop your body.<br>
<br>
Once everyone is inside, it's time to start the fun. You can start by whisking each other with broom.<br>
<br>
Feeling competitive? You can also fight with other players with sauna equipment. Or you can simply relax and enjoy the company of your friends, chatting, singing, or telling jokes.<br>
<br/>
Finally, when you've had enough of the sauna, you can cool off in the nearby pool or shower.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, this game is all about having fun, bonding with your friends, and experiencing the unique benefits of sauna culture. So why wait? Download game and get ready to sweat, laugh, and enjoy life to the fullest!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egg</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2784840/Egg/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2784840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><h2 class="bb_tag">About this game!</h2></strong><br/><br/>&gt; <strong>Egg</strong> is an interactive clicker game where you need to click egg to earn more eggs.<br/><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Features!</h2></strong><br/><br/>&gt; This game supports mouse and keyboard.<br/>&gt; This game supports gamepad (use <strong>A</strong> button on joystick to click).<br/>&gt; This game uses best HD quality textures that is possible to create.<br/>&gt; Runs on every hardware. Even on BESM.<br/>&gt; Supports all screen resolutions.<br/>&gt; Supports Windows 10/11 and so on.<br/>&gt; If you don't like the game you can always easily refund it.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/315210/Suicide_Squad_Kill_the_Justice_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Rocksteady Studios, the creators of the Batman: Arkham series, Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is a genre-defying third-person action shooter where the ultimate band of misfits must do the impossible to save the world: Kill the Justice League.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/SSKTJL_Intro.gif?t=1706907136"><br/>Join the newly “recruited” members of Amanda Waller’s infamous Task Force X (aka the Suicide Squad), Harley Quinn, Deadshot, Captain Boomerang and King Shark, as they set out on an impossible mission to Kill the Justice League. Drop into an expansive and dynamic open-world Metropolis ravaged by Brainiac’s invasion and terrorized by the heroes who once protected it. <br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/Traversal_2.gif?t=1706907136"><br/>Each Squad member brings their own traversal mechanics to help them navigate a sprawling and battle-torn Metropolis, combining free-roaming exploration and combat verticality for an unforgettable experience. Players are free to experiment with a variety of different play styles to unleash maximum damage on their enemies. Whether in single player or online with up to three of your friends, players can take on this suicide mission their own way.<br/><br/>Post-launch, players can expect a continuously evolving Metropolis with free new playable villains, environments, weapons, in-game events, and more, all included with purchase of the base game.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788630/Nothing_Together/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play together. Maybe.<br/><br/>Just do Nothing as the timer goes up and climb the leaderboards. If you do Something, you lose.<br/><br/>Play in <strong>Together </strong>mode, where up to 20 players unite to do Nothing, or compete with other players in <strong>Battle Royale</strong> to find out who's the best at doing Nothing!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161700/Persona_3_Reload/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a transfer student thrust into an unexpected fate when entering the hour "hidden" between one day and the next. Awaken an incredible power and chase the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fight for your friends, and leave a mark on their memories forever. <br/><br/>Persona 3 Reload is a captivating reimagining of the genre-defining RPG, reborn for the modern era.<br/><br/>Key Features: <br/>- Experience the pivotal game of the Persona series faithfully remade with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, and signature stylish UI. <br/><br/>-Fully immerse yourself in an emotional, gripping journey with new scenes, character interactions, and additional voiceover.<br/><br/>- Choose how to meaningfully spend each day through various activities, from exploring the Port Island to forging genuine bonds with beloved characters.<br/><br/>- Build and command your optimal team to take down otherworldly Shadows and climb closer to the truth.<br/><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Deluxe Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook: Filled with 64 pages of character art, concept art, backgrounds and other illustrations from the game!<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack: Listen to newly arranged tracks from the original Persona 3 plus all-new tracks from Persona 3 Reload, presented by the Atlus sound team for a total of 60 new songs.</li></ul><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Premium Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack<br/></li><li>Persona 3 Reload DLC Pack:  P5R Phantom Thieves Costume Set, P5R Shujin Academy Costume Set, P5R Persona Set 1, P5R Persona Set 2 , P5R BGM Set, P4G Yasogami High Costume Set, P4G Persona Set</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLCARD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1201540/HELLCARD/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Hellcard</strong> is a <strong>cooperative roguelike deckbuilder</strong> that can be played in both <strong>Singleplayer </strong>and <strong>Multiplayer </strong>modes. The game takes place in the paper dungeons known from Book of Demons, and its main mechanics revolve around deckbuilding and fast-paced tactical card battles. <br/><br/>If you are excited about <strong>HELLCARD</strong>, be sure to <strong>wishlist </strong>the game on Steam. Otherwise, consider wishlisting anyway - who knows, we might surprise you yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif5_600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/>What makes <strong>HELLCARD</strong> unique and different from other deck-building games is that <strong>monster placement actually matters</strong> and can be used to your advantage.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif4_600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>HELLCARD</strong> supports <strong>co-op battles</strong> with up to three heroes facing the Archdemon's hordes. In <strong>singleplayer mode</strong>, you can descend into the dungeons solo or recruit computer-controlled companions. In <strong>multiplayer mode</strong>, your friends or strangers can help you battle the hordes of hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif1-2-3-600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/r2g_logo_fixed.png?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>Return 2 Games</strong> is a series of unique mid-core games inspired by the golden days of PC gaming. Each R2G title is a tribute to a single hit game from the '90s: a reimagining of a single universal story for a brand-new audience, using modern means and innovative, often vastly simplified gameplay mechanics.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/pillars.png?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>HELLCARD</strong> was first envisioned as a new game mode inside the Book of Demons universe, but we soon realized that its design is huge and that it should be executed as a stand-alone spin-off game. If you want to learn more about Return 2 Games or support us in the development of the series, visit the <strong>Supporter Pack</strong> store page. On release, <strong>HELLCARD </strong>will be a part of it.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/706770/Return_2_Games_Supporters_Pack/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/706770/Return_2_Games_Supporters_Pack/</a><br/><strong>Book of Demons</strong>, the first part in the series is already here, be sure to check it out as it includes a free demo. <br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/449960/Book_of_Demons/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/449960/Book_of_Demons/</a><br/>Also, be sure to check out <strong>Book of Aliens</strong>, the second book in the series and a tribute to MicroProse’ UFO: Enemy Unknown that’s also in the works:<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1196230/Book_of_Aliens/" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1196230/Book_of_Aliens/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1131620/Dominion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Expand a small kingdom to a mighty Dominion!  <br/><br/>Play the Spiel des Jahres winning boardgame beloved by millions around the world. This is the officially licensed implementation.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Reigning.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Discover the game that defined a genre, Dominion was first to popularize deck-building and remains a staple of tabletop. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/GrowYourKingdom.png?t=1707010484">Collect as many Victory Points as you can by building a powerful deck. Your deck starts out a small sad set of Estates and Coppers, but you hope that by the end of the game it will be brimming with Gold, Provinces, and the inhabitants and structures of your kingdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/BuildEngine.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Choose wisely among the 10 cards available in the tableau to create the strongest combos to dominate your opponent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CollectAllExpansions.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Make your games more exciting with additional cards and rules from up to 15 expansions including the recent Plunder expansion! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/NearInfiniteVariety.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Over one hundred thirty-two septillion possible Kingdom combinations, 500+ cards, 15 and counting expansions, and ongoing promo packs make Dominion one of the most extensive and replayable boardgames in the hobby. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CompeteComputer.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Sharpen your skills with solitaire style solo play against a robust AI, with four levels of difficulty. Our innovative AI learns through self-play. Earn Achievements and win in Recommended Sets against each AI level. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/PlayWithFriends.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Join up to 6 players online through your device or pass and play among your friends. Play ranked or unranked matchmaking, with realtime and asynchronous modes. Set up a private table for a family game, challenge a stranger in the lobby, or invite a friend!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Daily.png?t=1707010484"><br/>A daily ritual to relax with over a cup of coffee. Try the Daily Dominion, a free puzzle level available to players around the world. Practice your strategy to keep up a winning streak and climb the leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CrossPlatform.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Play from any supported device, whenever you want, after verifying your email in-game. Join games with opponents on platforms other than your own to enjoy the largest possible multiplayer pool and speedy matchmaking. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/JoinCommunity.png?t=1707010484"><br/>With an active Discord and online community, make new friends or challenge new people to a game. Export and share kingdoms and game summaries to compare strategies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/FreeToPlay.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Download the game that started it all for free! The base set of Dominion is available at no charge. Try the rotation of expansion cards in the Daily at no cost once per day. Jump into a lobby game with expansions enabled to try before you buy. Only the host needs to own the expansions.    <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Intro.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Learn the ropes in this easy to pick-up, hard to master title. Play one of the most highly regarded strategy tabletop games of all time through our simple tutorial.  The core loop is easy to follow, but offers a wealth of strategy to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>1-6 player</strong> support<br/></li><li><strong>500 </strong> plus <strong>cards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Solo play</strong> against four AI difficulties<br/></li><li><strong>Async </strong>&amp; <strong>real-time</strong> multiplayer<br/></li><li><strong>Ranked</strong> &amp; <strong>unranked</strong> matchmaking<br/></li><li><strong>Lobby</strong> &amp; <strong>Private game</strong> tables<br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform multiplayer</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform purchases</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Daily challenge</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Challenging AI</strong> that learns through self-play<br/></li><li><strong>Recommended Sets</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Customize</strong>, save &amp; share <strong>Kingdoms</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Achievements</strong>, <strong>Stats </strong>&amp; <strong>Leaderboards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Pass &amp; Play</strong> mode<br/></li><li>Automated <strong>score-keeping</strong> &amp; hints<br/></li><li><strong>Smart-play</strong> options to streamline gameplay<br/></li><li><strong>Jumbo mode</strong> for readability on phones<br/></li><li><strong>Turbo mode</strong> to zoom through games quickly<br/></li><li><strong>Tutorial</strong> &amp; <strong>Rules</strong><br/></li><li><strong>4 languages</strong>: English, Japanese, German, French<br/></li><li><strong>15 expansions</strong> plus three promo packs </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Awards for the Boardgame</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Awards.png?t=1707010484"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kādomon: Hyper Auto Battlers Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1985320/Kdomon_Hyper_Auto_Battlers_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Enter_a_new_world!.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/enter_new_world_final.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>Welcome to the world of Kādomon, a mysterious land where cute and quirky monsters roam freely. Journey through randomly generated regions, battling and collecting Kādomon on your quest to be the best.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Over_180_Kadomon.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/dex_final.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>There’s 180+ monsters to add to your Kādodex, and each Kādomon has 2 super rare misprints to discover! Find over 60 of these monsters and their misprints to build the ultimate unstoppable team in the Kādomon prologue!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Battle_with_Unique_Monsters.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/unique_mon_final.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>All Kādomon have special characteristics, such as activated abilities, passive abilities and different typings (there’s 12 types in total!). Synergise your Kādomon’s attacks and create a super effective combo of monsters. Grow even stronger with every battle by levelling-up and evolving your team!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Experience_Hyper_Evolutions.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/exp_hyper.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>Once fully evolved, every Kādomon has the chance to get HYPER! Acquire very rare items that allow your Kādomon to break their limits and discover a hyper-powerful 4th form! With brand new designs and souped-up stats, you’ll be able to tackle the greatest of challenges, in the Kādomon prologue you will be able to discover Hyper Evolution for every starter Kādomon! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Fight_BIG_bosses!.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/big_bosses.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>Battle your team against elite enemies and bosses. Get your team ready to fight against MEGA opponents, and unlock brand new Kādomon if you win! Remember, there is always a greater foe to test your strength!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Discover_Secrets_.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Discover_Secrets_final.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>The Kādomon world is bustling with secrets, including random events that will change the tide of battle! In the Early Access release, experiment with different items and monsters, Kādomon might evolve in different ways, and if you’re lucky you might just encounter a Legendary Kādomon to join your team…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/shonnkknk.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/shonnka.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>In between battles, take a mosey around Shonkka's Shop! Here you can use the Money Berries you’ve earned to buy new Kādomon and items. Held items are incredibly useful to have as they give you permanent buffs or powerful single use effects when used wisely!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/881020/Granblue_Fantasy_Relink/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/881020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Story<br/>
Granblue Fantasy takes place in the Sky Realm, a world where myriad islands float in a great blue expanse. Take your role as captain of a skyfaring crew, joined by a scrappy little dragon named Vyrn and a young girl with mysterious powers named Lyria. Together you sail with a colorful cast of crewmates, including kings and misfits alike, for Estalucia, a fabled island beyond the end of the skies.<br/>
<br/>
In the Zegagrande Skydom, islands are guarded by powerful creatures known as primal beasts and winds carry tales of a secretive organization known as the Church of Avia. Unveil a web of intrigue reaching far beyond the borders of Zegagrande and engage in a battle for the fate of the Sky Realm itself.<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay<br/>
Engage in real-time combat with a party of four in this character action RPG—choose from a diverse roster of skyfarers, each with their own unique weapons, skills, and combat styles. Teamwork makes the dream work with party-based mechanics such as Link Attacks and Chain Bursts to help you crush foes in spectacular fashion. Tackle quests solo or with the help of others for up to 4-player co-op and take down treacherous foes to score rare loot to further enhance your gear. Every enemy and party formation has its own strengths and weaknesses—the key to victory lies in working out how these pieces fit together.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced combat not your thing? Assist modes can provide accessibility for gamers of all skill levels. Toggle on Full Assist to have all actions performed automatically during battle!<br/>
<br/>
The Sky Realm is rich in lore and history. Browse Lyria's journal at any point during the game to access a trove of writings on the world's peoples, places, and more. In addition to the wealth of side quests available, Fate Episodes allow you to delve into the backstories of each member of your crew!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlazBlue Entropy Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2273430/BlazBlue_Entropy_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/原创声明-英语.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗EN_.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>Charismatic character designs with unique aesthetic styles and dramatic animations create a flamboyant, awesome combat experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快的动作连招EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快动作连招.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>Smooth controls, infinite possibilities of combos, and realistic combat feedback. This is the roguelite game with the best action experience yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超多角色豪华制作EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/全员图618x346.jpg?t=1706765621"><br/>Ten playable characters with vibrant personalities, unique combat styles, and immersive voice-acting.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式自由定制EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式，自由定制en.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>There are hundreds of moves for you to build around, plus countless elemental effects and legacy skills passed between characters. The possibilities are infinite. Time to make the best fighter of your own!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/抉择拯救世界EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/GIF-抉择拯救世界EN.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>In the future where the world has been plunged into chaos, people enter a cyberspace called ACE, seeking their last chance to resolve the crisis.<br/>If you are the only person in this world who knows the truth, how will you react?<br/>The ending is also the beginning. Your decision will decide humanity's future.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2772560/Supermarket_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This Prologue is a limited version of the full game to stop waiting and jump into running your supermarket already. Don't forget to wishlist the full game to continue your most fun supermarket experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Design your store, optimizing for efficiency and aesthetics. Determine where products are displayed, manage your aisles, and ensure a smooth shopping experience for your customers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Order stock using an in-game computer and anticipate the arrival of your next delivery. Unpack goods, organize them in your storage room and display them on shelves, fridges, and freezers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Read product barcodes, handle cash and credit card transactions, and ensure customers leave satisfied with their shopping and checkout experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier_Raw.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Navigate the complexities of a real-time market. Buy products when prices dip and determine the best-selling prices to balance customer satisfaction with profit margins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><br/>Wishlist the full game "Supermarket Simulator" where every decision matters. Will you rise to the occasion, transforming a modest establishment into a retail powerhouse, all while balancing customer satisfaction, finances, and mafia expectations?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Lily - Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2220360/Paper_Lily__Chapter_1/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Something terrible has happened. You can’t bear to think about it - but you can’t live like this anymore. You stopped attending school, you haven’t left your house in months, you have no reason to get out of bed anymore. There are no choices left.<br/><br/>No choice except... that strange golden letter.<br/><br/>It’s time to get your life back together. <br/><br/>One last try.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/divider.png?t=1706724298"><br/><br/>Paper Lily is a story-driven, psychological horror RPG where each puzzle has multiple solutions and outcomes. <strong>There is always another way.</strong><br/>Follow Lacie's story as you explore a dangerous hidden world, solve puzzles in multiple different ways, and face strange enemies. The game is playable in about 4 hours and contains multiple endings depending on your actions.<br/><br/>Paper Lily - Chapter 1 is the continuation to the prologue, <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1698960" rel="" target="_blank">Project Kat</a>, but it can also  be enjoyed without having played it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/lacie_sai_walk.gif?t=1706724298"><h2 class="bb_tag">Out of Context Features</h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple ways of solving puzzles!<br/></li><li>Touch grass, and trees<br/></li><li>Minigames where you press buttons and push boxes around<br/></li><li>Call your mother<br/></li><li>Harmless Snack™<br/></li><li>Various things made of paper<br/></li><li>Bunnies (or whatever those things are)<br/></li><li>Demons<br/></li><li>Fast demons<br/></li><li>Social anxiety simulation<br/></li><li>Table salt<br/></li><li>...Is that Kat? Nah, probably not<br/></li><li>Bathroom etiquette<br/></li><li>Death</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2072450/Like_a_Dragon_Infinite_Wealth/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/Accolades_616.png?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>EPIC EMOTIONAL DRAMA</strong><br/>Two larger-than-life heroes brought together by the hand of fate, or perhaps something more sinister…<br/><br/>Ichiban Kasuga, an unstoppable underdog who’s no stranger to crawling up from rock bottom, and Kazuma Kiryu, a broken man facing down his last days.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/2_Epic_Emotional_Drama.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>BEST-IN-CLASS RPG ACTION</strong><br/>Experience one-of-a-kind combat with dynamic, fast-paced RPG battles where the battlefield becomes your weapon, and anything goes. Adapt your party’s skills to the situation with outlandish jobs and customizations to strategically subdue enemies with over-the-top moves. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/3_Best_In_Class_RPG_Action.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>INFINITE ADVENTURE</strong><br/>Live it up in Japan and explore all that Hawaii has to offer in an adventure so big it spans the Pacific. Unforgettable moments await at every step of the journey with a unique mix of quests and activities to enjoy at your leisure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/4_Infinite_Adventure.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Deluxe Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Ultimate Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/>- Assorted Outfit Bundle: Customize your party's look with outfits &amp; swimwear<br/>- Sujimon &amp; Resort Bundle: Get legendary Sujimon, resort guests and special boosters<br/>- Yakuza CD Collection Set: Increase your in-game playlist with classic karaoke tracks						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apollo Justice: Ace Attorney Trilogy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2187220/Apollo_Justice_Ace_Attorney_Trilogy/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2187220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2187220/extras/13_Apollo_CustomImages_600x338.png?t=1706177279"><br/><br/>Apollo Justice's Legal Journey Begins Anew!<br/><br/>Join rookie attorney Apollo Justice and his mentor, the legendary Phoenix Wright, in this collection of 3 games! This title features the 14 episodes of "Apollo Justice: Ace Attorney", "Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney - Dual Destinies", and "Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney - Spirit of Justice", and the 2 previously DLC-only Special Episodes for a total of 16 episodes!<br/><br/>Also included is a mountain of extra goodies that's sure to satisfy any Ace Attorney fan!<br/><br/>Orchestra Hall - Listen to the in-game background music and select orchestral arrangements!<br/><br/>Art Library - View illustrations, design specs, commissioned pieces, and even the special Spirit of Justice Prologue anime!<br/><br/>Animation Studio - Play around with character animations and recreate your favorite scenes!<br/><br/>This collection supports Japanese, English, French, German, Korean, and Traditional and Simplified Chinese. Mix and match to play in whichever languages you'd like!<br/><br/>Immerse yourself in this beautiful collection as you shout "Objection!" in these newly renovated halls of justice!<br/><br/>Some of the contents of the games in this collection are presented as initially released to preserve the games as originally created.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNDER NIGHT IN-BIRTH II Sys:Celes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2076010/UNDER_NIGHT_INBIRTH_II_SysCeles/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Sys:Celes sinks towards ruination.<br/>For the Immortalize, the collapse of all that is, looms on the horizon.<br/>The curtain rises on the final chapter of the Hollow Night. Catastrophe beckons...<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store1b.gif?t=1707122865"><br/><br/>Experience the Dramatic Stylish 2D Fighting Action in the latest entry of the UNDER NIGHT IN-BIRTH series!<br/><br/>The first numbered sequel in the series!<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Choose from a roster of 24 total characters, with renewed visuals!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store2.jpg?t=1707122865"><br/>3 new characters join the battle: Moonlight Dancer "Twin Barrel Beauty" Kaguya, Indomitable Rampart "Steel Guardian" Tsurugi, and Endless Entity "Eternal Re-Birth" Kuon.<br/>You won’t be able to take your eyes off the intense battles between these 24 fighters with the highly detailed HD pixel art graphics!<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Simple inputs make it easy to jump into the fray!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store3.gif?t=1707122865"><br/>New to fighting games? Not a problem – simple inputs mean even beginners can pull off moves with a single button!<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Now supporting rollback netcode for an improved online experience!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store4.jpg?t=1707122865"><br/>With the addition of Casual Matches, it’s easier than ever before to dive in and enjoy online battles.<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Introducing new moves and game mechanics!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store5.gif?t=1707122865"><br/>All characters now boast new moves, such as Hyde’s Blaring Outrage and Linne’s Soaring Dragon.<br/>The new game mechanics Creeping Edge and Celestial Vorpal open up additional depth to gameplay.<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ The final chapter! A new tale of the Hollow Night…</h2>Sever the cycle. An end to the endless.<br/>May the tale of these countless Nights be concluded, on this eve, the moment of destiny.<br/>A long-awaited continuation to the tale of the Hollow Night unfolds!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summon Masters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2100140/Summon_Masters/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2100140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a card and board game with the following features:<br>
<br>
Deck Building: Players can build their own decks to battle with. Depending on different strategies and opponents, players can choose different cards to counter.<br>
<br>
Tactical Gameplay: The game uses a 3x10 chessboard, and players can freely place cards to fight. Players need to develop tactics and arrange card positions and usage order within limited space.<br>
<br>
Different Professions: Players can choose freely from four professions - swordsman, mage, monk, and archer. Each profession has different characteristics and skills, and players can choose according to their preferences and tactical needs.<br/>
<br/>
Competitive Battles: Players can battle with other players after building their decks, and it is fun to fight with other people. Through battles with other players, players can improve their strength and tactical skills.<br/>
<br/>
Team Dungeons: In addition to fighting against other players, players can also team up with others to challenge high-difficulty dungeons. Players need to defeat powerful bosses through cooperation and strategy to get more rewards and cards.<br/>
<br/>
Special Challenges: Players can participate in special rules challenges and use their intelligence to defeat other players. These special rules make the game more interesting and challenging, and players need to constantly think and try new strategies.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced: Each game is fast-paced (within 5 minutes), and can be played in short fragments of time. The fast pace of the game allows players to enjoy the game in a short time, while also being able to play at any time and anywhere.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2248950/TransSiberian_Railway_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take the helm of a classic Russian locomotive, discover the raw beauty and wildness of Siberia and try to survive on the longest railway line in the world. This is the Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator. A game for real adventurers!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/drinking1.gif?t=1707121961"><br/><br/>Complete the tutorial and the first kilometers of the route for free.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/explosion_gif.gif?t=1707121961"><br/><br/>The Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator offers amazing rail and survival challenges on real Russian dangerous routes. Feel what it is like to put your hands at the helm of a powerful freight locomotive and explore the untouched natural landscape that is sure to delight you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/shooting_gif.gif?t=1707121961"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Prologue features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Detailed simulation of driving a VL10 locomotive - the locomotive control is slightly simplified.<br/></li><li> Locomotive repair system - Manage and replace locomotive parts that are constantly wearing out.<br/></li><li> Train traffic simulation - Follow rail signs and signals to avoid derailment or damage to a part of the locomotive.<br/></li><li> Work system - Earn by completing transport orders. <br/></li><li> Game modes (Survival) and (Simulator). It is recommended to play in the (Survival) mode. This is the leading game mode that is constantly being developed. <br/>For players who are not interested in survival mechanics, a simple Simulator mode is available. <br/></li><li> Mafia system - Complete missions for the mafia to earn extra money.<br/></li><li> Survival system with statistics of hunger, thirst, alcohol, hangover, disease and hypothermia - Eat and drink to avoid death. <br/>Keep the right temperature so you don't freeze.<br/></li><li> Shooting system - Use your weapons for hunting and self-defense.<br/></li><li> Purchase and sales system - Buy various items, food, tools, weapons and ammunition.<br/></li><li> Locomotive inspection mode - Inspect the condition of locomotive parts and replace them in time to avoid damage.<br/></li><li> Dynamic weather system with day and night cycle - Survive extreme weather conditions.<br/></li><li> Route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Novosibirsk-Main) - scale 1:1. Buy the full version with the route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Krasnoyarsk).<br/></li><li> Police system - A corrupt militia watches over your movements.<br/></li><li> Much more to discover.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Universim</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/352720/The_Universim/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>WHAT WOULD YOU DO WITH THE POWER?</strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Play God!</strong> </h2>Guide your fledgling sentient species (lovingly called “nuggets”) from Stone Age cave painters to star-faring explorers.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-1-2d869427c7.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Wield godly power</strong></h2>Command more than 15 godly powers to guide, protect — or discipline — your followers. Create devastating tornadoes, smite naughty followers with lightning bolts, or shake and sunder the very earth. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-1-998341a4ac.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Watch your Nuggets grow and thrive</strong></h2>Observe Nuggets' every move as they work and fight to survive. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-537928a55b.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Evolve and advance through the ages</strong></h2>Research more than 200 technological and societal advancements. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-daca04b5ec.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Expand your power and colonize the galaxy</strong></h2>Discover and colonize a galaxy of procedurally generated planets, each with  unique ecosystems and challenges to conquer.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-be2f66969b.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Manage delicate ecosystems</strong></h2>Manage the delicate balance of planetary ecosystems to help nuggets thrive. Your decisions and your followers’ ' actions influence global climates and have real environmental consequences. (Try not to kill them in an ecological disaster — well, unless you want to, of course.)<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-0095b39c11.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Delve into the deeper mystery of your existence</strong></h2>Unravel the layers of a deeper cosmic story that challenges your perception of who and what you are — and reveals unexpected twists!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-4830f44913.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>About This Game:</strong></h2><br/>The Universim is a strategy city builder game with “God” elements where you guide a civilization (Nuggets) from the Stone Age to the Space Age. Manage resources, dynamic challenges, and ensure your Nuggets can survive, thrive, and spread to the stars. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Animated_Planet_3.png?t=1705993770"><br/><br/>The Universim  features more than  200 research perks that will help you to shape your civilization. Be as benevolent or malevolent as you like to drive nuggets to evolve, advance, and expand. (Even the best civilizations need an occasional smiting).  <br/>Every planet in The Universim is procedurally generated and offers unique characteristics  and challenges, ensuring  that every world and every game is unique and engaging.  Ecological balance and resource management are critical to success. Nuggets have their own needs and behaviors you must attend to. Your guidance will shape how they deal with conflicts, natural disasters, alien creatures, and other civilizations. Their growth and evolution depends on you!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FSymAzCGWsk" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Crytivo_Discord.png?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FgUt5N68" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Discord_join.jpg?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://twitter.com/crytivo" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Twitter.png?t=1705993770"/></a> <br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Feepurl.com%2FbKnqM1" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/News.png?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><br/>This game published by <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/franchise/Crytivo" rel="" target="_blank">Crytivo</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intravenous 2: Mercenarism</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2651330/Intravenous_2_Mercenarism/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Wishlist_Game.png?t=1705699394"><br/><br/>Step into the shoes of Gideon, a ruthless mercenary who cares about nothing but his wealth. Set two months before the events of Intravenous 2, you will take on seemingly simple jobs, the effects of which will ripple out and affect the main game's protagonist. But why should Gideon care? He's just in it for the money.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Stealth_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Stealth or Firepower:</strong> the choice is yours. Sneak through shadows, turn off the lights, pick doors, or unleash a hail of bullets. The game will adapt to your play style.<br/></li><li> <strong>Customize Your Skills:</strong> develop your skills the way you want to, whether it's mastering the art of stealth or becoming a gunslinging virtuoso.<br/></li><li> <strong>Bullet Time:</strong> Gideon is no stranger to stimulants that enhance his cognitive abilities - bending time to give him the edge in tense situations.<br/></li><li> <strong>Vast Arsenal:</strong> choose from firearms, gadgets, and a variety of ammo types to creatively tackle the challenge<br/></li><li> <strong>Weapon Modification:</strong> personalize each firearm with suppressors, laser sights, and more, tailoring your arsenal to the task at hand.<br/></li><li> <strong>Responsive AI:</strong> engage in intense combat with enemies that react to your actions, take cover, use tactics and call for backup.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Action_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2744170/Artifact_SeekerPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/DS.png?t=1706492908"/></a><br/>The difference between the prologue version and the official version<br/>There is a special artifact in the prologue<br/>Characters: 2 in the prologue, at least 5 in the official version<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 3 in the final version.<br/>Systems: Tavern, Marketplace, and Endless Mode will be added to the game.<br/>Artifacts: More artifacts will be added to the game.<br/>Skills: More skills will be added in the official version.<br/>Affixes: More Affixes will be added in the official version.<br/>Events: There will be more interesting Events in the official version.<br/>Progress: No need to worry, all progress will be carry into the official version.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/11y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1z.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/2y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/gif1.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong>[/b]<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><strong><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </img></img></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Look Inside</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2801620/Look_Inside/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2801620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>FACE YOUR FEARS</strong><br/><br/>During the unseasonally harsh winter of 1981, a shocking discovery was made in the sleepy town of Hemlock, Vermont, population, just 56. The frozen body of a young woman, whom no one could identify. Stranger still, the manner of her death seemed to match that of an ancient ritual supposedly practiced in the area hundreds of years before.<br/>Look Inside is a gripping psychological thriller kinetic novel. Take control of Vermont State Detective David Parker as you investigate the case, search for clues, and ultimately answer the question: who was Dwale County Jane Doe?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elf Kicker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2745090/Elf_Kicker/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							It's the day after Christmas, following another successful night of delivering presents, Santa must endure one more challenge, The Elf Kicking contest. This relaxing 2D game features a player character kicking and punching Santa's elves through a variety of winter backdrops with a singular goal, to hit the target object and advance to the next level.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grieve</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1795790/Grieve/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1795790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Grieve is a singleplayer thirdperson action packed shooter, with various levels and tasks. Part of the main objective is to collect intel and save hostages in secured locations where you must bust into and clear all the enemies if necessary. You will be provided with guns, on most missions but you can loot for extra items if you would like to survive. You will be radioed by a friend on entry to a location to remind you of the basic and obvious things you need to be aware of in order to survive. Goodluck.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Legend of Elrian</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2729050/The_Legend_of_Elrian/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2729050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Legend of Elrian is an adventure inspired by adventure games of GameBoy era. The story takes place in an elven village where Famenor, the inheritor of the village leading, had mysteriously disappeared. You, Elrian (his brother), has to go to rescue him. You will have to pass through a dangerous forest to learn more about circumstances of this disappearance and try to rescue your brother.<br>
Key features :<br>
- 2D adventure with minimalized pixel art (5 colors)<br>
- Different weapons to defeat your ennemies<br>
- Riddles to solve for unlock ways						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spheric Bombs</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2771650/Spheric_Bombs/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2771650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Explore an Explosive World of Strategy and Reflection!</strong></h2>Immerse yourself in a turn-based 3D tactical puzzle game that tests your strategic skills. Guide a bomb through stimulating grid-based levels, where every move counts. Face unique challenges, unlock achievements, plan your strategy and survive to claim victory.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>25 Unique Levels:</strong> Go through a variety of levels, each presenting unique challenges and objectives.<br/></li><li><strong>Unlock 25 Achievements:</strong> Showcase your skills by unlocking 25 achievements, earned by completing each level with 100 life points.<br/></li><li><strong>Explosive Tactical Puzzles:</strong> Engage in a captivating blend of puzzle-solving and tactical decision-making, putting your thinking skills to the test.<br/></li><li><strong>Strategic Buffs and Debuffs:</strong> Consider the strategically placed buffs and debuffs throughout the various levels, adding a tactical dimension to every decision.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Face 8 Types of Enemies:</strong></h2>Discover imposing opponents, each possessing distinct characteristics. Anticipate their moves to survive, but beware – when they merge, they become even more powerful!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2771650/extras/gif_spherics.gif?t=1707487486"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Pyrospheric:</strong> Walks on magma cubes without taking damage.<br/></li><li><strong>Hydrospheric:</strong> Walks on water cubes.<br/></li><li><strong>Atmospheric:</strong> Jumps up to 4 cubes instead of 2.<br/></li><li><strong>Terraspheric:</strong> Reduces the player's damage resistance.<br/></li><li><strong>Chronospheric:</strong> Add 2 turns to the game.<br/></li><li><strong>Tempospheric:</strong> Skips the next player's turn.<br/></li><li><strong>Sinistospheric:</strong> Inflicts fatal damage to the player.<br/></li><li><strong>Electrospheric:</strong> Moves by 2 cubes instead of 1.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Merge rule:</strong></h2> If enemies are at the same level, the moving one consumes the stationary one; otherwise, the higher-level always consumes the lower-level.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Achievement Hunter Tips:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Sometimes, it's better to skip your turn on the current cube.<br/></li><li>Be aware of the enemies playing order to take advantage of it.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Developer's Note:</strong></h2>I'm thrilled to share this game with you. Your support means a lot. Have fun!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limsod</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2555030/Limsod/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2555030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Following a virus released from the laboratories, the population has been totally transformed into zombies determined to devour what remains of civilization. Accept your mission to wipe out all the zombies in these areas that have been left abandoned for years. Be careful, a small part of the zombies have been severely impacted, giving them special characteristics, which can turn your simple mission into a terrible hell. Quickly take your basic equipment and kill all the zombies to make the area peaceful again. Once you have achieved your goal, return to the base and upgrade your equipment for your next missions.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight with 8 different types of zombie, each with its own properties<br/></li><li>Explore over 20 unique maps with 10 different game modes<br/></li><li>Unlock a wide range of equipment modifications and upgrades that will influence gameplay<br/></li><li>Progress through your adventure to complete 80 quests and objectives</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2555030/extras/banner_01.png?t=1707489274"><br/><strong><u>Limsod is much more than just a zombie game. With its many game modes, multiple play styles are possible:</u></strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Survival mode: Survive 5 minutes in a zombie-infested map<br/></li><li>Unlimited mode: Survive in a vast world with no time limit<br/></li><li>Death Sleeves mode: Kill zombies, pass sleeves to unlock new map part and a new gameplay style<br/></li><li>Defense mode: Defend an antenna against a horde of zombies that attract him<br/></li><li>Training mode: Train in a shooting range on harmless zombies<br/></li><li>Point Race mode: Every action you perform earns points, get the points you need before time runs out<br/></li><li>Time Saving mode: Every zombie you kill saves you time, so survive as long as possible<br/></li><li>Melee mode: Use your weapon in a different way to exterminate the entire zombie horde<br/></li><li>Preview mode: Explore the maps peacefully<br/></li><li>Custom mode: Customize absolutely every parameter to create your perfect game mode</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I commissioned some abstract bunnies</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682510/I_commissioned_some_abstract_bunnies/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2682510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A hidden object game where you must find all the abstract bunnies and carrots to complete each level.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key features:</h2>🖼️ 15 Unique artworks<br/>❓ 1500+ Hidden objects total<br/>🐇 750+ Abstract bunnies<br/>🥕 750+ Abstract carrots<br/>💡 ∞ Unlimited hints if you get stuck<br/>♻️ Restore a small number of bunnies / carrots to a painting so you can find them again! <br/>🎵 Music for each artwork (optional)<br/>🏆 Achievements<br/>⌨️ Use your keyboard to move / zoom in if you have no scroll wheel<br/>💾 3x save slots<br/>🗑️ Reset progress entirely and play again<br/>🕒 ∞ Timer included to show how long you took to complete each level<h2 class="bb_tag">Context:</h2>The brief was simple. I commissioned artists to create a canvas filled with polygons, and hide as many abstract bunny and carrot shapes as they can inside it. Now it’s your job to find them all! With 15 abstract art pieces to choose from, and 1500+ abstract bunnies and carrots, you will have a lot of searching to do.<h2 class="bb_tag">Controls:</h2>Use your mouse to move around the image and zoom in / out. When you find a hidden object, click it and it will disappear. You can also use WASD to move and the arrow keys to zoom.<h2 class="bb_tag">Difficulty:</h2>A full range of difficulty is included, but all levels start unlocked, your progress is saved as you play, and you have unlimited, unrestricted hints if you get stuck. Using hints will not ruin your score, or affect your ability to unlock achievements. Play at your own pace!<h2 class="bb_tag">Get immersed:</h2>Each painting has its own music and ambiance to help you connect with the world, as you search for all the bunnies and carrots!.<h2 class="bb_tag">Replayable</h2>You can restore a small number of bunnies and carrots back into a painting so you can find them again! It’s much harder when there are only a few left (especially randomly). You can also use up to 3 save slots so you can replay without progress loss. Alternatively, you can reset your progress for the entire game if you’d like to start over.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lukewarm Massacre: The killer who may or may not be a moron.</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779850/Lukewarm_Massacre_The_killer_who_may_or_may_not_be_a_moron/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2779850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to this spectacular, amazing, astonishing, breathtaking, daring, dazzling, dramatic, eye-catching, fabulous, fantastic, grand, magnificent, marvellous, miraculous, remarkable, sensational, splendid, striking, stunning, thrilling, wondrous, razzle-dazzle, theatrical, marked, prodigious, staggering, stupendous adventure! You are getting chased by a dude with a significantly lower-than-average IQ, but you'll still get scared since this is marked as horror...or not, we're not forcing you to even play this game tbh.<br/><br/>This game includes one overworld, and that's it. Yes, there's only one area, what do you expect? GTA 5? Well, you're not getting it, you're getting this game instead. So either you are grateful for that and the hard work we clearly put into this game or you stop complaining! What, you don't wanna stop complaining? You hate this game? Ooookay, woooow, so eeedgyyy. Like c'mon kid, you're just trying to make people hate you at this point. This game is a masterpiece and you know it- I should jump off a building? I can't believe you said that, holy crap you suck.<br/><br/><strong><i>Description:</i></strong><br/>"Lukewarm Massacre: The killer who may or may not be a moron." is a survival puzzle <span class="bb_strike">comedy</span> horror game <span class="bb_strike">made in RPG Maker MV</span>.<br/><br/><strong><i>Story:</i></strong><br/>You play as Three, a 16-year-old boy who had gone camping with his dhampir friends, although, unfortunately for them, it went south and it soon turned into a survival game when a <span class="bb_strike">moron</span> killer in the forest is hunting down the three of them.<br/><br/>Can all of you survive the night?<br/><br/><strong><i>This game includes:</i></strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Crappy off-brand marketing</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A really dumb map design, it doesn't even make any sense.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A not-very-scary killer.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Jumpscares, if you can tolerate those.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>I don't know, go see for yourself.</li></ul><br/><br/><i>This game was originally released November 18. 2022.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Magic Land</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2307890/The_Magic_Land/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2307890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Magic Land is a massive online role-playing game where people live in a magical world of adventures, In an MMORPG people from all over the world meet on a virtual playground to explore areas, solve tricky riddles and undertake heroic exploits. Players are faced with the challenge of developing the skills of their selected characters, exploring a large variety of areas and dangerous dungeons and interacting with other players on a social and diplomatic level.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eldritchvania</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2423710/Eldritchvania/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2423710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2423710/extras/Title_-_600.png?t=1707483638"><br/>In Eldritchvania, you will explore unearthly ruins, solve arcane riddles and pick up your sword against the indescribable horrors that lurk amidst the forgotten depths of our world. Beware the creeping grip of madness as you uncover secrets not meant for the eyes of men.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2423710/extras/Resurs_3@0.5x.png?t=1707483638"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 70 hand drawn rooms to explore!<br/></li><li>Countless enemies and traps!<br/></li><li>Puzzles and riddles that will test your cunning!<br/></li><li>Upgrades and items to help you on your journey!<br/></li><li>Damnable bosses!<br/></li><li>Madness and insanity that affect how the game is played!<br/></li><li>Lore and story based on and inspired by the works of H.P Lovecraft</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2423710/extras/Resurs_2@0.5x.png?t=1707483638"><br/>The game follows the aged occultist, Dougald, as he desperately tries to track down his son, Fergus. All clues lead him to believe Fergus traveled to the small island of Blackhorn, just outside the coast of northern Scotland. Dougald is convinced he must save his son before he unearths the ungodly knowledge buried deep beneath the island. But will his quest force him to uncover the very same secrets? Unearthing the long since abandoned ruins of lost civilizations,  your cunning, endurance and sanity will be duly tested. Are you up to the task?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2423710/extras/Resurs_4@0.5x.png?t=1707483638"><br/>Eldritchvania is going to be a free, and will release on the 10th of February 2024<br/><br/>Be sure to wishlist the game if you want to be notified when Eldritchvania releases!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Touchdown Pinball</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2294300/Touchdown_Pinball/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2294300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Get ready for Touchdown Pinball, a pinball machine where you'll play an exciting match. Score field goals, touchdowns and show who is the greatest football player on this table. <br>
<br>
Discover all the missions and secrets, including a secret arena match where your abilities will be tested.<br>
<br>
Complete all the missions and become number 1 in the world or the best among your Friends, posting your high score on the online leaderboard.<br>
<br>
- Arcade design.<br>
- More than 8 missions to accomplish! Are you ready?<br/>
- Multiball, Extraball, Skillshot, Jackpots...<br/>
- Reproduction with all the details, lights and sounds.<br/>
- 4 different cameras to choose from.<br/>
- Vertical Gameplay.<br/>
- Online Leaderboard.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tug-of-war</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781010/tugofwar/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781010/extras/release_1.gif?t=1707480605"><br/><br/><br/>A simple one-button clicker game.<br/><br/>Play a tug-of-war as a witch trying to use cute cats as her familiars!<br/><br/>The pixel-style pictures and lively 8-bit music are the attractive points.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781010/extras/release_2.gif?t=1707480605"><br/>- - - - - - - - - -<br/>Thanks to<br/><br/>KuroNeko <br/>kJY1412<br/>limtinct<br/>LEE HYOJUNG <br/><br/>graphic<br/>// 9E0<br/><br/>MUSIC <br/>// Kei Morimoto<br/>// Hupple<br/>// alaki paca<br/>// くれっぷ						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nofio wireless adapter for Valve Index</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2154720/nofio_wireless_adapter_for_Valve_Index/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2154720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							Nofio wireless adapter for Valve Index is built for serious gamers. It comes with everything you need to convert your exising Valve Index to a truly wireless VR Headset. With a dedicated wireless transmitter and receiver, the conversion to wireless is easy, non-destructive and removeable. Simply connect the base transmitter to your PC (DisplayPort, USB and Power), attach the receiver to your headset and connect the supplied short Oculink cable and you are good to go.<br>
<br>
The Nofio adapter integrates directly with SteamVR, apart from a simple USB driver there is no custom software which needs to be run, or added hardware installed to your PC. The processing is performed completely onboard which means your PC resources are 100% dedicated to gameplay with no impact on gaming performance.<br>
<br>
The wireless connection is completely standalone, without the need for additional wireless routers which means video quality can be maintained without affecting existing network traffic.<br>
<br>
Nofio is built on the worlds first network aware CODEC technology from IMRnext. The compression ratio can be adaptively adjusted to suit changing network<br>
conditions, and subframe streaming allows the frame to be compressed and sent before the next frame is rendered. All of this results in visual quality and latency equivalent to a traditional cabled experience						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keep It Steady!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2799640/Keep_It_Steady/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2799640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Try to get the ball in the lit hole while avoiding the unlit holes by tilting a paddle.<br>
<br>
See how high of a score you can get in 3 minutes of playing Keep It Steady!<br>
<br>
In this retro style game you will be able to control the left and right sides of a long paddle. You must move these sides up and down to guide the ball and to carefully balance and roll it into the lit up yellow hole while simultaneously avoiding the black unlit holes. Be careful to not accidently roll the ball into the wrong holes or it will be game over!<br>
<br>
This game also includes a online scoreboard so you can play to try to take the chance at being the best player in the world!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ULTRATORO</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2274250/ULTRATORO/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2274250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ultratoro is a fast-paced driving game where the tracks have the shape of a donut.<br/>In Ultratoro you will…<br/><br/><strong>Drive at full speed</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2274250/extras/Gameplay.gif?t=1707469887"><br/>An arcade racer like no other.<br/>Experience a unique gameplay loop in a surreal non-euclidean universe.<br/>Challenge your friends for the best time and get your score into the global leaderboards.<br/><br/><strong>Explore a virtual world</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2274250/extras/LevelSelector.gif?t=1707469887"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2274250/extras/Story.gif?t=1707469887"><br/>Explore a non-linear overworld. By beating levels you unlock new paths, find shops and uncover the mysteries of torus-space.<br/>Ultratoro tells the story of a hacker infiltrating “Deusoft”, the biggest megacorporation in the world.<br/><br/><strong>Unlock cars</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2274250/extras/CarShop.gif?t=1707469887"><br/>Maneuver the cyberspace with style!<br/>With the coins found in the enemy servers you can buy new cars.<br/>Unlock every car shop and complete your collection.<br/><br/><strong>Create and share levels with the community</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2274250/extras/levelEditor.gif?t=1707469887"><br/>Featuring an easy to use level editor, anyone can create their own tracks and share them with other players. With full controller support, these creative tools are seamlessly integrated into the main game.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conor Origins - T Trilogy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748450/Conor_Origins__T_Trilogy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Conor's first three visual novels have been rereleased in one package! See the world through the eyes of a lonely man talking a walk, try to escape from a secluded prison, or help a girl confess to her crush. While one on them is a kinetic visual novel, there won't be any choices to make, but the other two will have a big impact on the world the characters are in.<br/><br/><u>They Cannot Hear Me</u><br/>It's the middle on winter and a lonely man goes for a walk late at night. He spends the time thinking about how sad his life has become and how things will likely never change for the better for him. Will anything interesting happen on his walk or is he doomed to spend the rest of his life alone? As he walks around town he'll be reminded of events from his past. The man in the story doesn't have a name because it's not really important, so you can assume it to be whatever you want. Since this is a short kinetic visual novel there really isn't much else to say. There are no choices, it's just a really short story.<br/><br/><u>Trapped</u><br/>When you wake up in a prison cell, you have no memory of who you are or how you even got there. If you don't want to rot to death, it's up to you to find a way out and explore the island you've been trapped on with a girl you'll meet outside named Mila. Like you, she has no idea how she got to the island or what's going on. If you want to get out of there, both of you are going to have to work to together to escape! If you're not careful, your choices could lead to your death or you'll just have to die of old age alone. Whichever comes first.<br/><br/><u>The Weird One</u><br/>Camille has made up her mind and plans to confess her feelings to a friend of hers. However, what she doesn't know is that this guy is much weirder than she thinks. Whatever choices she makes will have a huge effect on whatever universe she's in. Some decisions may allow her to continue to have a normal life but others will throw her in all kinds of weird situations. Will Camille be able to tell Dave how he she feels about him or will he drag him into whatever weird things are going on with him?<br/><br/>All of these stories aren't very long which is way they've been bundled together in one collection.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Photographer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1856660/Mr_Photographer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1856660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a vibrant journey through the lens of "Mr. Photographer," a captivating low-poly stylized family platformer game that challenges you to navigate through whimsical worlds, capturing the essence of adventure with every snapshot. As an aspiring photographer on the brink of turning your internship into a successful career, you'll leap, dash, and soar across platforms, collecting an array of photo cameras and SD cards to compile your masterpiece portfolio.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Game Features:</strong></h2><br/><strong>A Colorful Quest:</strong> Dive into a beautifully crafted, low-poly world where every platform is a step towards your dream. From the serene to the surreal, explore diverse landscapes brimming with life and color.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1856660/extras/mainstart.gif?t=1707467067"><br/><br/><strong>Collectibles Galore: </strong>Sharpen your skills and eye for detail by finding hidden platforms and secret caches filled with cameras and SD cards. Your dedication to exploration and collection directly influences your journey's length and the rewards you reap.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1856660/extras/hidden.gif?t=1707467067"><br/><br/><strong>Thrilling Gameplay Variations:</strong> Transition seamlessly from platformer to arcade action as you mount motocross bikes and pilot helicopters, adding exhilarating twists to your photographic expedition.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1856660/extras/moto.gif?t=1707467067"><br/><br/><strong>Challenge and Reward:</strong> With no checkpoints, "Mr. Photographer" offers a true test of skill and perseverance. Each attempt is a fresh start, compelling you to refine your strategies and master the game's intricacies.<br/>Speedrun or Marathon: Whether you're a speed demon aiming to finish in 1.5 minutes or a completionist targeting the perfect score in a 45-minute epic, your approach defines your experience. Optimize your route or scour every corner for the ultimate collection.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1856660/extras/heli.gif?t=1707467067"><br/><br/><strong>Embark on Your Photographic Adventure:</strong><br/>"Mr. Photographer" isn't just a game; it's a journey of growth, creativity, and determination. Your goal is simple yet profound: navigate the trials of an internship to emerge as an established photographer, capturing beauty, adventure, and the moments in between. Are you ready to frame your destiny and snap your way to success?<br/><br/>Join us in "Mr. Photographer," where every jump is a flash, every collectible a step closer to your dreams, and every playthrough a unique story. Your adventure starts now. Will you capture it?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I keep Dying in Another World</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2724600/I_keep_Dying_in_Another_World/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Engaging and gripping story from beginning to end, twists, turns, and despair await!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724600/extras/about.png?t=1707466903"><h2 class="bb_tag">WHAT!? I'VE BEEN ISEKAI'D!?</h2>What if one day you suddenly get summoned to Another World without explanation and... die just around the corner? What if after that, a suspicious Goddess tells you that you must do something... but she's so vague to not even explain what?<br/><br/>In this Kinetic Novel, follow John Smith, a regular junior programmer struggling with self-confidence, as he tries to <strong>stop a murder</strong> from happening. He will keep <strong>returning after death</strong> to continue with newfound knowledge, alliances, and ideas to fulfill the mission the Goddess tasked him with. <strong>As many times as it takes</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">COMPLEX, SERIOUS, LINEAR STORY</h2>What <strong>secrets</strong> is the Goddess hiding? Will she be a <strong>help or a hindrance</strong>?<br/>Uncover the <strong>conspiracy</strong> behind the murder.<br/>There are clues scattered on the way. Can YOU unravel the mystery before John does?<h2 class="bb_tag">FANTASY WORLD</h2>With a carefully designed story, characters, and world, dive into this <strong>anime-inspired</strong> tale!<h2 class="bb_tag">KEY FEATURES:</h2>- <strong>countless deaths</strong> - roughly 4 hours of story, depending on your reading speed<br/>- cinematic experience - immerse yourself at your own pace with intriguing and captivating story beats!<br/>- dark comedy, romance, thriller, and psychological horror all in one package!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legumi</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2774280/Legumi/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2774280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i>Legumi</i></strong> are a small, helpless species of bean-eating creatures that used to possess the secret to <strong><i>True Happiness</i></strong>. However, the secret has been lost for generations. In times of old, legumi would embark on quests, following invisible roads dotted with mysterious <strong><i>wisdom houses</i></strong>, which would lead to the place where True Happiness could be found. But the world has grown dangerous and full of monsters. Such a quest has not been attempted for generations.<h2 class="bb_tag">the Quest</h2>You play as a young legumi who is just brash and sad and brave enough to set out on the first <i>Quest for True Happiness</i> in living memory. Your survival will depend on your ability to manage your <i>time</i>, your <i>beans</i>, and the legumi's secret weapon, <i>pips</i>. <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Once you leave the comfort of town, you will have sixty seconds of energy for exploring<br/></li><li>Eating a bean will give you ten seconds of energy and two "pips"<br/></li><li>Pips are small, harmless explosives that can be thrown to scare off monsters<br/></li><li>Everything of interest in the world will appear as a distant glisten until you're close enough to get a better look<br/></li><li>If what you found is a monster, you can shoo it away by either satiating it's <i><strong>hunger</strong></i> with beans, or matching it's <strong><i>startle</i></strong> with pip explosions<br/></li><li>Pips all pop a random power between 0 and 3. You can throw as many as you think you need to to reach a monsters' bravery number. <br/></li><li>If you find a <i><strong>bean plant,</strong></i> you can harvest it for <i>three beans</i>. They will grow back in sixty seconds!<br/></li><li>explore until you find all the <strong><i>wisdom houses</i></strong> in an area, at which time the <strong><i>secret exit</i></strong> to the next area will appear somewhere nearby.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Collect money from foes and treasure, and upgrade yourself in towns. Become faster, braver, luckier, smarter, and less likely to fail.<br/></li><li><strong><i>Somewhat random</i></strong>: Legumi is never the same game twice! Objects of interest are shuffled around inside their regions, and shuffled again whenever you <i>do</i> fail.<br/></li><li>Boppin' original soundtrack<br/></li><li>The mysterious <strong><i>Champion's Labyrinth</i></strong> mode, available to Legumi masters, shuffles everything in the game around to provide a fresh new challenge</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terror Mansion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2794400/Terror_Mansion/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2794400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Terror Mansion is an exciting first person Horror video game that catapults you into a frightening Mansion.<br>
Your main objective is to escape the infested Mansion, finding objects and challenging riddles while exploring incredible scenarios.						</br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MagicArchitect_IntoDisaster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678660/MagicArchitect_IntoDisaster/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Dive into a magical journey where you get to decide which character to use to build your own magical prowess. An action-packed adventure awaits in this one-of-a-kind shooter game! Choose from various characters and spells to master their powers and earn a living. Will it be 3-Way, Spread, or Rapid Fire? Nurture your magic, sell it, and profit from your journey that starts now.<br>
<br>
In this roguelike game, experiment with a variety of magic and character combinations. Defeat enemies to collect orbs and enhance your magical abilities. With each playthrough lasting around 5 minutes, you can effortlessly try out different strategies.<br>
<br>
So, step into a world where magic meets the modern era, and use your magical skills to become incredibly wealthy! A new adventure may just be beginning. Let's enjoy this magical adventure...!"						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreality</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2765850/Unreality/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2765850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> Welcome to Unreality, a unique experience that will immerse you in a fascinating journey through the cosmos. In this platformer game, you will embark on an odyssey alongside our light particle, facing thrilling challenges as you explore beautiful vistas of planets and galaxies. </strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> Difficulty </h2> Precision in jumps and reaction time will be key to overcoming the challenges that await you. With three difficulty modes, Unreality offers you the opportunity to customize your gaming experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2765850/extras/show_difficult.gif?t=1707447716"><h2 class="bb_tag">Levels and Lives</h2> Each chapter features three levels, totaling 15 levels. Throughout your adventure, you will have three lives per level and a strategic checkpoint midway through the course. But beware! If you lose all three lives, you will be forced to restart the level from the beginning. Unreality's retro style will transport you to a visually captivating universe.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2765850/extras/show_lives.gif?t=1707447716"><h2 class="bb_tag">Enemies</h2> Each enemy in Unreality has a characteristic color and a unique movement, forming shapes and patterns that are challenging to overcome, adding a strategic element to your cosmic journey.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2765850/extras/enemies.gif?t=1707447716"><h2 class="bb_tag">Shield</h2> For those moments when the difficulty intensifies, the shield will come to your aid. If you face insurmountable obstacles in a specific area, the shield will allow you to progress without losing the magic of the game.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2765850/extras/shield.gif?t=1707447716"><h2 class="bb_tag">Atmosphere and Soundtrack</h2> The spatial ambiance of Unreality is unique, as all galaxy and cluster images are real captures from NASA's Hubble and Chandra space telescopes. Immerse yourself in the beauty of the cosmos as you overcome each level. The musical atmosphere, featuring compositions by Karl Casey @ White Bat Audio, will accompany you in every jump and challenge, further immersing you in the Unreality experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">Advanced Gamepad</h2> Accessibility is a priority in Unreality, as it is compatible with most generic gamepads. The game features a custom mapping system to adapt to each controller. Additionally, gamepad options are fully adjustable, allowing you to change jump and movement buttons to facilitate one-handed gameplay, especially designed for players with this condition.<br/><br/><strong>Get ready to explore, jump, and face challenges in this thrilling world. Are you ready for the adventure in Unreality? Let the intergalactic journey begin!</strong> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EcoGenesis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788330/EcoGenesis/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>EcoGenesis is a 2D black-box ecosystem simulator where you need to craft an ecosystem that can withstand the test of time.</strong> Starting with just a single-cell organism, you must unlock creatures and balance your environment while driving towards one of the three victory conditions in this turn-based simulation.<br/><br/><strong>Over 100 Different Animal Species</strong><br/>• Unlock and craft a multitude of different animals from land-dwellers like the bear and elephant to sea-creatures such as the blue whale and orca.<br/>• 10+ dinosaur species including the Rex and the Brontosaurus.<br/>• Each creature has a unique set of stats that changes the way it impacts the environment, the amount of resources it gives per turn, and how much it costs to craft.<br/>• Upgrade your creatures! Each organism has three unique hand-drawn sprites corresponding to their level.<br/>• Most creatures have <strong>abilites</strong> - make sure to pay attention to what they do!<br/><br/><strong>14x Different Resources to Manage</strong><br/>• Carefully manage your resources to allow you to craft and upgrade more animals to put into your environment.<br/>• Each resource has a unique hand-drawn sprite.<br/><br/><strong>Over 1000x Quiz Questions Corresponding to Each Resource Type!</strong><br/><br/><strong>Balance Your Ecosystem's 5x Key Traits</strong> - water, foliage, herbivores, carnivores, and temperature. Each one impacts the ecosystem in a unique way, so make sure to keep a keen eye on them.<br/><br/><strong>6x Different Weather Conditions</strong> - ranging from hurricanes to solar flares!<br/><br/><strong>A Multitude of Events</strong> - will your ecosystem be ravaged by a deadly flood, or will rains bring good luck to the riverbanks?<br/><br/><strong>30+ Missions</strong><br/><br/><strong>30+ Achievements</strong><br/><br/><strong>3x Victory Conditions</strong> - Biomass, Crafting Creatures, and Completing Missions.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Backrooms Deluxe</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2558700/The_Backrooms_Deluxe/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2558700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Discover various levels of danger while trying to escape the eerily familiar backrooms based on popular creepypasta lore.<h2 class="bb_tag">New and Unique Levels</h2>Traverse through 20+ unique levels based on the Backrooms lore. Regular content updates will add even more levels. Each level features a different way to escape, with various dangers along the way.<h2 class="bb_tag">Scary Entities</h2>In The Backrooms Deluxe, there are many entities blocking your way of finally exiting the backrooms. Each of the entities has its own appearance and mechanics<br/><br/>Join the official Discord Server for updates about it! <i>(updates will still be posted on Steam but the discord server has sneak peeks about it)</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project 47</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2767730/Project_47/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Awaken in a place forgotten by time, you will find nothing in your path but a variety of insects that will not hesitate to destroy you. During your journey you will find multiple abandoned structures, a reflection of the mysterious disappearance of the society that lived there.<br/><br/>You will control a curious <strong>android</strong>, your body is weak and your magnetic hands and feet don't give you much security against the dangers that lurk around you, so be careful. To discover the secrets of this universe, as well as understand your own existence, you will need to cross this unique world, seek answers to your questions and understand more about your past.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767730/extras/steam_descricao_player.png?t=1707427516"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features and Mechanics:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Face a variety of insects and other dangers to <i>challenge your skills and reflexes</i>;<br/></li><li>Be amazed by a <i>unique Pixel Art style</i>, with animations and scenes made one by one;<br/></li><li>Cross <i>five distinct biomes</i>, each with its own fauna, flora and various abandoned structures;<br/></li><li>Find <i>new skills</i> to help you on your journey and discover your destiny;<br/></li><li>Uncover the history and other events of this universe through old notes, in addition to observing the environment and even the architecture of the world;<br/></li><li>Enjoy more than <i>140 sound effects</i>, as well as <i>14 original songs</i>, to give the player depth and immersion;<br/></li><li>Reach the game's <i>23 achievements</i>, including story moments, collectibles and other hidden secrets;<br/></li><li>Discover <i>mechanics and threats specific to each biome</i>: Use elevators in the forest, swim through aquatic ruins, protect yourself from the scorching desert sun, guide yourself through the darkness of the caves.... <strong>Each new scenario will give you new challenges, possibilities and enemies</strong>;</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767730/extras/steam_descricao_floresta.png?t=1707427516"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767730/extras/steam_descricao_deserto.png?t=1707427516"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767730/extras/steam_descricao_vale.png?t=1707427516"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VTuber Manager</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2755230/VTuber_Manager/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2755230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Welcome to "VTuber Manager" – Where You Craft Your Own Virtual Empire!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2755230/extras/P001.png?t=1707425355"><br/>In this innovative simulation game, you'll step into the role of a VTuber studio manager, navigating through the endless possibilities of the virtual world. Your mission is to discover and develop top-notch VTubers and a professional team, creating a renowned studio in the realm of virtual entertainment.<br/><br/><strong>Explore a world of diverse gameplay</strong><br/><br/><strong>Scouting and Development:</strong> Choose and nurture potential talents and staff from a roster of over a hundred unique VTubers, customizing distinctive virtual personas and styles for them.<br/><br/><strong>Creative Production:</strong> Design and sell a variety of VTuber merchandise, ranging from adorable plushies to trendy apparel, captivating fans from all corners.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2755230/extras/einelitschi_VTuber_cat_ears_perfect_body_charming_pure_white_ba_38c3c0a2-2ba1-48b2-9bc8-7228805994eb.png?t=1707425355"><br/><strong>Content Creation:</strong> Produce engaging live stream highlights and execute well-planned promotional campaigns to enhance the online presence of your VTubers.<br/><br/><strong>Interaction and Challenges:</strong> Encounter dozens of different event dialogues in-game, where each decision can pivot the direction of your VTuber career.<br/><br/><strong>Multiple Endings:</strong> Every choice matters with multiple ending scenarios, ensuring each playthrough remains fresh and challenging.<br/><br/>"VTuber Manager" is more than just a game; it's a world filled with creativity and strategy. Your decisions shape the destiny of your VTubers and their fan communities. Are you ready? Let's embark on a journey to script your legendary story in this enchanting virtual world!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2755230/extras/einelitschi_Abstract_celebration_picture_fireworks_26447d27-e507-4f5a-a578-b68358c9fe94.png?t=1707425355"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OFFROAD MotorBike VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2793430/OFFROAD_MotorBike_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2793430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an adrenaline-fueled journey with our immersive VR Offroad MotorBike game, available now on Steam! Get ready to experience the thrill of conquering challenging terrains and mastering a variety of powerful offroad motorcycles.<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br>
<br>
Diverse and Challenging Tracks:<br>
Explore a multitude of exhilarating offroad tracks, each presenting unique challenges that will test your skills and determination. From rugged mountain trails to sandy desert dunes, the adventure never ends.<br>
<br/>
Extensive Motorcycle Selection:<br/>
Choose from a diverse range of high-performance offroad motorcycles, each with its own distinct characteristics. Whether you prefer speed, agility, or raw power, find the perfect bike to match your riding style.<br/>
<br/>
Immersive VR Experience:<br/>
Dive into the heart-pounding action with our VR technology that puts you right in the rider's seat. Feel the wind on your face as you navigate through the twists and turns of offroad landscapes.<br/>
<br/>
Realistic Physics and Graphics:<br/>
Our game boasts realistic physics and stunning graphics, delivering an authentic offroad racing experience. Feel the mud splatter, hear the engines roar, and see the dust rise as you tear through the challenging courses.<br/>
<br/>
Gear up, rev your engines, and prepare for the offroad adventure of a lifetime in Offroad MotorBike VR – where every twist of the throttle brings you closer to victory!<br/>
<br/>
!!! Oculus controllers cannot be used unless set as the default OpenXR Runtime for the Oculus computer. Please enter the Oculus application, go to Settings, then navigate to General. Click on the option 'Set Meta Quest Link as active' located next to the OpenXR Runtime selection.If SteamVR is open, you also need to restart it. !!!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luminous</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2795500/Luminous/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take on 30 colorful levels in Luminous! This light-based puzzle game requires careful thinking and observation as you race your way to the finish and set new records. Lighting is the key! Lights will both open paths and close them off, your job is to make sure they are all in their proper state in order to open a path to the end.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hentai Clicker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2708030/Hentai_Clicker/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Hentai clicker is an relaxing idle game where you get to click and dress your waifu as you please.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>• Interactivity whit the girl<br/>• customizable girl<br/>• Secret items.......<br/>• One handed gameplay<br/>• Content updates<h2 class="bb_tag">Future</h2>What we are planning to add to the game in the future<br/>• More interactivity<br/>• More clothes<br/>• More Upgrades						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunt Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778030/Hunt_Together/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778030/extras/HEADER_Hunt_Together_600x140.png?t=1707415237"><h2 class="bb_tag">Challenge your friends in a PvP VR Horror game!</h2><br/>Hunt Together is a multiplayer VR game offering two Player vs Player modes, in which you take on the role of the bold Hunter or the terrifying Ghost. Your task will be to defeat your opponent with the help of numerous skills, items and usable environmental elements 🛠️ The arenas of your battles are spooky, chilling locations, such as an abandoned mine, a haunted mansion or a forgotten orphanage. <br/><br/>In addition to being able to face your friends in the Elimination Mode (1v1) or the Hide and Seek Mode (1v3), you also can acquire new skins for your favorite characters and develop their skills through a progression system.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778030/extras/HTGIF.gif?t=1707415237"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778030/extras/HEADER_Features_600x140.png?t=1707415237"><br/>• Challenge your friends in a spooky horror PvP system with 1v1 and up to 1v3 modes<br/>• Two unique classes with dedicated skills and items<br/>• A suspenseful vibe of psychological horror<br/>• Haunted locations abound with possibilities and usable environment elements<br/>• Skins to customize your favorite character<br/>• Events and updates with new content to the game						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Inquisitor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1880470/The_Inquisitor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/the-inquisitor-intro.gif?t=1707415647"><br/><br/><strong>The Inquisitor</strong> is a story-driven, dark fantasy adventure game with action elements, that compels you to face difficult moral choices. The game is set in an alternative version of (religious) reality. Inspired by bestselling Inquisitor book series by Jacek Piekara. Once nailed to the cross and near death, Jesus becomes consumed by utter rage. He breaks free and unleashes violent vengeance on all the non-believers. Centuries pass and now an army of zealot Inquisitors brutally enforce the faith in this blood-soaked Church.<br/><br/>You are Mordimer Madderdin, an Inquisitor in God's service, sent to the town of Koenigstein which is plagued by a series of mysteries and sin. Solve the various cases and crimes of those who have transgressed against the faith, all while uncovering the truth of a darker evil from another realm that is trying to enter the world of the living.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/BeTheUltimate_EN.png?t=1707415647"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/be-the-ultimate-holy-judge-and-jury.gif?t=1707415647"><br/><br/>Be the ultimate Holy Judge and Jury: Your role as an Inquisitor is to maintain order and enforce the faith in God. But the world is full of sinners who have lost their way. Decide the fates of those you judge in multiple story-driven cases and missions. This is a world where morality and what is right have long strayed from each other. So, will you show mercy or undying belief in The Holy Law?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/MorallyTainted_EN.png?t=1707415647"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/morally-tainted-non-linear-tale.gif?t=1707415647"><br/><br/>A morally tainted, non-linear tale: This is a dark and gritty story centered around a religion preaching revenge and violence. Multiple branching story choices will test your morality. Choose your path and decide what kind of Inquisitor you will be - one of pity or one of retribution - and ultimately what mark you will leave on this world.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/EnlightenedSleuthing_EN.png?t=1707415647"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/enlightened-sleuthing.gif?t=1707415647"><br/><br/>Enlightened sleuthing: Mordimer has unique skills and abilities that allow him to solve the various crimes and mysteries that have befallen Koenigstein. Track down and interrogate suspects. Discover the hidden truths of the city and its inhabitants. Piece together the evidence and make your final judgments.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/DelveInto_EN.png?t=1707415647"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/delve-into-the-unworld.gif?t=1707415647"><br/><br/>Delve into the Unworld: Unbeknownst to those around him, Mordimer has the ability to enter the mysterious Unworld. There he can discover the deeper secrets that suspects have tried to hide in their souls. But there is a grave risk when venturing into this world and the dark force which reigns supreme here will do everything it can to destroy you for stepping foot into its realm.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/Persuasive_EN.png?t=1707415647"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/persuasive-interrogations.gif?t=1707415647"><br/><br/>Persuasive interrogations: The 1500’s remain a cruel era of justice. As an Inquisitor, you have free rein to use whatever methods and tools deemed necessary to persuade suspects to reveal ‘the truth’. These optional interrogations date back to the times of the real Inquisition and it’s up to you to decide if and how much force to apply to those under your investigation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/LetYourSword_EN.png?t=1707415647"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1880470/extras/let-your-sword-do-the-talking.gif?t=1707415647"><br/><br/>Let your sword do the talking: Sometimes a tongue just needs to be cut right out in order to loosen it. A full sword-based combat system means various cases will let or even require you to use brute force. Master your blade, find your openings, and use your enemy’s weak points against them.<h2 class="bb_tag">Other recommended games from Kalypso Media</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1287840/Disciples_Liberation/" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1287840/Disciples_Liberation/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coupling</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2753220/Coupling/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2753220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Blue and Pink</strong> are trapped in an underground cave where the only way out is via color-code portals. Help them navigate the tricky, sometimes hazardous environment to get back to the surface world.<br/><br/><strong>Swing</strong> you way through the cave towards your objective. If you mess up a swing, simply undo.<br/><br/><strong>Interact</strong> with the environments and solve the puzzle. Be careful, some of them are dangerous.<br/><br/><strong>Collect</strong> stars to perfect your playthrough.<br/><br/><strong>Enter</strong> the portals to get one step closer to the surface world!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Bots VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/874440/Border_Bots_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/874440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Border Bots VR is a puzzle simulation set on a future earth where AI is in control. As a human border agent, you begin a new role as a booth operator at an AI travel border. Interact and check over a variety of robots as they try to get through security. Some of their credentials might not be up to scratch, it's up to you to make sure they get the stamp of approval.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/874440/extras/Steam-banners-BB---ENG_V2Analyse-Documents.png?t=1707411689"><br/><br/>Step into the booth as a border control agent and swiftly process robots by analysing their documents for discrepancies, oddities, undeclared modifications and contraband! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/874440/extras/Steam-banners-BB---ENG_V2Booth-and-Apartment-Upgrades-.png?t=1707411689"><br/><br/>Earn credits through challenging gameplay to purchase booth upgrades to keep yourself ahead of the competition. You can also spend your credits on apartment customisations and bring your space to life!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/874440/extras/Steam-banners-BB---ENG_V2Quirky-Robots!.png?t=1707411689"><br/><br/>Meet and interact with a variety of quirky robots at the booth and in your apartment! Come face-to-face with sentient appliances as you discover more about their newfound consciousness and colourful personalities.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/874440/extras/Steam-banners-BB---ENG_V2Variety-of-gadgets.png?t=1707411689"><br/><br/>Use a variety of tactile gadgets in VR to examine robots at the booth. You'll need different tools for inspection including a 3D printer, Contraband Detector, Stun Gun, Barcode Scanner and much more.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUTRIDERS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/680420/OUTRIDERS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/680420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/680420/extras/GIF2---1-3-coop-v1.gif?t=1707490932"><br/>OUTRIDERS is a 1-3 player co-op RPG shooter set in an original, dark and desperate sci-fi universe. <br/><br/>As mankind bleeds out in the trenches of Enoch, you’ll create your own Outrider and embark on a journey across the hostile planet. <br/><br/>With rich storytelling spanning a diverse world, you’ll leave behind the slums and shanty towns of the First City and traverse forests, mountains and desert in the pursuit of a mysterious signal. <br/><br/>Combining intense gunplay with violent powers and an arsenal of increasingly twisted weaponry and gear-sets, OUTRIDERS offers countless hours of gameplay from one of the finest shooter developers in the industry – People Can Fly.<h2 class="bb_tag">INTENSITY OF A SHOOTER, DEPTH OF AN RPG</h2>OUTRIDERS’ brutal and bloody combat combines frenetic gunplay, violent powers and deep RPG systems to create a true genre hybrid.<h2 class="bb_tag">A DARK AND DESPERATE JOURNEY</h2>Discover the hostile planet of Enoch as you embark on a journey to the source of a mysterious signal.<h2 class="bb_tag">DYNAMIC 1-3 PLAYER CO-OP </h2>Play single-player or join up to two friends in drop-in drop-out co-op as you tackle the horrors of a hyper-evolved planet.<h2 class="bb_tag">FOUR UNIQUE CLASSES</h2>Create and customise your own Outrider and choose from four unique classes each with its own skill tree to define your own playstyle.<h2 class="bb_tag">SCAVENGE &amp; ADAPT</h2>Customise and upgrade your Outrider with countless items of mod-able guns and gear. Now with full and entirely free Transmog.      <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/680420/extras/GIF6-Class-Select-v2.gif?t=1707490932"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUTRIDERS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/680420/OUTRIDERS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/680420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/680420/extras/GIF2---1-3-coop-v1.gif?t=1707490932"><br/>OUTRIDERS is a 1-3 player co-op RPG shooter set in an original, dark and desperate sci-fi universe. <br/><br/>As mankind bleeds out in the trenches of Enoch, you’ll create your own Outrider and embark on a journey across the hostile planet. <br/><br/>With rich storytelling spanning a diverse world, you’ll leave behind the slums and shanty towns of the First City and traverse forests, mountains and desert in the pursuit of a mysterious signal. <br/><br/>Combining intense gunplay with violent powers and an arsenal of increasingly twisted weaponry and gear-sets, OUTRIDERS offers countless hours of gameplay from one of the finest shooter developers in the industry – People Can Fly.<h2 class="bb_tag">INTENSITY OF A SHOOTER, DEPTH OF AN RPG</h2>OUTRIDERS’ brutal and bloody combat combines frenetic gunplay, violent powers and deep RPG systems to create a true genre hybrid.<h2 class="bb_tag">A DARK AND DESPERATE JOURNEY</h2>Discover the hostile planet of Enoch as you embark on a journey to the source of a mysterious signal.<h2 class="bb_tag">DYNAMIC 1-3 PLAYER CO-OP </h2>Play single-player or join up to two friends in drop-in drop-out co-op as you tackle the horrors of a hyper-evolved planet.<h2 class="bb_tag">FOUR UNIQUE CLASSES</h2>Create and customise your own Outrider and choose from four unique classes each with its own skill tree to define your own playstyle.<h2 class="bb_tag">SCAVENGE &amp; ADAPT</h2>Customise and upgrade your Outrider with countless items of mod-able guns and gear. Now with full and entirely free Transmog.      <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/680420/extras/GIF6-Class-Select-v2.gif?t=1707490932"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking For Cats In a Badly Drawn Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2795860/Looking_For_Cats_In_a_Badly_Drawn_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Welcome to the badly drawn forest full of cute cats!</strong></h2><br/>🐈‍ This game has 3 different levels, in a forest theme. 😺 Try to find 100 kitties in each level! Click on them to color them!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795860/extras/FlyGif.gif?t=1707430802"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🐱 Look for kitties in the woods.<br/></li><li>😹 Look for kitties in the cabin.<br/></li><li>😺 Look for them in the snow.<br/></li><li>😹 Look for kitties at the lake.<br/></li><li>🙀 Look for kitties in the mountains.</li></ul><br/>🐱‍ Look inside, around mountain tops and in the woods, but be careful, some kitties hide too well!<br/><br/>Key features:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>😹 300 different kitties to find!<br/></li><li>🙀 There are hints if there are difficulties!<br/></li><li>🐱‍ There is a zoom function to help you see the kitties!</li></ul><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795860/extras/Cats.png?t=1707430802"><br/><br/>👓 Use your imagination and a sharp eye to spot all the cats in the most unusual situations!<br/><br/><br/><a href="http://store.steampowered.com/developer/lostvolbytesgames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795860/extras/SubscribeToPublisher.png?t=1707430802"/></a> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
