<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III - BlackCell (Season 2)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731840/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III__BlackCell_Season_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Get Call of Duty® Points* and in-game content for Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III and Call of Duty®: Warzone™.<br>
<br>
Offering includes:<br>
<br/>
- Battle Pass for Season 2<br/>
- 20 Battle Token Tier Skips<br/>
<br/>
Exclusive BlackCell Sector on the Battle Map:<br/>
<br/>
- 1100 Call of Duty® Points<br/>
- BlackCell Operator<br/>
- Assault Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Battle Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Finishing Move<br/>
<br/>
- BlackCell Bonus Topper with 11 additional reactive Operator skin alternatives and 6 Weapon Blueprints with Tracers.<br/>
<br/>
Activision may update, replace, or remove this in-game content at any time.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Touhou Danmaku Kagura Phantasia Lost</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2190220/Touhou_Danmaku_Kagura_Phantasia_Lost/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							『Touhou Danmaku Kagura Phantasia Lost』is a rebuild of Touhou Project's first officially approved smartphone rhythm game "Touhou Danmaku Kagura" as a standalone version.<br/><br/>Play Danmaku Kagura and collect the Mitama Cards, the Fragments of Memories to find the key to rebuild the now barren Phantasia.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Two different rhythm game experiences</h2></strong><br/>■Kagura Stage<br/>- In this mode you hit the notes at the right moment!<br/>- You can stack up combos and get a high score by hitting the notes consecutively, coming through the 6 lanes.<br/>- Over 160* arranged Touhou music will be playable with 4 different difficulties!<br/>*Includes music from paid DLCs<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/extras/kagura.gif?t=1707324790"><br/><br/>■Danmaku Stage<br/>- A totally new game experience that combines Danmaku shoot 'em up &amp; Rhythm games!<br/>- Hit the notes on the sides rhythmically and deal great damage to the boss!<br/>- Complete missions set for each stages and beat the stage!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/extras/danmaku.gif?t=1707324790"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Wide Variety of Music</h2></strong><br/>Contains 68 songs including the original Touhou music.<br/>Scheduled to release 4 Music Pack DLCs (A total of 102 scores)!!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/extras/songsEN1.png?t=1707324790"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/extras/songsEN2.png?t=1707324790"><br/><br/>Additionally, free DLCs also planned for release. The first will include Toby Fox &amp; ZUN’s collaboration song ‘U.N. Owen Was Hero?’, releasing February 8th!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/extras/FlanUndyne_21.png?t=1707324790"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2></strong><br/>To rebuild Phantasia, Reimu journeys to find the Fragments of Memories.<br/>The key to rebuilding is Danmaku Kagura.<br/>To rebuild the Phantasia and unveil the truth of its destruction, Reimu have to gather Mitama cards, the Fragments of Memories.<br/>Reimu's unending journey, begins.<br/><br/>Marisa begins her own journey to find Reimu<br/>Will the two, ever meet eye to eye?						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1707227820"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal from ECHOS</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1707227820"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about playtesting opportunities, dev news, limited edition merch and more.<h2 class="bb_tag">Wishlist &amp; Follow on Steam</h2>Make sure to wishlist and follow the game for the latest updates. Due for Release early Q2-Q3 2023.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vampire: The Masquerade - Justice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2431700/Vampire_The_Masquerade__Justice/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_Venice.gif?t=1707322060"><br/><br/>Become a vampire. Strike from the darkness and drink the blood of your prey. Use stealth, persuasion, and an arsenal of upgradable abilities to sneak past enemies undetected or punish the guilty in the seedy backstreets of nighttime Venice.<br/><br/><strong>Vampire: The Masquerade - Justice</strong> is an open-ended, narrative Adventure RPG set in the World of Darkness universe. You have the power to strike fear into the hearts of a criminal underworld as an untraceable shadow, picking off targets one-by-one.<h2 class="bb_tag">STEALTH IS YOUR WEAPON</h2>Shadows are your ally. Take to the rooftops and seek new paths away from enemy eyes. Use Shadow Traps to snatch up unsuspecting prey and drag them into Oblivion. Activate Cloak of Shadows and slip unseen through enemy defenses. In Vampire: The Masquerade - Justice, stealth is your weapon.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_BloodDrinking.gif?t=1707322060"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_sneaky.gif?t=1707322060"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A POWERFUL VAMPIRE</h2>Punish the guilty with brutal abilities. Launch yourself towards opponents with immense force or boil their insides with Cauldron of Blood. Approach from behind and sink in your fangs to stock up on blood. Load your crossbow with special bolts to kill, distract or knock out guards from afar. Dish out Justice with a vengeance.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_BloodDrinking_2.gif?t=1707322060"><h2 class="bb_tag">LEVEL UP AND EXPLORE</h2>The dark skies of Venice provide ample opportunity to level up powers and build a character suited to your playstyle. Tackle side-missions away from the campaign to earn more experience. Convince NPCs to aid your quest, solve puzzles, uncover collectibles and test yourself with optional tasks in each mission.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_update.gif?t=1707322060"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_enviornement.gif?t=1707322060"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXIT KUN</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781370/EXIT_KUN/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a game of finding differences and observing. Our game challenges players to carefully observe and spot the distinctions that lead them to the elusive "Exit KUN."<br>
<br>
Game Overview:<br>
<br>
You find yourself trapped in an enigmatic underground labyrinth, and your only goal is to reach "Exit KUN." The journey demands keen observation of your surroundings. Every detail matters, and anomalies could be your key to progress.<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br>
<br/>
Observe Carefully: Scrutinize your surroundings to uncover anomalies that may guide your way or pose a threat.<br/>
Turn Back if Needed: If anomalies are detected, swift decision-making is crucial. Turn back immediately to avoid unforeseen consequences.<br/>
Forward Momentum: Should your observation reveal no anomalies, press forward. <br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Developer Notes:<br/>
This game is inspired by Exit 8. You are free to create, upload, and monetize videos and other content featuring Game on platforms such as YouTube, Twitch, and other video-sharing websites. The characters, places, and elements involved in the game are fictitious. Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, or events is purely coincidental.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soak &amp; Splash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2051500/Soak__Splash/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2051500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the Soak &amp; Splash! Get ready to sweat, socialize, and have a blast with your friends in this unique game that combines the best of traditional sauna culture with modern party fun.<br>
<br>
First, step into the steamy sauna and feel the heat and humidity envelop your body.<br>
<br>
Once everyone is inside, it's time to start the fun. You can start by whisking each other with broom.<br>
<br>
Feeling competitive? You can also fight with other players with sauna equipment. Or you can simply relax and enjoy the company of your friends, chatting, singing, or telling jokes.<br>
<br/>
Finally, when you've had enough of the sauna, you can cool off in the nearby pool or shower.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, this game is all about having fun, bonding with your friends, and experiencing the unique benefits of sauna culture. So why wait? Download game and get ready to sweat, laugh, and enjoy life to the fullest!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egg</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2784840/Egg/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2784840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><h2 class="bb_tag">About this game!</h2></strong><br/><br/>&gt; <strong>Egg</strong> is an interactive clicker game where you need to click egg to earn more eggs.<br/><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Features!</h2></strong><br/><br/>&gt; This game supports mouse and keyboard.<br/>&gt; This game supports gamepad (use <strong>A</strong> button on joystick to click).<br/>&gt; This game uses best HD quality textures that is possible to create.<br/>&gt; Runs on every hardware. Even on BESM.<br/>&gt; Supports all screen resolutions.<br/>&gt; Supports Windows 10/11 and so on.<br/>&gt; If you don't like the game you can always easily refund it.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/315210/Suicide_Squad_Kill_the_Justice_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Rocksteady Studios, the creators of the Batman: Arkham series, Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is a genre-defying third-person action shooter where the ultimate band of misfits must do the impossible to save the world: Kill the Justice League.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/SSKTJL_Intro.gif?t=1706907136"><br/>Join the newly “recruited” members of Amanda Waller’s infamous Task Force X (aka the Suicide Squad), Harley Quinn, Deadshot, Captain Boomerang and King Shark, as they set out on an impossible mission to Kill the Justice League. Drop into an expansive and dynamic open-world Metropolis ravaged by Brainiac’s invasion and terrorized by the heroes who once protected it. <br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/Traversal_2.gif?t=1706907136"><br/>Each Squad member brings their own traversal mechanics to help them navigate a sprawling and battle-torn Metropolis, combining free-roaming exploration and combat verticality for an unforgettable experience. Players are free to experiment with a variety of different play styles to unleash maximum damage on their enemies. Whether in single player or online with up to three of your friends, players can take on this suicide mission their own way.<br/><br/>Post-launch, players can expect a continuously evolving Metropolis with free new playable villains, environments, weapons, in-game events, and more, all included with purchase of the base game.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788630/Nothing_Together/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play together. Maybe.<br/><br/>Just do Nothing as the timer goes up and climb the leaderboards. If you do Something, you lose.<br/><br/>Play in <strong>Together </strong>mode, where up to 20 players unite to do Nothing, or compete with other players in <strong>Battle Royale</strong> to find out who's the best at doing Nothing!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161700/Persona_3_Reload/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a transfer student thrust into an unexpected fate when entering the hour "hidden" between one day and the next. Awaken an incredible power and chase the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fight for your friends, and leave a mark on their memories forever. <br/><br/>Persona 3 Reload is a captivating reimagining of the genre-defining RPG, reborn for the modern era.<br/><br/>Key Features: <br/>- Experience the pivotal game of the Persona series faithfully remade with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, and signature stylish UI. <br/><br/>-Fully immerse yourself in an emotional, gripping journey with new scenes, character interactions, and additional voiceover.<br/><br/>- Choose how to meaningfully spend each day through various activities, from exploring the Port Island to forging genuine bonds with beloved characters.<br/><br/>- Build and command your optimal team to take down otherworldly Shadows and climb closer to the truth.<br/><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Deluxe Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook: Filled with 64 pages of character art, concept art, backgrounds and other illustrations from the game!<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack: Listen to newly arranged tracks from the original Persona 3 plus all-new tracks from Persona 3 Reload, presented by the Atlus sound team for a total of 60 new songs.</li></ul><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Premium Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack<br/></li><li>Persona 3 Reload DLC Pack:  P5R Phantom Thieves Costume Set, P5R Shujin Academy Costume Set, P5R Persona Set 1, P5R Persona Set 2 , P5R BGM Set, P4G Yasogami High Costume Set, P4G Persona Set</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonbreaker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/845890/Moonbreaker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/845890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Moonbreaker is a turn-based strategy, tactical skirmish game developed by Unknown Worlds, the team behind the Subnautica series. It is designed to be a true digital miniatures experience, set in an expansive sci-fi universe crafted by best-selling sci-fi and fantasy author, Brandon Sanderson. Through approachable turn-based competitive gameplay, immersive art, captivating lore, and deep customization, Moonbreaker offers a variety of gameplay experiences for all types of players.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/845890/extras/MB_GIF_1_TableTop@615x200.gif?t=1706814698"><br/><br/><strong>TURN-BASED, TABLETOP TACTICS:</strong> Lead your Units in fast-paced, turn-based strategic skirmishes. Play against other players, against AI, or in the single-player roguelike adventure mode “Boss Run.” It’s quick to pick up, hard to put down.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/845890/extras/MB_GIF_3_Roster@615x200.gif?t=1706814698"><br/><br/><strong>BUILD YOUR ROSTER:</strong> No two Units are alike and no two Rosters play alike. Each Unit has its own special set of abilities, playstyle, personality, and more. Create various Rosters of diverse Units to experience fresh dynamics and build the ultimate team. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/845890/extras/MB_GIF_2_Paint@615x200.gif?t=1706814698"><br/><br/><strong>PAINT YOUR CREW:</strong> Harness your creativity with Unit painting, designed to capture the feel of real miniature painting – without the real-world limitations. Professional digital painting tools go beyond what is traditionally possible (undo! mask! zoom!), creating the perfect space for blissful player expression.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/845890/extras/MB_GIF_4_Reaches@615x200.gif?t=1706814698"><br/><br/><strong>DISCOVER THE REACHES:</strong> Crafted by beloved fantasy author Brandon Sanderson, The Reaches is filled with vibrant, diverse characters and cultures. Unravel the vast world of Moonbreaker through Audio Dramas by award-winning author Dan Wells, fully-voiced in-game dialogue - performed by renowned voice actors - and an unlockable Codex full of lore.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boxes: Lost Fragments</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2019810/Boxes_Lost_Fragments/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2019810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FggGzdma9mA" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2019810/extras/discord.png?t=1706879962"/></a><br/><br/><strong>As a legendary thief, your next assignment lures you into a grand and lavish mansion. There you find a series of puzzle boxes, designed for an unknown purpose.</strong><br/><br/>Suddenly, you realize that this is no ordinary building and that you are no longer in control of what is unfolding, and perhaps never were. What should have been a quick in-and-out, turns into your own harrowing struggle for freedom and answers. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2019810/extras/clockworkDivider.png?t=1706879962"><br/>Inspired by the cryptic atmosphere, intricate machinery, and smooth controls of the best room escape games, we have created a diverse set of original puzzle levels that will test your resolve and skills to navigate this mysterious and compelling journey. Each level is beautiful, unique, and a true delight to explore and figure out.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLCARD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1201540/HELLCARD/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Hellcard</strong> is a <strong>cooperative roguelike deckbuilder</strong> that can be played in both <strong>Singleplayer </strong>and <strong>Multiplayer </strong>modes. The game takes place in the paper dungeons known from Book of Demons, and its main mechanics revolve around deckbuilding and fast-paced tactical card battles. <br/><br/>If you are excited about <strong>HELLCARD</strong>, be sure to <strong>wishlist </strong>the game on Steam. Otherwise, consider wishlisting anyway - who knows, we might surprise you yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif5_600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/>What makes <strong>HELLCARD</strong> unique and different from other deck-building games is that <strong>monster placement actually matters</strong> and can be used to your advantage.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif4_600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>HELLCARD</strong> supports <strong>co-op battles</strong> with up to three heroes facing the Archdemon's hordes. In <strong>singleplayer mode</strong>, you can descend into the dungeons solo or recruit computer-controlled companions. In <strong>multiplayer mode</strong>, your friends or strangers can help you battle the hordes of hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif1-2-3-600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/r2g_logo_fixed.png?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>Return 2 Games</strong> is a series of unique mid-core games inspired by the golden days of PC gaming. Each R2G title is a tribute to a single hit game from the '90s: a reimagining of a single universal story for a brand-new audience, using modern means and innovative, often vastly simplified gameplay mechanics.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/pillars.png?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>HELLCARD</strong> was first envisioned as a new game mode inside the Book of Demons universe, but we soon realized that its design is huge and that it should be executed as a stand-alone spin-off game. If you want to learn more about Return 2 Games or support us in the development of the series, visit the <strong>Supporter Pack</strong> store page. On release, <strong>HELLCARD </strong>will be a part of it.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/706770/Return_2_Games_Supporters_Pack/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/706770/Return_2_Games_Supporters_Pack/</a><br/><strong>Book of Demons</strong>, the first part in the series is already here, be sure to check it out as it includes a free demo. <br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/449960/Book_of_Demons/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/449960/Book_of_Demons/</a><br/>Also, be sure to check out <strong>Book of Aliens</strong>, the second book in the series and a tribute to MicroProse’ UFO: Enemy Unknown that’s also in the works:<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1196230/Book_of_Aliens/" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1196230/Book_of_Aliens/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1131620/Dominion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Expand a small kingdom to a mighty Dominion!  <br/><br/>Play the Spiel des Jahres winning boardgame beloved by millions around the world. This is the officially licensed implementation.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Reigning.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Discover the game that defined a genre, Dominion was first to popularize deck-building and remains a staple of tabletop. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/GrowYourKingdom.png?t=1707010484">Collect as many Victory Points as you can by building a powerful deck. Your deck starts out a small sad set of Estates and Coppers, but you hope that by the end of the game it will be brimming with Gold, Provinces, and the inhabitants and structures of your kingdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/BuildEngine.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Choose wisely among the 10 cards available in the tableau to create the strongest combos to dominate your opponent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CollectAllExpansions.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Make your games more exciting with additional cards and rules from up to 15 expansions including the recent Plunder expansion! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/NearInfiniteVariety.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Over one hundred thirty-two septillion possible Kingdom combinations, 500+ cards, 15 and counting expansions, and ongoing promo packs make Dominion one of the most extensive and replayable boardgames in the hobby. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CompeteComputer.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Sharpen your skills with solitaire style solo play against a robust AI, with four levels of difficulty. Our innovative AI learns through self-play. Earn Achievements and win in Recommended Sets against each AI level. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/PlayWithFriends.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Join up to 6 players online through your device or pass and play among your friends. Play ranked or unranked matchmaking, with realtime and asynchronous modes. Set up a private table for a family game, challenge a stranger in the lobby, or invite a friend!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Daily.png?t=1707010484"><br/>A daily ritual to relax with over a cup of coffee. Try the Daily Dominion, a free puzzle level available to players around the world. Practice your strategy to keep up a winning streak and climb the leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CrossPlatform.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Play from any supported device, whenever you want, after verifying your email in-game. Join games with opponents on platforms other than your own to enjoy the largest possible multiplayer pool and speedy matchmaking. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/JoinCommunity.png?t=1707010484"><br/>With an active Discord and online community, make new friends or challenge new people to a game. Export and share kingdoms and game summaries to compare strategies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/FreeToPlay.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Download the game that started it all for free! The base set of Dominion is available at no charge. Try the rotation of expansion cards in the Daily at no cost once per day. Jump into a lobby game with expansions enabled to try before you buy. Only the host needs to own the expansions.    <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Intro.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Learn the ropes in this easy to pick-up, hard to master title. Play one of the most highly regarded strategy tabletop games of all time through our simple tutorial.  The core loop is easy to follow, but offers a wealth of strategy to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>1-6 player</strong> support<br/></li><li><strong>500 </strong> plus <strong>cards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Solo play</strong> against four AI difficulties<br/></li><li><strong>Async </strong>&amp; <strong>real-time</strong> multiplayer<br/></li><li><strong>Ranked</strong> &amp; <strong>unranked</strong> matchmaking<br/></li><li><strong>Lobby</strong> &amp; <strong>Private game</strong> tables<br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform multiplayer</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform purchases</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Daily challenge</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Challenging AI</strong> that learns through self-play<br/></li><li><strong>Recommended Sets</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Customize</strong>, save &amp; share <strong>Kingdoms</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Achievements</strong>, <strong>Stats </strong>&amp; <strong>Leaderboards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Pass &amp; Play</strong> mode<br/></li><li>Automated <strong>score-keeping</strong> &amp; hints<br/></li><li><strong>Smart-play</strong> options to streamline gameplay<br/></li><li><strong>Jumbo mode</strong> for readability on phones<br/></li><li><strong>Turbo mode</strong> to zoom through games quickly<br/></li><li><strong>Tutorial</strong> &amp; <strong>Rules</strong><br/></li><li><strong>4 languages</strong>: English, Japanese, German, French<br/></li><li><strong>15 expansions</strong> plus three promo packs </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Awards for the Boardgame</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Awards.png?t=1707010484"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kādomon: Hyper Auto Battlers Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1985320/Kdomon_Hyper_Auto_Battlers_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Enter_a_new_world!.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/enter_new_world_final.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>Welcome to the world of Kādomon, a mysterious land where cute and quirky monsters roam freely. Journey through randomly generated regions, battling and collecting Kādomon on your quest to be the best.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Over_180_Kadomon.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/dex_final.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>There’s 180+ monsters to add to your Kādodex, and each Kādomon has 2 super rare misprints to discover! Find over 60 of these monsters and their misprints to build the ultimate unstoppable team in the Kādomon prologue!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Battle_with_Unique_Monsters.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/unique_mon_final.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>All Kādomon have special characteristics, such as activated abilities, passive abilities and different typings (there’s 12 types in total!). Synergise your Kādomon’s attacks and create a super effective combo of monsters. Grow even stronger with every battle by levelling-up and evolving your team!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Experience_Hyper_Evolutions.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/exp_hyper.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>Once fully evolved, every Kādomon has the chance to get HYPER! Acquire very rare items that allow your Kādomon to break their limits and discover a hyper-powerful 4th form! With brand new designs and souped-up stats, you’ll be able to tackle the greatest of challenges, in the Kādomon prologue you will be able to discover Hyper Evolution for every starter Kādomon! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Fight_BIG_bosses!.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/big_bosses.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>Battle your team against elite enemies and bosses. Get your team ready to fight against MEGA opponents, and unlock brand new Kādomon if you win! Remember, there is always a greater foe to test your strength!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Discover_Secrets_.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/Discover_Secrets_final.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>The Kādomon world is bustling with secrets, including random events that will change the tide of battle! In the Early Access release, experiment with different items and monsters, Kādomon might evolve in different ways, and if you’re lucky you might just encounter a Legendary Kādomon to join your team…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/shonnkknk.png?t=1706809791"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1985320/extras/shonnka.gif?t=1706809791"><br/><br/>In between battles, take a mosey around Shonkka's Shop! Here you can use the Money Berries you’ve earned to buy new Kādomon and items. Held items are incredibly useful to have as they give you permanent buffs or powerful single use effects when used wisely!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/881020/Granblue_Fantasy_Relink/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/881020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Story<br/>
Granblue Fantasy takes place in the Sky Realm, a world where myriad islands float in a great blue expanse. Take your role as captain of a skyfaring crew, joined by a scrappy little dragon named Vyrn and a young girl with mysterious powers named Lyria. Together you sail with a colorful cast of crewmates, including kings and misfits alike, for Estalucia, a fabled island beyond the end of the skies.<br/>
<br/>
In the Zegagrande Skydom, islands are guarded by powerful creatures known as primal beasts and winds carry tales of a secretive organization known as the Church of Avia. Unveil a web of intrigue reaching far beyond the borders of Zegagrande and engage in a battle for the fate of the Sky Realm itself.<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay<br/>
Engage in real-time combat with a party of four in this character action RPG—choose from a diverse roster of skyfarers, each with their own unique weapons, skills, and combat styles. Teamwork makes the dream work with party-based mechanics such as Link Attacks and Chain Bursts to help you crush foes in spectacular fashion. Tackle quests solo or with the help of others for up to 4-player co-op and take down treacherous foes to score rare loot to further enhance your gear. Every enemy and party formation has its own strengths and weaknesses—the key to victory lies in working out how these pieces fit together.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced combat not your thing? Assist modes can provide accessibility for gamers of all skill levels. Toggle on Full Assist to have all actions performed automatically during battle!<br/>
<br/>
The Sky Realm is rich in lore and history. Browse Lyria's journal at any point during the game to access a trove of writings on the world's peoples, places, and more. In addition to the wealth of side quests available, Fate Episodes allow you to delve into the backstories of each member of your crew!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlazBlue Entropy Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2273430/BlazBlue_Entropy_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/原创声明-英语.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗EN_.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>Charismatic character designs with unique aesthetic styles and dramatic animations create a flamboyant, awesome combat experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快的动作连招EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快动作连招.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>Smooth controls, infinite possibilities of combos, and realistic combat feedback. This is the roguelite game with the best action experience yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超多角色豪华制作EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/全员图618x346.jpg?t=1706765621"><br/>Ten playable characters with vibrant personalities, unique combat styles, and immersive voice-acting.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式自由定制EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式，自由定制en.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>There are hundreds of moves for you to build around, plus countless elemental effects and legacy skills passed between characters. The possibilities are infinite. Time to make the best fighter of your own!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/抉择拯救世界EN.png?t=1706765621"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/GIF-抉择拯救世界EN.gif?t=1706765621"><br/>In the future where the world has been plunged into chaos, people enter a cyberspace called ACE, seeking their last chance to resolve the crisis.<br/>If you are the only person in this world who knows the truth, how will you react?<br/>The ending is also the beginning. Your decision will decide humanity's future.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Dorado: The Golden City Builder - Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2410890/El_Dorado_The_Golden_City_Builder__Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1451470/El_Dorado_The_Golden_City_Builder/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1451470/El_Dorado_The_Golden_City_Builder/</a><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1505940/Orc_Warchief_Strategy_City_Builder/" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1505940/Orc_Warchief_Strategy_City_Builder/</a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>This is the prologue of our upcoming El Dorado: The Golden City Builder - the prologue is just part of the full game that will let you get to know the game before its official release and it's completely free.</strong></h2><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F2YPZ6fDBsh" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/extras/ElDorado-Discord.png?t=1706714077"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build the mightiest and most expansive empire of Yucatan</strong></h2>Your aim in the game of El Dorado: The Golden City Builder - Prologue, is to create the mightiest empire of the whole Yucatan peninsula. Develop your early small settlement into a city bustling with life and dripping with gold. Build, develop, manage your resources and appease the Gods. Dominate other newly rising or existing settlements of other families through conquest or peaceful talks. Diplomacy or blood… it is your choice.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/extras/El-Dorado-GIF_1-Build_the_mightiest_and_most_expansive_empire_of_Yucatan.gif?t=1706714077"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Become the architect of your mythical city</strong></h2>As the Leader, you will be responsible for every building built on your territory, such as sawmills, temples, housing, barracks and many more. Skillfully plan your city as every path may play a vital role in managing your city. Well-planned zones of your empire will have a special impact on the proper and quickly develop your city. The fate of the citizens depends on you.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/extras/El-Dorado-GIF_2-Become_the_architect_of_your_mythical_city.gif?t=1706714077"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Gather resources</strong></h2>There are many resources on your territory crucial for the development, conquest and keeping your empire stable. Some will be used for daily life, other resources will have a chance to become part of a variety of weapons – so vital to plan your skirmishes.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/extras/El-Dorado-GIF_3-Gather_resources.gif?t=1706714077"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Offer sacrifices to the Gods to earn their favor…</strong></h2>Without sacrifices, there is no game based on a mythical ancient tribe, right? God's favor is one of the basic and important quests in the game. Thanks to their approval your city will not only develop freely but also expand its borders and acquire greater military and political capabilities. Satisfy your Gods to avoid their wrath. You can make sacrifices through your Priest in places of worship such as temples. Choose an appropriate slave, organize a grand festival in honor of the chosen Deity and perform secret dark rituals to the delight of the audience. In return, you can expect divine protection from different cataclysms or an increase in yields from your farms and fields.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/extras/El-Dorado-GIF_4-Offer_sacrifices_to_the_Gods_to_earn_their_favor….gif?t=1706714077"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>… or prepare for their wrath</strong></h2>Gold, riches, extraordinary development… it can’t be that easy. Each repeating or grand one-time festival requires sacrifices. If you happen to forget about worship, the Deities will send many cataclysms to your empire or other problems that will hinder your development. Some will be more or less taxing, but it is always better to evade a lone lightning bolt striking your home and setting the city ablaze or a huge tornado wreaking havoc in your city. Plan well what and when you offer your Gods as no mortal has survived their wrath.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/extras/El-Dorado-GIF_5-…_or_prepare_for_their_wrath.gif?t=1706714077"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Conquer and enslave neighboring people</strong></h2>Every gold is paid for in blood and war is the easiest way to get rich fast. Plunder resources, earn slaves and conquer new land needed for development. Gods are not the only worry, there are other peoples and tribes aiming for the same goal as you. Organize military expeditions, and reinforce the war front or defense lines with resources, which will help in your skirmishes with the enemy. Skillful resource management during war will have an impact on whether your people will come back as victorious conquerors bearing gifts or losers. Fight for the title of the mightiest ruler of the Golden City, El Dorado!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410890/extras/El-Dorado-Last.png?t=1706714077"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Do not lose yourself in pride.</strong></h2> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcast Tales: The First Journey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/882590/Outcast_Tales_The_First_Journey/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/882590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F7hSuXNCpMP" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/882590/extras/Discord_button_update.png?t=1706789517"/></a><br/><br/>The First Journey is just the beginning of a much grander experience (as the name sort of implies!). So, for now, familiarize yourself with the wasteland - you'll spend a lot more time in it when Outcast Tales is out!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Be tactical</strong> (or mash buttons;  might work just as well)!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/882590/extras/OT-GIF-Intro.gif?t=1706789517"><br/><br/>Robots, mutants, desert raiders: almost all enemies have something up their sleeve. So do your characters: some abilities are most effective in combination with others. Find your opponents' weaknesses, humiliate them on the battlefield, and never ponder the moral implications of your actions!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Use your strengths</strong> (if you can find any)!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/882590/extras/OT-GIF-Personas.gif?t=1706789517"><br/><br/>Combine class and personality types to give each of your characters a unique set of abilities. A Preacher Mercenary and an Antihero Mercenary will behave quite differently. Create a balanced crew, or just try out the wildest combinations to see how they turn out!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Overcome challenges</strong> (or mess everything up)!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/882590/extras/OT-GIF-Events.gif?t=1706789517"><br/><br/>Your characters will encounter dozens of unique situations that test their skill and wits. The Pacifist might talk his way out of trouble, the Egghead might try setting up traps, and the Daredevil will most likely just start blasting! In Outcast Tales, there are no wrong answers.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Develop relationships</strong> (like in a dating game, but not quite)!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/882590/extras/OT-GIF-Relations.gif?t=1706789517"><br/><br/>Your characters can develop deep bonds or even fall in love - but can also come to despise each other, all depending on your actions. Your journey can become a wholesome story about newfound friendship, or a gruesome tale of three strangers constantly at each other’s throats. Whatever sounds more fun…<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Let the chat join the action</strong> (or, more realistically, set you up)! </h2><br/>Connect the game to your Twitch account so that your viewers can influence the gameplay! The Twitch Integration feature will enable your chat to make crucial decisions during events, as well as choose your next destination or ability upgrade. And don't worry, your viewers won't ever try to harm you. They love you. Right..?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BioGun: Clinical Trial</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2778550/BioGun_Clinical_Trial/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778550/extras/BGN_Prologue_GIF_1.gif?t=1707142146"><br/><br/><strong>Transfer your progress from this prologue to the main game</strong><br/><br/>Join Bek on his journey to save the entire canine species from an extinction caused by the sinister Dooper Virus. Inject yourself into a zany hand-drawn world of germs, cells, and winding passages full of vibrant characters and ferocious bosses with a story that takes place inside our beloved pets.<br/><br/>Give your dog a fighting chance by aiding its immune system to fight off the Dooper Virus. Befriend cells on your journey, absorb new powers from vanquished foes and explore vital organs to prevent them from failing! Will you be the vaccine to save dog-kind from extinction or will DocX have to return to the drawing board?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778550/extras/BGN_Prologue_GIF_2.gif?t=1707142146"><br/><strong>Game Features</strong><br/><br/>Prologue version of the game BioGun. The story begins with clinical trial.<br/><br/>Fast paced side-scrolling 360 shooter action with all the modern gameplay mechanics you’ve come to expect and more.<br/><br/>Blast your enemies with an impressive array of weapons. Augment your DNA and modify your playstyle using Nano-Chips. <br/><br/>Take on bosses inspired by real diseases in uniquely designed encounters.<br/><br/>Complete side missions to aid Cells in need. Explore each organ to earn rewards and learn about the life forms that live there.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778550/extras/BGN_Prologue_GIF_3.gif?t=1707142146"><br/>Traverse a hand-drawn microscopic world full of traditionally animated cells, germs, viruses and bacteria. Meet the wondrous creatures, both friendly and hostile, that inhabit it. Discover the many secrets cleverly hidden in your dog's body.<br/><br/>You will be accompanied on your mission by a blood-pumping score by Juhani Junkala<br/><br/>Save humanity's best friend. Prove that you’re the vaccine that can put an end to the pet-demic. What are you waiting for? Put on your hazard suit and blast some viral scum! The fate of dog-kind is in your hands!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2772560/Supermarket_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This Prologue is a limited version of the full game to stop waiting and jump into running your supermarket already. Don't forget to wishlist the full game to continue your most fun supermarket experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Design your store, optimizing for efficiency and aesthetics. Determine where products are displayed, manage your aisles, and ensure a smooth shopping experience for your customers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Order stock using an in-game computer and anticipate the arrival of your next delivery. Unpack goods, organize them in your storage room and display them on shelves, fridges, and freezers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Read product barcodes, handle cash and credit card transactions, and ensure customers leave satisfied with their shopping and checkout experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier_Raw.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Navigate the complexities of a real-time market. Buy products when prices dip and determine the best-selling prices to balance customer satisfaction with profit margins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><br/>Wishlist the full game "Supermarket Simulator" where every decision matters. Will you rise to the occasion, transforming a modest establishment into a retail powerhouse, all while balancing customer satisfaction, finances, and mafia expectations?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Lily - Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2220360/Paper_Lily__Chapter_1/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Something terrible has happened. You can’t bear to think about it - but you can’t live like this anymore. You stopped attending school, you haven’t left your house in months, you have no reason to get out of bed anymore. There are no choices left.<br/><br/>No choice except... that strange golden letter.<br/><br/>It’s time to get your life back together. <br/><br/>One last try.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/divider.png?t=1706724298"><br/><br/>Paper Lily is a story-driven, psychological horror RPG where each puzzle has multiple solutions and outcomes. <strong>There is always another way.</strong><br/>Follow Lacie's story as you explore a dangerous hidden world, solve puzzles in multiple different ways, and face strange enemies. The game is playable in about 4 hours and contains multiple endings depending on your actions.<br/><br/>Paper Lily - Chapter 1 is the continuation to the prologue, <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1698960" rel="" target="_blank">Project Kat</a>, but it can also  be enjoyed without having played it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/lacie_sai_walk.gif?t=1706724298"><h2 class="bb_tag">Out of Context Features</h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple ways of solving puzzles!<br/></li><li>Touch grass, and trees<br/></li><li>Minigames where you press buttons and push boxes around<br/></li><li>Call your mother<br/></li><li>Harmless Snack™<br/></li><li>Various things made of paper<br/></li><li>Bunnies (or whatever those things are)<br/></li><li>Demons<br/></li><li>Fast demons<br/></li><li>Social anxiety simulation<br/></li><li>Table salt<br/></li><li>...Is that Kat? Nah, probably not<br/></li><li>Bathroom etiquette<br/></li><li>Death</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707277988"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707277988"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707277988"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707277988"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707277988"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707277988"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707277988"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707277988"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707277988"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707277988"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707277988"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707277988"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2072450/Like_a_Dragon_Infinite_Wealth/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/Accolades_616.png?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>EPIC EMOTIONAL DRAMA</strong><br/>Two larger-than-life heroes brought together by the hand of fate, or perhaps something more sinister…<br/><br/>Ichiban Kasuga, an unstoppable underdog who’s no stranger to crawling up from rock bottom, and Kazuma Kiryu, a broken man facing down his last days.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/2_Epic_Emotional_Drama.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>BEST-IN-CLASS RPG ACTION</strong><br/>Experience one-of-a-kind combat with dynamic, fast-paced RPG battles where the battlefield becomes your weapon, and anything goes. Adapt your party’s skills to the situation with outlandish jobs and customizations to strategically subdue enemies with over-the-top moves. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/3_Best_In_Class_RPG_Action.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>INFINITE ADVENTURE</strong><br/>Live it up in Japan and explore all that Hawaii has to offer in an adventure so big it spans the Pacific. Unforgettable moments await at every step of the journey with a unique mix of quests and activities to enjoy at your leisure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/4_Infinite_Adventure.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Deluxe Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Ultimate Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/>- Assorted Outfit Bundle: Customize your party's look with outfits &amp; swimwear<br/>- Sujimon &amp; Resort Bundle: Get legendary Sujimon, resort guests and special boosters<br/>- Yakuza CD Collection Set: Increase your in-game playlist with classic karaoke tracks						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apollo Justice: Ace Attorney Trilogy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2187220/Apollo_Justice_Ace_Attorney_Trilogy/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2187220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2187220/extras/13_Apollo_CustomImages_600x338.png?t=1706177279"><br/><br/>Apollo Justice's Legal Journey Begins Anew!<br/><br/>Join rookie attorney Apollo Justice and his mentor, the legendary Phoenix Wright, in this collection of 3 games! This title features the 14 episodes of "Apollo Justice: Ace Attorney", "Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney - Dual Destinies", and "Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney - Spirit of Justice", and the 2 previously DLC-only Special Episodes for a total of 16 episodes!<br/><br/>Also included is a mountain of extra goodies that's sure to satisfy any Ace Attorney fan!<br/><br/>Orchestra Hall - Listen to the in-game background music and select orchestral arrangements!<br/><br/>Art Library - View illustrations, design specs, commissioned pieces, and even the special Spirit of Justice Prologue anime!<br/><br/>Animation Studio - Play around with character animations and recreate your favorite scenes!<br/><br/>This collection supports Japanese, English, French, German, Korean, and Traditional and Simplified Chinese. Mix and match to play in whichever languages you'd like!<br/><br/>Immerse yourself in this beautiful collection as you shout "Objection!" in these newly renovated halls of justice!<br/><br/>Some of the contents of the games in this collection are presented as initially released to preserve the games as originally created.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summon Masters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2100140/Summon_Masters/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2100140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a card and board game with the following features:<br>
<br>
Deck Building: Players can build their own decks to battle with. Depending on different strategies and opponents, players can choose different cards to counter.<br>
<br>
Tactical Gameplay: The game uses a 3x10 chessboard, and players can freely place cards to fight. Players need to develop tactics and arrange card positions and usage order within limited space.<br>
<br>
Different Professions: Players can choose freely from four professions - swordsman, mage, monk, and archer. Each profession has different characteristics and skills, and players can choose according to their preferences and tactical needs.<br/>
<br/>
Competitive Battles: Players can battle with other players after building their decks, and it is fun to fight with other people. Through battles with other players, players can improve their strength and tactical skills.<br/>
<br/>
Team Dungeons: In addition to fighting against other players, players can also team up with others to challenge high-difficulty dungeons. Players need to defeat powerful bosses through cooperation and strategy to get more rewards and cards.<br/>
<br/>
Special Challenges: Players can participate in special rules challenges and use their intelligence to defeat other players. These special rules make the game more interesting and challenging, and players need to constantly think and try new strategies.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced: Each game is fast-paced (within 5 minutes), and can be played in short fragments of time. The fast pace of the game allows players to enjoy the game in a short time, while also being able to play at any time and anywhere.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2248950/TransSiberian_Railway_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take the helm of a classic Russian locomotive, discover the raw beauty and wildness of Siberia and try to survive on the longest railway line in the world. This is the Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator. A game for real adventurers!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/drinking1.gif?t=1707121961"><br/><br/>Complete the tutorial and the first kilometers of the route for free.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/explosion_gif.gif?t=1707121961"><br/><br/>The Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator offers amazing rail and survival challenges on real Russian dangerous routes. Feel what it is like to put your hands at the helm of a powerful freight locomotive and explore the untouched natural landscape that is sure to delight you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/shooting_gif.gif?t=1707121961"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Prologue features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Detailed simulation of driving a VL10 locomotive - the locomotive control is slightly simplified.<br/></li><li> Locomotive repair system - Manage and replace locomotive parts that are constantly wearing out.<br/></li><li> Train traffic simulation - Follow rail signs and signals to avoid derailment or damage to a part of the locomotive.<br/></li><li> Work system - Earn by completing transport orders. <br/></li><li> Game modes (Survival) and (Simulator). It is recommended to play in the (Survival) mode. This is the leading game mode that is constantly being developed. <br/>For players who are not interested in survival mechanics, a simple Simulator mode is available. <br/></li><li> Mafia system - Complete missions for the mafia to earn extra money.<br/></li><li> Survival system with statistics of hunger, thirst, alcohol, hangover, disease and hypothermia - Eat and drink to avoid death. <br/>Keep the right temperature so you don't freeze.<br/></li><li> Shooting system - Use your weapons for hunting and self-defense.<br/></li><li> Purchase and sales system - Buy various items, food, tools, weapons and ammunition.<br/></li><li> Locomotive inspection mode - Inspect the condition of locomotive parts and replace them in time to avoid damage.<br/></li><li> Dynamic weather system with day and night cycle - Survive extreme weather conditions.<br/></li><li> Route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Novosibirsk-Main) - scale 1:1. Buy the full version with the route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Krasnoyarsk).<br/></li><li> Police system - A corrupt militia watches over your movements.<br/></li><li> Much more to discover.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Universim</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/352720/The_Universim/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>WHAT WOULD YOU DO WITH THE POWER?</strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Play God!</strong> </h2>Guide your fledgling sentient species (lovingly called “nuggets”) from Stone Age cave painters to star-faring explorers.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-1-2d869427c7.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Wield godly power</strong></h2>Command more than 15 godly powers to guide, protect — or discipline — your followers. Create devastating tornadoes, smite naughty followers with lightning bolts, or shake and sunder the very earth. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-1-998341a4ac.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Watch your Nuggets grow and thrive</strong></h2>Observe Nuggets' every move as they work and fight to survive. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-537928a55b.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Evolve and advance through the ages</strong></h2>Research more than 200 technological and societal advancements. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-daca04b5ec.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Expand your power and colonize the galaxy</strong></h2>Discover and colonize a galaxy of procedurally generated planets, each with  unique ecosystems and challenges to conquer.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-be2f66969b.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Manage delicate ecosystems</strong></h2>Manage the delicate balance of planetary ecosystems to help nuggets thrive. Your decisions and your followers’ ' actions influence global climates and have real environmental consequences. (Try not to kill them in an ecological disaster — well, unless you want to, of course.)<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-0095b39c11.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>🔵Delve into the deeper mystery of your existence</strong></h2>Unravel the layers of a deeper cosmic story that challenges your perception of who and what you are — and reveals unexpected twists!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/ezgif-2-4830f44913.gif?t=1705993770"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>About This Game:</strong></h2><br/>The Universim is a strategy city builder game with “God” elements where you guide a civilization (Nuggets) from the Stone Age to the Space Age. Manage resources, dynamic challenges, and ensure your Nuggets can survive, thrive, and spread to the stars. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Animated_Planet_3.png?t=1705993770"><br/><br/>The Universim  features more than  200 research perks that will help you to shape your civilization. Be as benevolent or malevolent as you like to drive nuggets to evolve, advance, and expand. (Even the best civilizations need an occasional smiting).  <br/>Every planet in The Universim is procedurally generated and offers unique characteristics  and challenges, ensuring  that every world and every game is unique and engaging.  Ecological balance and resource management are critical to success. Nuggets have their own needs and behaviors you must attend to. Your guidance will shape how they deal with conflicts, natural disasters, alien creatures, and other civilizations. Their growth and evolution depends on you!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FSymAzCGWsk" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Crytivo_Discord.png?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FgUt5N68" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Discord_join.jpg?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://twitter.com/crytivo" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/Twitter.png?t=1705993770"/></a> <br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Feepurl.com%2FbKnqM1" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/352720/extras/News.png?t=1705993770"/></a><br/><br/>This game published by <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/franchise/Crytivo" rel="" target="_blank">Crytivo</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intravenous 2: Mercenarism</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2651330/Intravenous_2_Mercenarism/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608270/Intravenous_2/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Wishlist_Game.png?t=1705699394"><br/><br/>Step into the shoes of Gideon, a ruthless mercenary who cares about nothing but his wealth. Set two months before the events of Intravenous 2, you will take on seemingly simple jobs, the effects of which will ripple out and affect the main game's protagonist. But why should Gideon care? He's just in it for the money.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Stealth_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Stealth or Firepower:</strong> the choice is yours. Sneak through shadows, turn off the lights, pick doors, or unleash a hail of bullets. The game will adapt to your play style.<br/></li><li> <strong>Customize Your Skills:</strong> develop your skills the way you want to, whether it's mastering the art of stealth or becoming a gunslinging virtuoso.<br/></li><li> <strong>Bullet Time:</strong> Gideon is no stranger to stimulants that enhance his cognitive abilities - bending time to give him the edge in tense situations.<br/></li><li> <strong>Vast Arsenal:</strong> choose from firearms, gadgets, and a variety of ammo types to creatively tackle the challenge<br/></li><li> <strong>Weapon Modification:</strong> personalize each firearm with suppressors, laser sights, and more, tailoring your arsenal to the task at hand.<br/></li><li> <strong>Responsive AI:</strong> engage in intense combat with enemies that react to your actions, take cover, use tactics and call for backup.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2651330/extras/Action_Approach.gif?t=1705699394"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2744170/Artifact_SeekerPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/DS.png?t=1706492908"/></a><br/>The difference between the prologue version and the official version<br/>There is a special artifact in the prologue<br/>Characters: 2 in the prologue, at least 5 in the official version<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 3 in the final version.<br/>Systems: Tavern, Marketplace, and Endless Mode will be added to the game.<br/>Artifacts: More artifacts will be added to the game.<br/>Skills: More skills will be added in the official version.<br/>Affixes: More Affixes will be added in the official version.<br/>Events: There will be more interesting Events in the official version.<br/>Progress: No need to worry, all progress will be carry into the official version.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/11y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/1z.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/2y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/gif1.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/3y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong>[/b]<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/4y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/5y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><strong><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.png?t=1706492908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744170/extras/6y.gif?t=1706492908"><br/>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </img></img></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frostrain</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735630/Frostrain/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/01_Thumnail.png?t=1706325941"><h2 class="bb_tag">Roam the frozen world</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Roam_the_frozen_world.gif?t=1706325941"><br/>Climate change has turned the world white and frozen, and the only thing moving on the planet is you, your passengers, and your train. It's a dead world, but ironically, it's all the more fascinating for it. A vivid landscape awaits you to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Keep your passengers happy</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Keep_your_passengers_happy.gif?t=1706325941"><br/>The passengers on your train will work diligently at your command, but be careful: if you don't manage their happiness properly, they might throw you off the train.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build your own train with card decks</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Build_your_own_train_with_card_decks.gif?t=1706325941"><br/>Each time you pass through a city, you'll be able to add new train cars by launching a heavy lift drone. Be careful with each choice you make. If you are lucky, you'll be able to build a better, more synergized, happily-ever-after train deck, but it won't always go as you planned.<h2 class="bb_tag">Reach the Promised Land</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Reach_the_Promised_Land.gif?t=1706325941"><br/>Lead your passengers in search of the Promised Land, somewhere on the eastern edge of the world. But the journey to the Promised Land isn't all smooth and pleasant. You'll have to pass through toxic areas, and a severe storm is brewing behind you. Pay attention to your passengers' happiness levels and lead them safely to the Promised Land. The journey is in your hands.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoardLand</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735620/BoardLand/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Create your own strategy with the dice</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/extras/Cardnals_1.gif?t=1705310503"><br/><br/>The dice is rolled!<br/>Are you going to move? Are you going to act?<br/>Different effects are applied to each die, and the numbers determine your behavior.<br/>How do you combine numbers to get the best results?<br/>Every time you pick a number, you'll have to choose carefully.<h2 class="bb_tag">Make a powerful board by strengthening the tiles.</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/extras/Cardinals_2.gif?t=1705310503"><br/><br/>Tiles get more and more powerful!<br/>Every time you act on a tile, the tile gains experience, and the tile with enough experience is upgradeable.<br/>Combine tiles with multiple properties to create the best strategy, your own board<h2 class="bb_tag">Defeat the monsters and bosses</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735620/extras/Cardinals_3.gif?t=1705310503"><br/><br/>Monsters disturb you!<br/>Monsters can summon Fireballs, or they can curse and cause obstacles to certain tiles.<br/>You have to move and act with the dice, avoiding these patterns every time.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696480/Nothing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2696480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play. Or is it?<br>
<br>
Just do Nothing as the timer goes up. If you do Something, you lose.<br>
<br>
If you don't like doing Nothing, go play Something instead.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summoners War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2426960/Summoners_War/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2426960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>▶Features</strong><br/><strong>[Tactical RPG play]</strong><br/>Witness the dazzling display of each monster 's unique skills.<br/>23 different Rune sets to pick and choose additional abilities for your monsters!<br/>Come up with the best strategy to win battles in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[Endless Fun]</strong><br/>Decorate your Village, battle other summoners , explore dungeons , fight in PvP battles , expand your collection, train monsters , and more.<br/><br/><strong>[The Key of Colletion RPG : Massive Collection]</strong><br/>Fire, Water, Wind, Light and Dark!<br/>5 different attributes, and 1500 different monsters!<br/>Collect as many monsters as you can and win battles with your own decks .<br/><br/><strong>[Real-time Raid]</strong><br/>Battle as a team with your greatest monsters !<br/>A real-time battle with 3 users!<br/>Defeat the boss with your fellow Summoners using various tactics.<br/><br/><strong>[Homunculus]</strong><br/>The Forbidden Summoning Magic has finally been revealed!<br/>You can Evolve the skill of your choice with this special monster.<br/>Summon Homunculus and show off your strategy in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[All about Turn-Based RPG : World Arena]</strong><br/>Enjoy a real-time battle with Summoners worldwide!<br/>Experience a breathtaking battle that starts from Pick &amp; Ban.<br/>Reveal your unique strategy to the world and win battles .<br/><br/><strong>[Guild Content]</strong><br/>A sensational Guild PvP battle in the Isle of Conquest!<br/>Explore the Tartarus' Labyrinth and dungeons with Guild Members.<br/>Make your Guild the greatest of all.<br/><br/><strong>[Dimension Hole]</strong><br/>Fight against the ancient power emerged from a new dimension!<br/>Defeat the Ancient Guardians and meet the powerful monsters with new awakening power.<br/><br/><strong>[Artifact]</strong><br/>Artifacts are now dropped with MAX power-up levels!<br/>Summoners , fight against the powerful bosses and acquire Artifacts!<br/>Enhance your monsters with various sub properties of Artifacts.<br/><br/><strong>[Progression and Farming Structure Revamp]</strong><br/>Summoner progression structure renewed and content reward greatly improved!<br/>Dive into Summoners War and experience the enhanced progression system!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harmoni</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781170/Harmoni/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Harmoni is an open Source 4 Key Rhythm Game Made In Lua/Love2D!</strong><br/>Press DFJK (keybind settings not currently added) to press the notes.<br/><br/>Comes with 1 songs included.<br/><br/>Currently 1 additional Song Pack is available. (more will be available in the future)<br/>To download the Base Song pack, just run the game and press F1 in the Song Select menu to open the Song Packs Google Drive.<br/><br/>(currently the instructions.txt file included with the Base Song Pack is outdated, to install the Song Pack, download it, open it, and extract everything from inside the music.zip file to Harmoni’s Music folder (press F2 in the Song Select menu to open the Music folder.))						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Purrs in Heaven</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696770/Purrs_in_Heaven/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2696770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Poor Lanna has gone to heaven following a tragic accident. Fortunately, she has the chance to come back to life. Help the kitten pass all the tests and defeat the guardians, keepers of the 3 pieces of her soul. Do you accept the challenge?<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>    30 game levels.<br/></li><li>    Simple puzzles of increasing difficulty.<br/></li><li>    Hidden shmup mini game.<br/></li><li>    Unlockable challenges and difficult mode for the most skillful.<br/></li><li>    Beautiful pixel art.<br/></li><li>    Wonderful soundtrack inspired by Ghibli composers.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Eclipse Arcade: Q.P.I.D.</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2309240/Digital_Eclipse_Arcade_QPID/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2309240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2309240/extras/banner_600x359.png?t=1707322304"><br/><br/>Happy Valentine's Day! Q.P.I.D. is the latest release from Digital Eclipse Arcade, a series of all-new games inspired by classic '80s arcade vibes.<br/><br/>Like everyone else on the internet, Q.P.I.D. loves cats. Unfortunately, the cats that the Quadrangular Programmable Inversion Device has been sworn to protect have gotten themselves into places they shouldn't be. With nerves of steel and a heart of gold, Q.P.I.D. is determined to rescue as many of them as possible, even if he has to bend the laws of physics to do it. Toggle gravity, blast enemies, avoid hazards, and collect cats before your battery runs out. Part platformer, part puzzler, Q.P.I.D. delivers a hero who's state of the heart.<h2 class="bb_tag">Instructions</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Flip gravity to move objects, enemies, and obstacles<br/></li><li>Rescue cats on each level<br/></li><li>Collect all hearts for a perfect score<br/></li><li>Keep Q.P.I.D. juiced with charging stations</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Hazards &amp; Helpers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>LOLLIDROPS aren't tasty — they're nasty. These mines will explode when you get near, but they won't be triggered by swapping gravity.<br/></li><li>HEARTACHERS demand their personal space; get too close to these shuffling scorpions, and they'll zap you. They also devour hearts!<br/></li><li>BEAM UPS shoot deadly laser light straight out when they're activated — but you can flip their switches when you flip the gravity.<br/></li><li>WUVLIES make their way the only way they know how: End over end. You can blast these flipping foes, but beware — shortly after being incapacitated, they explode!<br/></li><li>BIG CRUSHERS do exactly what their name implies: They crush (on) you big time. Don't get trapped beneath them!<br/></li><li>HEARTIANS attack in swarms when disturbed and slow you down, so be ready to blast them all before they reach you.<br/></li><li>SPEED ROLLERS give you a turbo boost. Walk through a light-blue column and get ready for a rapid ride!<br/></li><li>BOUNCE PADS put a spring in your step, sending you skyward when shifting gravity might have some negative effects.<br/></li><li>TETHERS automatically collect nearby hearts. Avoid entering dangerous spaces just by tugging on these heartstrings.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Hints</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Q.P.I.D. might fall faster or slower than some of the enemies and obstacles. Use that to sneak past them during gravity shifts.<br/></li><li>Sometimes flipping gravity will put hearts right in the path of a Heartacher. Look for alternate locomotion paths like bounce pads and speed rollers to avoid that risk.<br/></li><li>Lollidrops can't be destroyed by blasting them, but they can be deflected with a barrage of shots. Use this to create opportunities to sneak past them. </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Controls</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Move: Joystick/WASD<br/></li><li>Blaster: Button 1/Mouse Button 1<br/></li><li>Flip Gravity: Button 2/Mouse Button 2<br/></li><li>Self Destruct: Button 1/Mouse Button 1 + Button 2/Mouse Button 2</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Additional Options</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>F1 toggles CRT scanlines on/off<br/></li><li>F2 toggles CRT curvature on/off<br/></li><li>F3 switches in window size in windowed mode<br/></li><li>Back button on controller accesses CRT/windowed options<br/></li><li>F9 resets the game<br/></li><li>Alt-Enter toggles between 16:9 fullscreen and 4:3 windowed mode</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">About Digital Eclipse Arcade</h2><br/>A series of throwback games made for the Digital Eclipse community, Digital Eclipse Arcade is a celebration of pure arcade gameplay. Sign up for the Digital Eclipse email newsletter to be the first to get exclusive drops.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai Summer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1323830/Shanghai_Summer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1323830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1323830/extras/Title_Screen_EN.gif?t=1707321776"><br/><br/><strong>The Story</strong><br/><br/>Shanghai, 2003<br/><br/>Suddenly, Baichuan senses something is not right with his life - sometimes, he feels he can see his memories, so real yet so unfamiliar. This all seems to begin with an unexpected invitation from Baichuan's ex-girlfriend, Qiuyu, who has been away for many years.<br/><br/>Twelve summer days, just like twelve lucid dreams...<br/><br/>"The time seems to be working anomalously on you."<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1323830/extras/Hospital_EN.gif?t=1707321776"><br/><br/><strong>The Characters</strong><br/><br/>Dream-chasing, freelancer artist - Fengyi;<br/>Troubled and misguided high school student - Xiaobo;<br/>A university student who is burdened by her family's issue - Jingxian.<br/>......<br/><br/>Even though their lives are a total mess, they still manage to carry on, embrace and accept their "regrets", and live to the fullest.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1323830/extras/Inqury_EN.gif?t=1707321776"><br/><br/><strong>The Gameplay</strong><br/><br/>Through the 'Topics' and 'Clues' gathered from everyday life, dive deep into the hearts and minds of your dearest friends.<br/><br/>To be comforted by them; To be inspired by them; To turn all the little things that happened in your life into your own strength, and eventually, at the finale of the twelfth night – <br/><br/>To " fix" the shattered dream.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1323830/extras/Street_EN.gif?t=1707321776"><br/><br/><strong>The Stages</strong><br/><br/>Classrooms, Bookstore "What-If", Neighbourhood Cafe...<br/><br/>Much of every boy and girl's life revolves around such a mundane city scene. And it is precisely within the mundanity that some new possibilities exist. The key to turning one's fate around may very much be held in the hand of someone passing by among the crowds on the streets...						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Touhou Danmaku Kagura Phantasia Lost</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2190220/Touhou_Danmaku_Kagura_Phantasia_Lost/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							『Touhou Danmaku Kagura Phantasia Lost』is a rebuild of Touhou Project's first officially approved smartphone rhythm game "Touhou Danmaku Kagura" as a standalone version.<br/><br/>Play Danmaku Kagura and collect the Mitama Cards, the Fragments of Memories to find the key to rebuild the now barren Phantasia.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Two different rhythm game experiences</h2></strong><br/>■Kagura Stage<br/>- In this mode you hit the notes at the right moment!<br/>- You can stack up combos and get a high score by hitting the notes consecutively, coming through the 6 lanes.<br/>- Over 160* arranged Touhou music will be playable with 4 different difficulties!<br/>*Includes music from paid DLCs<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/extras/kagura.gif?t=1707324790"><br/><br/>■Danmaku Stage<br/>- A totally new game experience that combines Danmaku shoot 'em up &amp; Rhythm games!<br/>- Hit the notes on the sides rhythmically and deal great damage to the boss!<br/>- Complete missions set for each stages and beat the stage!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/extras/danmaku.gif?t=1707324790"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Wide Variety of Music</h2></strong><br/>Contains 68 songs including the original Touhou music.<br/>Scheduled to release 4 Music Pack DLCs (A total of 102 scores)!!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/extras/songsEN1.png?t=1707324790"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/extras/songsEN2.png?t=1707324790"><br/><br/>Additionally, free DLCs also planned for release. The first will include Toby Fox &amp; ZUN’s collaboration song ‘U.N. Owen Was Hero?’, releasing February 8th!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2190220/extras/FlanUndyne_21.png?t=1707324790"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2></strong><br/>To rebuild Phantasia, Reimu journeys to find the Fragments of Memories.<br/>The key to rebuilding is Danmaku Kagura.<br/>To rebuild the Phantasia and unveil the truth of its destruction, Reimu have to gather Mitama cards, the Fragments of Memories.<br/>Reimu's unending journey, begins.<br/><br/>Marisa begins her own journey to find Reimu<br/>Will the two, ever meet eye to eye?						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jigsaw Puzzles Infinite</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1946140/Jigsaw_Puzzles_Infinite/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1946140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							If you like jigsaw puzzles - this is your game.<br/>Sit back, relax and build puzzles to your heart's content.<h2 class="bb_tag">What you get with Jigsaw Puzzle Infinite:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Infinite possibilities</strong>- Choose from one of the dozens of included puzzles or add your own images without any limits<br/></li><li><strong>Classic mode</strong> - Jigsaw puzzles you know and love. Take your time and build the puzzle with the help of useful sorting features<br/></li><li><strong>Sorting</strong> - Sort pieces by section, sort out edges, or just spread them out neatly <br/></li><li><strong>Zen Mode</strong> - Enter the flow and assemble the puzzle piece by piece<br/></li><li><strong>Pieces snap to each other </strong>and are not placed on a preset grid - just like real puzzles<br/></li><li><strong>Adjust difficulty </strong>- Freely choose number of pieces and snapping distance<br/></li><li><strong>Different piece shapes </strong>- Choose from multiple possible shapes of the pieces<br/></li><li><strong>Free camera movement </strong>- Zoom in and out, and move around the board freely <br/></li><li><strong>Every puzzle unique </strong>- Pieces are randomized each time new puzzle is generated<br/></li><li><strong>Never lose any progress </strong>- Don't worry about losing data, autosaving will keep it safe<br/></li><li><strong>No microtransactions </strong>- Enjoy the puzzles up to 200 pieces or unlock all current and future content with a single purchase</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jigsaw Puzzles Infinite</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1946140/Jigsaw_Puzzles_Infinite/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1946140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							If you like jigsaw puzzles - this is your game.<br/>Sit back, relax and build puzzles to your heart's content.<h2 class="bb_tag">What you get with Jigsaw Puzzle Infinite:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Infinite possibilities</strong>- Choose from one of the dozens of included puzzles or add your own images without any limits<br/></li><li><strong>Classic mode</strong> - Jigsaw puzzles you know and love. Take your time and build the puzzle with the help of useful sorting features<br/></li><li><strong>Sorting</strong> - Sort pieces by section, sort out edges, or just spread them out neatly <br/></li><li><strong>Zen Mode</strong> - Enter the flow and assemble the puzzle piece by piece<br/></li><li><strong>Pieces snap to each other </strong>and are not placed on a preset grid - just like real puzzles<br/></li><li><strong>Adjust difficulty </strong>- Freely choose number of pieces and snapping distance<br/></li><li><strong>Different piece shapes </strong>- Choose from multiple possible shapes of the pieces<br/></li><li><strong>Free camera movement </strong>- Zoom in and out, and move around the board freely <br/></li><li><strong>Every puzzle unique </strong>- Pieces are randomized each time new puzzle is generated<br/></li><li><strong>Never lose any progress </strong>- Don't worry about losing data, autosaving will keep it safe<br/></li><li><strong>No microtransactions </strong>- Enjoy the puzzles up to 200 pieces or unlock all current and future content with a single purchase</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chakana, Gold of the Gods</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2782340/Chakana_Gold_of_the_Gods/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782340/extras/banner-TopSTM1.png?t=1707330677"><br/><br/>It is a platform / metroidvania game inspired by Andean Mythology, with a focus on exploration, combat and discovery. Each level presents new challenges, enemies and secrets to unravel. Collect valuable items to improve your skills and unlock new areas as you progress on your adventure. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782340/extras/IMGSteamPG4.png?t=1707330677"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in the world of Chakana, a world in destruction and experience the myths and legends of Andean Mythology. From mysterious temples to the vast jungles of the Amazon, each scene is full of details and references that will take you on a fascinating journey.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782340/extras/IMGSteamPG1.png?t=1707330677"><br/><br/>In the game you control Hoyustus, the jaguar warrior, in his goal to free his people from the oppression of a usurping god in the magical world of Chakana. Discover his unique abilities, such as his deadly spear and his condor wings that allow him to explore inaccessible areas. He learns new techniques and unlocks special powers as you progress through the different jungle settings, temples and ancient ruins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782340/extras/IMGSteamPG5.png?t=1707330677"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782340/extras/IMGSteamPG2.png?t=1707330677"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sticky Struggles</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1931070/Sticky_Struggles/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1931070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Inspired by the classic Sokoban games, Sticky Struggles adds its own unique gameplay mechanics. When you're located next to a block, it sticks to you, and the only way to let go of it is by placing it in the correct location! Are you ready for the challenge?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1931070/extras/relax-focus.gif?t=1707310908"><br/><br/>Enjoy a minimalist game world with relaxing music. No flashy visuals and loud sound effects.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1931070/extras/lots.gif?t=1707310908"><br/><br/>Play through 50 challenging levels. Once completed, you get instant access to 25 bonus levels!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1931070/extras/achievements.gif?t=1707310908"><br/><br/>There are plenty of achievements to earn, can you collect them all?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1931070/extras/challenging.gif?t=1707310908"><br/><br/>There are multiple ways to solve each level. Can you figure out how to solve it in the lowest amount of moves possible?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1931070/extras/2d-3d.gif?t=1707310908"><br/><br/>You can easily toggle between 2D and 3D view.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1931070/extras/20240121-description_logo.png?t=1707310908"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairy Treasure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2601000/Fairy_Treasure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2601000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Gorgeous original brick-breaking game with tons of new fun bricks and amazing power-ups never seen before!<br>
<br>
In your quest of recapturing the Fairy Treasure, you will travel along the Fairy River from castle to cave in level after level of fast arcade fun and gorgeous sceneries.<br>
<br>
Gather magic scroll parts to find hidden treasures, solve puzzles to unlock secret areas and collect keys to unleash the mighty chain ball. <br>
<br>
Fairy Treasure features tons of challenging levels of block-breaking fun in an astounding world of fantasy and magic. May the fairies be with you!<br/>
<br/>
Fairy Treasure features: <br/>
 ✔ Magic fairy tale theme with a compelling story <br/>
 ✔ Tons of levels of brick-breaking fun <br/>
 ✔ 112 different bricks and enemies <br/>
 ✔ 14 power-ups and magic potions <br/>
 ✔ Gorgeous theme inspired graphics and music <br/>
 ✔ Realistic game physics <br/>
 ✔ Accurate controls and super smooth gameplay<br/>
 ✔ Three difficulty levels to master <br/>
 ✔ Global high scores let you compete against players from around the world <br/>
 ✔ Excellent replay value <br/>
 ✔ and much much more... <br/>
<br/>
If you like breakout and arkanoid-style games you will definitely love this highly innovative brick breaker game! <br/>
<br/>
Game On!  :)						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeonoid 2 Awakening</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2644320/Dungeonoid_2_Awakening/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2644320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Bust blocks on your path to victory in an adventurous mashup of nostalgic game genres!</h2><br/><br/>Classic dungeon crawling gets a block-busting twist in Dungeonoid 2 Awakening, a top-down adventure presented in retro pixel art style! In this genre mashup, you’ll pick from 4 role-playing classes, each with their own unique stats and special skill, then set off on a quest to conquer evil by controlling a floating platform to deflect a magical orb into targets along the way.<br/><br/>Move the platform left or right at the bottom of the screen and bounce the orb to keep it in play. Let the orb fly past you, and you’ll lose a heart. But fret not, by destroying walls, gravestones, enemies and more with your orb, you’ll cause power-ups and modifiers to drop towards your platform, some of which might heal you, some might shrink you, some might energize your orb for stronger attacks or have other effects! Charge your special attack to unleash particularly effective spells and attacks against big blocky bosses before they bring your adventure to an end!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Experience a unique mix of dungeon crawling adventure and brick-breaking action!<br/></li><li>Control a deflector platform and ricochet a magic orb to destroy targets.<br/></li><li>Select from multiple role-playing character classes to suite your playstyle!<br/></li><li>Collect power-ups and modifiers to turn the tide of battle.<br/></li><li>Face off against big bosses and unleash special charge attacks!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endless Faith</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2782910/Endless_Faith/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"I am proud to introduce the game 'Endless Faith' to you. 'Endless Faith' is a game that takes players on an infinite box adventure where they will encounter numerous obstacles on their journey to infinity. The goal is to overcome these obstacles by propelling them in different directions. Players have the freedom to use various features as they wish.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
- Endless Faith box adventure: Players will explore an endless space, constantly encountering new challenges.<br>
- A path filled with obstacles: Use strategic thinking and quick reflexes to overcome obstacles on the way.<br>
- Customizable features: Players have the chance to choose features that suit their gaming style.<br>
<br/>
'Endless Faith' offers players an immersive gaming experience as they embark on an infinite space journey. Use strategic thinking and quick reflexes to overcome various challenges the game presents. Customize your gaming experience by selecting features that align with your preferred playstyle as you journey towards infinity."						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>仿  Imitate</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2793150/__Imitate/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2793150/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Introduction</h2>This is a short story that can be read in just fifteen minutes.<br/>The story takes place in a near future time period.<br/>He, who had lost his lover in an accident a few years ago and was depressed, finally made that decision on this ordinary day.<br/>He wanted to move on,<br/>he wanted to lie in someone's arms and say goodbye to the past...<br/><br/>"Hello, my name is Sheryl, and I'm glad you chose me to serve you"<br/>For Sheryl and the whole world, this day in the future was just an insignificant fragment in the flowing stream of time.<br/>But in this fragment that was ignored by time, he took another step forward.<br/>He knew how much courage it took to take this step, and this courage had to push him out of the illusions of the past, and bring him to the place where he had promised himself to start over.<br/><br/>"Are you really a cyborg... and not a human?"<br/>He asked her the question that most people would blurt out when they first saw her, and she gave the usual answer.<br/>She was not human,<br/>perhaps, no one wanted to make her a "person".<h2 class="bb_tag">Operation Tips</h2>Right mouse button = back<br/>Ctrl/long press enter = fast forward<h2 class="bb_tag">About the Author</h2>Personal social accounts:<br/>Bilibili: @灵虚之幽<br/>Weibo: @灵虚之幽<br/>Feedback:<br/>Work feedback QQ group: 901140212						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WitchHand</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420880/WitchHand/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/store-gif-01.gif?t=1707293059"><br/><br/>In <strong>WitchHand</strong>, you use cards to build your empire of witches. Maximize the production of your villages and use your resources strategically to upgrade and expand. Focus on trade, alchemy research, or war in order to secure your coven's place amongst the Council of Fates, influencing the destiny of all. Work with your neighbors to secure a better future or crush them and use their bones to fuel your spells. When the witching hour comes each night, your witch's powers are at their strongest, while unseen forces work against you. You must expand and manage your coven to new heights if you are to withstand the coming darkness. No rest for the wicked.<h2 class="bb_tag">A CIVILIZATION OF WITCHES</h2>WitchHand folds the 4X strategy formula into card-based gameplay. You'll perform strategic actions like exploring, expanding, and exterminating through real-time card placement. Manage worker placement, village production, and research in order to advance the strength and reach of your coven.<h2 class="bb_tag">WIELD THE POWERS OF THE WITCHES OF THE REALMS</h2>Each witch has a unique selection of spells, buildings, and units that defines them. Empower your villages and production with the Celestial Witch. Overpower your enemies with the might of the Chaos Witch. Cook delicious, stat-boosting meals with the Chef Witch. Choose the witch that best suits your playstyle and have full control over your research paths to further personalize your playthrough.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/spellbook_and_wonder_crop.gif?t=1707293059"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXPLORE THE MYSTERIES OF THE NINTH</h2>The Council of Fates does not have faith in your expedition to the Ninth. Make alliances with rival factions or declare war and take their resources for your own. Manage your relationships through trade and gifts or with a well-placed fireball spell. Grow your coven to new heights and prove the Council wrong.<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES:</h2>🧭 <strong>Explore</strong> the Ninth Realm to discover new sites for your villages, necessary reagents to fuel your spells, and clues to the mystery of the Ninth's sudden appearance.<br/><br/>🏘️ <strong>Expand</strong> your coven by building new villages, perfecting production, and trading with the local factions.<br/><br/>🔥 <strong>Exterminate</strong> the beasts of the void, whose relentless assaults on your coven jeopardize your mission.<br/><br/>🧙‍♀️ <strong>Choose</strong> the witch to lead your coven, each with unique spells and playstyles.<br/><br/>⌛ <strong>Impress</strong> the Council of Fates and benefit from their powerful boons.<br/><br/>🕊️ <strong>Peaceful Mode</strong> - The option to play without the constant threat of extinction.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/combat-crop.gif?t=1707293059"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/store-gif-04.gif?t=1707293059"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oberty</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2469570/Oberty/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2469570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2469570/extras/w_en.png?t=1707292481"><br/><strong>Oberty</strong> is a minimalist shape-blending puzzle.<h2 class="bb_tag">Black + Black = White</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2469570/extras/octagramWhite.gif?t=1707292481"><br/>Rotate and blend cards with XOR rule: "Black + Black = White".<br/>Oberty gives you a few tiles with simple geometric shapes, choose some, rotate and combine tiles to reach target shape.<br/><br/>• 200+ puzzles to complete<br/>• Relaxing<br/>• Minimal<br/>• Monochromatic<br/>• Atmospheric original soundtrack<br/>• Inclusive color schemes for people with visual impairment<br/>• Level editor, create and share you cards with friends<h2 class="bb_tag">LEVEL EDITOR</h2>Create your own unique level-cards, share it to your friends by sending picture. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2469570/extras/editor600.gif?t=1707292481"><br/><br/>To play level simply load it from picture of level-card.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2469570/extras/cardLoad600.gif?t=1707292481"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heroes of the Seasons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2782260/Heroes_of_the_Seasons/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/extras/cooltext450428220967685.png?t=1707274850"><br/>Heroes of the Seasons is a Boss-Rush Turn-Based RPG with Visual Novel Styled storytelling. Hire 3 Mercenaries and protect Christmas with all your might!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/extras/cooltext450428227209374.png?t=1707274850"><br/>Set in the Year 242 A.R. (Arcane Renaissance) in the World of Vyen. Mayor Nelly of Utania Village has started decorating everything with Christmas lights and pretty stars. She had everyone in the village prepare delicious meals and treats for the holidays, and they planned on celebrating Christmas Eve together as a whole village. But one day, the biggest Christmas hater of them all, Frinch, the Goblin King, threatened Utania Village that he would ruin Christmas and destroy everything. We must protect the holidays at all costs! Thankfully, Mayor Nelly found Mercenaries willing to lend their aid in protecting Christmas and preserving the holiday spirit. Help Mayor Nelly and her friends by forming your Heroes of Christmas to fight King Frinch's army! <br/><br/>But wait, how are we sure that King Frinch is the only adversary to the holidays? What if a certain Lovecraftian lord is yearning to end the festivities? Or a jealous demoness with burning desires to destroy the Goddess' festive creation? Or a mere simpleton who's more than meets the eye, pulling the strings? We will never know unless we fight all of the haters.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/extras/cooltext450428235631348.png?t=1707274850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/extras/Boss_Rush_Mechanics.png?t=1707274850"><br/><strong>Boss Rush Mechanics</strong>:<br/><br/>Generally, most modes follow this setup, except for Jam Mode, which is easier and faster to finish. You face a wave of mobs, then a boss, and afterward, rest at a camp to buy items, talk to your mercenaries, visit your home to decorate or unwind, save, and open the menu.<br/><br/>After completing three sets of mob waves and bosses, you will face the Final Boss. Upon victory, you can claim rewards and unlockables and keep all the Vyse (Gold) and equipment you've acquired. If you wish, you are then taken back to the mercenary select screen to play another round of the game modes.<br/><br/><strong>Visit your HOME to DECORATE and UNWIND</strong>:<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter__2_.gif?t=1707274850"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/extras/Mercenary_Types.png?t=1707274850"><br/><strong>Mercenary Types</strong>:  As you pick your 3 Mercenaries to battle the Christmas-haters and become Heroes of Christmas, you will be able to pick between three types of mercenaries.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/extras/Tank.png?t=1707274850"><br/><strong>Tank</strong>: Tank-type mercenaries have high survivability to protect themselves and the party. They can provoke enemies to target them in their allies' stead. Their defenses are initially strong, but most tanks aren't fit to deal heavy damage to enemies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter__1_.gif?t=1707274850"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/extras/Nuker.png?t=1707274850"><br/><strong>Nuker</strong>: Nuker-type mercenaries are the main damage dealers. They can dish out heavy physical or magical damage to the enemy ranks, but they lack the survivability to protect themselves from enemy retaliation.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/extras/2024-01-1216-43-01-ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter.gif?t=1707274850"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/extras/Support.png?t=1707274850"><br/><strong>Support</strong>:  Support-type mercenaries are versatile characters who can heal allies HP and MP, give party buffs and shields, and debuff enemies (Depending on the support character's skills.) Their survivability isn't as great as a tank's, and their damage-dealing is not as great as a nuker's, but they're rather decent at both aspects.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter.gif?t=1707274850"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/extras/Elemental_Weaknesses.png?t=1707274850"><br/><strong>Elemental Triangle</strong>: Both players and enemies will have Elemental Affinities (Physical,  Force, and Arcane) and will be affected by the Elemental Triangle weakness system.<br/><br/><strong>Get to KNOW YOUR MERCENARIES.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter__3_.gif?t=1707274850"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782260/extras/cooltext450428295609597.png?t=1707274850"><br/>- Fast-Paced Turn Based Battles<br/>- Home decoration<br/>- Fight Challenging Mobs and Bosses as you progress<br/>- Replayability<br/>- Customizable party combinations and gears<br/>- Unlockables<br/>- Fun Character interactions<br/>- Christmas Spirit is everywhere!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Street Clean TD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2561050/Street_Clean_TD/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2561050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Protect the streets from the living trash.<br/><br/>You have just arrived in the city to buy materials, only to see that it has been invaded by living trash.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2561050/extras/GameplayGif.gif?t=1707267374"><br/><br/>Clean Street TD is a strategy game in which you have to defend the sewers from different types of garbage, build cleaning turrets which will help you defeat all your enemies, but carefully choose which upgrades you will buy, since each turret has a limit of two improvements.<h2 class="bb_tag">Torretas</h2>Built with the materials you have on hand, although they do not have the best technology, they are everyone's best hope to stop the threat of living trash.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2561050/extras/CatapultTurret32.png?t=1707267374"><h2 class="bb_tag">Enemigos</h2>Experiments created by a mad scientist made garbage come to life and now they seek to cover all the sewers to flood the city.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2561050/extras/LeafEnemy32.png?t=1707267374"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each turret can choose two of four upgrades. Think about which one you'll need.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2561050/extras/LimitUpgradeEnglish.png?t=1707267374"><br/></img></li><li>Enemies with unique abilities.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2561050/extras/EnemiesGifs.gif?t=1707267374"><br/></img></li><li>Purchase permanent upgrades in the store<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2561050/extras/ShopEnglish.png?t=1707267374"><br/></img></li><li>An extra difficulty that you can customize<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2561050/extras/CustomEnglish.png?t=1707267374"/></li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wo Long: Fallen Dynasty</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1448440/Wo_Long_Fallen_Dynasty/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1448440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1448440/extras/wolong_store.gif?t=1707267643"><br/><br/>From the depths of darkness, a dragon soars. <br/><br/>A new dark fantasy Three Kingdoms action RPG from Team NINJA, the developers of <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/franchise/KOEITECMO/list/76629/" rel="" target="_blank">Nioh</a>.<br/><br/>184 AD, Later Han Dynasty China. The land is overcome by chaos and destruction. The imperial dynasty that prospered for many years is now about to collapse. <br/><br/>Wo Long: Fallen Dynasty is a dramatic, action-packed story of a nameless militia soldier fighting for survival in a dark fantasy version of the Later Han Dynasty where demons plague the Three Kingdoms.  Players fight off deadly creatures and enemy soldiers using swordplay based on the Chinese martial arts, attempting to overcome the odds by awakening the true power from within. <br/><br/>Wo Long refers to a crouching dragon, and also refers to a hero or person of greatness who is not yet known. This is the story of officers, who will later become heroes, during their ‘unknown’ period, and also the story of a protagonist’s rise from being a ‘nobody’.<br/><br/><strong>Demons in the Kingdom</strong><br/>A dark fantasy set during the chaotic Three Kingdoms period, the narrative vividly tells the tale of a militia soldier’s strenuous fight for survival during a Later Han Dynasty infested with demons. It’s madness in the Three Kingdoms like never before!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1448440/extras/01_616×346_.jpg?t=1707267643"><br/><br/><strong>Awaken the Power Within</strong><br/>Defeat deadly enemies to boost morale and awaken the power from within! Overcome adversity through unique new strategies, including battle styles based on the “Five Phases”.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1448440/extras/03_616×346_.jpg?t=1707267643"><br/><br/><strong>Live by the Sword</strong><br/>Renowned for ruthless strikes that can change the tide of battle in an instant, sword practitioners of the Chinese martial arts gracefully change pace as they shift between offensive and defensive maneuvers. Overwhelm opponents with a flurry of force in a series of intense and bloody battles while learning the precision and skill necessary to become a true master of the sword.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1448440/extras/02_616×346_.jpg?t=1707267643"><br/><br/><strong>Various Play Styles with Weapons and Wizardry Spells</strong><br/><strong>-Weapons</strong><br/>Choose from a wide variety of weapons, from glaives to dual swords, to discover which fits your fighting style.<br/><strong>-Wizardry Spells</strong><br/>This secret art draws upon the power of the Five Phases, which allow for attacks using such elements as flames and ice. Upon achieving higher Morale Ranks, you can gain the ability to utilize even more powerful Wizardry Spells.<br/><strong>-Divine Beasts</strong><br/>Divine Beasts like Zhuque and Baihu are brought forth through alliances with other warriors. By calling upon these Divine Beasts, you are able to perform feats of great power.<br/> <br/>Note: You must have an internet connection in order to use various content.<br/>Note: This is the standard edition of the game. The Digital Deluxe Edition is also available.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gothic Virtual Tabletop</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2757850/Gothic_Virtual_Tabletop/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Gothic Virtual Tabletop is a virtual tabletop application that can be customized to support most TTRPG systems, including wargames.<h2 class="bb_tag">Built-in System-agnostic Character Sheets</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Customizable character sheets support any system from the ever-present D&amp;D, to that fantasy heartbreaker from the 90s.<br/></li><li> Easily access character sheets by double clicking on a token, not by switching to another tab.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Revolutionary Hotbar System</h2>When you select a token, a state-of-the-art Hotbar appears at the bottom of the screen. The Hotbar displays all the information a player or GM cares about in one compact space, making GM-ing large combats or managing multiple playable characters a breeze. Gone are the days of dozens of tabs worth of stat blocks cluttering your monitor!<h2 class="bb_tag">Robust Macro System</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Roll dice, edit your character sheet, send predefined messages in chat, and even play sounds at one press of a button.  <br/></li><li> Customize the color and text of any macro button, and where they should be shown on the Hotbar<br/></li><li> Support for user-defined variables, which can include mathematical equations and/or any value on a token's character sheet.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Support For Almost Any TTRPG System or Wargame </h2>Default Character Sheet values and macros, as well as compendium weapons, armour, spells, and tables are defined in .json files and stored independently on a per-campaign basis. Easily customize Gothic Virtual Tabletop to suit each and every one of your needs.<h2 class="bb_tag">Built-In Compendium</h2>Define weapons, armour, abilities, spells, and rollable tables present in your system of choice and easily add them to a token at the press of a button.<h2 class="bb_tag">Built-in Jukebox</h2>Browse your campaign's music library and add queue up the perfect songs for the occasion!<h2 class="bb_tag">Absolutely Sublime Text Chat </h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Rolls always show what the individual die rolls were, even when part of a complex equation or macro.<br/></li><li> Easily whisper to other players, or the GM.<br/></li><li> Roll dice for all to see, or just to the GM in secret.<br/></li><li> Roll on tables and show the result in chat.<br/></li><li> Support for robes and wizard hats.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Per-map whiteboard layer for drawing up battle strategies or doodling while that player takes the slowest turn ever.</h2><h2 class="bb_tag"> Feature-rich Map editor</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Quick and easy fog-of-war tools to keep curious players from scouting out secret rooms and ambushes.<br/></li><li> Adjust the grid to fit any image, whether it has a baked-in grid or not.<br/></li><li> Turn grid lines on and off.<br/></li><li> Supports Common types of map grids, including square, hex (horizontal), hex (vertical), and no grid.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">No Loading Screens</h2>Okay, there is one loading screen that appears when a player first connects to the server and downloads assets. After that, you're free to game in peace.<h2 class="bb_tag">Self Hosted</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> All your maps, tokens, sounds, and music files are stored locally, on your computer. Gone are the days of juggling storage space when trying to upload a new map for your next encounter!<br/></li><li> Password Protected Lobbies<br/></li><li> Easily view who is connected to the server in the bottom left, a green bubble means connected, and yellow means connecting.  </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noxium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2237480/Noxium/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2237480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to your new job mining Noxium for a sketchy business. Keep the power on and everything should be fine. Noxium can only be traded at night, hence why we need someone like you to keep the operation running throughout the night. We have cameras setup throughout the warehouse so you can keep an eye on everything. Good luck!<h2 class="bb_tag">Manage</h2>Use the terminal throughout the nights to manage the Noxium mining operation. Keep all of the servers online for maximum mining efficiency. Occasionally the servers will have problems and you will have to diagnose the issue and fix them.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2237480/extras/Terminal.gif?t=1707258024"><h2 class="bb_tag">Monitor</h2>There are <strong>4</strong> cameras scattered throughout the warehouse. Keep an eye out for anything strange that might halt or slow down the Noxium mining operation.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2237480/extras/Monitor.gif?t=1707258024"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive</h2>There are a few threats you will face throughout the nights. Stay alert, any single moment could become your last.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2237480/extras/Survive.gif?t=1707258024"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2237480/extras/Hide.gif?t=1707258024"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little Droid</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2500570/Little_Droid/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2500570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In the game "Little Droid" you will find exciting levels with a variety of traps, obstacles and riddles. You will explore amazing locations including a secret bunker, deep dungeons and mysterious forests. Each level offers new challenges and secrets to uncover.<br/><br/><strong>Little Droid</strong> is a classic 2D pixel art side-scrolling adventure where you have to find the source of a mysterious signal. More than 20 secret rooms, many enemies and bosses. The droid will have to be constantly charged to complete the entire game.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2500570/extras/littledroid2.jpg?t=1707256365"><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Pixel art<br/></li><li>Single player game<br/></li><li>Various enemies<br/></li><li>many secrets<br/></li><li>Exploring the world</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HellEscape</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2135030/HellEscape/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2135030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>„The gates of hell are open night and day; Smooth the descent, and easy is the way:<br/>But to return, and view the cheerful skies, In this the task and mighty labor lies.“</strong><br/><br/>HellEscape is a 2D bullet hell with auto-fire and roguelike elements. Inspired by games like Magic Survivors and Vampire Survivors, but takes a different approach. Explore the unforgiving world of HellEscape, complete special missions, and uncover the hidden lore with 19 unique Heroes and over 70+ different weapons!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>9 Stages!<br/></li><li>55 Missions!<br/></li><li>27 Heroes!<br/></li><li>55 Special Artifacts!<br/></li><li>105 Weapons &amp; Abilities!<br/></li><li>60 Unique Power Ups!<br/></li><li>100 Monster Types!<br/></li><li>362 Achievements, 46 on Steam!<br/></li><li>13 Types of Random Daily Challenges!<br/></li><li>20 Mounts to unlock!</li></ul><br/>Note: currently doesn't work on steam deck. Only fully tested on windows.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timeray</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2773780/Timeray/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2773780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Your name is kong you have a devil staff which grants you powers to control the time,  you have to survive in a open world, there are two power ups one which makes you faster another makes you normal speed,if you slowed by enemy.<br>
hey guys this game is about using powers like timeball which slows down time and you can stop time of the world and enemy also can fire you with timeball or timesphere and blackhole also you can stop time in a range and time ray. this game is about surviving using your time powers.simply this is about surviving from enimies,game is still in development.<br>
    You can change maps by 1,2,3 keys.by pressing E key you can stop time in the wolrd,press R key to strat the time of world,use can use F,C,Q, to use different powers of time.<br>
 Experiment using different time powers.<br>
<br>
Time powers are abilities that allow one to manipulate the flow of time, such as speeding it up, slowing it down, stopping it. Some examples of time powers are:<br>
<br/>
Time Manipulation: The ability to control time in general, such as creating time loops, altering the past or future, or changing the rate of time for oneself or others1.<br/>
Time Travel: The ability to move across different points in time, either physically or mentally1.<br/>
Time Stopping: The ability to halt the flow of time for a certain area or target, making everything appear frozen1.<br/>
Time Vision: The ability to perceive past or future events, or alternate timelines1.<br/>
Time Blast: The ability to unleash a powerful burst of temporal energy that can damage or affect the target’s time1.<br/>
There are many more types of time powers, and some of them can be very creative or complex. For example, some video games feature time powers that can create a time shield, a freeze zone, a time dash, or a time bomb2. Time powers can also be combined with other abilities, such as spatial manipulation, dimensional travel, or reality warping1.<br/>
<br/>
Time powers are often considered very powerful and dangerous, as they can alter the natural order of things and cause paradoxes or anomalies. Therefore, time powers usually have some limitations or drawbacks, such as requiring a lot of energy, concentration, or skill, or having negative side effects, such as aging, memory loss, or temporal instability1. Time powers may also be subject to certain rules or laws, such as causality, fate, or destiny1.<br/>
<br/>
Time powers are a popular theme in fiction, especially in science fiction and fantasy genres. Some famous examples of characters with time powers are Doctor Strange, The Flash, Hiro Nakamura, Max Caulfield, and Tracer1. Time powers can also be used as plot devices, such as in Back to the Future, The Terminator, Steins;Gate, and Avengers: Endgame.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OM6N</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/681000/OM6N/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/681000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/681000/extras/episodic_campaign.png?t=1707242420"><br/><strong>Experience a challenging campaign spanning across many unique locations as you fight to uncover the source of this malevolent omen.<br/><br/>Arm yourself with over a dozen different weapons as you fend off the hordes of Hell. <br/><br/>Collect powerful tomes to increase your chances of survival against the onslaught.<br/><br/>Encounter numerous types of demonic foes thirsting for your mortal blood.</strong><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/681000/extras/rogue_mode.png?t=1707242420"><br/><strong>Hungry for more mortal? Slaughter Hell's minions endlessly in this alternative game mode.<br/><br/>Gain experience, rank up, and conquer the leaderboard to prove you are truly the best.<br/><br/>Climb to the top to be forever remembered in the Hall of Immortals.</strong><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/681000/extras/bonus_content.png?t=1707242420"><br/><strong>Discover and unlock bonus side content naturally as you progress on your journey.<br/><br/>Enjoy free future content updates including new levels, modes, customizations, and more!</strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder Is Game Over: Deal Killer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2478850/Murder_Is_Game_Over_Deal_Killer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2478850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A new murder mystery to solve! “Deal Killer” takes Detective Guy and Cleo the clue-sniffing dog to the remote heights of the Italian Alps to solve the murder of a powerful businessman. A prominent video game publishing executive has summoned our detective duo to an isolated mountain chalet for a private party celebrating a major corporate deal, but he’s found dead shortly after their arrival. The victim’s inner circle is full of back-stabbing enemies, and there’s also a local legend about a ghostly harbinger of death to contend with. Stranded in a horrendous blizzard, can Detective Guy and Cleo solve this baffling mystery before the case goes cold?<br/><br/>Features:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Solve a murder mystery<br/></li><li>Search for clues<br/></li><li>Interview suspects<br/></li><li>Explain the solution<br/></li><li>New disguise mechanic<br/></li><li>Third game in "Murder Is Game Over" series</li></ul><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2478850/Murder_Is_Game_Over_Deal_Killer/?utm_source=bottom" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2478850/Murder_Is_Game_Over_Deal_Killer/?utm_source=bottom</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Master</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2791320/Traffic_Master/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In the bustling city of Metroville, traffic congestion has reached unprecedented levels, causing frustration and delays for its residents. To address this issue, the city council introduces the "TrafficMaster" traffic control initiative. As a rookie traffic control officer, the player embarks on a journey to become the renowned TrafficMaster, responsible for managing traffic flow.<br>
<br>
Equipped with cutting-edge VR technology and guided by experienced mentors, the player faces a series of challenging levels in Metroville's downtown area. They strategically control traffic lights, coordinate lane changes, and respond to emergencies to maintain smooth traffic flow. Each level unlocks new areas with more complex traffic scenarios, such as rush hour traffic, construction zones, and unexpected events.<br>
<br>
Throughout the game, the player interacts with fellow officers, frustrated drivers, and pedestrians, gaining insights into the impact of their work on the city's inhabitants. With each level completed, the player earns promotions and contributes to reducing congestion and improving the quality of life for Metroville's residents.<br>
<br>
As their expertise and efficiency grow, the player aims to become the renowned TrafficMaster, recognized for their ability to keep Metroville's streets flowing smoothly and efficiently. By immersing players in the challenging and rewarding world of traffic control through virtual reality, the game aims to provide an engaging and educational experience.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slot Shots Pinball Ultimate Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687940/Slot_Shots_Pinball_Ultimate_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							No subscriptions, no monthly fees, no DLC, and no tickets required to play! Thirteen pinball tables for just one price! Get ready for the next edition of Slot Shots Pinball featuring five brand new tables along with all of the original tables released in 2022. <strong>It is Steam Deck compatible and it runs at a very smooth 60 FPS.</strong> Each of our new tables feature beautiful 3d background environments, new camera angles, wider and more detailed playfields, better looking LEDs, better graphical assets and special effects, more complex missions, online leaderboards to compete on, full controller support, sixty achievements, mouse / keyboard support, and finally every new table has a twenty+ minute soundtrack to listen to while you play. Each table has the classic three ball mode, lots of missions, and multiball waiting to be activated.<br/><br/>Major Update 1/24/24 - A new DMD system has been updated into the title (shown in all of the screen shots). Each table has it's own DMD theme!<br/><br/>*New* table line up:<br/>1. Dracula's Pawn - A vampire themed castle playfield, featuring a very gothic soundtrack and a very vocal Dracula. The playfield has multiple flippers, fun missions, and a castle waiting to be explored!<br/>2. Neon Nights Ultra - A futuristic table with a neon city background, a pulse pounding soundtrack, and some of the best pinball shots we can throw down on a playfield. This one is pure fun at it's finest. <br/>3. Ocean Breeze - Bad day at work? Family and friends got you down? Come relax at our Ocean Breeze pinball paradise, just don't feed the shark! <br/>4. Mystic Ballistic - A jungle themed table with some pretty vocal shot awards. This playfield has a few secret areas that reward you with slot shot spins and access to the lower spinning playfield. <br/>5. Tomb Keeper Manor - A completely new version of Tomb Keeper Mansion, including all new missions, an extended 23 minute soundtrack featuring 10+ minutes of new music, all new LEDs, all new decorations, new sound effects, various graphical art and special effect improvements- this is a completely new table that kept the house intact! <br/>**Also included are the following seven tables found in the original Slot Shots Pinball (plus one extra).<br/>6. Dream World - A bright, colorful, rainbow and candy filled table with three flippers.<br/>7. The Kraken's Cove - A dark pirate themed table with a giant kraken in the center!<br/>8. Super Vixel Land - A retro themed pixel/voxel super wide table.<br/>9. Slot Shots Casino - A fantasy themed casino with a spinning lucky wheel in the back.<br/>10. Bass Hunter - A fishing themed table with a playfield on top of an aquarium! <br/>11. Neon Nights 2 Skylines - A dark neon playfield with a pulse pounding synth soundtrack.<br/>12. Outergalactic Aliens - A remake of last year's table with all new LEDs.<br/>13. Neon Nights Original - It all started with this table, welcome to the original neon nights!<br/><br/>For a full guide on completing the missions for all of the new tables, general tips, and more you can view the user manual here:<br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fslotshotspinballultimateedition.my.canva.site%2Fpinball" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://slotshotspinballultimateedition.my.canva.site/pinball</a><br/><br/>What do the first Steam curator reviewers have to say about this title?<br/>Gold Bear Games - Recommended - Cute pinball in the ultimate edition with a full selection of tables. Nice graphics, interesting effects and thirteen tables for every taste. Simple and exciting.<br/>Adult World Gamers - Recommended - Slot Shots Pinball Ultimate Edition is a must for pinball enthusiasts and casual players alike.<br/>CzechLP - Recommended - Publishers of quality virtual pinball tables are sadly few and far between on Steam, but Pinblend Studios once again proves that they are one of them. There are 13 different tables to choose from.<br/>Cubiq - Recommended - Nice pinball with a lot of tables and classic gameplay. Worth a look!<br/>Review Prizm - Recommended - Gosh, this game made me realize, how much I've missed pinball games! Is it the best one out there? No, but it do its job well, so you will have lot of fun in it!<br/>United Critics - Recommended - Master the flippers in Slot Shots Pinball: where every table is a new adventure in arcade nostalgia.<br/>Comunidad en español - Recommended - Nice graphics. 13 tables currently. For quick games it's fine. A game that all pinball lovers will like.<br/>Emote Reviews - Recommended - Pipe Hype<br/>Imaginarium - Recommended<br/>Pink Unicorn - Recommended<br/>Rise and Shine, Mr. Gamer - Recommended<br/><br/><br/><br/>PLEASE NOTE: This title was built using the Unity game engine and there is a slight delay while playing if using BOTH shift keys at the same time to control the flippers. This is a known issue with the Unity game engine. If using a keyboard we recommend picking and using ONE shift key on either side, and then another key to control the other flipper such as S, L, CTRL or Tab.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duel with the Devil</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2794050/Duel_with_the_Devil/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2794050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dangerous demons have attacked the entire city and the city is in crisis.<br>
<br>
you have accepted the mission to save the city<br>
<br>
As a duelist with endless possibilities, you must fight against the evil demon army<br>
<br>
Being wrong with the demon's powerful attacks can put your life in danger.<br/>
<br/>
we have to find a way to survive in this crisis<br/>
<br/>
If you defeat demons and gain experience points to level up, you can choose skills that will be randomly given to you.<br/>
<br/>
Try to properly combine a total of 20 skills to create the best result<br/>
<br/>
Victory or defeat can be determined by how you combine your skills, so you must choose carefully.<br/>
<br/>
You may lose your life to the boss's powerful Chinese medicine, so you should use evasion techniques to avoid it						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amidst The Haze</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2688140/Amidst_The_Haze/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688140/extras/Sobre_o_Jogo__2_.png?t=1707236641"><br/><br/>Enter a world where survival becomes a lethal game. where your simple trip to the supermarket turns into a terrifying nightmare when a thick, unfathomable fog engulfs the city, isolating the supermarket as the only safe haven. What seems like a safe haven, however, turns out to be<br/>serves as a deadly prison for those who venture beyond its limits.<br/><br/>In "Amidst the Haze," the normality of an ordinary trip to the grocery store is quickly transformed into a survival nightmare. A dense, ominous fog engulfs the city, confining a group of customers and employees to the supermarket,<br/>the only apparently safe place. However, what lurks outside this sanctuary could be an unknown, lethal threat.<br/><br/>This oppressive fog is not merely atmospheric, but rather a veil that conceals terrifying, nameless entities. Those who venture out of the supermarket face an uncertain fate,<br/>risking their lives before these dark creatures. The fight for survival becomes a battle between staying within the familiar but increasingly claustrophobic walls or risking the unknown outside.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688140/extras/Caracteristicas__1_.png?t=1707236641"><h2 class="bb_tag">]ATMOSPHERE</h2><br/>Survive inside a supermarket filled with intense and claustrophobic fog, where supernatural beings live.<h2 class="bb_tag">]OBJECTIVES]</h2><br/>You will need to join the others in the supermarket and find a way to survive the unknown. Seek an answer to everything that is happening,<br/>solve missions and fight for your life.<h2 class="bb_tag">DURATION</h2><br/> Considerably short game, there are no save points.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2777390/Market_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2777390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In a quiet and peaceful neighborhood, you embarked on a long journey to purchase the market of your dreams, and finally, you have reached your goal. Now, it's time to manage your own market to provide quality products and friendly service to the neighborhood residents!<br>
<br>
In this exciting simulation game, you will have the opportunity to manage your own neighborhood market. With a wide range of products, from beverages to food items, from cleaning products to technology goods, it's in your hands to satisfy your customers.<br>
<br>
Personalize and Expand Your Market<br>
Customize your market as you desire! Control every detail, from shelf arrangements to storefront displays. As you earn, expand your market and warehouse, add new products, and enhance your business by increasing customer flow.<br>
<br/>
Enjoyable Simulation Experience<br/>
<br/>
Market Simulator offers a detailed graphical interface, realistic simulation features, and a fun-filled experience with engaging tasks. Establish your own business, grow it, and achieve success by serving the people in your neighborhood.<br/>
<br/>
Remember, your neighborhood will become more beautiful with you, and it will become even more vibrant with your market! Good luck!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLeM</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1861440/CLeM/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1861440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1861440/extras/Experience_a_dark_adventure_full_of_mystery.png?t=1707237075"><br/>You awaken in a cold, dimly lit room, your senses slowly adjusting to the surroundings that, oddly, feel familiar. A strange sensation lingers in you, reminding you that something is not quite right. As you find your bearings, your attention is drawn to a peculiar item on the ground. A notebook labeled "CLeM" lies before you. As you delve into its pages, covered with intricate sketches of insects accompanied by vague symbols, you find a note containing a cryptic message: “Bring me BEAUTY.” Lost in deciphering the contents, a voice interrupts your focus.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1861440/extras/1.gif?t=1707237075"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1861440/extras/Solve_puzzles_and_find_your_way.png?t=1707237075"><br/>Puzzles intertwine with exploration, weaving a unique narrative experience we call “Puzzlevania” with a shadowy story to unravel and countless challenges to overcome.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1861440/extras/CLeM---Puzzles-Improved-v2_1.gif?t=1707237075"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1861440/extras/Craft_enchanted_toys_and_uncover_secrets.png?t=1707237075"><br/>Craft magic toys to unveil hidden secrets, access unreachable spots, and reclaim items from the past as you uncover new revelations in familiar spaces. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1861440/extras/3.gif?t=1707237075"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1861440/extras/Discover_a_cute_and_dark_world.png?t=1707237075"><br/>Investigate a seemingly desolate house accompanied only by an obscure voice and a notebook full of annotations and drawings on alchemy, insects, and other creepy crawlies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1861440/extras/4.gif?t=1707237075"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1861440/extras/Embrace_your_destiny.png?t=1707237075"><br/>Choose your fate in this dark story of manipulation, pride, forgiveness, and redemption.<br/><br/><u><strong>Features:</strong></u><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A new genre, “Puzzlevania,” intertwines puzzles and exploration. Discover hidden secrets in each room as you delve deeper into the mysteries with every crafted magical toy.<br/></li><li>Unique and beautiful art style with hand-drawn elements.<br/></li><li>2D graphics with 3D environmental navigation.<br/></li><li>Challenging and diverse puzzles to solve.<br/></li><li>An enigmatic story with a dark turn.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That Way!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781490/That_Way/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							That Way! is a platformer about planning your path to reach a series of guarded vaults. For each vault, create a list of commands that will help your partner reach it. When you are ready, send them to him one by one to get him there. <br/><br/>You will navigate through 50 levels, each containing more hazards than the last. Plan carefully and watch your timing to ensure your victory!<h2 class="bb_tag">Controls</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Shift: Switch between "Plan" and "Run" modes<br/></li><li>Ctrl/Command + Arrows: Pan Camera<br/></li><li>Esc: Pause</li></ul><br/><strong>Plan Mode Controls</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>WASD: Add new command<br/></li><li>Up/Down Arrows: Scroll through commands</li></ul><br/><strong>Run Mode Controls</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Enter: Send command</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Failed Trust</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2745140/Failed_Trust/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Game name: "Failed Trust"</h2><h2 class="bb_tag">Description:</h2>Welcome to "Failed Trust", a thrilling adventure that takes you through the labyrinthine corridors of a mysterious tech hub. No one explained why you were here, but you were tasked with picking up important documents. Immerse yourself in a world of technology and mystery as you try to unravel the unusual history of this place.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay:</h2>The technical center that appears on your way hides unexplored areas and unique mechanisms. Your guide will be an energy accumulator that allows you to dive deep into the center. Collect energy from glowing lamps and energy shields to illuminate your path and open doors leading to new sections of the tech center.<br/><br/>Your adventure will be filled with unexpected finds, interesting mechanisms and puzzles necessary to move deeper into the center. Solve problems and uncover the secrets hidden in its intricate vaults.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features:</h2>- Expand the tech center: Explore the different sections of the center, discovering its structure and functionality.<br/>- Energy Storage: Use a unique mechanism to collect energy and illuminate the spaces around you.<br/>- Interactive Puzzles: Solve challenging puzzles to open up new paths and navigate challenging areas of the center.<br/>- A mysterious story: Uncover the secrets of the tech center's past as you follow the flow of your tasks and goals.<br/><br/>Walk through the corridors, collect documents and unravel the mysteries of the "Failed Trust". Good luck on your journey through this mysterious place!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Garbage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2691580/Space_Garbage/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2691580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2691580/extras/steamHeader.png?t=1707230058"><br/><br/>Do you like Tetris? Doesn't matter. Space Garbage is here to rotate Tetris 90 degrees on its head and add a little car to it.<br/><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Discover exotic garbage across 4 unique levels!<br/></li><li> Master the art of the stack and take your rightful place on the leaderboard!<br/></li><li> Support a solo developer who doesn't know what they're doing! </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1707227820"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal from ECHOS</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1707227820"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about playtesting opportunities, dev news, limited edition merch and more.<h2 class="bb_tag">Wishlist &amp; Follow on Steam</h2>Make sure to wishlist and follow the game for the latest updates. Due for Release early Q2-Q3 2023.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vampire: The Masquerade - Justice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2431700/Vampire_The_Masquerade__Justice/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_Venice.gif?t=1707322060"><br/><br/>Become a vampire. Strike from the darkness and drink the blood of your prey. Use stealth, persuasion, and an arsenal of upgradable abilities to sneak past enemies undetected or punish the guilty in the seedy backstreets of nighttime Venice.<br/><br/><strong>Vampire: The Masquerade - Justice</strong> is an open-ended, narrative Adventure RPG set in the World of Darkness universe. You have the power to strike fear into the hearts of a criminal underworld as an untraceable shadow, picking off targets one-by-one.<h2 class="bb_tag">STEALTH IS YOUR WEAPON</h2>Shadows are your ally. Take to the rooftops and seek new paths away from enemy eyes. Use Shadow Traps to snatch up unsuspecting prey and drag them into Oblivion. Activate Cloak of Shadows and slip unseen through enemy defenses. In Vampire: The Masquerade - Justice, stealth is your weapon.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_BloodDrinking.gif?t=1707322060"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_sneaky.gif?t=1707322060"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A POWERFUL VAMPIRE</h2>Punish the guilty with brutal abilities. Launch yourself towards opponents with immense force or boil their insides with Cauldron of Blood. Approach from behind and sink in your fangs to stock up on blood. Load your crossbow with special bolts to kill, distract or knock out guards from afar. Dish out Justice with a vengeance.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_BloodDrinking_2.gif?t=1707322060"><h2 class="bb_tag">LEVEL UP AND EXPLORE</h2>The dark skies of Venice provide ample opportunity to level up powers and build a character suited to your playstyle. Tackle side-missions away from the campaign to earn more experience. Convince NPCs to aid your quest, solve puzzles, uncover collectibles and test yourself with optional tasks in each mission.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_update.gif?t=1707322060"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2431700/extras/VTMJustice_SteamStorePage_enviornement.gif?t=1707322060"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
