<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Hoplite: Arachne’s Trial</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2738430/Legendary_Hoplite_Arachnes_Trial/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Try out the free prologue to get a taste of the exciting gameplay and easily transfer your progress to the full game.<br/><br/><strong>Transfer your progress to the main game</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_04.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>The main game offers three acts, 38 areas, mini-games, and a lot of gear options for your hero. Progress seamlessly transfers from the prologue to the main game.<br/><br/><strong>Face 10 Levels and 2 Boss Battles</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_02.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>Face the challenge of 10 distinct levels, each filled with hordes of mythic monsters. Try 6 different armies and test your skills against Arachne at the end of the prologue.<br/><br/><strong>Customize Your Build and Power Up Your Army</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_01.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>Customize your build by trying out various gear combinations you come across. Find the perfect match for your playstyle as you explore. Strengthen your army by upgrading them and merging with the Hero to amplify your power, ready to face and conquer the enemy.<br/><br/><strong>War technique</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_03.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>Elevate your armies with War Technique—a fresh way to upgrade. Experiment with various combos and effortlessly switch up your enhancements for effective improvements.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Momodora: Moonlit Farewell</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1747760/Momodora_Moonlit_Farewell/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1747760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Momodora: Moonlit Farewell" is the latest installment in the Momodora series. Join Momo, High Priestess of the village of Koho, as she embarks on a divine mission to save her people from imminent destruction at the hands of the demon hordes summoned by a malevolent bellringer.<h2 class="bb_tag">Story:</h2>Momodora: Moonlit Farewell presents the account of the greatest calamity to befall the village of Koho, five years after the events of Momodora III.<br/> Once the toll of an ominous bell is heard, the village is soon threatened by a demon invasion.<br/>The village's matriarch sends Momo Reinol, their most capable priestess, to investigate the bell and find the bellringer responsible for summoning demons. It is their hope that by finding the culprit, they will also  be able to secure the village's safety, and most importantly, the sacred Lun Tree's, a source of life and healing for Koho...<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Gorgeous pixel art and animation<br/></li><li> Action-packed gameplay focusing on melee combos, dodging enemy attacks, and firing arrows at enemies<br/></li><li> The "Sigil" system, which allows for greatly customizable play styles<br/></li><li> Intense and core-shaking boss battles<br/></li><li> Deep exploration into a world rich in lore and atmosphere<br/></li><li> Freely adjustable difficulty levels, allowing you to relax and explore the alluring world at your own pace or take on mighty foes for a real challenge</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Developer's Voice:</h2>Hello!<br/><br/>This is rdein, creator of the Momodora series. Recently my team and I have announced the latest installment in the series, “Moonlit Farewell”. This is a concluding story, following through from the events of Momodora 3. With this new tale, I also intend to close the book on many of the past games’ mysteries and questions.<br/><br/>I’m aware that many players are more familiar with the story of Kaho, which is set in a distant past. As such, I’m designing “Moonlit Farewell” to be as enjoyable as possible without prior knowledge of Momodora 1 to 3’s stories. Moreover, the series has always been focused on action and minimal stories. So please, don’t worry too much about “catching up”!<br/>Lastly, we hope to bring you our best game with this new title, using all the knowledge we’ve learned in the past 10 years. Please look forward to it!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frostrain</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2735630/Frostrain/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/01_Thumnail.png?t=1705033707"><h2 class="bb_tag">Roam the frozen world</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Roam_the_frozen_world.gif?t=1705033707"><br/>Climate change has turned the world white and frozen, and the only thing moving on the planet is you, your passengers, and your train. It's a dead world, but ironically, it's all the more fascinating for it. A vivid landscape awaits you to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Keep your passengers happy</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Keep_your_passengers_happy.gif?t=1705033707"><br/>The passengers on your train will work diligently at your command, but be careful: if you don't manage their happiness properly, they might throw you off the train.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build your own train with card decks</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Build_your_own_train_with_card_decks.gif?t=1705033707"><br/>Each time you pass through a city, you'll be able to add new train cars by launching a heavy lift drone. Be careful with each choice you make. If you are lucky, you'll be able to build a better, more synergized, happily-ever-after train deck, but it won't always go as you planned.<h2 class="bb_tag">Reach the Promised Land</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2735630/extras/AboutGame_Reach_the_Promised_Land.gif?t=1705033707"><br/>Lead your passengers in search of the Promised Land, somewhere on the eastern edge of the world. But the journey to the Promised Land isn't all smooth and pleasant. You'll have to pass through toxic areas, and a severe storm is brewing behind you. Pay attention to your passengers' happiness levels and lead them safely to the Promised Land. The journey is in your hands.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696480/Nothing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2696480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play. Or is it?<br>
<br>
Just do Nothing as the timer goes up. If you do Something, you lose.<br>
<br>
If you don't like doing Nothing, go play Something instead.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Flame: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517810/The_Last_Flame_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_1.png?t=1705209899"><br/>The Last Flame is a roguelike auto-battler which focuses on build creation, strategy and decision making. Recruit special heroes, fight deadly encounters, loot and craft powerful gear, discover and create unique synergetic builds! Every run, you will need to create powerful builds that will take down your foes!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_A3.gif?t=1705209899"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_2.png?t=1705209899"><br/>The Last Flame offers an incredible amount of build diversity. Combine heroes, items, relics and origins together to create amazing builds! Hero and team building have been designed with flexibility and freedom at their core which allows you to discover and create unique synergetic builds every single run!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Builds.gif?t=1705209899"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_3.png?t=1705209899"><br/>In between the automated combats, you will have to cleverly guide your heroes through the adventure by making the smart decisions! Manage your resources, choose the optimal path in the map, make powerful builds, and strategically position and plan the combat phase!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Tactical.gif?t=1705209899"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/comingToFullVersion.png?t=1705209899"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get access to a lot more stuff! Make amazing builds with over 250 items, 55 heroes, 120 relics and 55 origins.<br/></li><li>Continue the adventure in the third act, and meet the final boss in a special act!<br/></li><li>Face 30 challenging enemies and 10 bosses!<br/></li><li>Progress through 5 difficulties which will challenge your knowledge and strategy!<br/></li><li>Push your builds to their limit in the endless mode, a mode where you try to reach the highest floor!<br/></li><li>Experience the game in diverse and fun new ways with the challenge modes!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_ENDLESS.gif?t=1705209899"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summoners War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2426960/Summoners_War/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2426960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>▶Features</strong><br/><strong>[Tactical RPG play]</strong><br/>Witness the dazzling display of each monster 's unique skills.<br/>23 different Rune sets to pick and choose additional abilities for your monsters!<br/>Come up with the best strategy to win battles in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[Endless Fun]</strong><br/>Decorate your Village, battle other summoners , explore dungeons , fight in PvP battles , expand your collection, train monsters , and more.<br/><br/><strong>[The Key of Colletion RPG : Massive Collection]</strong><br/>Fire, Water, Wind, Light and Dark!<br/>5 different attributes, and 1500 different monsters!<br/>Collect as many monsters as you can and win battles with your own decks .<br/><br/><strong>[Real-time Raid]</strong><br/>Battle as a team with your greatest monsters !<br/>A real-time battle with 3 users!<br/>Defeat the boss with your fellow Summoners using various tactics.<br/><br/><strong>[Homunculus]</strong><br/>The Forbidden Summoning Magic has finally been revealed!<br/>You can Evolve the skill of your choice with this special monster.<br/>Summon Homunculus and show off your strategy in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[All about Turn-Based RPG : World Arena]</strong><br/>Enjoy a real-time battle with Summoners worldwide!<br/>Experience a breathtaking battle that starts from Pick &amp; Ban.<br/>Reveal your unique strategy to the world and win battles .<br/><br/><strong>[Guild Content]</strong><br/>A sensational Guild PvP battle in the Isle of Conquest!<br/>Explore the Tartarus' Labyrinth and dungeons with Guild Members.<br/>Make your Guild the greatest of all.<br/><br/><strong>[Dimension Hole]</strong><br/>Fight against the ancient power emerged from a new dimension!<br/>Defeat the Ancient Guardians and meet the powerful monsters with new awakening power.<br/><br/><strong>[Artifact]</strong><br/>Artifacts are now dropped with MAX power-up levels!<br/>Summoners , fight against the powerful bosses and acquire Artifacts!<br/>Enhance your monsters with various sub properties of Artifacts.<br/><br/><strong>[Progression and Farming Structure Revamp]</strong><br/>Summoner progression structure renewed and content reward greatly improved!<br/>Dive into Summoners War and experience the enhanced progression system!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portal: Revolution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/601360/Portal_Revolution/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Portal: Revolution is a fan-made mod for Portal 2 which plays before the events of Portal 2 in the dead and decaying Aperture facility.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/ezgif-7-f507c3c464_1_.gif?t=1705083406"><br/><strong>Over 40 new puzzles</strong><br/>The campaign contains 40 brand new puzzles making use of new test elements and presents existing mechanics in a new way not seen in Portal 2.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resurrected "Pneumatic Diversity Vent" element<br/></li><li> New laser cube variant<br/></li><li> Over 15 puzzles using only the blue Portal-Gun<br/></li><li> Gel Cleansing Field</li></ul><br/><strong>Difficulty</strong><br/>Portal: Revolutions puzzle difficulty starts where Portal 2 stops, but fear not. All new mechanics and advanced portal tricks are taught to you. We have ensured through rigorous playtesting that every player can solve the puzzles. Although very few chambers require portals to be fired mid-air, no puzzles require advanced tricky movement.<br/><br/>Depending on your experience with Portal 2 mechanics, you can expect about 5 to 7 hours of playtime.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/banner_story_2.gif?t=1705083406"><br/>Set inbetween Portal and Portal 2, Portal: Revolution tells a brand new story using new characters. You play as a test subject who is awoken by a personality sphere called Stirling and join his mission to find a powerful device capable of restoring Aperture to its former glory.<h2 class="bb_tag">ENGINE</h2>Portal: Revolution uses a modified version of Portal 2: Community Edition's engine, which is a custom version of the Counter-Strike: Global Offensive Source Engine branch using licensed source code provided by Valve Software.<br/><br/>This allowed us to introduce many mechanics and improvements to the engine to create an experience which would be impossible in Portal 2.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Memories</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2495450/Winter_Memories/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1705043544"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Header_EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter-Memories-Cards_GIF.gif?t=1705043544"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Trading_Others_EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_1-EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/>After the unforgettable summer memories you’ve made half a year ago, Yui, Rio, and Miyuki are back. With the change of seasons and the cold falling snow, a new page to your story is about to begin. <br/><br/>Revisit the peaceful, seaside town, and spend time catching up with your family and friends.<br/><br/>What new memories will you make this winter?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_3-EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Miyuki_EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Rio_EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Yui_EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_4-EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/><strong>A Relaxing, Adventure RPG<strong><br/><br/><strong>Explore the Beautiful, Seaside Town<strong><br/><br/><strong>Manage How You Spend Your TIme<strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pesticide Not Required: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2480450/Pesticide_Not_Required_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The free prologue for Pesticide Not Required, a game that combines auto-attacking bullet heaven roguelites with farming game mechanics to create an expansive set of strategies and build combinations. Destroy huge hordes of evil insects, grow tons of crops, create your own build path, and unlock unique characters to play with!<br/><br/>This prologue version contains similar mechanics to the main game, but has less achievements, progression unlocks, unlockable characters, weapons, maps, and enemy varieties.<h2 class="bb_tag">Create Overpowered Builds</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/extras/CombatChaosFisher.gif?t=1705210453"><br/>You are the bullet hell! Grow an arsenal of ridiculous weapons and craft your own unique build with a combination of 40+ stats. Additionally, each character has their own unique traits that keep runs fresh.<h2 class="bb_tag">Farm, Fish, and Mine</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/extras/FarmFishMineWinterGif.gif?t=1705210453"><br/>Earn vital gold and experience from growing crops, catching fish, and mining. Expand your plot to harvest huge quantities of crops and build carefully to enhance your farming, fishing, and mining capabilities.<h2 class="bb_tag">Automate Your Farm With Pets</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/extras/PetsGifAutumn.gif?t=1705210453"><br/>Recruit friendly pets that will enhance your farm, collect loot, and kill enemies.<br/><br/>Other Features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Season-themed map variations with multiple difficulty levels<br/></li><li>Many unlockable characters with special traits<br/></li><li>Persistent skill tree upgrades<br/></li><li>Quick ~20-minute play sessions<br/></li><li>Tons of achievements to unlock<br/></li><li>Full gamepad and keyboard support<br/></li><li>Go WUMBO!</li></ul><br/>Pesticide Not Required: Prologue is inspired by awesome games like Brotato, Vampire Survivors, and Atomicrops.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Esports Godfather Origin</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2739460/Esports_Godfather_Origin/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/游戏简介英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>"Esport Godfather" is a management simulation card game that revolves around the theme of MOBA esports. In this game, you will assume the role of a coach in an esports club and personally build your own team! Starting from scratch, what kind of playstyle will you devise for your team? In a constantly evolving meta, can you derive a unique understanding of what it takes to win? How will you unlock the potential of your handpicked athletes and mold them into superstars?<br/><br/>Ultimately, will you be able to become a legendary figure in the esports industry, crafting your own esports story and lifting the championship trophy?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/选手培养英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>Each athlete is unique! They all have their own strengths and weaknesses.<br/>If an athlete's efficiency in earning money increases over time, they are undoubtedly a skilled late-game specialist.<br/>Successful ambushes can unlock hidden potential, propelling some athletes onto the path of godlike.<br/>As a coach, it's your responsibility to analyze each athlete's characteristics, devise training plans tailored to their needs, and guide them on their journey to becoming superstars!<br/><br/>· Every athlete possesses distinct abilities that will impact their performance on the battlefield!<br/>· An athlete's hero pool is crucial for Ban &amp; Pick strategies!<br/>· The tactic cards utilized by athletes in matches serve as the foundation of all strategies!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/版本变更英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>The meta environment is ever-changing!<br/>Changes in the equipment pool, the structure of economic income, and the source of decisive advantages, even slight alterations to the rules can drastically shift the priorities of Ban &amp; Pick and alter the strategic approach!<br/><br/>· Equipment will be added or removed as the versions change!<br/>· The timing of crucial team fights will shift with each version update, making team composition crucial!<br/>· Does harassment grant more gold? Do kills damage towers? Each gameplay rule brings a fresh experience!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/指挥战斗英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>You have the power to command the battlefield, with athletes attentively listening to your orders.<br/>Should you play it safe and focus on farming under the towers, or launch aggressive assaults and initiate attacks?<br/>Perfect team composition requires perfect leadership! The game is ever-changing, and you must face your opponents head-on!<br/><br/>· Each hero and athlete possesses their own tactic cards. It is through creative combinations and strategic application that they become unstoppable!<br/>· Offense or defense? Aggression or caution? The outcome rests in your hands. Formulate strategies and implement tactics!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/其他内容英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>· Over 50 unique heroes in the starting lineup, each with their own special abilities!<br/>· 200+ tactic cards, granting you control over the battlefield!<br/>· Diverse athlete training options! As a mentor, it's important to tailor your teachings to each individual!<br/>· Unearth young talents and cultivate new forces in the youth training camp!<br/>· Choose sponsors, a top-tier club deserves the support of top-tier sponsors!<br/>· Trash-talking sessions, asserting dominance is a must before crucial matches!<br/>· Abundance of events, includes unexpected occurrences, athlete communication, team pep talks!<br/>· Training match plans, knowing your opponents inside out ensures victory after victory!<br/>· Regular season, playoffs, transfer periods—different decisions await you at different times!<br/>· When athletes reach their limits, you must help them break through and reach new heights!<br/>· Create a custom team logo for your club!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/工作室LOGO英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703868247"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1704804364"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1704380508"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1704380508"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1705051187"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1705051187"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1705051187"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1705051187"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1705051187"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1703186631"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1704392583"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1704392583"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1704392583"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1705031379"> </img></a><br/><br/>Vegas Infinite is for players aged 18+ only.<br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MageCraft</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2344550/MageCraft/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2344550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Magic Meets Strategy</h2><br/>MageCraft is all about using magic to outsmart enemies in close-quarters turn-based encounters. Stay behind cover and keep your foes at bay, while raining down a wide variety of spells to overcome the odds.<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover Shadowy Secrets</h2><br/>Meet a team of young wizards at the beginning of their magical education. Apprenticed to the most powerful sorcerer known to history, but stalked by mysterious enemies. Hardly having even begun, these magicians will have to contend with unexpected enemies and insidious dark magic.<h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Spell Book</h2><br/>The main progression of MageCraft is in learning new spells for your team to wield in battle. Each wizard has their own specialization, and can gain increasingly powerful magic which they will need to take on the dangerous enemies the game presents. Balance the massive damage-dealing elemental magic with the strategic AoE nature spells or wield the power of time itself to give yourself an upper hand in combat! With many devastating spells available to acquire, you will always be finding new ways to outwit your enemy.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complex IV</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2460770/The_Complex_IV/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2460770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Complex IV is a role-playing game based on Dungeons &amp; Dragons. Using a simplified subset of the SRD 5.1 ruleset, the game doesn't use aspects like class, race or gender. Instead, skills are used to determine what your character is good at. Characters can reach god-status at level 20.<br>
<br>
Play on your own or with up to 5 other players online. Combine your skills or compete against each other - it's your choice.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Malice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157060/Project_Malice/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157060/extras/page_final.gif?t=1705175487"><br/><i><br/>The year is 213X. Earth has gone to s**t.<br/><br/>The infected roam the streets. They've killed everything you live for. Your kings have fled to the cosmos. Your gods have stopped answering your prayers. Your money is worthless. You have nowhere to go. Hunger and thirst begins to set in. There is no hope. Only pain and suffering.<br/><br/>But perhaps, amidst the chaos... you can find something to make your time worthwhile. This is where it all began... and this is where it will end. The future of humanity is in your hands.</i><h2 class="bb_tag">OVERVIEW</h2><br/>Project Malice is an isometric third person shooter roguelike about a ruined Earth, and those who are unfortunate enough to dwell on it. What started off as just an uncontrollable outbreak of infection transformed into something far much worse. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157060/extras/page_combat.gif?t=1705175487"><h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A myriad of enemies, like a lot of enemies<br/></li><li>Bosses that will curb stomp you to a pulp<br/></li><li>Tons of random whatever to collect<br/></li><li>Allies who are dumb enough to follow you around<br/></li><li>Dialogue that lets you <i>really</i> get to know the characters<br/></li><li>A bunch of secrets and extra challenges for you to walk past<br/></li><li>Cameos from other games<br/></li><li>Way too much lore</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">OTHER INFO</h2><br/>This game was originally created for Ludum Dare 49, which eventually spiraled into something much more. I wanted it to be an amalgamation of everything I've made up until this point, so the game contains a lot of references to my other games which take place in the same universe. It's possible you might need to play some of those if you would like to understand the full scope of the settings, characters, and story.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kalyzmyr</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1826090/Kalyzmyr/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1826090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fe28ByRr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1826090/extras/spr_icon_joindiscord.png?t=1705168055"/></a><br/><br/><strong>Once the legendary warrior Smyrna, now long forgotten in the depths of Kalyzmyr. Break your chains and earn your freedom! Use your mighty axe and devastate your foes that keep you locked in Kalyzmyr! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1826090/extras/ezgif.com-gif-maker__2_.gif?t=1705168055"><br/><br/>Fight and defend through hordes of demons in this old-school fast-paced action game. <br/>Each floor starts with a defense phase where you defend yourself from hordes of creatures by buying and upgrading defensive equipment. Kill monsters to earn money and experience. Level up your stats and skills, loot chests to level up your equipment using materials. Optimize your build to overcome challanges.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1826090/extras/Inventory1-small.gif?t=1705168055"><br/><br/><strong>Randomized boons that can either boost your strength or weaken you.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Feeling weak? Or did you get unlucky? Break the door to turn back to the previous floor anytime. Farm lower levels and be prepared to face stronger opponents.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Unleash Your True Power</strong><br/>Unleash Smyrna’s true potential by activating ‘Berserk’ mode which allows you to attack at maximum speed for the duration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1826090/extras/BerserkRun_Combat1-small.gif?t=1705168055"><br/><br/><strong>Challange Bosses</strong><br/> You can challange boss of the current level by paying Crystals to the Mushroom King for extra materials.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1826090/extras/BossChallangeRoom1-Small.gif?t=1705168055"><br/><br/><strong>Defeat three bosses and make your escape from the sunless dungeon Kalyzmyr.</strong> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garbageman</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2681500/Garbageman/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2681500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Frank is a garbage man that's on a very important mission: he must keep the columns of the unstable Clock Building free of trash bags in order to prevent the building's imminent collapse. In this simple but fun arcade game, help Frank do his job and get a big score!<br/><br/>&gt; Main features/characteristics:<br/>- Simple gameplay;<br/>- Score attack;<br/>- Six columns to protect;<br/>- Three kinds of presents to collect:<br/><i>-&gt; present 1: score points;<br/>-&gt; present 2: powerups (eg. gravity reduction, jump speed etc.);<br/>-&gt; present 3: special (trash bag magnet for up to 5 seconds).</i><br/>- Retro-style graphics;<br/>- High Score autosave.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEZORUB</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2745220/LEZORUB/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Is a captivating simulation and clicker game where players take on the persona of a proficient carpenter striving to survive in the wild. Their tasks include efficiently handling contracts, enhancing carpentry abilities, collecting valuable wood, and expanding their settlement by building new spaces and obtaining advanced tools. The overarching objective is to craft exquisite furniture pieces and thrive in this challenging setting.<br/><br/>Resource gathering involves collecting various types of wood, each with its own unique qualities and worth including oak, pine, mahogany, birch, and cedar. Different woods have different harvesting times, with more valuable ones taking longer to gather.</i><br/><i><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Players have the ability to craft furniture by utilizing various woods and crafting techniques to create personalized designs.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base expansion includes the construction of additional buildings, which can be built using in-game currency. These buildings can include workshops, warehouses, and specialized facilities.</li></ul></i><br/><strong><i><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2></i></strong><br/><i><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The player must fulfill contracts with specific requirements, including wood type and furniture design.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Successful completion of contracts results in rewards, reputation, and experience points.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Seasonal or special event contracts provide exclusive rewards and furniture designs.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Carpentry skills are honed through points earned for completing contracts.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Skill upgrades unlock new furniture designs and base improvements.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Players can conduct research by investing money to unlock superior carpentry methods.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Advanced research yields permanent skill upgrades and bonuses.</li></ul></i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liquid Light</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2750690/Liquid_Light/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2750690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A relaxing 1bit puzzle game set in a world where all the light is liquid. There are all sorts of creatures in the darkness, waiting for the light to bring them form, but no need to worry, they are quite tame. <br>
<br>
This puzzle game revolves around utilizing the liquid light and liquid dark to gain the curiosity and cooperation of the other creatures in the world. The Lightposts and Darkposts will be tools for your success, but with the help of the other creatures in the world, can you progress. While sometimes the creatures are covered in darkness and lack physical form, that can sometimes be advantageous as they no longer block the way. Sometimes though, you need a creature who's body is covered in light that allows it to take a physical form and help you cross gaps that would otherwise spell your doom.<br>
<br>
This is a puzzle game inspired by the classic game Lode Runner, but capitalizing on the puzzle aspect and downplaying the franticness of the game. The Creatures in the world also feature incredibly simple AI so they always do exactly what you intend for them to do. <br>
<br>
This game also features a level select which is accessible through the pause menu just in case you get hung up on one particular puzzle.<br/>
<br/>
Complete with 8-bit sound effects and peculiar creatures, this game is certain to tickle your brain!<br/>
<br/>
This game currently features:<br/>
- 1 Tutorial<br/>
- 16 Levels<br/>
- Five Creature variants<br/>
- Levers<br/>
- Two Lamppost Variants<br/>
- Light Platforms<br/>
- Also a home screen... because of course						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retro Run</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1476720/Retro_Run/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1476720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Retro Run</strong> is an fast paced FPS platfromer, where you platform your way to the end goal, <strong>the runner energydrink!</strong><br/><br/>Do everything in your power to get to the precious <strong>Runner energy drink</strong>! The game will take you through diffrent types of ''<i><strong>gamemodes</strong></i>'' that will be challenging their own way. <br/>Platform your way thorugh the abyss in the <strong>platforms</strong><br/>And balance on the cars to try not to fall onto the street under you while enemies try to end you in <strong>Car Ride</strong>!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edge Of Survival</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2644960/Edge_Of_Survival/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2644960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Escape to a relaxing, survival sandbox surrounded by wildlife and nature. Scavenge materials and craft tools to turn your base<br/>into a warm, well-supplied home. Survive by fishing, hunting, cooking, and growing your own food. Complete tasks in order to<br/>maintain the forest running. but... be careful though, the forest is as dangerous as it is wonderful.<br/><br/>EXPLORE<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2644960/extras/ExploreGif.gif?t=1705146152"><br/>Explore a living, colorful world, ranging from dense forests to dark caves.<br/><br/><br/>GATHER, CRAFT and BUILD<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2644960/extras/GatherCraftBuildGif.gif?t=1705146152"><br/>There are hundreds of items that can be crafted and used for survival, from the simplest tools made of sticks and rocks to advanced Rifle,<br/>improved armor, and tools. You can also<br/>build a variety of workshops, from primitive leather dryers to pre-industrial era machines<br/><br/>GROW<br/>Nurture delicate (and delicious) plants, Eat them raw or cook them for better nutritional values.<br/><br/>SURVIVE<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2644960/extras/Survive.gif?t=1705146152"><br/>Dangerous animals roam some areas of the forest. It's best to keep your distance if you can. Or simply upgrade your gear to fight them						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astra Strike</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2560750/Astra_Strike/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2560750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Astra Strike is a team-based first-person tactical shooter set in the near future. Players play as one agent In the main game mode, players are assigned to either the attacking or defending team with each team having five players on it. Players have abilities. <br>
<br>
Every player starts each round with a "classic" pistol and four abilities. Other weapons and ability charges can be purchased using an in-game economic system that awards money based on the outcome of the round any kills the player is responsible for, and any objectives completed. <br>
<br>
The game has an assortment of weapons including secondary guns like sidearms and primary guns like submachine guns, shotguns, assault rifles and sniper rifles. There are automatic and semi-automatic weapons that each have a unique shooting pattern that has to be controlled by the player to be able to shoot accurately.<br>
<br>
● 1 Agent<br/>
● 2 Team-based gamemodes<br/>
● 6 Unique maps<br/>
● Exhaustively optimized for high frames-per-second gameplay.<br/>
● Proximity-based voice chat for real-time communication with friendlies						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groove that Goob</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2632630/Groove_that_Goob/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Not so long ago…</h2>The party-loving Globulons threw a rave so wild that it shattered their cherished Oracle Jukebox––the sole source of music in the Mixolydian Galaxy. To restore cosmic harmony, a lone Globulon named Goob emerges, setting its sights on abducting the Milky Way's source of sound. To do this, Goob must sneak to the top of Astral Ace’s penthouse party in a towering spacescraper. In this top-down, rhythm-stealth game, players groove their way across vibrant dance floors, evade wild partygoers, and absorb dancers to inherit their unique rhythms.<h2 class="bb_tag">Dance like Everyone's Watching</h2>Engage in rhythm-stealth gameplay, where each level unfolds a rhythmic adventure. Move consistently to the beat, and elevate your dance style by switching up rhythms through the absorption of fellow dancers. The cosmic party comes alive with Dynamic Dance-Offs, triggered when Goob slips up in front of other dancers. Prove your party prowess in these encounters by matching button inputs with precision and hopefully evading detection.<h2 class="bb_tag">An Absorbent Alien Attacks</h2>Unleash Goob's shapeshifting power by absorbing unsuspecting dancers strategically. Goob will not only copy their appearance but also their unique rhythms; use this power wisely to navigate across dangerous dance tiles with cunning and creativity.<br/><br/><i>Groove that Goob</i> invites you to a galaxy where rhythm meets stealth. Dance your way through the vibrant disco, face off in deadly dances, and absorb the essence of the party to orchestrate a cosmic comeback!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genjiro: Samurai Defense</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2381310/Genjiro_Samurai_Defense/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2381310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A Samurai Hack &amp; Slash, Roguelike, City Defense Game!<br>
Upgrade your skills and defend the city from waves of incoming enemies.<br>
<br>
For how long can you hold them off?<br>
<br>
Each character has 3 Skills + Dodge (L-Shift, Space) and Block (Right click, Reduces incoming damage by 60%)<br>
<br/>
Playable characters : Samurai , Onna-musha <br/>
<br/>
Ninja and Monk characters will be released in future updates.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
*please report any bug you found in the game to the email in "Credit" Tab in main menu*						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incubus Quest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2429890/Incubus_Quest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429890/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1705122015"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429890/extras/Incubus_Quest_Description_1_EN.png?t=1705122015"><br/>A war between succubi and incubi has been raging for years in Lugrand, and Shadow was unluckily born as the weakest incubus there ever was.<br/>When the succubi launch a surprise attack and capture or wipe out nearly the entire incubus population, Shadow makes it out thanks to a mysterious power he awakened to. But since he's the weakest, it's decided that he needs to train against humans before taking on the succubi. He teleports to Ardia, a different world where he'll gather experience and maybe make an ally or two. The problem is, he's so weak as an incubus he risks defeat even at the hand of humans...<br/><br/>Explore Ardia and grow stronger before returning to Lugrand to mount a resistance and launch a counterattack against the succubi and their army!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429890/extras/Incubus_Quest_Description_2_EN.png?t=1705122015"><br/>Learn to handle yourself and your foes through many battles. You're weak, but that doesn't mean you're powerless! Battles are as much a conversation as a fight, and you must control the ebb and flow to come out on top by using different skills depending on your current foe's inclinations. Pick your fights based on your current strengths and overcome every roadblock.<br/><br/>Many foes await you, but the world of Ardia has many weaker targets spread across its wilderness areas and the three main cities. Being defeated isn't a problem thanks to your newly awakened power, but actually defeating the enemy may be another matter entirely. Battle as many people as you can and grow stronger before returning to Alvarez to take the fight to the succubi!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429890/extras/Incubus_Quest_Description_3_EN.png?t=1705122015"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429890/extras/Incubus_Quest_Description_Rangeleis_EN.png?t=1705122015"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429890/extras/Incubus_Quest_Description_Silhouetta_EN.png?t=1705122015"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429890/extras/Incubus_Quest_Description_4_EN.png?t=1705122015"><br/><strong>Dozens of unique foes</strong><br/>On the road to becoming stronger, you'll face dozens of named humans and succubi alike. Each has a different story to tell and will try to exploit your weaknesses in different ways. And if you fail, well... You can always try again! Just try not to get too used to it, or you might start enjoying it.<br/><br/><strong>Sprawling cities</strong><br/>The many settlements in Ardia offer a vast array of activities that will help you grow stronger and earn some money. Casino? Check. Bath house? Check. Secret laboratory with androids and giant robots? Check! Don't waste too much time though. The incubi back home are counting on you!<br/><br/><strong>Character customization</strong><br/>You'll be able to modify some of the main character's features for a more personalized experience. This includes physical characteristics, inclinations, as well as many costumes you'll acquire through the game. Some NPCs get costumes as well, both friends and foes!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crystal Story: Dawn of Dusk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1746590/Crystal_Story_Dawn_of_Dusk/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1746590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Welcome to the World of Crystal Story!</h2><br/>Crystal Story: Dawn of Dusk marks the introduction and foundation of the series!  <br/><br/>Crystal Story is a series that blends together charming retro-style graphics, with fast-paced action and turn-based battles, heavily inspired by 16-bit classics! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1746590/extras/mansion-opt.gif?t=1705104011"><h2 class="bb_tag">- Meet Mina -</h2><br/>Players take the role of Mina, a young adventurer from the <i>Dawnside</i>, who must traverse a perilous and shattered world called the <i>Duskside</i>, to find her long-lost brother who was kidnapped by the forces of a great demon named <i>Termina</i>.<h2 class="bb_tag">- It’s All in the Arts -</h2><br/>Mina’s gifted with the ability to use fire-elemental magic called <i>Arts</i>! Arts allow her to navigate harsh conditions while battling any foes that stand in her way! Mina can also supercharge Arts to trade blows with stronger enemies in tougher encounters!<h2 class="bb_tag">- Features -</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>	Use Arts to traverse a challenging world and defeat enemies and solve puzzles!<br/></li><li>	A hybrid retro-modern-styled adventure will bring you back to the past, but with a modern twist!<br/></li><li>	Take on optional side quests in future updates!<br/></li><li>	Includes an optional CRT filter for nostalgic flair! </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">- Dynamic Updates -</h2><br/>Besides run-of-the-mill bugfixes, tweaks, and quality-of-life improvements, Dawn of Dusk will be regularly updated to keep things fresh with additional content, areas, sidequests, and <strong><i>more</i></strong>.    <br/><br/><strong><i>Completely free of charge. Simply update and have fun!* </i></strong><br/><br/><i>*(Please note: some content will require you to complete Dawn of Dusk in order to be unlocked.)</i> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die Erdnussbutter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2726180/Die_Erdnussbutter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Shoot, dash, and power your way through enemy lines in the arcade-style 2D side scroller, Die Erdnussbutter! Use the power of peanut butter to destroy enemy rations, battle bosses, and spread the smooth (or crunchy) flavor of freedom throughout the battlefield. Peanut butter not included.<br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>4 weapons, each with their own special and ultimate abilities<br/></li><li>3 stages<br/></li><li>3 bosses<br/></li><li>14 unique upgrades to power up with<br/></li><li>Randomly generated levels for non-stop replayability</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arsenal Online</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2641740/Arsenal_Online/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2641740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Arsenal Online is a high-octane 2D shooter. Jump into some quick and explosive shoot-em-up action!<h2 class="bb_tag">SOLO AND CO-OP PLAY</h2>Play one of many fun game modes either solo or with a friend online! Each game mode has a different objective, such as <strong>Sniper</strong> where accuracy is rewarded, or <strong>Time Attack</strong> where maximum kills is the goal.<h2 class="bb_tag">HUNDREDS OF WEAPONS AND ATTACHMENTS</h2>Unlock hundreds of weapons and attachments, ranging from pistols, SMGs, assault rifles, LMGs, sniper rifles, and more!<h2 class="bb_tag">FIRING RANGE</h2>Just want to equip a weapon and shoot targets? Enter the firing range where all weapons and attachments are immediately accessible.<h2 class="bb_tag">KEY FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hundreds of weapons and attachments to unlock<br/></li><li>Multiple game modes<br/></li><li>Customizable loadouts and classes<br/></li><li>Rank progression system<br/></li><li>Online multiplayer or local play<br/></li><li>Worldwide leaderboards<br/></li><li>Achievements</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hopebringer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1520420/The_Hopebringer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1520420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Hopebringer is a top down RPG, featuring procedurally generated scenarios in a fantasy setting. Partake in single player, or online co-op adventures. Unlock new scenarios, which you can then repeat at any time in multiplayer. <br/><br/><strong>Key Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Top down combat in a fantasy survival RPG setting.<br/></li><li>Procedurally generated scenarios which are repeatable. <br/></li><li>Unlock new scenarios as you progress. <br/></li><li>Single player or co-op multiplayer.<br/></li><li>Three unique skill lines for each class. <br/></li><li>Customize your skills by improving them with up to 25 ranks per skill.<br/></li><li>Battle vs. powerful bosses.<br/></li><li>Adventure alongside NPC companions and pets.<br/></li><li>Upgrade your equipment using a socket system.<br/></li><li>Transmute items to create more powerful variations.<br/></li><li>Powered by Unreal Engine 5. </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TYRONE SOULZ</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2585050/TYRONE_SOULZ/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							It was supposed to be an uneventful arrest, but after the suspect made a blood pact with Yakub, this rookie cop is in for much more than he bargained for. Can he defeat Tyrone and return home to his family?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>The TL;DR</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The world's first and only Yakubian inspired souls-like (extremely good gameplay)<br/></li><li>Epic boss battle against Tyrone (a black man)<br/></li><li>Full voice acting<br/></li><li>Drink white energy drinks to recover HP<br/></li><li>It's only $1.95 just buy it<br/></li><li>The trailer is better than the game<br/></li><li>Canon to the lore of the CUCKOLD SIMULATOR universe<br/></li><li>Extremely difficult (I can barely beat it)</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585050/extras/try_your_best.png?t=1705122218"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2585050/extras/movie_001.gif?t=1705122218"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Something</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696520/Something/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2696520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The easiest game you're ever going to play. Or is it?<br>
<br>
Keep doing Something as the timer goes up. If you do Nothing, you lose.<br>
<br>
If you don't like doing Something, go play Nothing instead.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping With Sakuya Izayoi</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2739620/Sleeping_With_Sakuya_Izayoi/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2>In this small visual novel, your partner Sakuya Izayoi is tired after a long day of working at the Scarlet Devil Mansion, she invites you to relax with her in her private quarters! Talk to her, kiss her or just simply enjoy each other's presence.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Chose up to 3 locations, the mansion quarters, the forest of magic or even an apartment room! <br/></li><li>Ambient music <br/></li><li>Gorgeous artwork with various expressions! <br/></li><li>Kiss Sakuya! <br/></li><li>Talk to Sakuya! <br/></li><li>Relax with Sakuya! <br/></li><li>Sakuya! </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JustScroll</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2675800/JustScroll/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2675800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							Change the volume of your system in an intuitive way by scrolling with your mouse. You could be watching a video, playing a fullscreen game or talking with friends, you no longer have to minimize anything or lose focus by going through convoluted menus every time you want to adjust your volume. All you have to do is either hold the Windows key and scroll, or simply bring your cursor to the taskbar and scroll.<br>
<br>
Allow JustScroll to make your Windows experience easy and intuitive. Tried and tested for more than half-a-decade to ensure optimal feel and ease of use, it works by seamlessly integrating with your machine. Just install and enjoy.<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
- Windows Key + Scroll. Control your volume no matter what you are doing. This will NOT minimize your game / application.<br>
	- Volume Adjust: hold the Windows key and scroll to adjust your volume.<br/>
	- Mute: hold the Windows key and middle-click with your mouse to mute.<br/>
- Taskbar Scroll. Control your volume with just one hand in an intuitive and easy way.<br/>
	- Volume Adjust: position your cursor on the taskbar and scroll.<br/>
	- Mute: position your cursor on the taskbar and middle-click with your mouse.<br/>
<br/>
Advanced Features:<br/>
- Emergency Mute. Has your friend ever sent you an annoyingly loud video that you wanted to mute instantly? Well now you can, as JustScroll has an "emergency mute" that will mute your volume instantly as soon as you scroll your volume down fast in a panic.<br/>
- Precision Scroll. For the many that have an obsession with volume numbers, hold the left mouse button for a more precise adjustment of the volume. Is your volume stuck between 8 or 12? Bring it to 10. Or the other way around, whatever you prefer!<br/>
<br/>
Because of how intuitive changing your volume with JustScroll is, it will feel like second nature in no time. It also launches with Windows, which you can always change by right-clicking on the tray icon and unticking "Run on Startup".<br/>
<br/>
JustScroll offers a modern look and feel that fits right with the contemporary Windows environment, as it supports both dark and light Windows themes in regards to its tray icon looks.<br/>
<br/>
Download and start scrolling now!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nyran Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2540810/Nyran_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an epic journey with <strong>Nyran Survivors</strong>, an action-packed roguelite where you'll confront endless hordes of foes and take on formidable bosses. Unleash powerful skills, evolve your character and master ancient spells. Earn spoils from each battle to unlock new classes, upgrade your abilities, and forge a path to become the ultimate Mediator.<h2 class="bb_tag">Classes</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540810/extras/Classes.gif?t=1705082297"><br/>Choose your path from an array of distinct classes, each offering unparalleled abilities. Play up to <strong>10</strong> classes with more on the horizon.<h2 class="bb_tag">Items</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540810/extras/Items.gif?t=1705082297"><br/>Over <strong>80 items</strong> for you to equip with more along the way.<h2 class="bb_tag">Skills</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540810/extras/Spells1.gif?t=1705082297"><br/>Nyran Survivors has over <strong>100 unique spells and abilities</strong> for you to collect and master with more to come!<h2 class="bb_tag">Boss Fights</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540810/extras/Bosses.gif?t=1705082297"><br/><strong>6 unique bosses</strong> per map for you to defeat for a total of <strong>30 bosses</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540810/extras/Upgrade.gif?t=1705082297"><br/>Upgrade your class through <strong>40 levels</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">Passives</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540810/extras/Passives.gif?t=1705082297"><br/>Select from a variety of <strong>12</strong> distinct passives to enhance your abilities throughout the battle, with the option to have 3 active simultaneously.<h2 class="bb_tag">Leaderboards</h2>Can you secure the top spot and become a true legend? Let your name shine on the global stage of Nyran Survivors! The game lists the top 100 players' rating per map.<br/><br/><i>* uses a logged in Discord account</i> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARRIVAL: ZERO EARTH</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1613580/ARRIVAL_ZERO_EARTH/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1613580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1613580/extras/steam_store_custom_content_620x180.png?t=1705080862"><br/><br/>Aliens have invaded the earth and you have to assemble an army of local townspeople to fight them!<br/><br/>Fight giant alien machinery, navigate through different biomes and alternate history timelines to discover and obliterate the true prime evil.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Set in Finland during the Winter in the '90s <br/></li><li> Roguelike semi-autobattler gameplay<br/></li><li> Control one large army through different procedurally generated levels<br/></li><li> Collect items to gain new abilities<br/></li><li> Different Unit types to build your army from<br/></li><li> Units choose who they attack automatically, but you control where they move</li></ul><br/>In the game you unlock new units and items between runs, but there are no permanent stat upgrades between runs.<br/><br/>The game has:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 7 Unique Biomes<br/></li><li> 18 Different Unit Types<br/></li><li> 27 Different Item Types<br/></li><li> 5 Enemy Types<br/></li><li> 1 Boss Fight</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F*CK STALIN</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2711350/FCK_STALIN/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2711350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">ABOUT</h2>In F*CK STALIN your task is to torture Joseph Stalin and get as many points as possible using a wide variety of blocks and weapons.<h2 class="bb_tag">GAMEPLAY</h2>In the game you can build your own torture constructions, create an infinite number of Stalins and inflict suffering on him with firearms and white weapons, for which you receive points.<h2 class="bb_tag">LEADERBOARD</h2>All the points earned in the game are added up and then recorded in the global leaderboard. Perhaps it is YOU who will find yourself at the top of it!<h2 class="bb_tag">PHOTO MODE</h2>You can stop the game at any time using the advanced photo mode to take the perfect shot and share it with the community.<h2 class="bb_tag">STEAM WORKSHOP</h2>The game has support for Steam Workshop. Download maps created by the community or add your own creations.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Stories: Alice's Adventures Collector's Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733270/Christmas_Stories_Alices_Adventures_Collectors_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2733270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You’re enjoying your Christmas when the White Rabbit from Wonderland comes to you for help! The Christmas spirit is vanishing all over the world, but why? Come along for a fun adventure and return joy to the world by restoring harmony to the characters of Wonderland! Meet familiar characters in new places in this enchanting hidden-object puzzle adventure game!<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore another classic Christmas tale in the bonus game!<br/></li><li>Replay HOPs and mini-games!<br/></li><li>Complete your achievements and collectibles!<br/></li><li>Enjoy exclusive art, music, and other unique content!<br/></li><li>Never get lost with the strategy guide!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rutabaga Desert Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2679270/Rutabaga_Desert_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2679270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Lead the Invasion of the Middle Yeast as Rutabaga III and His Trusted Ally, Habanero Jr.</h2>After Rutabaga III's publication of his Cruciferous Manifesto, he has put his fellow vegetable freedom fighters on the front lines. All part of his genius plan, pushing the human forces forward, and allowing for him and Habanero Jr. to sneak into the Middle Yeast and finally destroy the Flying Oppression Cube... once and for all.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Classic side-scrolling action<br/></li><li>Parallax backgrounds and multiple areas <br/></li><li>Singleplayer and Local Co-op (Multi-player requires multiple devices)<br/></li><li>Highscore system to compete with friends<br/></li><li>Tight flight controls and mashable fire button<br/></li><li>Power-ups <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2679270/extras/Power-ups.png?t=1705078853"><br/></img></li><li>4 different enemies, with rayshield variants <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2679270/extras/Enemies-sheet.png?t=1705078853"><br/></img></li><li>Boss enemy, the Flying Oppression Cube<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2679270/extras/THE_CUBE_turning4-sheet.png?t=1705078853"><br/></img></li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom of Atham: Crown of the Champions</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1676380/Kingdom_of_Atham_Crown_of_the_Champions/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i>Kingdom of Atham: Crown of the Champions</i></strong><br/><br/>Embark on an immersive medieval fantasy survival odyssey where every decision shapes your destiny. Reclaim the stolen Crown and face the malevolent Shadowbringers.<br/><br/><strong><i>Crafting Mastery:</i></strong><br/>Forge your legacy with an intricate crafting system. Create powerful weapons, enchanted armor, and essential tools. Customize your gear to suit your playstyle and enhance your chances of survival.<br/><br/><strong><i>Skills and Abilities:</i></strong><br/>Hone your skills as you progress. Choose from diverse skills, specializing in combat, magic, summoning dragons and more or crafting. Evolve your character, adapting to new challenges and unlocking unique abilities and weapons to become the ultimate champion of Atham.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676380/extras/1.png?t=1705078563"><br/><br/><strong><i>Mystical Magic:</i></strong><br/>Unleash the arcane with a rich magic system. Learn spells, harness elemental powers, and master the art of enchanting weapons. Magic is your key to overcoming adversaries and unveiling the secrets hidden within Atham.<br/><br/><strong><i>Treacherous Dungeons:</i></strong><br/>Challenge your mettle in intricately designed dungeons. Face formidable guardians, and collect various items along your journey. Each dungeon is a unique trial that will test your wits, combat skills, and courage.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676380/extras/2.png?t=1705078563"><br/><br/><strong><i>Diverse Lands:</i></strong><br/>Explore the diverse landscapes of Atham, from the desolate ruins of Minorith to the enchanting Al'Math Forest. Each land presents its own challenges, creatures, and secrets. Traverse the Plains of Bastonia, The deserted Lake Town, Ir'aloks Mountains, and beyond, each with its own unique charm and danger.<br/><br/><strong><i>Epic Quests:</i></strong><br/>Embark on epic quests guided by the wise Great Elder Osimodius. Uncover the lore of Atham, make moral decisions, and shape the kingdom's fate. The narrative unfolds as you progress, with twists and turns that keep you engaged in the rich tapestry of this fantasy realm.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1676380/extras/3.png?t=1705078563"><br/><br/><strong><i>Building Strongholds:</i></strong><br/>Survival demands strategic thinking. Build and fortify strongholds to withstand the encroaching darkness. Customize your stronghold, manage resources, and create a home base where you can prepare for your next great adventure.<br/><br/><strong><i>Become the True Champion:</i></strong><br/>Only the bravest will prevail in the Kingdom of Atham. Will you rise as the true champion, vanquish the Shadowbringers, and restore light to this mystical realm? Your journey awaits, adventurer. The fate of Atham rests in your hands.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minigame Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/305900/Minigame_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/305900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Minigame Game is a first-person focused minigame collection that supports anywhere from 2-16 players. Grab your weapons and enter the "Minigame Game" arcade!<h2 class="bb_tag">Test your skills!</h2>Shoot, bunnyhop, swing, and dance your way to victory in a variety of minigames designed to put your classic FPS skills to the test. Featuring 35+ minigames that will pit you with and against your friends.<h2 class="bb_tag">Get the high score! </h2>Whoever has the most points at the end of each minigame playlist is crowned the winner of the arcade. Your score and achievements are tracked to unlock cosmetics that you can show off!<h2 class="bb_tag">Level up!</h2>As you level up you’ll be able to choose from an ever-increasing selection of minigames. From fist fights and rocket jumping to shooting glass floors and swinging through space, there’s a minigame for everyone!<h2 class="bb_tag">Host your own arcade lobby!</h2>Compete in a random collection of minigames of your choosing with friends and other players online. Add modifiers such as increasing the number of rounds, enabling team selection, or even playing with bots! <i>(Bots are not available in all minigames but more are being added as we continue to update the game!)</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minigame Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/305900/Minigame_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/305900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Minigame Game is a first-person focused minigame collection that supports anywhere from 2-16 players. Grab your weapons and enter the "Minigame Game" arcade!<h2 class="bb_tag">Test your skills!</h2>Shoot, bunnyhop, swing, and dance your way to victory in a variety of minigames designed to put your classic FPS skills to the test. Featuring 35+ minigames that will pit you with and against your friends.<h2 class="bb_tag">Get the high score! </h2>Whoever has the most points at the end of each minigame playlist is crowned the winner of the arcade. Your score and achievements are tracked to unlock cosmetics that you can show off!<h2 class="bb_tag">Level up!</h2>As you level up you’ll be able to choose from an ever-increasing selection of minigames. From fist fights and rocket jumping to shooting glass floors and swinging through space, there’s a minigame for everyone!<h2 class="bb_tag">Host your own arcade lobby!</h2>Compete in a random collection of minigames of your choosing with friends and other players online. Add modifiers such as increasing the number of rounds, enabling team selection, or even playing with bots! <i>(Bots are not available in all minigames but more are being added as we continue to update the game!)</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Hoplite: Arachne’s Trial</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2738430/Legendary_Hoplite_Arachnes_Trial/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Try out the free prologue to get a taste of the exciting gameplay and easily transfer your progress to the full game.<br/><br/><strong>Transfer your progress to the main game</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_04.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>The main game offers three acts, 38 areas, mini-games, and a lot of gear options for your hero. Progress seamlessly transfers from the prologue to the main game.<br/><br/><strong>Face 10 Levels and 2 Boss Battles</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_02.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>Face the challenge of 10 distinct levels, each filled with hordes of mythic monsters. Try 6 different armies and test your skills against Arachne at the end of the prologue.<br/><br/><strong>Customize Your Build and Power Up Your Army</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_01.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>Customize your build by trying out various gear combinations you come across. Find the perfect match for your playstyle as you explore. Strengthen your army by upgrading them and merging with the Hero to amplify your power, ready to face and conquer the enemy.<br/><br/><strong>War technique</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738430/extras/LEH_181_gifs_600x194_03.gif?t=1705075545"><br/>Elevate your armies with War Technique—a fresh way to upgrade. Experiment with various combos and effortlessly switch up your enhancements for effective improvements.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seasons of Rocco</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2700510/Seasons_of_Rocco/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the enchanting world of 'Seasons Of Rocco,' where nature reclaims its space, and a lovable raccoon named Rocco looks to you for guidance. In this cozy simulation, your goal is to assist Rocco in surviving the challenges of each winter. Explore Rocco’s world in 2 playable seasons; Autumn and Spring.<br/><br/>Rocco's world is a tranquil haven, offering a peaceful escape for those who cherish relaxation over challenges. Immerse yourself in the soothing ambiance of nature's beauty, where seasons unfolds with its unique charm.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700510/extras/Autumn_banner.png?t=1705075237"><br/>Help Rocco gather fruit to prepare for the winter ahead. Discover the treasures scattered in the warm hues of autumn, and experience the joy of gathering nature's bounty. Explore through rustling leaves, gather fruit for Rocco and sort them at his Tree House! 🍂❄️<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700510/extras/Spring_Banner.png?t=1705075237"><br/>As spring arrives, plant the seeds collected during winter, and experience the joy of new life budding. Explore the blooming landscapes as nature awakens, bringing forth vibrant colors. Witness the beauty of renewal and growth in every corner of Rocco's world. 🌱☀️<br/><br/><br/>'Seasons Of Rocco' is more than a game; it's an invitation to unwind, explore, and create a harmonious world filled with heartwarming moments. Join Rocco and embark on a journey where the seasons become chapters of joy.<br/><br/><br/>About Vivid Visions Studios:<br/><br/>Vivid Visions Studio was founded back in October of 2023, as part of our Bachelor program at the Rotterdam of Applied Sciences in The Netherlands. We're a team of 17 students, starting our very first game development project. For our debut in the gaming world, we aimed to bring more positivity into the industry. With "Seasons of Rocco," we're taking our first steps toward creating a wholesome gaming experience. We're excited to see what the future will bring!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer Repair Shop</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2479290/Computer_Repair_Shop/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479290/extras/gifmain.gif?t=1705075217"><br/>Identify and fix problems with computers arriving for repair. Replace quality parts with crappy parts if you wish.<br/>Fix broken parts and assemble them in a computer. Then put it up for sale and negotiate with customers. Fool them if you can.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479290/extras/gifrobo.gif?t=1705075217"><br/>Develop viruses and infect computers with the money you earn. Join the robot wars and develop your own robot.<br/><br/>Hack customers computers and find out their bank details. Steal the money and leave no trace behind.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479290/extras/gifbacroom.gif?t=1705075217"><br/>Research mysterious websites and explore extremely dangerous areas.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479290/extras/follow2.gif?t=1705075217"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun vs. Zombies</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2734750/Gun_vs_Zombies/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2734750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Gun vs. Zombies, the ultimate showdown between firepower and the undead! Brace yourself for an intense, physics-driven experience where your trusty gun becomes more than just a tool—it's your lifeline against waves of hungry zombies.<br>
<br>
In Gun vs. Zombies, you're in control of a unique weapon that's not just about aiming and firing. This isn't your typical shooter; the gun's physics play a crucial role in your strategy. Every shot you take applies forces to the gun, causing it to move dynamically. Your skill in managing this movement while taking down hordes of zombies will determine your survival.<br>
<br>
Your mission is clear: defend the precious brain located on the stage. Waves of relentless zombies are relentlessly advancing, driven by an insatiable hunger. It's up to your sharpshooting skills and mastery of the gun's physics to keep them at bay and prevent them from reaching their ultimate goal.<br>
<br>
Compete against other players and showcase your skills on the global leaderboard! In Gun vs. Zombies, it's not just about surviving the zombie onslaught—it's about proving your mastery. Climb the ranks by showcasing your prowess in eliminating the undead.<br>
<br/>
Are you ready to experience the adrenaline rush of controlling a weapon that challenges traditional shooting mechanics? Get ready to immerse yourself in Gun vs. Zombies, where precision, strategy, and the laws of physics collide in a battle for survival!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystical Map</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1955640/Mystical_Map/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Mystical Map is a rogue-lite that allows players to draw out their own path in each playthrough. Maps are randomly generated, but YOU have the ability to choose your path and use any items found to enhance it. Chart your course and take on various action platforming challenges!<h2 class="bb_tag">Rogue-"lite" with a personal twist</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955640/extras/mapgif.gif?t=1705071218"><br/><br/>Each adventure is not the same. This is due not only to a randomized map with randomized rewards, but one where you choose which rooms to challenge... and which to ignore. Are you a speed runner looking to optimize efficiency? Or a completionist seeking out new challenges? Maybe you even found a rare item to enhance your current route!<h2 class="bb_tag">Room types include:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Elite enemies<br/></li><li>Platforming challenges<br/></li><li><span class="bb_strike">Mimic</span> Treasure Rooms<br/></li><li>And more!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955640/extras/platgif.gif?t=1705071218"><h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Randomized maps that allow complete control over paths.<br/></li><li>Action platforming gameplay with engaging mechanics to combine the best of both genres.<br/></li><li>Items and enhancements to help you through your run.<br/></li><li>Challenging enemies and bosses waiting for you if you choose to face them.<br/></li><li>Permanent upgrades to reward you for each and every run.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955640/extras/combatgif.gif?t=1705071218"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>36 Nights</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2703750/36_Nights/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703750/extras/logo-descr.png?t=1705071160"><br/><br/>36 Nights is a tower defense game with roguelike and bullet heaven elements. Buy turrets and upgrade your survivor to defend against waves of zombies. You'll need careful strategy and a little luck if you want to survive 36 nights...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703750/extras/header-text.png?t=1705071160"><br/><br/>Bullet heaven meets tower defense! Control a character with an upgradeable gun, and place turrets in the map to defend yourself! Be strategic about how to spend money and what upgrades you choose for your character in order to survive the night. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703750/extras/features-text.png?t=1705071160"><br/><br/>- 5 unique areas<br/>- 6 unlockable characters<br/>- 40+ character upgrades<br/>- 15+ turret upgrades						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wicked Times</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2604240/Wicked_Times/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Wicked Times is a straightforward role playing game which uses real photos to depict locations and enemies. It's a hero manager/autobattler type of game. As you face stronger and stronger enemies you are given a set of side activities to strengthen your character, which become essential as the game progresses. Heal yourself with potions. Upgrade your spell book to deal more damage and your armor to withstand the backlash of the monsters.<br/>Awaiting are 60 enemies, 3 final bosses, 64 locations, 6 cities and 12 side activities to strengthen yourself before facing your enemies.<br/>Buckle up for the journey to stop the demon Kugraltha and his minions.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604240/extras/LibraryLogo4Description_New.png?t=1705070983"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
